You've been good...
...ish..behavior.
In 8 of 12 months time served
we have the discretion to
grant parole, Friday the 10th,
five days from now.
Are you sorry about
what you did?
Yes.
Yes?
That's the correct answer,
isn't it?
Are you trying
to annoy us?
No, I'm just trying
to give you
the answers you need
to cover your asses,
fill out your forms,
and let me out of here.
We need you
to show us remorse.
Is that how
our system works?
Release the best actors?
I shudder to think
what that world would be like.
You drove your car into
your ex-girlfriend's house
and then fled the country
for three months.
I knew that her daughter
was at grandma's,
like every Friday,
and I saw everyone else
move into the living room.
They could've moved back.
Which I would've noticed
since I was driving
right towards them.
Shut up. We got an order
to reduce overcrowding.
But let me be clear--
you mouth off to one guard,
we catch you with a single
cafeteria tray in your cell,
you break any rules
I don't even remember,
you can park your ass here
for four more months.
So forget being sorry.
Can you stay out of trouble
for five days?
Yes.
♪ House 8x01 ♪
Twenty Vicodin
Original air date on October 3, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
[Indistinct chatter]
Get in line for meds!
Asofa!
Why you keep
helping him out?
Yeah, why would I
wanna make sure
that my homicidal cellmate
is taking the right
anti-psychotics?
(Hsueh)
House!
Mendelson!
He's on 80 mg of Propranolol.
That's 40.
You're right.
Sorry.
No worries.
I like my nurses
naughty.
(House) I'm starting
to think, Mendelson,
that you just really like
the taste of my spit.
[Laughs]
Hey, House.
Check out
our new brand, huh?
You really got a thing
for swastikas, Mendelson.
Like an ironic thing?
It's a German name.
So is "House."
I'm Jewish.
Nah, I'm a black,
gay gypsy.
Knight to
King's Bishop three.
Queen to
King's Bishop seven.
Hey.
You're House, right?
I got these weird pains
in my elbows
and in my knees--
You know,
what's weirder
is how the clinic
is a large room
and you somehow
confused me with it.
Although, to be fair,
I am large.
Hi, Rollo.
I realize this is probably
a rhetorical question--
why are you
stealing my stuff?
Hey, House. I heard
you're on short time.
You won't need this.
You heard about
my parole,
but not about
my violent reactions
when people steal
my tuna.
Put it back.
Nuh-uh.
Really?
You're stepping
to a guy
who outweighs you
by 50 pounds,
and he was carrying
a cane, which,
while prison-approved,
would still cause some issues
if inserted
into your colon.
Yeah, like you
losing your parole.
And you ain't gonna
rat me out neither,
'cause you don't wanna
get a snitch jacket
and wind up shanked
in the showers.
So you're just gonna let me
walk out of here.
You wanna get back
at these guys...
Get out alive on Friday.
[Buzzer]
All right,
now go to work, House.
Oh, and that was
Checkmate, right?
(House)
Yep.
I heard you're on that
short time, House?
If you like tuna,
you're a little late.
I want your stereo
and your headphones.
[Chuckles]
It can wait till you
finish your work.
Drop it off in my cell.
[Laughs]
(Adams)
99.9.
I'm gonna start him
on ceftriaxone.
(Sykes)
Good catch.
I might've missed that.
It's not gonorrhea.
I didn't say it was.
Not out loud,
but you're figuring
that joint pain,
plus fever,
plus a low lifestyle
equals a ceftriaxone
prescription.
(Nick) So you're saying
I got the clap?
I've only been in here
one week.
My girlfriend's clean.
I ain't got
a girlfriend in here.
(Adams) How do you know
about ceftriaxone?
House used to be
a doctor.
Not going back,
and that look of shock
is elitist and offensive.
Doctors can be degenerates.
This is America.
There's subtle
eyebrow loss.
It's lupus.
Well, there's no discoid
or malar rash on his face.
Which would be dispositive
if he was just a giant head.
(Sykes)
He's got a point,
but I'll let you
make the call.
No, there's no reason
to search for a bodily rash
since lupus doesn't usually
present that way.
"Usually"?
Well, I guess that's
good enough for prison work.
You don't write people up
for mouthing off, do you?
[Scoffs]
Not usually.
You don't wanna mess
with Stomper.
He didn't get that name
because he's a fan
of Santa's reindeer.
You think one of
Santa's reindeer
was called Stomper?
You're missing my point.
I'm not gonna listen to a guy
who can't name the reindeer.
Well, you saw what happened
in the yard with Diaz.
He barely said
a couple of words
and set the boy off.
Oh, no.
I know that look.
[Indistinct chatter]
Hey, Stomper.
Where's my stereo?
I brought it
to your cell.
It ain't there.
I was just getting
to that part.
Rollo followed me in
and took it.
No way Rollo'd
diss me like that.
Way. I don't wanna start
any rumors, but--
But what?
Well, he was all, you know,
"I could take Stomper."
And I was all,
"how come?"
And he was all,
"'cause of how Diaz
kicked his ass
last month."
In fact, he actually
called you "Stompee,"
with an "ee."
I think his gist was...
(Stomper)
You took my stereo?
(Rollo) Get out of
my House, Stomper.
I ain't got
no stereo.
[Loud bang]
Well,
then what's this, then?
What? I didn't
put that there!
You're gonna lie to my face,
you lying son of a bitch!
What? I didn't do
anything!
Next time I will
take your stereo!
[Alarm buzzes]
(Rollo)
Ow!
[Alarm buzzing]
[Jazz music playing]
That was stupid.
Is that, like,
a synonym for "clever"?
By the time they
get out of solitary,
I'll be teaching physics
at the University of Fiji.
You have four days left.
How many more tricks
do you got?
[Cricket chirping]
[Cricket chirps]
Don't.
This another pet?
'Cause it's
gonna end badly.
Again.
Remember we talked
about this?
At least I talked,
and you stared at me eerily.
I think it was eerily.
"Eerily" felt like
the best-case scenario.
[Indistinct chatter]
(House)
Hey.
Take off your shirt
so I can find the rash.
Oh, now you
wanna help me.
'Cause that doctor
didn't believe you?
Well, if you can think
of a better way
to prove that
she's an idiot,
I'm all ears.
Now, let's get this
over with.
Yeah.
That's Nicole.
She lives
at her mom's now
on account
that she lost her job.
Her mom hates me,
so she can't visit,
she ain't accepting
my calls.
Well, that's what happens
when you date a 12-year-old.
You don't believe me?
Belief implies a level
of giving a crap
that I am never
gonna achieve.
(House)
Pull down your pants.
Hey.
It's not that I
was trying to prove
that you're an idiot
or anything,
but lupus boy and I were
at the beach this morning,
and I noticed a rash
on his left thigh.
I checked you out.
You were
a pretty big deal.
What went wrong?
Something very obvious
and very boring.
Drug related?
Forging prescriptions?
Oh, you're good,
just like
lupus boy will be
when you start him
on prednisone.
Name should've been
a giveaway.
I'll send him up.
Why are you so sure
I'm gonna do
what you say?
Because you're a smart,
old-money, trust-fund girl
who took this job
because your liberal ideology
makes you wanna
make a difference,
but you're already
getting bored,
and this is interesting.
Why would you
say any of that?
Your shoes--
a different,
expensive pair every day,
but never leather,
which means you're both
rich and liberal.
Antique locket--
it's unpolished gold.
Not some hipster thing.
It's a family heirloom,
which means old money.
Osler scarf--
only on Fridays,
which means you did
your residency at Hopkins,
which means you're smarter
than our interactions
would so far indicate.
And your eyes--
the only time
you haven't looked bored
in the three months
since you've been here
is when we've been
discussing this diagnosis.
So, yeah, you'll
treat him for lupus.
[Indistinct chatter]
(Sullivan)
House.
He wants you.
(Mendelson)
Parole?
You didn't tell me.
I didn't want a big,
emotional scene.
But you know what
the rules are.
On short time,
tax goes up.
How many do you want?
All of 'em.
Come on, Mendelson.
I should be
on six a day.
I get four,
and I give you two.
Fine. Get one in my cell
after lights-out.
Plus Wednesday,
Thursday, Friday,
that's 11 in all.
I count 20.
You knew on Monday,
you get out Friday.
Five days.
You should've told me
earlier.
They give out
four a day, Max.
[Laughs]
You'll figure
something out.
You're a creative guy.
What if I just go
into protective custody,
spend the next three days
in the hole?
Oh, you could P.C. up.
But then
you'll get out,
and unlike you...
I got friends
on the outside.
(House)
Porter.
Doc,
what ya need?
I'm running a special on
grilled cheese this week.
Got some
new girly mags too.
I was thinking of
something more...
Vicodin-y.
At least 16,
and I need them
Friday at noon.
Ooh, I mean,
that's pricy,
but it can be done.
How about you have one of
your peeps on the outside
send $200 to my boy
up in Trenton?
I am peep-less.
This is just you
haggling, right?
No. You ever see me
chatting on the phone,
taking visitors?
All right, but I'm gonna
have to clean you out.
I'm gonna need to see
some tuna.
some stamps, uh, stereo--
just get 'em to me
as soon as you can.
[Man screams]
[Breathing heavily]
What happened?
I was trying
to use the phone.
I just--I just got jostled
a little, that's it.
Who hit you?
I just--I just bumped
into the wall.
[Groans loudly]
[Breathing heavily]
Huh.
That's not lupus.
Is that good?
Does it feel good?
[Sighs]
(Asofa)
Sick.
No, I'm just going through
a bit of withdrawal.
I'm trying to survive
on one a day
for the next few days.
No.
Fix him.
It's not lupus.
He broke his arm.
Or it is lupus,
and he was in a fight.
He was in a jostle.
'Cause if he admits
he was in a fight,
then he goes to the hole.
That's why he'd lie
to the guards.
He's got no reason
to lie to me.
Huh.
See? There are
those eyes again.
How about
a viral syndrome?
Or MRSA?
No, that wouldn't chew up
the bone that fast.
But reaction
to meds could.
- May I?
- May you what?
Make me lose my job
by showing you
a patient file?
But why don't you assume
no recent meds?
How long can I assume
that he's been smoking?
Based on
his yellow fingers.
You're thinking
lung cancer.
Metastatic.
I'll X-ray him on Friday.
We share a traveling
X-ray machine
two other clinics.
I'm out of here
on Friday.
He's not.
Well, how about...
If he throws a clot
and strokes out,
you can use the X-ray
to do the autopsy.
Start him
on blood thinners.
Very interesting practice
you must've run.
No need for tests.
No need for proof.
Where are you going?
To the proof store.
You were right
about Nicole.
About me not caring?
I thought so.
It wasn't her mom.
It was her.
She doesn't wanna
talk to me.
Listen, I'm trying to
listen to your lungs,
not your self-pity.
Cancer can wait.
Hey, heading out
to the yard?
Mm-hmm.
You mind trying
to find me a cricket?
The ol' swap trick?
You don't think that will
piss off your cellie even more
when he figures
it's a different bug?
I'll dress 'em the same,
like in Vertigo.
Well, I'll try, but they
spray so much pesticide
I'm surprised we're alive.
Good point.
Hey.
How's it coming?
It ain't.
The confederates be giving
themselves spankin' new tats.
They putting a claim
on all of my Vicodin.
Now, I love you and all,
my brother,
but not as much
as I love my gang
of crazy, roided-out
Nazi bitches.
Turn to an inch
to the left.
Hear
the difference?
Yeah!
It's called
an acoustical shadow.
It means
he's got a tumor.
How did you find that
without a stethoscope?
I didn't even know
you could do this!
Start
the blood thinners.
So I for sure
got lung cancer?
- No.
- Yeah.
All you've proven
is there's an anomaly
in his chest.
Which means
your initial diagnosis
could still be right.
Which apparently
really bugs you.
I could do
a clotting test.
That's...
That's a good idea.
We're just gonna cut
your earlobe a bit
and check back
in two minutes.
If there's a little blood
bubbling up, that's normal.
But if it's
completely clotted,
it may indicate cancer.
Okay? Ready?
Are you really
leaving medicine?
What are you gonna do?
You know, for someone
who asks as many favors
as you do,
you sure don't make
any effort
to win me over.
Before I went
to med school,
I thought about getting
a Ph.D. in physics.
You ever heard of
dark matter?
The way galaxies rotate,
the motion of the Universe,
it means there's
six times more stuff
than we can detect.
But it's theorized.
No one's ever proved
it exists.
So you wanna
research it?
Why?
It's the greatest
mystery there is--
the theory
of everything.
And completely divorced
from humanity.
Well,
me and humanity,
we got together
too young.
Tsk.
You have a gift.
There is something
in this world
you are
undeniably great at.
You can read people.
You--
you understand them.
You gotta go back
to medicine.
Well, if that gift is related
to what brought me here,
you'll understand if I wanna
check the returns policy.
Hey!
Is this supposed
to happen?
Cool.
Jiminy didn't chirp much
last night.
If it's a disease,
then he's six inches under.
But this could also
be pesticide poisoning...
Which bicarbonate of soda
has been used to treat.
See?
Just so much
and no more.
Mm...
This is where
you say "thank you."
Or I say thank you
for not killing me.
Thank you.
[Sighs]
Hey.
The X-ray didn't show
any tumors.
The acoustical shadow
was just a lipoma.
I'm thinking--
you all right?
I'm fine.
Ibuprofen?
That's not gonna help.
You can look
at the patient file
if you want.
You trust me?
Any reason I shouldn't?
You're really not good
at reading people, are you?
Or buildings.
People are complicated.
And people change.
Not that much
to the first,
and not at all
to the second.
But if it'll
get me the file...
If we add "clotting disorder"
to the symptoms,
it's gotta be a toxin.
This guy's the only one
with symptoms.
It's either gotta be his cell
or his work station.
The laundry room.
So maybe a solvent
or detergent?
Can you get me an escort
to gather samples?
Dr. Adams.
Why does he
have a file?
[Indistinct chatter]
You need to get
cotton swabs--
but not now.
I got something to do.
You're a prisoner
on tier time.
By definition,
you have nothing to do.
Call her family,
her friends, her work.
I'm gonna get through
eventually.
You're moving slower.
You're getting weaker.
This thing's attacking
your bones, your joints,
your blood.
Look, my girl's
more important.
She's not your girl,
you idiot.
She was the girlfriend
of a loser drug dealer.
Think she's got
the self-control
to wait around
for three years?
You think she should?
There's a reason
we're locked away
from nice,
normal people.
Your life outside
is over.
Your friends, your girl,
everyone you worked with,
they've moved on.
Get out of my house.
Get out!
[Bang]
Where's Sykes?
Off at his other clinics.
Great. Well, I'm gonna
go through the laundry.
Give me some swabs.
No.
What? He yelled at you
for letting me see the file?
You'll get over it.
A few years of therapy--
Why did you lie to me
about what you were in for?
Okay, so I drove a car
into a wall
instead of stealing
some pills.
You obviously
don't care what I did.
You care that I lied to you.
You feel jilted.
I feel stupid.
It--it doesn't even
make sense.
Why are you
doing time?
You didn't have
any priors.
You didn't hurt anyone.
I had a bad lawyer.
[Scoffs]
I'm sorry.
We can't talk about
this case anymore.
Ugh!
We hear you're gonna
need an incentive
to get all my pills
by tomorrow.
I--I can't get all 20,
but once I get out--
Give us a minute.
Why do you think
I'm on buspirone?
The stress!
And I get the runs
almost every day.
Any sign of weakness,
20 guys would line up
to stick a sharpened-up
toothbrush in my eye.
So as much as
my better nature
really wants
to give you a pass...
It just wouldn't be good
for my health.
See you tomorrow.
(House)
I need your help.
You have any matches?
No, that's
serious contraband.
What are you
planning to do?
What about
a stick of gum?
Sure.
I'm gonna need that too.
Why?
Why do I need the pen
that you always carry around
and never write with?
This is plan "B."
[Pop]
What happened
to your cheek?
[Indistinct yelling]
What is it?
[Knock on window]
[Alarm beeping]
A fire?
House, we gotta
evacuate this area.
Come on.
(Nick)
Hey. Hey, House.
You were saying something
about how I should, like,
uh, swab or--
You're confusing me
with the clinic again.
What?
You're abandoning me?
As soon as you leave,
I am.
Why? What changed?
I'm just done.
No you, no medicine,
no fixing people.
Done.
Now get out.
No!
[Breathing heavily]
Your lips
are swelling.
Open your mouth.
Did you just
eat something?
Meatloaf,
potatoes, coffee...
You allergic
to anything?
[Breathing heavily]
Guard!
You're going into
anaphylactic shock.
Guard!
Dammit.
I gotta make a hole
so you can breathe.
[Toilet flushes]
(Alvarez)
House, get away from him.
He's having
an allergic reaction.
He can't breathe.
Lie on the ground with
your hands behind your head.
Alvarez, look at
what I'm doing!
It's a tracheotomy.
Come on, man.
You know I'm a doctor.
[Wheezing]
What's wrong with him?
I have no idea.
[Cricket chirping]
Saving us both from
contraband charges.
[Toilet flushes]
It was great
knowing you.
[Knock on door]
I need to be taken
into protective custody.
Wow.
That was great.
I think I really dodged
a bullet there.
You don't need P.C.?
Uh, it's nothing personal.
We'll reschedule.
Rain check, I promise.
It wasn't the food.
It was the heat.
It's mastocytosis.
It can be set off
by hot liquids,
like the coffee
he just drank.
Masto's usually
a skin disease.
Usually?
It can hit any organ.
Joint pain, osteopenia,
and anaphylaxis,
eyebrow loss...
It fits.
It's a possibility.
I'll run some blood tests.
Thank you.
(House)
No, no!
It's almost impossible
to confirm masto
with blood work.
Just give him
five aspirin.
If he has masto,
he'll go into
anaphylactic shock
and won't be able
to breathe again.
You do understand the meaning
of the word "confirm."
I'll do it.
I almost died
in that cell.
House, you're in here
because you think you can do
whatever you want
whenever you want.
You can't,
and neither can I.
The A.C.L.U.
would have my job,
my license,
maybe even my house,
if I do an unauthorized
experiment--
But if--if it is masto--
It's not.
What do you have to lose
by giving him the aspirin?
I'm not taking
the risk.
It's his risk to take.
If he has another attack
and there isn't a doctor in
the next cell, he could die!
So for one second, will you
stop covering your ass
and do the test?
I think House
is right.
No.
You're a moron and a coward.
I'll do it myself.
(Sykes)
Guard.
You're done here,
just like every other place
you've ever set foot
in your life.
If I ever see you
in here again,
I will write you up,
and they will revoke
your parole.
(Adams)
Dr. House.
Did you get all
the Vicodin you needed?
I'm not an idiot.
That fire,
the bruise on your face...
I talk to prisoners.
I know about exit taxes.
You're clearly
getting squeezed.
I need 20.
And let me back
into the clinic
when Sykes is gone.
We'll take care
of Nick.
You can't if you're
not willing--
Just take care
of yourself.
[Indistinct chatter]
Well done.
If knew if you'd learned
nothing else in here,
you'd learned the smart thing
is to fall in line.
[Sighs]
You're
absolutely right.
[Pills clattering]
(Alvarez)
Hey, hey, hey!
I need backup here.
Hey! Hey!
Son of a bitch.
(Mendelson)
You'd better be fast...
[Groans]
Come on.
Come on!
Thanks for getting me
to the clinic.
Take him out.
I've got only two years
left in my stretch.
Take him out.
(House) C.O.! We have
a little problem here!
I need backup,
I need backup!
Alvarez!
[Indistinct yelling]
(Alvarez)
Mendelson! Sullivan!
Mendelson!
You're gonna pay for this.
Hey...I'm just
playing solitaire.
[Thud]
[Alarm ringing]
Hands behind your head!
On the ground!
(Adams)
You are so lucky.
We got a guy in an ambulance
heading to Princeton General.
Another dozen getting
teargas hosed off them.
(Guard)
Hey! Sit down!
Where's the aspirin?
(Guard)
Back off!
Oh, God.
Did you get beaten up
on purpose?
House,
what are you doing?
Hey!
(Hsueh)
House, open up!
This is a direct order!
Yeah, it's always
a direct order.
Eight months. Haven't heard
an indirect order in here.
Dr. Adams!
They're gonna revoke
your parole.
They're gonna charge you
with extra crimes.
You'll be here
six more months, minimum!
Sorry. Distracted.
You were saying?
I checked your file.
You didn't have a bad lawyer.
You had no lawyer.
You took the first deal
they offered you,
because you wanted
to punish yourself.
Do you think
getting beaten up,
you think saving this one guy
will wipe your slate clean?
No.
Then why are you
doing this?
'Cause I have a gift.
Once you drink this,
should get an attack
almost immediately.
That is, if I'm right.
Just bought yourself
months in solitary.
Was it really worth it?
If I'm wrong, no,
it wasn't.
(Sykes)
No! No! No! Get the cup!
Get the cup!
Just drink it!
Drink it!
(Sykes)
No! Grab the cup!
(Hsueh)
Hands behind your back.
What were you
thinking?
I don't know.
I--I was scared.
No!
You're fired.
You're beyond fired.
You're completely
unhireable anywhere.
You understand that?
Yes.
Now shut up and let's see
if he has an attack.
(House) Come on, just
a little more time.
(Sykes)
Get him out of here.
[Clattering]
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net