[Banging on door]
Get up, House.
Must be some mistake.
I specifically requested
my wakeup startle
three hours from now.
Some VIP visitor. Dean of Medicine
from your old hospital.
I've had dreams
about this.
I'm going to assume
this is another one.
Get up.
I can refuse to see
any visitor I want.
Tell the Dean
that I don't want to see her.
He said you'd say that.
He?
What's the hiring policy
over there?
All ass based?
I can get you out of here.
Not unless that file
has a file in it.
Judge's order
for your immediate release.
I had eight months added
to my sentence two months ago.
The math is pretty basic.
We have a crisis.
Which is good news
for you.
You're out tonight
on conditional parole.
The condition being
that you're employed by me
at PPTH.
No, thanks.
You think it's a good idea
for me to go right back
to my old life?
For either of us?
Your patient
is two lungs in a box.
And it only has 12 hours left.
No pulse, no body.
No ability
to answer questions.
It's your perfect patient.
I did pay for the room
for the whole week, but...
♪ House 8x02 ♪
Transplant
Original air date on October 10, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
(Foreman) Donor's an 18-year-old
college kid back from Hosftra.
Goes to a homecoming party
with his buddies,
hops on his motorcycle,
ends up an organ donor.
Asystole in the E.R.
No pulse.
No blood circulating.
His heart, liver, kidneys
were all toast.
Surgeons had the recipient
on the table
when they realized the lungs
had increased airway resistance.
The team closed her up, put the
lungs in suspended animation.
Buys 24 hours to fix it,
12 of which have passed.
We still have no clue
what's wrong.
Nice painting.
Blues and Greens.
Calming,
but with a hint of nurturing.
Totally offsets the stench
of suffereing and death.
Where's my patient??
We need to not talk.
ICU isolation room.
The transplant team
will meet you there
with updates
from the past two hours.
Great.
Take this.
How about you drop it
in your office?
I completely understand
and almost respect
your desire to appear
to be Dean of Medicine,
given that your title
is Dean of Medicine.
On the other hand...
Seriously?
[Elevator dings]
Get this straight.
You break the law,
you go back to jail.
Scam extra Vicodin,
back to jail.
Flout my authority,
make the hospital look bad,
back to jail.
I own you.
Yes, massa.
See, that would be
an example.
[Elevator dings,
doors open]
When did Cuddy leave?
She gave her notice
the day after your incident.
Took a job--
Don't need the details.
[Drilling]
(Foreman)
Ortho needed more space.
You're this way.
Where's my stuff?
(Foreman)
No idea.
What about my team?
Pathetic.
The first thing
you said to me
was you don't want
your old environment.
The fourth thing you said was,
"where's my old environment?"
It's been a year.
Taub, Chase, Thirteen
all moved on.
The world does that
sometimes.
No, it doesn't.
Here's your new office.
And there's your new team.
Hi.
I'm not interested in another
department's sloppy seconds.
I'm not sloppy seconds.
3:00 a.m.
If Foreman had called you in
from home,
you wouldn't have
pressed clothes,
coiffed hair,
and makeup,
which means you were
already here in the hospital.
Yes, I was on call
for neurology.
Well, if that were true,
you'd be working right now
and unavailable
to help.
Which means that you're
hanging out in the hospital
pretending to work.
Which means
you're not just a reject,
you're a cowardly reject
who was trying to hide
her rejectedness from someone.
I am not a reject.
Then go back to neurology.
I can't.
I punched my attending.
[Door slides]
ARDS secondary to trauma
is our leading hypothesis.
FiO2 is 93%--
Prison!
Sorry
I thought I heard
everyone else think that.
I was in prison,
you see.
It was a long time ago,
but still you're curious.
Never was raped,
not raped-raped.
Well, raped-raped,
but not raped-raped-raped.
Well, now that we've got that
completely behind us.
Sorry, Dr. House,
welcome back.
Is there cake?
(Simpson)
No.
The lungs are dry.
Well it's not ARDS.
It's the autumn.
Tick borne disease season.
Ehrlichiosis causing bronchialitis.
You'll appreciate that I left
the "idiots" subtextual.
Blood smear was clear,
and we "idiots" treated
with broad spectrum antibiotics.
- Cocaine.
- Tox screen was clean.
Dead men don't pee.
Tox screen tests
for metabolites
in the urine.
Coke never got past
the lungs.
Also explains
the motorcycle crash.
Idiots.
Let's get the lungs
on treatment.
(House)
Great idea.
Unless you're wrong.
And by you,
I mean me.
Then this treatment
will burn holes in the lungs.
I'd call you idiots again,
but at this point
I'm starting to doubt
whether you understand
what I mean
by the word.
Kato.
Get Black Beauty
and meet me out front.
We're gonna find
the dead kid's stash.
[Door sliding]
Since an 18-year-old
with organ donor
on his license
is not a cancer patient,
I'm figuring the recipient
is a lifetime member
of the Wilson cares too much
club.
Excellent deduction.
You're the reason
I'm out of the big house.
Doesn't quite make up
for never visiting--
Springing you
was Foreman's idea.
I wasn't convinced until Simpson
failed three times.
It amounts
to the same thing.
You wanted me back.
See, I knew
you'd over-interpret it.
Strong, emotional reaction.
I guess that's what
a lifetime membership gets you.
Healed, thank you.
I was wrong.
I went to prison.
I paid the price.
[Wilson's pager beeps]
You're a changed man.
I said I was wrong.
I didn't say
I changed.
I haven't.
Neither have you--
Analyze it
however you like.
What can I do?
My chest.
Angina's back.
Upping the nitro
should knock it back down.
[Sighs]
Sis and I were talking,
trying to figure out
how many hospital sleepovers
we've had.
[Laughs]
It definitely started
with the great mastectomy
of 2001.
God, I miss my boobs.
They were spectacular.
[Laughs]
It's unlikely.
Especially since,
with the extent
of the emphysema,
she needs a double lung.
How are you doing?
Better already.
It's a good thing
that worked.
I was gonna make you
bring me a bottle.
Oh, lighten up,
Sis.
You know,
the least you could do
is laugh
at a dying lady's jokes.
Your drinking
wasn't funny then,
and it's not funny now.
Because you're not dying.
The hospital brought in
a consultant
to work
on the lungs.
Do you know him?
Is he--is he good?
He is an excellent doctor.
We probably shouldn't be turning
up unannounced like this.
Their son just died.
Bright side--
they're probably up weeping.
Hey, we both assaulted
our bosses.
It's like we're twins.
Okay, I'll go first.
My boss dumped me.
And yours what?
Called you his China doll?
Joked about what a crappy deal
you got for Manhattan?
Assumed you have
a huge penis?
I have no idea
what flavor you are,
so I decided
to cover the spread.
My mom's Filipino,
Dad's Korean,
and my boss
grabbed my behind.
Behind what?
Oh, yeah, your--
grabbed your tushy.
So now you're pretending
to be on call
so that
your overly protective boyfriend
won't find out
that you got groped.
[Doorbell rings]
I don't have
a boyfriend.
It's my parents.
If they found out
what I've done,
they'd be mortified.
Your parents know
your call schedule?
I live with them.
Right.
No issues there.
I told you
my son didn't do cocaine.
Druggies are not known
for their honesty.
Trust me
on this one.
Mr. Weathers,
I am sure you're right,
but we need to be thorough.
Did your son
ever smoke marijuana?
He was an athlete.
Took real good care
of himself.
Hey, take it easy.
Steve loved all that--
Sorry.
But we're on a clock.
I think
he's about to throw us out.
Nope.
His son is dead.
The only way
that has any meaning
is if we fix the lungs
and transplant them.
As long as we find something.
And find something.
Do you know
any of the kids
at the party
with your son?
Bunch
of his high school buddies.
Decided to have
an all-night game
in Brandon Broome's basement.
I understand
that we're in a hurry
but maybe he should.
Your son isn't wearing glasses
in any of these pictures.
He just got them
a couple of weeks ago.
Because he was having headaches?
[Doorbell rings]
Answer the question
before answering the door.
Yeah, he was.
He was not doing cocaine.
He had a brain tumor.
[Doorbell rings]
Don't bother.
It's for me.
Turns out
they monitor these monitors.
Thank you, officer.
I thought the bracelet
was decorative.
My aunt had one
just like it.
Wait a minute.
You're allowed
to be at the hospital.
to go home.
That was made clear.
Dead kid's house
was on the way to my apartment.
Assuming I got lost, twice.
Those consultants in my office
are only costing the hospital
100 bucks every minute
I keep them waiting.
Why didn't you just tell me
what you were doing?
I knew you were very busy
being vaguely important.
I might have cleared it
with the cops.
Yeah, it's the word "might"
that bumps me.
House.
Getting you out of jail
was not a popular decision
with the board.
I need you
to solve this,
and I need you to do it
without making me
look like I can't control you.
For both our sakes.
And the subsequent lingering
black mark on your record.
I'm not worried.
We have to wheel this out
to the MRI.
We should probably leave
the body in the bag.
There's a mass in the arm.
Analyzing part of this tumor
is gonna be quicker than a scan.
You worry about what people
think of you,
and parental secrets.
The only way
that you don't worry
about this hearing
is if you don't think
there's gonna be one.
The only way that happens
is you leave
Princeton Plainsboro.
I had a video interview
with Chicago yesterday.
It went well.
My money's
on rhabdomyosarcoma.
Chicago has a great program,
and you're a dumbass.
Running away from home
is a time-honored tradition,
but you're not doing it
to flee your parents.
You're doing it
to protect them.
That's an insult
to everything teen prostitutes
have worked for.
Time to grow up
and come clean.
You're right.
I should just drive my car
didn't it turn out that he'd
stolen the hot dog cart?
No, borrowed.
Bobby was very insistent
on that point.
[Laughs]
Seems like someone's
feeling better.
No more chest pain.
I haven't heard the name Bobby
in a long time.
How's he doing these days?
I don't know.
We're not in touch.
And don't even pretend
like you're not relieved.
You never liked him.
Bobby is an incredibly fun,
great guy.
Just not a great influence.
I would have gone
with "colossal drunk."
I was gonna leave that implied,
but, yes, colossal drunk.
What? It's good for a couple
to share a hobby.
Your catheter bag
is empty,
despite taking in 200 ccs
of fluids.
I'm gonna have
to dial back the nitro.
- Won't her chest pain come back?
- We don't have any choice.
The nitro is dropping
the blood flow to your kidneys.
They're shutting down.
[Celine Dion's
My Heart Will Go On]
♪ Near, far ♪
♪ wherever you are ♪
♪ I believe ♪
This is so our song.
♪ That the heart
does go on ♪
My patient
is running out of time.
Not worried.
My team is confirming
the diagnosis as we speak.
♪ You open the door ♪
I want
to be understanding.
It's your first day back--
See?
I smell empathy.
♪ And you're here ♪
♪ in my heart ♪
Like when I gave you
that necklace
that you just dumped
in the ocean.
What were you thinking?
♪ My heart will go on ♪
House, I haven't forgotten
our friendship.
For every good memory,
there's a slew of bad ones.
[Knock at door]
Come in.
Paraneoplastic syndrome's out.
The lung donor
didn't have cancer.
Tell that to the tumor
that I found in his arm.
That mass wasn't a tumor.
It was coagulated plasma.
E.R. pumped him
full of it.
I.V. leaked
into his arm.
I even did
a complete MRI.
We've got nothing.
Just 'cause it wasn't
a tumor
doesn't mean it didn't mess
with the lungs.
They're reacting
to something in the plasma.
But every unit of plasma
can have
up to 25 contributing donors.
We need to track down
all of them.
Still.
It's not as bad
as a thousand people
going down
in a gigantic boat, right?
My heart will go on.
No. You can't
leave the hospital.
25 donors
contributed to the plasma
that the lung donor got.
My team cannot track down and
interview them all in six hours.
I vouch for you
to the cops,
you take
some parole-violating detour
celebrating your freedom,
justified, of course,
by some absurd theory
connecting it to donor.
You asked me
to ask you.
Was that just so you'd enjoy
saying no?
I don't trust you, House.
I can't.
Actually you have to.
Not absolutely.
Not outside the walls
of this hospital.
Fine, then give me a team
I don't have
to put in quotation marks.
Use the people
already on the case.
Give me
Chase, Taub, Thirteen.
We don't have the money
to pay them.
Oh, yeah.
It went to interior designers,
I understand.
You only have Park because
she's on neurology's tab.
You are making minimum wage.
I am?
[Sighs]
Get out of my office,
please.
[Cell phone rings]
Number three
went to a baseball game
the day before he donated.
Boredom is not transmissible.
He ate a bag
of peanuts,
and peanut proteins
would be.
If our donor
had an allergy,
it could explain
the lungs.
Nice.
What?
Don't start that.
(House)
Start what?
I'm enjoying our conversation.
The repartee.
There was no repartee.
That was repartee.
I'm not doing this
for you.
I'm doing it
to help my patient.
It's just good
to hear your voice.
That's my whiteboard.
I need it.
And he really doesn't care
how the cast comes off.
Dr. Foreman warned us
that you'd try something.
Told me
to call him if you did.
I'd like to do that.
[Cell phone rings]
I'll take this outside.
Yeah.
(Park)
Donor six traveled to Thailand
around Khorat.
Region was endemic
with dengue fever.
Good.
[Cell phone rings]
- Yeah.
(Park) Alcohol.
For it to affect
a pool of plasma.
These guys
have got that covered.
Acute etoh ingestion
could have--
hey, paint around them!
Who's painting?
(Park)
The crew's just starting.
Paint fumes
didn't cause contamination.
But maybe the old paint did.
They scraped off
the underpass,
probably because it contains...
(Both)
Lead.
Chest pain back?
Is there any way
to take the edge off?
We're still working
on the lungs.
We should know soon.
Soon is good.
[Tapping on glass]
How's the chelation going?
Reverend Moon started it
about 20 minutes ago.
You missed lunch
tracking down
the plasma donors.
Got you a Reuben
from the cafeteria.
Thanks.
Lead exposure's
a nice diagnosis.
I hope it pays off.
It will.
I appreciate your confidence,
but she's not really--
Oh, no,
she could die.
But technically
it will still pay off.
Even if your patient dies,
someone will get the lungs.
You really haven't changed.
But I've given up
red meat.
What round of chelation
is this?
Fourth.
Are you checking up on me
or on House?
This case.
Unique situation.
Oxygenating?
98%.
Airway resistance down.
Is House okay?
I have no idea.
[Knock at door]
Dad,
what are you doing here?
Got your text.
What text?
The one asking me
to bring you some dinner.
I went by neurology.
The secretary said
you were on leave.
I'm consulting
on this case.
Unique situation.
It looks
very complicated.
You can help
with that?
[Monitor beeping rapidly]
Lungs are crashing.
I have to go.
Bye.
(Foreman)
Increasing to 100% FiO2.
Saline flow
is down to 10 ccs.
Blockage?
Clot in the line?
Chelation
is making it worse.
It means
we were wrong about lead.
Hold the analysis
and help me save this thing.
Saline's flushing it forward
but getting no return.
One-way valve.
Vasospasm.
If you're right,
calcium channel blocker
the lungs have
no nervous system.
Will that still work?
We'll know soon.
Left lung is pinking up.
Good job.
Right middle lobe isn't.
Nothing.
We killed part of the lung.
Page Dr. Pinto stat
to the cath lab.
We're going to the cath lab?
Are you thinking
that maybe--
what?
Who?
One dead lobe means
four alive ones.
It means
enough to transplant
with a side order of dead tissue
that we can test.
It makes sense.
Unlike you stealing my phone.
You have
unlimited texting.
Until your parents know,
you will never see that punch
for what it really was.
Your February 4th.
Sri Lankan
Independence Day.
I told you
I'm Korean and Filipino.
And I told you
I wasn't listening.
By my actions.
Violence isn't an appropriate
way to handle conflict.
It was a moment
of weakness.
You barked at me,
picked a fight
with a painting crew.
Maybe it's time
to recognize
it's not a character flaw.
Maybe it's your character.
- Pinto!
- House.
Embrace your inner bitch.
[Door opens]
So why did chelation
make the lungs worse?
We got about five minutes
till pinto gets back.
- Give me a hand with this.
- No.
I tracked down
another bag of plasma
from the batch
they used on the donor.
Negative
for all our other exposures.
Sarcoidosis
could be inflamed
by the treatment.
I am a cripple
in need of assistance.
Transplant team
ran an A.C.E.
Negative.
It's mine.
And it's your job.
My job is to assist you
in curing the lungs.
This chair will help me
do that.
What if the scrapings
from the bridge
chelation for lead
wouldn't have made them worse.
But...
Maybe the problem isn't
a heavy metal from outside.
It's inside.
But it's not leaving the body
like it's supposed to.
It's stuck.
Iron.
The donor had hemosiderosis.
His body wasn't disposing
of iron.
Massive amounts
choke up the lungs.
Then our chelation
would wreak havoc
because it picks up
too much stuff.
Go stain the dead lung tissue
for iron.
I'm sorry, young lady,
I simply will not help you
steal this chair.
Hi.
She can barely
catch her breath.
Lungs ready yet?
We're testing
for iron overload.
I thought it was lead.
This is not an exact process.
Your small airways
are collapsing.
You're not getting
enough oxygen.
I'd like to try forcing
an oxygen-rich slurry
into your lungs.
It should open up the airways
and buy you some time
until the lungs are ready.
Fluid?
In my lungs?
Sounds like drowning.
Gonna hurt,
isn't it?
Yes.
A fair amount.
No.
I'm done.
[Knock at door]
(Wilson) House, the nurses
saw you come in.
Enter.
It's a bathroom.
Ah, explains the hole
in this chair.
God, I missed doors.
And air freshener.
Now go away.
I'm waiting
for some test results.
My patient signed a DNR.
She's giving up.
Looks like someone else
will be getting the lungs.
Making this yet another
interaction with you
it's not my fault
you can't handle your patient.
She said she's done.
I spent half an hour
trying to change her mind,
but she'd made her decision.
I accepted that.
It's called respect.
Well, what's after respect?
You find
another angle.
You hold her hand,
get the sister
to beg,
stick your fingers
in your ears,
pretend you can't hear.
You do whatever it takes.
Oh, whatever it takes.
Thanks, House.
I hadn't thought
of that.
[Door opens]
What are you testing for?
Hemosiderosis.
I'm staining
for excess iron.
Promising.
When your dad showed up
unexpectedly,
House have a hand in that?
I'm guessing he does things
like that a lot.
I spoke to the head
of neurology in Chicago.
I gave you
a good recommendation.
Did you mention
what happened?
Lawyers say
I'm not allowed to.
It works out well
for everyone.
Why exactly
is that good for you?
Excuse me?
I'm a talented physician,
top 2% of my class.
I'm an asset to this hospital,
an asset you're about to lose
to Chicago.
You applied
for the job.
You asked me to call
and recommend you.
Andrews is the one
that should leave.
He's the supervisor.
He touched me first.
I can't discuss
any of that,
not before the hearing.
But if you're having doubts
about Chicago,
I can call them back.
No. Thank you.
Dr. Foreman?
Would you look at this?
Iron?
No.
White blood cells.
Classic presentation
of infection.
How the hell
did we miss that?
Biopsy revealed,
white blood cell inflitrate.
Infection was right, after all.
Fresh fruit in prison
is usually chicken.
Why aren't you
more alarmed?
We're running
out of time.
Aahh, she's dying!
Were you able to figure out
what was wrong
while I was screaming?
Infection was the first thing
that the transplant team
treated for.
Which would have worked
if the bacteria
had been out in the open.
If they're hiding
inside the lung cells...
I'm thinking brucella.
And to wipe that out,
you need special ops.
An intact immune system.
But that's
what white blood cells are.
They're part
of the immune defense force,
like the infantry.
But those lungs need
the Air Force and the Marines,
antibodies raining down
from above.
Antibiotics
and IVIG.
Did you use metaphors
for your old team?
Or do you just think
I'm particularly stupid?
No,
they were stupid too.
What are you doing here?
I'm here
for Vanessa.
Now is not the time,
Bobby.
She asked me
to come.
Right, Doc?
Actually,
it was my idea.
What?
What were you thinking?
She doesn't want
to see him.
When Vanessa was ready
to quit chemo,
Bobby's the one
who got her
to do one more round.
Yeah,
and then he got her drunk.
At least tell me
you haven't been drinking today.
I should go.
Hail, hail,
the gang's all here.
Case is under control.
It's me time.
Vanessa's gonna do
the lung slurry.
You were right
to push me.
I needed that.
Thank you.
So we're good?
It was good advice.
Just came here
to say thank you.
I like you.
I have fun with you.
And, if you can honestly say
that you don't like me,
you don't have fun with me,
I can accept that.
But just do
whatever you have to do
to get over this.
You can punch me
in the face,
kick me in the nuts.
Either/or.
Both seems excessive.
The thing is, House...
I don't like you.
[Door opens]
When did
the discoloration start?
A few minutes
after I started the IVIG.
Means we're wrong
about infection.
And by we,
you mean you.
You screwed up the lungs.
Wrong about autoimmune,
not cancer,
heavy metals,
genetic issues...
Increase peep.
We're close to the point
of no return.
The lungs will never be viable
for transplant.
I need...
I need ideas.
IgA nephropathy.
That's already ruled out.
- Lupus.
- No.
Maybe we're just out of time.
We're out of time
when we're out of time.
When they die
or she dies.
Keep them stable
as long as you can.
I need to think.
[Cheers and excited chatter]
(Wilson)
One, two...
Three...
Make a wish.
[Cheers and applause]
The lungs are a smoker.
You of all people
should know better.
But the kid
never smoked.
He played poker.
Who plays poker
without cigars?
Even if he didn't light up
himself...
It was a rainy night.
The windows were closed.
All parents think
their kids are special.
And these ones
were right.
At least his white blood cells
were special.
They had on on switch for
reacting to smoke, but no off.
When he inhaled small amounts
of smoke, he had small problems.
No one even noticed.
Big amounts of smoke,
that's enough
to trash a lung.
As soon as he breathed in
all that cigar smoke,
he was a dead man.
the motorcycle accident was an
unnecessary dramatic flourish.
Eosiniphilic pneumonitis.
But the steroids
would have treated for that.
I was right.
Not about anything medical,
but my metaphors were perfect.
We need to hit it harder.
We need to carpet bomb,
blitzkrieg.
We need the nuclear option.
At some point you're going to
say we need to radiate, right?
See, the metaphors work.
But that'll destroy
the good lung too.
Better to go with a strong
cocktail of immunosuppressants.
Won't be fast enough.
Wilson needs these lungs.
[Fink's Yesterday Was Hard
On All of Us]
♪ Where do we go
from here ♪
♪ ♪
♪ and is it real ♪
♪ or just ♪
It's working.
♪ Something we think
we know ♪
♪ ♪
He did it.
♪ Where are we going now ♪
I'm not going to Chicago.
If you stay,
we have to have a hearing.
I know.
♪ 'Cause if it's the same
as yesterday ♪
♪ you know I'm out ♪
♪ just so you know ♪
♪ ♪
♪ because, because ♪
♪ our paths,
they cross ♪
♪ ♪
Dad...
Do you have a minute?
(Simpson)
Thoracic cavity clear.
Ready for the donor lungs.
♪ On all of us ♪
♪ ♪
Thank God
you called him.
♪ From here ♪
♪ who can we trust ♪
I wonder
what happens now.
She can handle it.
♪ Are you real ♪
♪ or just something ♪
♪ from wanderlust ♪
♪ ♪
♪ who can you trust ♪
♪ when tears we flower ♪
(Foreman)
House.
Got something
for you.
♪ From ashes to ashes ♪
♪ from dust to dust ♪
I found your stuff
in storage.
♪ Because, because ♪
This is all you get.
Ortho still has
the outer office.
Well, that sucks.
Where are Chase, Taub,
and Thirteen gonna sit?
You're welcome,
House.
♪ On all of us ♪
♪ ♪
[Door opens]
Ah!
♪ Where do we go ♪
♪ from here ♪
♪ ♪
♪ where do we go ♪
Dinner later?
I'll pick something up.
I heard about
a good new vegetarian place.
Screw that.
I want a steak.
♪ Because, because ♪
I'll meet you
at your place at 8:00.
♪ ♪
♪ our paths,
they cross ♪
♪ mm-mm ♪
♪ yesterday was hard ♪
♪ on all of us ♪
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net