If you don't know
how to use a computer,
we will teach you here.
Most jobs require at least
basic word processing skills.
We try to get you up
to 50 words per minute.
We also have a course
in how to talk to someone
in an interview.
Stuff like
what employers
are looking for,
how to turn negatives
into positives.
We can also provide clothes
for the interview
if you need them.
People donate shoes
and suits all the time.
Wh-what if I had
a history with, uh...
With drugs?
That is nothing
to be ashamed of.
Many of our clients have
struggled with addiction,
and, if you want to get clean,
we'll help you do that.
And what if I have a kid?
No one to help you?
You know, if I need
someone to watch her
while I'm in class or,
uh, on an interview.
Could you help with that?
We do not provide
child care.
Actually, it's something
that comes up often.
I would love
to be able to do it.
I just don't
have the resources.
But it's definitely
on the wish list.
Okay.
Okay, uh, thank you.
I'll be back.
[Cell phone ringing]
Oh, I have to take this.
Yes, please come back,
and we'll get you started.
It was nice to meet you,
Benjamin.
[Phone continues to ring]
Okay.
Hey, Oscar.
Agh!
Oh, that is too bad.
Did they tell you why?
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Well, you know what?
Sometimes, you just
don't get the job, but...
Oscar, I gotta call you back.
Uh...
Uh, uh...
Benjamin!
Benjamin, wait!
Oh, my God.
Uh...
[Grunting]
Somebody call an ambulance!
House 8x03 Charity Case
Sync by Ali's Ultimately
[Clippers buzz]
[Clippers shut off]
[Clippers buzzing]
[Hanni El Khatib's
Build. Destroy. Rebuild.]
♪ Gotta build ♪
♪ and destroy ♪
♪ then rebuild ♪
♪ oh, I'm gonna build,
build, build ♪
♪ destroy ♪
♪ then rebuild ♪
♪ and destroy ♪
♪ ♪
Why am I watching you
cut your hair?
If I do it at home,
I'm the one
who has to clean it up.
Does a friend watch you where
it's happening, and wonder why?
New life, new look.
Does that mean
you like your new life?
If you're asking
if your job is safe,
that depends on
what you have to say
about the file
you're holding.
It doesn't seem
like much of a case.
Although,
I'm sure I'm wrong.
You are.
Tell my why.
Guy collapsed after being
on his feet for hours
on a hot day
without breakfast...
So that's really weird.
E.R. found nothing wrong.
Then I decided
I should test his wallet.
He's rich?
That's why
we're taking the case?
No, we're taking the case
because no one knows
what's wrong with him.
And he's rich.
Dr. Adams.
Give her the file.
This is my only copy.
My M.O. depends upon
the use of a team.
Definitionally,
that involves...
more than one person.
So I really have no choice.
Give her the file.
You can't afford a team.
Adams is free.
And I'm referring
both to her availability
and her price tag.
New girl, meet newer girl,
and vice versa.
You said we were
meeting for coffee.
Well, when someone
asks if you want coffee,
they obviously don't
just mean coffee.
Wait...did you think
I was referring to sex?
Would you shut the blinds
on your way out?
I thought you were
referring to talking.
Talking about medicine.
Specifically,
as it refers to the guy
whose name is on the file
she still hasn't handed you.
I'm not working, House.
I'm in the process of
looking for a paying job.
In the meantime,
there's no way
a do-gooder like you
has been volunteering
all over town--
ladling kittens,
spaying soup...
There is a free clinic
in Trenton.
Well, think of this
as today's free clinic.
Only with fewer bums
with herpes.
I don't think we actually
have much of a case.
I think it's just
dehydration.
What happened
the last time
another doctor told you
I was wrong about a case?
I lost my job.
You saved a life.
Is an ultrasound
really necessary?
I'm feeling
much better now.
Oh, a sudden collapse
at your age
can indicate a deterioration
of the heart muscle.
Pretty serious condition.
It can also
just be dehydration.
Next time, you could probably
drop the undercover act.
[Chuckles]
I walk in in a suit,
and they're gonna
put their best foot forward.
Also, I don't own a suit.
You give away millions
and you don't own a suit?
I gave those away too.
One day, I was writing
a check to my landscaper,
and it suddenly hit me--
$6,000 to take out plants
and put in different plants.
So I can look at them.
Shouldn't I use that money
to do something important?
And by money,
you mean
all your money.
I started
with 10 million,
and I couldn't think
of a reason not to give 20.
Or 40.
I figure I could
live off $25,000 a year.
One-room apartment.
Bus pass, thrift stores.
Bare necessities.
I still have
my software company.
And when I make more,
I'll give that way too.
- He's nuts.
- He's generous.
There's a neurological issue.
He's getting rid
of everything.
His echocardiogram
is negative
for cardiomyopathy.
Head CT showed no signs
of stroke or hemorrhage.
He has one pair of pants.
Most people
with his kind of money
are commissioning
oil paintings
of their Yorkshire terrier.
Benjamin is sacrificing
his own comfort
to help others.
That's because helping others
is his Yorkie oil painting.
That's good.
Not sick.
That's naive and sick.
You really want
to improve things?
You do it
through policy.
This guy empties his pockets,
what really changes?
That's right,
all those babies with aids,
they're just using us.
My parents had
$800 between them
when they got here.
They scraped and borrowed
so we could
go to good schools,
and I worked my ass off.
No one gave me a handout.
It makes me work harder.
Rebuttal.
What's your
evil plan?
I object to your cynicism.
- It's been earned.
- That's what I object to.
The new Dean of Medicine
has an ethical obligation
to come in with
a completely open mind
about all employees,
thus letting me
blithely run roughshod
for at least four weeks.
My theory is that you're
running a battery of tests
to convince him
that you saved his life,
then con him into funding you
to hire back your team.
- What?
- Your old team?
[Shouts]
What?
This is your new reality.
You've got your office.
You've got neighbors.
You've got one employee,
one volunteer.
Until she finds
actual, paid work,
or gets sick of you.
I talked
to Chase and Taub.
They're willing
to come back.
What about Thirteen?
Not a good choice.
She's not long term
because she has no long term.
Not taking your calls?
She will.
Discharge the patient.
Unexplained
loss of consciousness
could be cardiomyopathy,
global anoxia,
subarachnoid hemorrhage--
dehydration.
He was given fluids,
and he got better.
And I'm sure your tests
have come up negative,
or you would have
shut me up already.
Which means he goes home.
(Park)
There is a symptom...
Extreme altruism.
You've got
two choices, House.
You can recognize
that your patient
is just a very nice,
healthy guy,
and send him home,
or you can consider
altruism a symptom.
In which case,
you cannot take his money.
Send him home.
And check with admitting
for the net worth
of all new patients.
I'm not coming back,
House.
Technically,
you're back right now.
I need you
to stop calling me.
First 17 messages
were cute, but--
I'm putting the band
back together.
Interesting that you
never showed up at my place,
what with your love
of annoying me
and your inability
to take no for an answer.
I'm guessing ankle monitor.
Guilty as charged.
Literally.
I'm not a doctor
anymore, House.
The job went away,
but not the profession.
You look healthy, so...
That's not it.
You met a boy.
Or a girl.
Fall in love,
wanna be happy.
You decided to...
Enjoy what time you have left.
You're going to Thailand.
Girl.
And Mykonos.
[Yawns]
Turns out
I like boring.
No, you wanna like boring.
But if you actually
liked boring,
you would have figured
that out in fifth grade,
when you were bored.
Please stop calling me.
No.
You showed up
to tell me that you
don't want to hear from me.
That's a mixed signal.
I will choose
to listen to your actions
rather than your words.
They're more honest.
I'm a little confused.
The test is designed
to determine if you're--
No, I mean your running
a test and discharging me.
Was I dehydrated or not?
I think so.
But, out of an abundance
of caution,
my colleague
has taken it upon herself
to do one more test.
All right.
You scare me a little.
[Laughs]
Why?
I've been considering
applying to
Doctors Without Borders.
Going overseas a while,
and that seems like
a huge sacrifice.
But...You--
you don't scare her.
You make her
feel guilty.
Oh, you...
You like your life
that way it is.
Most people give the minimum
they have to give
so they can enjoy
what they have left.
I guess my minimum
is just...
Higher than most.
Complete recruitment
and interference pattern.
His leg muscles are fine.
I feel, uh, funny.
Where?
My chest.
You're tachycardic.
Your heart's
beating too fast.
Unbelievable.
[Heart monitor beeping]
[Benjamin grunting]
Patient got tachycardic
to 185.
We pushed 18 milligrams
adenosine.
There's definitely
something wrong with him.
Which is awesome.
Now there's something
to cure,
which means
there's something to be
disproportionately
financially grateful for.
Morning.
Got you a coffee.
Thanks.
Arrhythmia could easily
have caused the collapse
that landed Father Teresa
in here in the first place.
Oh, that's fine.
Keep it.
We looked at his heart
yesterday,
didn't see any
structural abnormalities.
I'm thinking
occult long QT syndrome?
What about Whipple's?
If it was Whipple's,
there'd be
some kind of neurological
involvement.
You don't think
defying human nature
is neurological?
Racing heart:
Medical condition.
Bleeding heart:
Stupid condition.
Are you saying that
because you believe it,
or because it's in your
financial best interest
to think his generosity
isn't just temporary?
I'm told that some people
are just nice.
I'm trying to embrace
that wisdom.
Benjamin's been taking
allergy medication
the last few weeks.
Long QT syndrome
can be medication-induced.
Flush him with saline,
get rid of the antihistamines,
then do an EKG.
No, wait.
I'll do the flushing.
Take the damn $2.00.
She hasn't even
sipped the coffee.
I just got so angry.
You know?
So I made
a terrible mistake.
Now I'm trying
to start my life over.
To help people
the way I always wanted.
But my department
got defunded, and...
it's my fault.
Just can't stand to think
of all those patients
going untreated because
I don't have the resources
to do my best work.
How about I help you out?
How do you mean?
I'll give $1 million
as an endowment to the hospital,
earmarked for diagnostics.
Wow.
I am an opportunistic
ex-con
who just gave you
a two-minute sob story
as step three
in my master plan,
and you've offered me
$1 million.
Which is step 17.
Is that bad?
Ethics are not
my strong suit.
Hypothetical--
if I'm offered oral sex
from a sexaholic,
do I have to decline?
Don't answer yet.
Saying no will cause
both of us pain.
Saying yes will cause
both of us pleasure.
You can't take sex
from a sexaholic.
You can't give booze
to an alcoholic,
and you can't
take this guy's money.
Could be wrong
about the symptom.
I'm wrong all the time.
Taking money
from a sick person
is ethically suspect
at best.
What is this, Canada?
All we do is take money
from sick people.
We work for it.
I'm working!
How much?
$20.
Well, what if it was?
It's the same principle.
$20, $1 million...
What's the difference?
Actually, the difference
is pretty much $1 million.
He came up
with the figure, not me.
[Beeping]
Crap.
Got a patient with
end stage renal disease.
Her heart can't
support dialysis.
She needs a transplant,
but...
you tuned out as soon as it
stopped being about you,
didn't you?
- What?
- I gotta go.
It's all moot.
Patient probably
has long QT.
Probably just a really,
really decent person.
They exist, right?
You can't take
the money, House.
(Benjamin)
Is long QT bad?
It's a tough thing
to control.
Is there someone
you want me to call?
There's someone
I would like to call.
She's the same person
who won't take my calls.
My wife.
When I started giving away
the money, I--
I hoped she'd want
to do it with me.
She didn't.
I miss them.
I have two little boys.
Having a family
doesn't exempt me
from social responsibility.
But family comes first.
It should.
I know that
sounds weird, but...
someone who's
related to you,
does that empirically
make them more special?
More deserving than
anyone else?
Yes, it gives you
a responsibility.
My boys have a roof
over their heads.
They're not starving.
I pay court-ordered
child support,
and, frankly, it's, uh...
more than they need.
I love them more
than anything, I just...
I can't justify
buying video games
and private schools
when other people's children
are starving.
I hope, one day,
they'll understand that.
Your hands are trembling.
Is it the electrodes?
Are you in pain?
No.
What's happening?
I'm not sure, but it's not
what we thought it was.
So...
arrhythmia, fainting,
muscle tremors.
Plus, unfortunately,
mental changes.
I still don't think
it's neurological.
God bless you.
He lost his wife and kids
because she couldn't
stop giving money away.
He lost his wife
because she couldn't
accept not being
filthy rich.
She's not drinking
the coffee either.
Drink it, don't drink it.
The point is,
I gave it to you,
so we're even.
Even?
It was a gift.
An insignificant token.
There was nothing owed.
That was the whole point.
Why?
Yeah, why?
She's the crazy one.
So a guy gives everything
away to strangers: Sane.
Girl who doesn't want anything
from a stranger is crazy.
You're not a stranger.
And your perverse
view of the world
is making you force
a neurological component
onto an obviously
cardiological--
Your parents
didn't love you enough.
So you need to prove
your superiority.
Or they love you
too much,
so you need
to prove your humility.
Or it's just rich guilt.
I'm betting on the last one.
There's a whole list
of drugs
that could have
caused his symptoms.
I doubt the guy
would spend money on drugs
when there are
orphans out there
without cable.
Anyway, he'd be
getting better right now,
not worse.
Could be
polyarteritis nodosa.
That comes with a rash.
Echovirus.
[Echoing] Virus, virus,
virus, virus...
Fits his physical symptoms.
And could,
but doesn't necessarily
cause personality changes.
Works for everyone?
Start him on antivirals.
And, Adams...
when you treat,
and he gets better,
and doesn't give Bob Cratchit
Christmas day off,
you owe me a coffee.
(Thirteen) Click the third tab
from the left
and find the box that says
"previous entries."
You get a drop-down menu
sorted by patient name
and department.
Thank you.
Appreciate your help.
You're gonna read too much
into this, aren't you?
No, not at all.
We're gonna
fundamentally disagree
about what it means
to read too much into this.
Aren't we?
Yes, absolutely.
Look, I thought about
what you said,
and I realized
you were right.
Great.
See you tomorrow morning.
No, you won't.
Afternoon?
I can't think of
another interpretation.
Shut up.
Look, I'm not sure
what you were
trying to achieve.
I'm never quite sure.
But you were actually
a friend to me
when I needed it.
I don't wanna come back
to work for you.
But I was wrong to try
to push you out of my life.
Everything has gone blue.
That's not supposed
to happen, right?
Stay there.
I'm comin'.
No...You don't have
to do that.
Although,
if you did come,
maybe you could swing by
the Hunan Palace
and get some lo mein
and a szechuan beef.
That is six miles
out of my way.
Oh, okay, then.
Guess I'll get something
from the hospital cafeteria,
which is where I get
all my meals
since I can't go anywhere.
[Sighs] Fine.
I'll get the food.
You're a peach.
I started the last round
of pleconaril.
Can you do me a favor?
A favor?
You want me
to return these?
Give them to someone?
Wear them
while you masturbate?
[Scoffs]
I...want you
to have them.
That's not a favor.
It was a two-for-one sale.
I couldn't resist.
I need to justify
buying them.
They're $120.
My car is in the shop.
I'm short on cash
this month.
I can't pay you back.
The first pair were $120.
These...were free.
You do know I punched
the last person
that pissed me off?
Was it Santa?
What's your
patient's status?
Better.
We're discharging him.
[Sighs]
Good.
Hey, hey, hey.
Why do you care?
Specifically.
Although I'm curious
about a general answer too.
Your guy just signed up
to donate a kidney
to my patient
with renal failure.
Did he meet your patient
with renal failure?
No, he heard the nurses
talking about her,
that she was short
on time.
I was wrong.
Don't say that.
House, she really
needs this kidney.
He's not better.
His mental status
is declining.
Or he's doing
an amazing thing
for another human being.
I thought it was
an ethical no-brainer
that we can't take stuff
from sick people.
I changed my mind.
He's still sick.
His symptoms
have gone away.
Not all of them.
Offering an organ
to a stranger
is a symptom.
A couple dozen
people a year
make undirected
kidney donations.
Yeah, how many of them
are also in the process
of pauperizing themselves?
If the guy threw himself
on a grenade,
he'd be a hero.
If it saves a life,
who cares?
You do!
Yesterday, when you made
the exact opposite argument.
If there's even
a chance I'm right,
it'd be dangerous to give
his kidney to someone else.
More dangerous than
complete renal failure?
My patient needs this.
Now.
Why do you wanna
give away your kidney?
There are 70,000 people
in this country
on the active waiting list
for a kidney,
and less than 10,000
dead people a year
to give them one.
Yeah.
If only we could kill
60,000 more people a year,
all would be golden.
I'll give you
your money.
See? Crazy.
Being a live donor
has risks.
I looked it up.
The risk is 1 in 4,000
I could die
during surgery,
which means,
if I don't donate,
I'm valuing my life
at 4,000 times someone else's.
It's not like
I want to be
cut open and have a part
of me taken out.
But I've got two,
and this woman has none.
She'll die without it.
Perfectly logical.
People with mental deficiency
can be logical.
Just like sane people
can be illogical.
This kidney thing is
the only evidence you have
that he's sick.
I'm gonna let him
be a donor.
Dr. House,
it's not a symptom.
Come back after you're
convinced that I'm healthy,
and I will
give you your money.
No, you won't.
We have time
for one more test
before we move him.
What test?
Whatever test will prove
there was
an echovirus-irus-irus,
and he's not cured,
obviously.
I've been saying all along
this could be Whipple's.
Causes arrhythmia,
tremor,
and mental changes.
Bad idea.
There's no joint pain.
Where's Adams?
We thought
the case was over.
She has a job interview.
Why is she here?
'Cause I called her.
Bigger question
is why that worked.
I'm here because
I have time
and you have
a crisis and I--
we're too busy
for rationalizations.
Patient made a big downgrade
in his personal life.
He's probably not
eating all that healthy.
Magnesium deficiency?
Wait until they take him
back to his room--draw blood,
do an expanded
electrolyte profile.
No, he hasn't had
anxiety or any
trouble sleeping.
I think it's
Whipple's disease.
Bad idea.
He doesn't have joint pain.
Joint pain is common,
but not definitive.
Whipple's explains
all of his symptoms,
including
the personality change.
And it would respond
to antibiotics,
which is why
he started to feel better.
Which doesn't mean
he's not still sick.
You were right.
Counts for nothing
if you can't defend it.
Book a procedure room.
Do an upper endoscopy and run
a PCR test for Whipple's.
Guilt.
You feel guilty
about leaving.
Yes, I think
that little of you
and that much of me.
You're nothing without me.
Not leaving me.
Leaving humanity.
I'm going
with my girlfriend.
The woman I love.
To have fun.
You're trying to make me
feel guilty
because you're
saving lives here.
And I think that's great.
I'm proud to have
been a part of it,
but...now...
I just wanna be happy.
Oh...no one's
unhappy in Greece.
It just appeared
in the last few weeks.
He's having trouble
holding a pencil in school.
Does it itch?
Do anything different
lately?
You get a new baseball
glove, a new kitten?
Well, the neighbors
put in a pool,
so he's been spending
a lot of time over there.
But, well, if it was
something in the water,
it would be everywhere,
wouldn't it?
It is in the water.
He's allergic to chlorine?
No...
[Inhales deeply]
He's allergic to
summer lilac.
That's my lotion.
And it's not in the pool.
No, it's on the palms
of his hands.
In the pool
is the neighbor's daughter.
Or the neighbor's hot wife.
Here's some lube.
Sorry.
Too late for your eyesight.
Endoscopy didn't reveal
any lesions
in the small intestine.
I'm running PCR test now.
Found it in my office.
Appears to be a gift.
That can't be good.
Damn it.
You got her
the job interview.
And that was supposed
to be the end of it.
I...don't take charity.
Good for you!
You loon.
I don't like
owing people things.
So either
you're so insecure
that you feel like you need
to always have the upper hand,
or you're so arrogant
that the notion of a favor
is insulting to you.
Or it's your family,
some kind of
immigrant pride thing.
I'm betting
on the last one.
I just don't like it.
It makes me feel...Icky.
That's the reason?
Ickiness?
You never even tried
to analyze this?
It's even crazier
than the gift thing.
House...
there's no sign of
tropheryma DNA.
It's not Whipple's.
Well...we did
what we could.
You sure you wanna
do this?
[Chuckles]
Relax.
This is gonna make me
very happy.
[Heart monitor beeping]
[Air hissing faintly]
(Man) Go a little bit more
along here.
[Pulse increasing]
Dr. Simpson.
Heart rate's 140,
pressure's dropping.
Get him adenosine, stat.
Patient's unstable.
Surgery's off.
[Alarm beeping]
Arrhythmia's back.
He's on Heparin
and stable for now,
but this could
put him at risk
for stroke or embolism.
Maybe he got bit
by a spider.
The symptoms can take
up to three days to manifest.
He'd have localized pain.
LCDD?
Almost always
hits the kidneys.
Ah, Dr. Foreman.
Perhaps you can help us.
I can't decide whether to
take out an "I told you so" ad
in the New England Journal
or stay classy
and just spray-paint it
on your car.
You're off the case.
That seems like
an overreaction.
You dosed him.
Couldn't stand
to lose him as a patient,
so you faked his symptom
to prove you right.
That's idiotic.
Sorry.
Don't apologize.
I don't know if you're
power crazed or paranoid,
but I know she's right.
Two lives are
in the balance here.
House, I worked for you
for seven years.
I know how you operate.
So when I see symptoms
magically show up
right when you need them--
And I was your boss
for seven years.
And I know what a suspicious,
micromanaging hard-ass you are.
Why would I do this now?
Knowing you can send me
right back to jail?
What'd you give him?
Nothing!
You can't prove otherwise.
So why don't you
do the smart thing here?
You're off the case.
You no longer have access
to this patient.
You can't let him do this.
[Sighs]
He's the boss.
And he's right.
[Object bounces on floor]
I assume
you dosed the patient
because you're
really certain
he has a neurological
condition?
I assume you're
interpreting my actions
in the best possible light
'cause you didn't
get the job?
[Paper crumpling]
What's with you and Park?
Nothing.
I expect my people
to lie better than that.
Either you're
getting her gifts because
you want her to like you,
in which case I don't like you,
or you're getting her gifts
to screw with her.
In which case,
I will be teaching you
my secret homey handshake.
I just...I thought
it was interesting
she couldn't
accept that coffee.
I wanted to see
how deep it went.
But now?
Oh, now I just
want to win.
[Chuckles softly]
What was in the box?
Gift certificate.
The spa.
Nah, that's
not gonna do it.
You're up against
a lifetime of training.
If you wanna win,
you gotta do something
she can't possibly
reciprocate.
You gotta push
her neuroses to the point
where even she thinks
that she's crazy.
One more favor.
Then I promise,
I'll leave you alone forever.
Or I'm lying.
Either way,
it's more interesting
than whatever
you're doing now.
Can I help you?
I'm his wife.
We're separated.
I heard he was sick.
I just...
Wanted to see him.
He's giving a kidney
to someone he's never met?
He wants to, yeah.
I know he's
talked about you.
He's been alone
all this time.
I'm sure it would
mean a lot to him
to see you.
I wanted to spend
my life with him, but...
I need to feel like he loves me
more than other people.
Like he loves
our kids more.
Maybe that's selfish.
I should go.
Was that my wife?
I don't know.
You the guy,
the kidney donor?
There was a problem, but...
I'm gonna try again.
Um...to give it
to the same lady?
She needs it.
Okay. Never mind.
Wait.
What do you--
what do you want?
Uh, it's nothing.
It's just...
I have polycystic
kidney disease.
And I need a transplant,
and they say I don't
have much time,
so when I heard
that you were willing,
I just...
But I'm glad
it's going to someone.
I'll give it to you.
But you already
promised it to someone else.
I have another one.
Saving one life is good.
Saving two is better.
You give away two kidneys,
and you die.
I could live on dialyses
for years.
Yes, and--
and then you die.
And then I could donate
my other organs.
Heart, lungs.
I could save
four or five more lives.
Foreman's gonna need
a diagnostician.
This guy is crazy.
Arrhythmia,
muscle tremors,
and, yes,
mental changes.
If his heart
doesn't rupture,
he's liable to rip it out
and give it away.
You know, the "down" vibe in here
[Electrical buzzing]
is totally ruining
my Charlie's Angels fantasy.
[Buzzing continues]
And that haircut
isn't helping, either.
It seems like
Graves disease
or some other
thyroid issue.
Is she on the team now?
Like, forever?
His thyroid levels were
within normal range
when he
was admitted.
Could be
Coxsackie B virus.
Or pericarditis.
What about porphyria?
It's a little weird
without the rash,
but it fits all
of his other symptoms.
And if it is acute
intermittent porphyria,
that would explain why
his symptoms keep recurring.
It's unlikely...
but it's possible.
What else?
I said what else?
[Whirring]
Oh, for...
[Muttering]
[Whirring cuts off]
There. That's better.
Now, what else?
Well, if there's nothing
better than possible,
then possible
gets upgraded to probable.
I'll start him
on hematin.
No, I'll go.
So what's the answer?
Are you now on the team?
[Mocking park]
Like, forever?
I don't know.
'Cause I was thinking
of ordering T-shirts.
I don't know...House.
I mean,
what am I supposed to do?
I trained to be a Doctor.
I know how to take
someone's pain away,
how to make a stopped heart
beat again.
We've brought
people's kids back.
Their husbands...
So...guilt?
Yes, you were right.
You're always right.
I just...
I have the skills
to help people.
Is it okay for me
to walk away from that
because I...want
to just have fun?
Obviously not.
[Bell dings]
How's your patient?
She died a few hours ago.
Thirteen is back.
No department.
No money.
And somehow,
you managed to con her
into hanging around.
I have a gift.
What?
It was a con.
The patient was faking?
No, I was.
I brought him in here
under false pretenses.
Just to get his money.
I ordered a bunch
of random tests
to keep him here.
One of them was
a head CT, which uses...
Iodine contrast.
You think he's
allergic to Iodine?
No, again.
Just don't interrupt me.
Thirteen was right.
This is a thyroid issue.
He has Plummer's disease.
He has a nodule
in his thyroid.
It produces
excess hormone.
Not enough
to test abnormal,
just more than his brain
is used to.
Just enough to make him
irrationally generous,
make him vulnerable
to overheating.
(Wilson) Then you pumped his body
full of Iodine
and kicked him
into thyrotoxicosis.
(House)
I said don't interrupt.
But, yes, you're right.
Take out the nodule,
he'll be fine.
Two days, one surgery.
I now accept,
that your all better.
Where's my money?
You made me sick.
You were already sick.
I just made you
much, much worse.
Seriously...the money.
You're not giving it
to me, are you?
When you're facing death...
some things come into focus.
My wife.
You love your family.
You want them back.
Your altruism
was always a symptom.
No, it wasn't.
I'm still gonna--
Keep less?
How much less?
Just enough
to spoil your kids?
No.
But they need it more
than people with TB
or children in Indonesia
with no eyes?
Diagnosticians
with hearts of gold?
I don't wanna give you money
because you're an ass.
I was an ass last week.
I love my family.
I want to be with them.
That doesn't make me
a bad person.
No.
It makes you
a healthy person.
My mechanic called.
He said the work's
been paid for.
You mentioned your car
was in the shop.
That's $4,500.
Smile and say thank you.
Or I get you G.P.S.
You win.
Thank you.
Your car
is getting fixed.
You're right.
She went for it.
Good work.
Need a lift tomorrow?
'Cause your car
is still in the shop.
I don't take charity.
I'm just glad it's over.
Nothing is ever over.
♪ To live, oh ♪
♪ and I've been trying
hard against ♪
♪ unbelievable odds ♪
♪ ♪
♪ gets so hard
in times like now ♪
♪ to hold on ♪
♪ ♪
♪ but guns they wait
to be stuck by ♪
Thirteen.
Wait a minute.
♪ ♪
♪ there ain't no one
goin' to turn me 'round ♪
You're fired.
Now what?
House, I'm starving.
I'm not joking.
You're fired.
Don't come in tomorrow.
House...
I can work with people
who've got nowhere else to go.
People who got
something to prove.
People who just get off
on weird cases.
What I can't work with
is someone who's here
so she doesn't
have to feel bad.
♪ Places where they send you ♪
You're trying to save me.
Yes...I think
that little of you
and that much of me.
♪ They'll zip you up
and dress you down ♪
♪ and stand you in a row ♪
♪ but you know
you don't have to ♪
♪ you can just say no ♪
Okay.
♪ ♪
♪ and there ain't no one ♪
Bye, House.
♪ Goin' to turn me around ♪
♪ ♪
♪ there ain't no one ♪
♪ goin' to turn me around ♪
♪ ain't no one... ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net