Okay, boys and girls.
Guess what kind of animal
Wacky Benny's making now?
Give you a big hint.
Bor-ing.
Is it a dead animal?
I say we put him
out of his misery
and bring out Emma's cake.
He's so new to this.
How's he gonna learn
if we stop his act?
You're a sucky clown.
And you're
a super-duper audience.
Hey, that is not okay.
Hey, keep your hands
off my son.
Tell him to keep
his hand off me.
I can't move my arm or leg.
House S08E06
"Parents"
By Mikhel for Subtitulos.es
==SPREAD THE WORD==
So how does a completely healthy
teenager have a mini-stroke?
Head CT and cerebral
angiogram are normal.
Clotting parameters are normal.
You're forgetting
the wrinkly clump
in the middle of his shirt.
Thought we'd diagnose
the middle-aged clown first.
It's probably
from my seat belt.
Wrinkle pattern's too varied.
It looks like someone
shoved you or grabbed you.
Probably from the diaper bag.
If the patient's using drugs,
cocaine could have caused
an arterial spasm in his brain.
The tox screen was clean.
I'm gonna say it was the
ex-girlfriend you cheated on,
not the ex-wife
you cheated with.
If the latter
was prone to violence,
you'd have been scattered
in various dumpsters years ago.
Seriously?
No one else wants to talk
about the patient?
New office furniture.
Meaty topic.
What's the action
on the ex-wife?
It was Rachel's boyfriend Phil.
His company's moving him
back to Portland.
He wants me to change
my visitation order
so he can ask Rachel
and my daughter
to move out west with him.
Things got a little heated.
The patient
was punched in the groin.
Could have triggered a massive
sympathetic discharge.
Carotid duplex is normal.
Who's better qualified
to be the daddy?
The guy who spilled
a little DNA in her gene pool
or the guy who's gonna be there
day and night
to pass on important values
like not shtupping mommy
after the divorce?
I am her daddy.
She's staying here.
House has a point.
A couple nights a week
with each kid
may make you feel better.
Doesn't replace two
'round-the-clock parents.
'Round-the-clock or not,
parenting's an impossible job.
No way not to mess it up.
Why shouldn't Taub be
the one to do it?
- Thank you.
- Makes sense.
Park's tiger mom and dad
were so insufferable,
she has to measure
their affection in hours.
Chase's careerist dad
and alcoholic mom
were so indifferent,
he has to believe it's a wash.
Your turn.
What did your
screwed-up parents do
to screw up
your view of parenting?
They were good parents.
That's an oxymoron.
Chase is right. All parents
screw up all children.
He's also dreamy,
but it's not relevant now.
So all parents screw up
all children,
but it makes
some huge difference
if I keep my daughter here
or let her move?
Endocarditis.
Flipd a piece of vegetation
into his brain,
which could have broken up
before the angiogram.
Transesophageal echo
to confirm.
Screwed up is your best case.
Bouncing between
a philandering workaholic dad
and an embittered,
sexually betrayed mom,
it's gonna lead
to screwed-up squared.
Is endocarditis treatable?
Very. The echo will show us
any growths on his heart valve.
Most likely meds
will be enough.
He won't even need surgery.
He's just taken up performing
and it's very stressful
for him.
Could that have caused this?
It's not stressful.
I have fun.
Stress wouldn't be relevant,
but anything that
increases his adrenalin
could have made it worse.
Maybe we find you a new hobby,
one you're a little better at.
I'm gonna get better at it,
and it's not a hobby.
I-I think I want to get a job
working as a circus clown,
making people laugh.
Ben, I-I don't think
that's a good idea.
It was good enough for my dad.
You're a, uh...
no, his biological father.
Could his dad's melanoma
be a factor here?
That wouldn't be related.
Ben, you barely knew him.
You're such a smart kid.
You could aim a lot higher
than face paint
and seltzer bottles.
I need treatment
for my type 2 diabetes.
There is absolutely no part
of that sentence that is true.
I've been experiencing
weight gain, fatigue,
and sluggishness.
Weight loss is a symptom
of diabetes.
Fatigue is a symptom
of thinking you have disease
you don't actually have,
and sluggishness is a synonym
of fatigue.
I need Insulin.
I know it.
Much as I'd like to kill you
by dangerously lowering
your blood sugar,
murder violates my parole.
That bloodwork is week's old.
Test me again.
I am the test.
The test is negative.
The test also thinks you're
a giant pain in the ass.
That last insult
was your cue to leave.
Test me.
Fine. Wait right here.
Thank you.
Sleep study.
Please make sure
he's not disturbed
for the next eight hours.
We need to talk
about Saturday night.
No, no, no, no, no.
Historians will talk
of Saturday night, not us.
The legendary night
on which we watch Santos
shatter Rubio's jaw
and you epically pay me $50.
I have a chance
to really watch it.
A patient of mine has a pair
of tickets he can't use,
and obviously you're under
hoe and office arrest.
I just wanted to make sure
you were cool
if I go to without you.
Uh, no, thanks.
I'm afraid I'm gonna have to
decline your invitation
to not spend Saturday night
with you.
These are ringside seats.
Cameras are ringside too.
If you want,
I could sweat and spit
and bleed on you
from time to time.
I'd take you if I could.
Well, I'd take me
if either of us could.
See what a tough spot I'm in?
I'm going to that fight.
All right, I'll take
the other ticket.
Let me worry about logistics.
Patient's heart valves
are normal.
It's not endocarditis.
But he has a thickened
pericardium,
which makes no sense.
He has a heart problem
but not one that could have
caused his T.I.A.
Syphilitic vasculitis
would explain the T.I.A.
And the pericardial
inflammation.
Syph test was negative.
Plus, the kid's never been
sexually active.
Yeah, I got that from
the line in his chart
that says "birthday clown."
His late father
was a circus clown.
Histoplasmosis?
He's not immuno-compromised.
And I assume you added that
irrelevant tidbit
because you're moved by
the son's idiotic tribute
and think it justifies keeping
your daughter in New Jersey.
What if he has a heightened
immune system?
I mentioned it because...
Take your time.
We'll continue
with the medicine.
Sjogren's could have given him
chronic pericarditis
and cerebral arteritis.
Sjogren's it is.
IV immunosuppressant to treat.
Anything?
This will calm
your immune system.
Should be out of here
within the week.
My mom will be happy
to hear that.
I've got an internship
that starts in three weeks.
I take it it's not at
a place with a big top.
It's at
my stepdad's law office.
I know I'm not any good
at being a clown yet,
but when I do get a laugh
and see those kids' eyes
light up,
that's how my dad made me feel
when I was a kid.
You need to hang on to that.
Heh.
My mom says he was
a loving father
but always broke
and always on the road.
It's just a stupid way
to make a living.
You're 16.
Plenty of time to make money.
Wanting to build a connection
with your dad
and pass on some of the joy
that he gave you,
that's not stupid at all.
Ooh. I got it.
Is, uh, is this because
of the medication?
Is it normal?
It's not normal,
and it's not Sjogren's.
T.I.A.,
thickened pericardium,
and now he's bleeding
from his nose and mouth.
What are you doing with her?
"Her"?
Surely this bundle of fun
has an actual name.
It's Sophie.
Both your kids are named...
She's Sophie.
The other one's Sophia.
It different enough.
they actually have
two completely different
derivations.
No, they don't.
I wasn't in a strong
negotiating position.
Why is she here?
Ruby dropped her off.
Seemed pretty upset.
Apparently someone forgot
that it was daddy's night.
She wasn't even gonna leave her
until I said that I was
letting you off early.
Damn it. I just started
back on the team.
My schedule's a mess.
If your own kids
are a scheduling item,
maybe you should let
one of them move.
Patient has low platelets.
Makes me think D.I.C.
She doesn't seem
to like that idea.
You're right.
He has no
schistocytes in his smear.
He also has a low red count.
What if it's
a retroperitoneal bleed?
No Grey-Turner's sign.
She wasn't fussing like that
when I was holding her.
Maybe she likes
the sound of my voice,
which is weird because I have
no genetic connection to her.
Could it be she doesn't
know the difference?
So many children of your own.
No wonder you have such insight
into my relationship
with my babies.
Good point.
How could I comprehend
that you're too despised
to keep them from having
the same name,
too overwhelmed to remember
your own calendar,
and too vain to admit
that at this stage,
you don't matter
to either baby.
Low white count
suggests infection.
What if you're allright?
Low platelets
plus low red count
plus low white count equals...
Aplastic anemia.
Kid needs a bone marrow
transplant.
Everyone except Adams,
transfuse his platelets
till you find a match.
You started college
a semester late
because you left high school
because you had
five incompletes
in your junior year.
And you're offering
one bad semester
as proof that my parents
screwed me up?
Did okay before that.
Straight as after that.
I went through
a rebellious phase.
Don't tell me.
Mom and dad were at
each other's throats
and the academic crisis
was a cry for help.
Sorry to mess with
your world view,
but I'm not messed up,
so my parents couldn't have
messed me up.
Mom's HLA is only a 3/6 match.
Maternal grandmother's
worse than that.
Where did you unload the baby?
- Maternity ward.
- Shut up.
You realize you're making
House's argument for him.
The part where he said
any parent who uses day care
should ship their child
across the country?
No, the part where he said
that baby doesn't need you.
You've only got her
a couple days a week
and most of that's spent with
a rotating cast of nurses.
That's how daddy likes to
spend his time too.
Shut up.
First cousin's also a whiff.
So much for genetics mattering.
I'll try the marrow registry.
- Dr.
- Park is searching the registry.
Transfusing his platelets will
keep him healthy while we wait.
Are you sure there's no one on
the father's side of the family?
If one of them's a match,
that'd speed things up a lot.
His parents died young.
He was an only child.
There's no living relatives
that I know of.
Something will turn up soon.
How soon is soon?
Will he miss a lot of school?
I'm actually thinking of
just getting my ged.
How do you expect to get
into a good college?
I'm gonna take classes
on magic and juggling
and try to make a go of this.
Ben, you keep
your grades up, you can do
anything in the world.
Like what? Work in
some boring office?
I mean, do you think my father
would have done that
for ten minutes?
You don't remember your father.
You don't know...
I want to build
a connection with him,
pass on some of the...
The joy that he gave me.
My, uh, my back hurts.
Uh...
His BP is dropping.
We think we've dealt wit
all the liability issues.
I'm in a meeting.
Sorry.
Since you paged me, I didn't
want to keep you waiting.
Yeah, I paged you,
which means you're next.
That's cool.
I'll wait.
That's a good start.
Let's go through it
point by point.
First up...
I'll call you back.
Just got this.
The American Associate
of Rheumatology
wants you to speak,
9:00, Saturday,
in Atlantic City.
Dr. Neusinger canceled on them
at the last minute.
Hmm. I hate conferences.
This is a big one,
and it's the premium slot.
I'd like you to do it.
I'll clear it with
your parole officer.
What do I need to do for you?
Halve the clinic hours
that you recently doubled
and double the hooker budget
that you recently halved.
I think you refer to it
as petty cash.
Fine.
Just one thing.
I'm gonna ask them to
put you on in the morning.
We're doing them a favor.
Why should you
have to spend the night?
You said that 9:00
was the premium slot.
I mean, I want to feel like
I've earned my hookers.
The place'll be a madhouse,
especially since it's two miles
from the Rubio fight
at the exact same time.
Nice try.
You called up,
pretended to be Neusinger,
cancelled, and suggested
yourself as a replacement.
You go to that fight,
you go to prison.
But that'd be redundant,
when I have an angry black guy
waiting for me to drop
the soap right here.
Better go do some of those
clinic hours I recently doubled.
Test my urine.
Looks like I was wrong
about my diagnosis.
Yeah. I have diabetes.
No, but you're not
a hypochondriac
or you would have imagined
some new disease
after I shot down
the first one.
So whose urine is that?
Diabetic girlfriend without
health insurance?
It's not a scam.
I'm sick.
Now I have swollen ankles.
The medical term is cankles.
Is there some black market
in Insulin
that I don't know about?
It's in my genes.
My old man got diabetes at 50.
My older brother got it at 50.
I just turned 50.
Well, it's a great argument
if diabetes was a gold watch.
I got sciatica, like my dad.
Class-four hemorrhoids,
like him.
I need to get a jump
on this thing.
We had to stop the transfusion.
Patient's having an allergic
reaction to donor platelets.
No one in mom's family's
a match,
and as far as she knows,
dad has no living relatives.
It's been years since he died.
If the kid's dad
died young of melanoma,
how come the overprotective mom
never took him
to a dermatologist?
Are you gonna test my urine
or what?
Not diabetes.
Use cross-matched platelets.
Try to find the patient
some blood
that's closer to his own.
And get the real story
on clown, senior's death.
Mom's hiding something.
It's a good bet that it's
medically relevant.
Apple juice.
Easiest way to fake a spike
in blood sugar.
His family history of melanoma
may have affected
his cellular outlook.
If we had more data
on the exact type of melanoma
his father had...
Otherwise, we might not be able
to find a marrow match.
He never had melanoma.
How did he die?
He didn't.
He lives in pennsauken
under a different name,
Mitchell Gordon.
How could you keep this
from me? From Ben?
He really needs to know
his dad just breezed
in and out of his life,
drunk and incoherent?
It's better to think
the man's dead but decent.
You realize I have to invite
someone else to the Rubio fight?
- Nope.
- No realization whatsoever.
You have a LoJack on your leg.
I was happy watching the fight
on pay-per-view.
You're the one who insisted
we go to Atlantic City.
Your biological father
was a decent,
God-fearing minister.
The guy who raised you
was a cold-hearted jerk.
I'm trying to figure out
why you're so convinced
Adams has parentally
inflicted damage.
You're trying to deflect.
Now you are.
You have to believe that every
parent screws up every child
or you were screwed out of
a decent childhood.
My decent daddy of the cloth
was also being indecent
with my married mom.
He probably would have taken
other kids to the playground.
It's not my fault.
Bad parenting.
Mitchell Gordon?
I've already got a religion.
Go away.
We're doctors.
Your son Ben
is in the hospital,
at Princeton-Plainsboro.
He's very sick.
Yeah, well, I don't have
a son. Not anymore.
We know there are
some issues there,
but your bone marrow
could cure him.
There's a hospital
two miles from here.
It's a simple test.
You said he was at
Princeton-Plainsboro?
His mother feels it's better
to do the test
at a different hospital.
Well, I guess I don't have
a son anymore.
House isn't gonna give up.
Just tell him
about your parents
or make up a lie.
I don't want to lie.
I don't want to validate
his ridiculous theory.
It's not ridiculous.
En the best-intentioned
parents
end up damaging their kids.
You're a smart,
successful doctor.
How much damage could you have?
Know how I got
interested in medicine?
When my mother drank,
she couldn't handle me,
so she locked me
in my father's study.
Only so many hours you can cry
and bang on the door
before you give up,
find something to read.
We all have family dysfunction.
That's why we're successful.
To fill that hole.
My parents have a lot of money,
but they didn't make it
legally.
White-collar crime?
It started with card games.
High-stakes poker.
Then my dad got into narcotics,
at first just selling
but then using too,
or he never would have gotten
into the slave trade.
Children mostly.
Easier to pack in small crates.
Plus the shipping's
a lot cheaper.
Won't even trust
a co-worker.
What did your parents
do to you?
You have to go
see him yourself.
He wouldn't even ce
to the door a second time.
Okay.
I'll drive over there.
It's a pleural effusion.
He had a bleeding problem
earlier.
Must be bleeding
into his lungs.
Except there's no blood.
What does it mean?
It means you don't have to
make that drive.
The problem isn't his marrow.
It's his liver.
- Liver failure.
- Explains everything.
The question is, what explains
the liver failure?
It's not an infection.
We tried antibiotics,
but he's not responding.
More curiously,
what explains the mom
lying about dad pushing up
squirting daisies?
This is how you plan
to get to the boxing game?
Why are you looking at her?
'Cause I'm stunned, and
I have to look at something.
Match, bout, fight,
contest, day, Helena.
Almost anything works
after "boxing,"
except the word "game."
Your bigger problem is,
the people who design
those things aren't idiots.
Can you believe she used to
work in the can?
Nothing is tamper-proof.
It's a synthetic problem.
His liver's not
synthesizing proteins,
so fluid is leaking out
of his blood vessels.
And mom's a selfish jerk.
She traded up,
married a lawyer,
wants to forget
the lowly circus clown.
You're defending the father
because you feel like a jerk
for baking buns
in two different ovens.
You want to believe the
mythical biological connection
excuses being a man slut.
Ow!
I don't know why I'm starting
to doubt your expertise.
You do have a classified ad
and a piece of metal.
It's temperature that
sets it off, not force.
The rivets go pop,
I slide in the heating pad.
Easy peasy.
More likely the patient has
a hyperammonemic problem.
His liver's not
cleaning out his blood.
The buildup of toxins
is causing everything.
I'm defending the dad
because he got screwed.
After he lost his son,
he lost his job.
Been in and out of rehab,
ve up clowning.
Yes, as a parent, I empathize.
I say we tell the kid.
He's a minor,
the mom's his guardian,
and it's not even
medically relevant.
She robbed them of
12 years together.
Or she ripped off
the band-aid too late.
That memory that she let
son of Bozo establish
is making him chase his father's
moronic profession
when he could be living
the high life in Portland.
And I mean that
metaphorically, of course.
This is where you dazzle me
with your contingency plan.
I see why employers are
reluctant to hire ex-cons.
Well, what about the patient?
Is the problem hyperammonemic
or synthetic?
Can't treat for both.
One requires hemodialysis,
the other a liver transplant,
and we couldn't even get
the kid a marrow match.
Get the mom's consent to
pump him full of protein.
If it's a synthetic problem,
more fluid will leak
into h chest
and his heart will fail.
If it's hyperammonemic,
toxins will overwhelm his body
and he'll go into a coma.
Do you only like tests that
involve the risk of death?
There are some slower,
less conclusive tests,
but why take that risk?
In here.
Oh, my God.
The water.
This is completely my fault.
There are very serious risks,
but if we don't figure out
what he has,
we can't treat him at all.
I may be a little
out of bounds here,
but in case there are
complications,
it might be a good time
to come clean to your son,
let his father visit.
A little out of bounds?
I don't know the history,
but everyone makes mistakes.
Your son worships him.
Doctor's right about that.
Oh, yeah? And when
did he learn that?
When he encouraged Ben
to drop out of school?
Mitchell is not Ben's father
any more than a sperm donor
would have been.
Dr. House?
Unless you're a locksmith
or an electrician
with political contacts,
I'm busy.
My husband saw
you in the clinic.
Wants treatment for diabetes.
My condolences
on your forthcoming divorce.
He keeps imagining symptoms,
and now I have to make him
these awful anti-diabetic meals.
Since I have no intention
of testing him,
treating him,
or cooking for him...
Could you write me a fake
prescription for Insulin?
The advantage
of fake prescriptions is,
you don't have to be
a real doctor to write one.
Just tell me what's safe
to inject in his thigh.
His symptoms will go away
and then I can show him
he was never sick.
Water?
Imaginary medicine
is not my specialty.
I do have
an imaginary colleague
who's just sent me
an imaginary page.
Imagine how sorry I am.
Still mad about
what happened in the lab?
I'm not mad.
I'm being professional.
You claim
you're not screwed up.
You may even believe it.
But House doesn't and I don't,
so you can wait till he camps
out on your parents' lawn
or you can admit you don't
live on some higher plane
and thank me later.
My, uh, my eye feels weird.
What's happening to me?
You look tired.
I hate it when people say that.
I know, I look bad.
I thought you were gonna
go to bed early last night.
Like an idiot, I went out
with my girlfriends
to pretend I have a life,
when all I did
was flirt with guys
who'd have no interest
in a mom,
miss the baby I couldn't
wait to get rid of,
and then get yelled at
by my mom
for staying out too late.
- You need your own place.
- Yes.
I moved back home because it was
too drafty at the four seasons.
So go back to work
at the hospital.
Day care costs more than
what I earned as a nurse.
Have you considered
sub-standard day care?
Why don't you stay here toght?
No. I mean,
in the guest room.
I'll watch the baby again,
and you can get
a real night's sleep.
You'd do that?
Win-win.
Mommy gets a rest,
daddy gets more time
with his little angel.
There's some sweats
in the closet in the back.
Lucky girl.
Gets another sleepover
with da-da.
It makes a difference.
Doesn't it?
Didn't answer your page
last night.
Sorry. Battery died.
We got the patient's eye
back in place
with steroid injections,
but a bulging eyeball means
it's not a liver problem.
And mom's determination
to keep dad away,
even as her kid
gets sicker and sicker,
means she's got more to hide.
It's not diagnostically
relevant.
Let's let it drop.
You just lost my vote.
You flip-flopped
on parental rights.
I've been trying to
persuade the mother,
but it's her son,
so it's her call.
Well, that very evolved of you.
Don't usually see Darwinian
changes over breakfast.
You made nice-nice with Phil,
you decided that
he'd make a decent father
for thing 2 after all.
I had Sophie again last night
and Ruby slept
in my guest room,
which has nothing to do
with Phil,
who will never be a father
to my children.
Angioneurotic edema can
cause rapid swelling.
Hey, we're having
a conversation here.
No abdominal pain.
So that must have been nice,
having Ruby
and the baby under one roof.
Yes, it was nice having
my daughter in my home.
That's why I would like her
sister to live near my home.
Anasarca?
Swelling would have
followed gravity.
Isn't that getting this whole
parenting thing ass backwards?
Aren't you supposed to figure
out what you can sacrifice
to maximize their niceness?
And do you think I should
sacrifice myself
from their lives?
Just one life,
until the other one's mommy
meets someone nicer than you.
Swelling that fast
and localized
has to come
from the lymph nodes.
Burkitt's lymphoma.
Swelling. Cankles.
That's not a
symptom of Burkitt's.
- Are you saying it's...
- It's Burkitt's.
Prep him for chemo.
I think you should
give House permission
to go to Atlantic City.
We'll stop by
the rheumatology conference.
Everyone's covered.
No.
The guy has earned the right
to go to one boxing match.
He's done everything
you've asked...
Funded and staffed
his own department.
Hasn't even broken as much
as a traffic law.
You're right.
So you'll let him go?
No.
I get why he wants to go
to that fight.
I'd love to go myself,
which is kind of
why I have to stop him.
My job is to be the jerk.
House has to believe that
I have authority over him.
He can't function
under someone's thumb.
I know, which means
you can't go either.
Your job is to be his friend,
to stay here and sit with him
and watch the fight
on pay-per-view
while bitching about me.
If we both do our jobs,
we might actually get him
through his parole.
You're right.
Sorry to show up like this.
I was expecting
a battery of lawyers.
No lawyers.
Phil had something that
he would like to say,
so I thought that he should
say it in person.
It was wrong of me
to confront you
about taking Rachel
to Portland.
You don't want to move
to Portland?
Of course I do, but this is
about your daughter too
and I'm not gonna do
something like this
without your support.
So you guys are trying
to manipulate me
by playing good cop/good cop?
Is that how little
you think of me?
It's clear you're back
working for House.
I will see you this weekend
when you pick up Sophie.
Sophia.
We actually started
calling her Sophie.
Yeah.
Great.
It's cute.
Cankles.
Is there some problem with
the prescription you gave me?
I'm faint. I've been
gaining more weight.
I think I need a bigger dose.
If you double his placebo,
he might drown.
Also, you forgot to mention
that your heart rate is slow.
My... my heart rate is not...
52.
The technical term is slow.
Those awful anti-diabetic
meals you eat,
do they contain bok choy?
A pound of it.
Every day.
Bok choy has glucosinolates
which inhibit thyroid function
and account
for all your symptoms.
So this isn't diabetes?
You have a bad case of irony.
The food that you're eating
to stop making you sick
is making you sick.
Hey, maybe I don't have my
father's crummy genes after all.
On the other hand,
maybe you're fat enough
to get diabetes
even without him.
I can't believe I have cancer.
We caught it early.
You should be okay.
I could die. I never went
anywhere, did anything.
If my father had lived,
everything would have
been different.
Your mom and stepdad love you.
They've given you a great home.
That counts for a lot.
He's crashing.
Everything's shutting down.
Renal failure, lung
failure, heart failure,
all before we started chemo.
Burkitt's lymphoma is
fast-moving, but not this fast.
No rush. ICU stands for
take your time in Latin.
Multiple aneurysms.
That would mean that every
symptom after his T.I.A.
was a coincidence.
Cholesterol emboli?
Bingo. Fits perfectly.
Check the file.
Confirm that we did major
abdominal surgery on him
and then completely
forgot about it.
House.
Hello?
What the hell
are you doing here?
I was told that this might be
my last chance to see my son.
You had no right!
This is none of your business!
- I didn't.
- I called him.
This man's Ben's hero.
Let them spend
five minutes together.
No! Get out of here!
Wait.
You sexually molested your son.
Your walk.
Tabes dorsalis.
You have
late-stage syphilis,
which you gave to our patient
presumably 12 years ago,
which also explains why mom
is not big on family reunions.
I shouldn't be here.
We tested him for syphilis.
He was negative.
After 12 years, the active
infection would have died down
everywhere except the arteries
in his brain,
where it could hide out
from our tests.
But when
that six-year-old heckler
punched him
in his juggling pins,
it kicked up the dormant
bacteria in his pelvis.
The immunosuppressants
we gave him
sent it into overdrive.
The antibiotics we gave him
actually started destroying
the syphilis.
But like pouring water
on a fire,
that led to a trail
of toxic smoke and ash
which made his immune system
overcompensate.
Severe Jarisch-Herxheimer
reaction.
Is this true?
Yes, Jarisch-herxheimer is real.
It sounds silly, but...
Oh, you mean
the... the... right.
I found stains on his clothes.
He didn't understand
and he didn't seem traumatized.
I kept trying to talk to him,
but before long, he'd forgotten,
and he seemed...
And he seemed happy
and he seemed normal.
So you made daddy go away
and you made sure junior had
no reason to go looking.
I was just trying
to protect him,
like I should have done
from the start.
Sorry.
IV penicillin and
anti-TNF antibodies,
he'll be fine.
Apart from the whole
daddy-rape thing.
We're not done.
No, we are not.
Notify the dad's
sexual partners.
Notify his employer,
his landlord.
Notify the police.
I meant the kid.
We're not gonna tell him
he was molested?
To make him miserable or
to forfeit your license?
To tell him the truth.
He's a virgin.
How do we explain the STD?
It's a medical diagnosis.
Screw the parents.
The kid's our patient.
I guess Taub's got
a tough choice to make
when the kid wakes up.
Why is it my choice?
'Cause you're a dad.
How could the rest of us
possibly understand?
What was...
What was wrong with me?
It's called syphilis.
Uh, you... you can get that
without having sex?
I didn't tell him.
Your heart said
he needed to know.
Your brain knew he's
better off without it.
Following your heart is easy.
Following your brain is tough.
Especially after years
of following
that much smaller third organ.
That's why all parents
screw up all children.
Evening.
Clever tactic, pretending
you're not interested anymore.
How could that possibly work
as a tactic?
The fact is, once I saw
those incompletes,
I knew your parents
screwed you up.
The details are just gravy.
You're wrong.
The only evidence you have
is proof of something else.
I ran away from home.
Because you had lousy parents.
Because I didn't.
All my friends' parents
were divorced
or having affairs
or barely knew
their kids' birthdays.
You envied their dysfunction?
I-I thought it made them
deeper somehow.
It was stupid.
I hitchhiked to Manhattan,
moved in with an older guy.
In two months,
I came running home.
It took my parents years
to get over it.
That's when you
started to excel.
You were making it up to them.
Your parents screwed you up
by not screwing you up.
How does briefly
wishing I was screwed up
make me screwed up?
It's normal to be screwed up.
It's really screwed up
to romanticize it.
I guess that's why you wanted
to work with prisoners.
It's why I wanted
to work with you.
It was a tactic.
Chris.
Yeah.
I need to talk to you and Phil.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
I can't let you move.
You drove all the way out here
just to tell us
what you already told us.
I'm sorry.
House, open up.
I don't want to miss
the opening bell.
House?
Telecast, we expect an
electric atmosphere
in the arena and a sellout
crowd of about 10,000
for Rubio versus Santos,
two great fighters
with illustrious careers
who might have been expected
to meet a long time ago.
As for Santos,
his handlers tell us
that he's done more roadwork
than at any time in his career,
hoping to prove tonight that
he can box for 12 full rounds.
Significant because Santos
hasn't heard the final bell
in more than six years.
He comes in with
11 straight knockout wins
and we saw how a power puncher
with a left hook
was able to cut Rubio
over the right eye
in the tenth round
of that last fight.
By Mikhel for Subtitulos.es
==SPREAD THE WORD==
www.tvsubtitles.net