"The Patuxent River
Naval Air Station near D.C.
Was commissioned in 1943
by John McCain's grandfather."
I'm thinking of going
hang gliding.
Pax river is,
like, completely flat.
Think that's why they tested
the V-22 Osprey there.
I like naval stuff.
I like their oranges and lint.
What looks like kidney
disease, but isn't?
And where's Chase?
Root canal and Berger's.
The first one
was regarding Chase.
Root canal, if done correctly,
doesn't look like
kidney disease.
Got a case for you.
Smells funny.
Patient had an idiopathic
anaphylactic reaction.
It stumped two E.R. docs
and an immunologist
from Johns Hopkins.
Patient went from
asymptomatic to fried kidneys
in less than a year.
Stumped three internists
and a department chair
from Harvard.
14-year-old girl,
intermittent attacks.
Four-year-old boy,
consistently at death's door.
This patient died
five years ago.
I didn't say which side
of the door he was on.
The fact that he's dead
makes it more interesting.
Four-year-olds
do not die of Berger's.
I thought it was relevant.
Death is a consequence,
not a symptom.
If it's not a symptom,
it's not relevant.
Shouldn't we be
trying to maximize
what we can save here?
14-year-old,
your freom, our asses?
Right...
Save your asses.
House S08E07
"Dead And Buried"
By Mikhel for Subtitulos.es
==SPREAD THE WORD==
She was in a car accident
when she was two.
She only had minor injuries,
but her father died.
That was 12 years ago.
You think that's pertinent?
No, I think it's sad.
She got sick in the middle
of her 14th birthday party.
Which is sad and pertinent.
Maybe she was opening a present
that triggered the reaction.
- Where's House?
- Pissing contest with foreman.
Last thing she ate
was strawberry cake,
but allergy tests
for everything were negative.
Do you like your dentist?
I'm still going
to my pediatric one.
What's your dentist's name?
Williams.
What if it's not
an allergic reaction?
Hereditary angioedema
or systemic mastocytosis
could mimic anaphylaxis.
You're not sure of his name?
You just saw him this morning.
His assistant's name is Angie.
Her home number is...
Normal complement studies.
No skin leons.
You had a manicure.
This is fresh!
You weren't at the dentist.
Why would you lie about that?
To avoid having
this conversation.
- Elevated BP.
- What about pheochromocytoma?
Or an anaphylactoid reaction,
which could be triggered
by certain opioids.
You've had your hair cut
three times since I've met you.
You can't be embarrassed
about a manicure.
There's gotta be
a deeper reason.
Did House give you homework?
She's not on any meds.
Haven't you heard?
Everybody lies.
And the tox screen was clean.
Feel free to jump in
at any time.
We'll check
catecholamines for pheo
and run an expanded
opioid panel.
You see what the patient
says about drug use
when her mother's
out of the room.
No, never.
Nobody's here
to bust you, iris.
We just need to know if...
No, I already told you.
I just take vitamin C
sometimes.
What exactly were you doing
when you had your reaction?
Opening a birthday present.
The magic 8 ball.
The joke gift, not the cocaine.
Is that it?
Certain drugs could
explain her reaction.
What kind of drugs?
What kind did you have in mind?
Iris has always been
a moody girl.
And now that she's a teenager,
it's gotten worse.
So for the past few months
I've been...
Giving something to relax her.
Diazepam.
I tell her it's vitamin c.
Being normal
is very important to iris.
She couldn't handle the thought
of being on meds.
Anti-anxiety medications
would explain it.
If we keep her off,
she'll be moody, but healthy.
Or it's something else.
I need to DDX
a patient with you.
I thought you had
a team for that.
According to foreman,
they're only for DDXing people
who are still alive.
You have a dead patient?
Bigotry is boring
when we add modifiers.
I don't see creed, LOR, pulse.
Foreman will find out
you're taking this case,
and he'll bust you.
But you know that,
which means...
You want to go back to jail...
Because it's the one place
you're unable to iulge
your self-destructive habits.
Yeah, it's much
more likely that I'm
taking this case because I miss
showering with cro-magnons
than that I actually happen
to find it interesting.
Four-year-old kid.
His kidneys died,
they transfused.
His lungs died.
He died.
Have you seen
bride of the monster?
I just got the ed wood box set.
What if the chicken
was the egg?
What if the lung involvement
came first?
I don't really
care about the movie.
I just don't want
to indulge your...
Lupus.
Because this is
a bad idea, House.
If the kid had a rash
or some circulation issue...
Damn!
I just realized I'm late
for my anger management class.
Traffic, for sure.
Taxes.
Definitely taxes.
Spoiled grandchildren.
Platitudes.
Any others?
And I lose my temper
when someone suggests
that a handful of pop-psych
catch phrases
can control our most seminal,
intractable, and natural reacon
to a dead child.
Am I right, Emory?
I don't think Emory
wants to share right now.
They blew it, didn't they?
They missed your son's rash.
A faint one, on his cheek.
He didn't have a rash.
I think we should talk about
Lena's grandchildren.
They're alive.
Was he sensitive to sunlight?
No.
Greg...
Cold fingers and toes?
No!
Wegener's granulomatosis.
I need to examine your son.
You're a bit late
for that... You ass.
With you
and your wife's consent,
we can get an exhumation order.
Find out what killed him.
Ex-wife.
And you'll never
get her consent.
She's moved on...
New hub, new kid.
She wants nothing to do
with drew's death.
Or me.
You're angry because
your kid died.
More than that,
because you don't
have an answer.
People need answers.
He's in a crypt
at St. Jude's Cemetery.
You feeling any
pain or cramping here?
A bit.
But not just there, um...
Here.
Breast tenderness.
Have you been having
regular periods, iris?
Not really.
What is it?
I think we should
run a pregnancy test.
Iris isn't sexually active.
She doesn't even
have a boyfriend.
Pregnancy would explain
all of her symptoms.
Can even cause
some unpredictable
allergic reactions.
How can I be pregnant
if I've never even had sex?
We just need a drop of blood.
What's the matter?
My...
My arms.
I can't feel my arms.
At this rate,
I'm gonna need to pick out
a plot for myself.
Thanks to your
generous donation,
you have all morning.
More like 13 minutes.
Before we proceed
any further, doctor,
I'd like inquire
as to exactly what procedure
you intend to perform
on the remains.
Have you ever heard
of the north American
man/dead boy love association?
I consider these grounds
to be a holy place,
and I would ask you to observe
them with due decorum.
So you're taking bribes
to plunder graves,
and I need to show respect.
I think they got
the cause of death wrong.
And if I find a hole
in the cartilage of his nose,
right about here,
then it means I'm right.
Please be respectful.
I prepared the sarcophagus
for you.
Thank you, Igor.
It's Milton.
You owe me a new pair of pants.
- She is pregnant.
- Test came back positive.
So... She lost
the use of her arms
and her innocence.
A vengeful God?
Or...
Cerebral tumor.
Vasculitis.
Ms.
I gather from the silence
that Chase isn't there.
Nope, I'm here.
Where are you?
"Nowhere"...
He said cryptically.
I assume you concur
with the diagnosis.
Absolutely.
Even tugh
there are three diagnoses?
And ms and vasculitis
usually get better
with pregnancy.
Yeah, I was saying
I agreed with the other one.
He's had his eyebrows waxed.
I met a woman
who likes her men well groomed.
All over?
I assume, from the silence,
that Chase has had a brazilian.
Cool.
Interesting.
Ouch.
Question is...
Is this really about a woman?
Or is it about
something more profound?
Another question is,
could the paresthesia
be caused by an std?
HIV-related
mononeuritis multiplex.
I gatherrom the silence
that either you all
agree with Chase
or you're just staring
at his emasculated brow.
In either case, test for HIV
and do an MRI
to rule out tumors.
And check Chase
for testosterone.
Blood work was
negative for HIV.
All the money's on tumor.
How was the brazilian?
It was fine.
Hurt a bit.
What about House's theory?
Why'd you really do it?
'Cause I'm vain and shallow.
And you weren't before?
The girl I was seeing wasn't.
There's nothing profound here.
No tumor, either.
It's not her brain.
Everything looks good.
What's the matter?
My arm, it's...
Still nothing?
No, now they're sore.
Paresthesia's gone.
Could the bruising be caused
by a physical trauma?
You think she fell
out of bed, repeatedly?
A blood disorder.
Maybe thrombocytopenia.
A vitamin K deficiency
or scurvy
could explain
bleeding problems,
and prnancy
could exacerbate it.
Boys, do a home search.
Girls, do lab tests.
I'm pretty sure
that's not sexist.
Where have you been?
Picking up dry cleaning.
Filling up the tank.
Violating the dead.
If you don't believe me,
call the monitoring company.
I did.
Unfortunately, the Patuxent
River Naval Air Station
was GPS testing
and disrupted the signal,
at the exact, same 45 minutes
you weren't here.
Well, if I'd known I had
45 minutes of freedom,
I'd have gone hang gliding.
I admire the creativity.
What happens when
the stunt doesn't work?
Think you're gonna have
to pay off a bet?
Think I'm gonna
triple your clinic hours?
I'm gonna call your P.O.,
and you're gonna
go back to jail.
There are mees'
lines on his fingernails,
so now I'm thinking
heavy metal poisoning.
You're an addict.
And I'm an idiot for thinking
that your addictions
were limited to pills,
anti-social behavior,
and sarcasm.
Sorry.
Vicodin repeating on me.
You're also
addicted to puzzles.
You show all
the classibehaviors.
Lying, neglecting
responsibilities,
and you can't stop,
no matr how devastating
the consequences.
Working on a medical case
is not a parole violation.
It's my job description.
Your job description
is doing what foreman
tells you to do.
Never mind
bride of the monster.
You need to watch Norma rae.
Before we get started,
I just want to thank you all
for agreeing to relocate.
Um, I had an appointment
in this part of town,
and I absolutely didn't want
to miss this meeting.
But, uh, thank you.
I'm buying.
Not literally.
Hey, Emory,
should we, uh,
powder our noses?
Hey, did you know
your ex-wife
still lives right
behind this place?
She finishes work at 4:00.
Picks up her new kid
at 4:15.
Gives us about 20 minutes.
I made some calls.
It's amazing what
people will tell you
if you ask brutally enough.
Was that table here?
Some kinds of
pressure-treated wood
can contain arsenic.
We shouldn't be here.
We don't have a choice.
This is the only way
you're gonna get your answer.
Does your ex leave
a spare key anywhere?
How did he look?
Peaceful.
Vitamin k deficiency's a bust.
Fridge has more spinach
and broccoli
than a farmer's market.
The brazilian...
You said it hurt
"a bit."
You've had one?
More than one, and you haven't.
They hurt all your bits.
That's my dark secret.
What's yours?
I had the nails
and eyebrows done,
but that's it.
I just needed to create
a distraction, though.
I met a TV producer
at a dinner.
She asked me to appear
on the medical segment.
Screen tested it yesterday
and shot it today.
You're a TV doctor?
It's a one-off.
When's it air?
Two hours ago.
Otherwise, I'd still be lying.
This is what she was opening
when she had her attack.
Will anyone believe Chase
is an actual doctor?
"Don't count on it."
Huh.
She does have a boyfriend.
Love letters.
Porn.
The nasty kind.
Torture, rape...
Animals.
Sweet kid.
This is all that's left.
One box in the bottom
of a closet.
Ohh.
He used to wear
those stupid things
all the time.
Used to have
to pretend I was scared.
Made in the people's
Republic of Lead Paint.
Back door.
Let's get out of here first.
We need to catch
the end of our class.
I met him at school.
He was the only boy
that liked me.
It's a little more than like.
We haven't had sex.
Oh, come on, iris.
You're pregnant.
So I'm just lying
about everything?
Well, you lied
about the boyfriend.
You obviously lied about sex
and this... Garbage.
They're his.
He can't keep them
at his place.
Well, I'm glad
we could be so accommodating.
What else don't I know?
Honey...
What is it?
He came here last night.
And he told me I should leave.
But I didn't
want to, and he got mad.
He hit you?
Physical trauma.
Explains the negatives
of the blood disorder.
We should call the police.
I won't tell them anything.
That's ridiculous.
He beat you!
What is it?
It's getting hard to see.
What the hell
is happening to me?
Rubbing alcohol, vinegar.
Not sure what this is.
Aren't there
actual medical tests?
Dead patients usually
get a lower standard of care.
Pink means lead.
Orange means Mercury.
And rust means arsenic.
And what's brown mean?
Scotch.
He used to call him
"deezer."
He couldn't say "zebra."
He'd have his own words
for everything.
We called 'em "drewisms."
How does your ex-wife do it?
How come she's not...
Angry and miserable?
She treated it
like it never happened.
She never even cried.
Not even at his funeral.
I was a mess,
and she just sat there like...
A statue.
We have a problem.
Does it limp?
Why do you care
if he works on two cases?
'Cause next,
it'll be three cases,
then four.
Then animal cases
and ghost cases.
Then animal ghost cases.
Assuming, of course,
we are talking about House.
You're just setting yourself
up to fail.
He has a lot more
to lose than I do,
and he knows that.
He's rational.
No, he's not.
He's the most rational man
I've ever met.
Annoyingly so.
He isn't gonna put himself
back in jail over a dead kid.
He's an addict,
and he will
put himself back in jail
over a puzzle.
He'll back down.
Halfway through
the perimetry exam,
her tunnel vision went away.
She can see perfectly.
TIA.
The word "transient"
is right there in the name.
Ah, here we go.
Chesa, after giving
the pics an eye or two,
I can confirm
that Lauren's surgeries
cost her some big bikkies.
Not only was there a gut tuck,
nose tuck, and arse tuck,
but her new, fake norks
stick out
like nuts on a mutt.
The original script was...
Shh, shh, shh.
Anyone notice...
He's enlightening us.
That's 'cause he's retooled
the ol' todger.
Let's just hope
no one cut the wrong wire, eh?
So you just wanted
to look pretty on TV.
Question is,
why did he want that?
Clinic time.
What do you want us to do?
MRA 4 TIA.
ROFL.
Thought you only had clinic
on Tuesdays.
Oh, you're right.
Hi. I'm here
for the free flu shot.
I got a call saying...
I'm here to find out why
you didn't care about
your first kid.
Losing a child...
Just breezed right through it.
How do you know about
my first kid...
Didn't even squeeze out
a single tear at the funeral.
Where are you getting this?
You couldn't wait
to squeeze out
a brand-new
replacement kid.
Damn it.
You had no right to say that.
I know.
I deserved the slap.
But I was hoping that
you weren't capable of it.
Apathetic hyperthyroidism.
Could have kidney involvement.
Could be genetic.
Definitely causes apathy.
I was hoping that
your lack of emotion
was a symptom of something
you could have passed on
to your first son.
You know Emory.
We belong to the same club.
He wants to relive this.
I don't.
So I heard.
Emory was a wonderful man.
Never afraid to show
his emotions.
Which is great,
most of the time.
But when drew died...
It overwhelmed him.
I vowed I wouldn't
let that happen to me.
That's why you left him?
I left because of his eyes.
He had drew's eyes.
Who used to babysit drew?
My father, but...
His place or yours?
There are two types of people.
Those who can move on,
and those who can't.
My father keeps up
a good front,
but he's just like Emory.
You need to leave him alone.
So he has two types
of people inside of him.
Mra was normal.
Yeah, how did...
I found out where
your boyfriend lives.
When I paid him a visit,
he took off.
Ran in front of a car.
You're lying.
He's down in the E.R.
right now.
Shut up, you lying
sack of crap.
Iris!
How do you know I'm lying?
How do you know
your boyfriend's okay?
'Cause I'm right here,
you dick.
Iris has dissociative
identity disorder.
Also known as multiple
personality disorder.
Are you saying I'm crazy?
It's the mind's response
to a severe trauma.
A person experiences something
that's too difficult to accept,
so they create
alternate personalities
that don't have to accept it.
Some think it's quite
a natural reaction.
Iris hasn't had
any severe traumas.
The car accident?
I was two.
I don't remember anything.
These personalities
that I'm supposed to have...
Where are they?
They only come out
when you're afraid or anxious.
That's why House used
the hurt boyfriend story.
But if there's no boyfriend,
where did
the bruises come from?
The pregnancy?
When you say
your boyfriend hit you,
it means you actually
hit yourself.
And the pregnancy...
Doesn't take a boyfriend.
Just a boy.
You may not be aware
of half the things you've done.
How could this be happening
to my own daughter
without me knowing it?
Diazepam was masking it.
Taking her off
made it more apparent.
But I... I wasn't on...
"Diazepam"?
What is that?
That's what those
vitamin pills were.
Iris... I am so sorry.
I just... I thought
you were moody.
I didn't want you to think
you needed medication.
Oh, my God.
I n't believe
how stupid I've been.
We need you to help us
with something.
Different alters can he
different apparent symptoms.
Allergies, paresthesia,
vision loss,
changes in blood pressure.
Do you think I'm making this up?
Your symptoms are real.
But some are physiological,
and others are psychological.
So there's something
wrong with her...
In addition
to the multiple personalities?
Yes, but we won't know what
until we access her alters
and compare their symptoms.
Well, how do you do that?
Hypnosis.
Foreman's nogonna back down.
He's not an idiot.
Yes, he is.
Just like you.
If you keep being stubborn,
he will keep being stubborn.
Eventually,
you will screw something up.
Which will be bad news
for both of you.
But... Only one of you
will be in prison.
It just isn't worth it, House.
Okay.
Uh, y-yes, sir.
I... yes,
I know I told you
that I had a chiropractor's
appointment,
but, uh, I got a flat.
I know, right?
So...
You know,
don't send out the marines.
I should be back on the road
in a few minutes.
Okaybye.
Dr. James Wilson,
county coroner.
I'd like to ask you
about your grandson,
drew lemaine.
What did he do
when he was here?
Where did he play?
What did he eat?
We watched lot of TV.
And ate biscuits.
Did you give him sidewalk chalk?
No.
Finger paints?
No!
A sandbox?
It's like I said.
We watched a lotta TV.
You expecting someone?
What?
Dr. Wilson my ass!
I told you to leave him alone,
you son of a bitch!
Temper trigger.
Who am I talking to now?
Nobody.
You must be somebody.
I'm too little.
Nobody sees me.
Nobody knows I'm here.
BP just went to 140 over 90.
What is it?
My arms.
You can't feel them?
It's okay.
We can fix that.
Do you hurt anywhere else?
Not right now.
But you used to hurt?
When I ate strawberries.
And when I remember...
Do you remember being hurt?
I remember everything.
Baby...
It's going to be okay, baby.
Iris?
Why didn't you ever tell me?
It was my fault daddy died.
Oh, no. No.
Yes, it was.
I was crying
and he couldn't drive.
It was my fault daddy's...
Oh, no.
No, no, honey.
Yes.
You were just a baby.
It wasn't your fault.
No, shh.
Oh, baby.
It was my fault.
I'm sorry, mommy.
Shh.
I'm so sorry.
It wasn't a miscarriage.
Test shows
she's still pregnant.
Okay, cross out everything
that doesn't appear
in every alter.
When she opened
the magic 8 ball,
that triggered a switch
to a personality
with a strawberry allergy.
Pregnancy, vaginal bleeding,
and elevated b.P.
Could be pre-eclampsia.
Worst case, could be
an ectopic pregnancy.
We need to ultrasound.
Not seeing an embryo
in the fallopian tube.
I'm not seeing
an embryo anywhere.
Which idiot
did the egnancy test?
I did one of them.
Chase did another.
Taub did a third.
Three tests, three positives.
What happened to your eye?
I grabbed park's ass.
Exoplanets.
I think he said exoplanets.
Wait for it...
We can't actually see them...
But we infer their existence
because of the effect they have
on the star they orbit.
Pregnancy test only
infers an embryo's existence
because of elevated hcg levels.
Which could also be caused
by choriocarcinoma,
which affects the placenta,
mimics pregnancy,
and causes elevated BP
and vaginal bleeding.
Occult choriocarcinoma,
which is why we didn't
see it on the ultrasound
tell all the alters
that they have cancer.
Mom or dad?
Mom, dad, and mom's dad.
The good news is,
made me realize
that you were right.
I can't drop it.
But now that I accept that,
I feel much less conflicted.
I've ruled out wegener's,
Berger's, heavy metal poison...
Two trains
are about to collide,
and I'm trying
to talk them out of it.
Feels like
I'm missing something.
No, no.
You don't want to listen to me,
then I don't want
to listen to you.
That is so fifth grade.
I agree.
And you know why?
Because I'm just as bad as you.
I knew ts would fall
on deaf ears,
but I just kept
talking and talking.
You're right.
You don't even know
what I just said.
That is ridiculous.
You said, "blah blah
blah blah blah, deaf ears,
blah blah blah blah blah."
Absolutely essential
information.
Ray...
Ray!
Leave him alone.
What are you doing to him?
It's okay.
Mickey...
You? You brought him.
I asked him to meet me here
for a family reunion.
Ray!
Let's just get
out of here, okay?
I know what killed your son.
You don't get it, do you?
I don't care what killed him!
It's called alport syndrome.
It's a genetic condition
characterized
by kidney failure,
bronchial myomas, mees' lines,
and deafness.
Idiot. Drew wasn't deaf!
House...
Son of a bitch!
Get away from them!
House, House!
It's a genetic condition!
Shut up!
Genetic!
Your father has the gene.
So do you.
It's grandpa's slight deafness
that gave the game away.
You're apparently asymptomatic.
You could still pass
the gene onto your children.
Plural.
You're lying.
He has high-frequency
hearing impairment.
And so did drew.
That's why drew
made up his own words.
'Cause he couldn't
hear properly.
It's okay.
Now that we know what it is,
he'll need treatment,
but he'll live.
You know, there are platitudes
that can help you with that.
I miss him too.
She's responding well.
Cuddy threatened him
with clinic duty.
I thought
threatening him with jail
would be different.
Not an irrational thought.
I'm still sending him back.
He saved two lives.
Which means it's too late
for me to back down.
It's no longer my choice.
It's just me telling him
he can get away with anything.
I have to send him to prison.
Your job is to keep
this machine running.
It's your choice
to make House a useful tool
or a monkey wrench.
Cuddy's way didn't fail
because she didn't
try to control House.
She managed him.
She knew better than anybody
what a tool he could be.
What would Cuddy have done?
Ten clinic hours.
Cuddy's not here anymore.
You got 30.
By Mikhel for Subtitulos.es
==SPREAD THE WORD==
www.tvsubtitles.net