(Woman over P.A.)
Attention, passengers...
You have to lift up the sign
so he can see it.
Evan.
Hey, buddy.
Aren't you excited
to see your Uncle Brant?
No.
No?
I think you are.
I think something else
is making you upset.
You know I'm leaving soon,
and it's okay to be upset
about that,
but, hey, do you remember
what I told you
when we were watching wrestling
on Saturday night?
Yeah.
That you and Uncle Brant
are like the Reaper Brothers.
That's right.
And Uncle Brant
has been in the ring
a whole year.
Now it's time
for daddy to tag in.
But while I'm away,
I need you
in your Uncle's corner,
making sure he keeps you
and your mom safe.
Can you help me
with that?
Good.
Now let's get ready
with that sign.
(Woman over P.A.)
Attention, ladies and gentlemen,
we are now boarding
at Gate 47.
Now.
Brant,
what happened?
Captain,
please step aside.
Sir, this is my brother.
What's going on?
Pfc Macklin has been
charged with treason.
Oh, so there's got to be
some mistake.
I'm sorry.
Brant!
♪ House 8x15 ♪
Blowing the Whistle
Original air date on April 2, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
[Massive Attack's Teardrop]
♪
[Indistinct male voices]
(Adams) Army apparently thought
they were clearing
an insurgent hideout.
After this was leaked
on Saturday,
the A.P. investigated.
[Gunfire]
34 civilian casualties.
Six kids.
There will be MPs stationed
at every entrance
to the second floor, as well
as outside his patient room.
No. Don't do that.
Every time there's people
in uniform in the cafeteria,
they get served first.
Make sure your IDs
are clearly visible.
I'll speak with the cafeteria
staff about showing
more disrespect.
20-year-old male, generalized
tonic-clonic seizures.
Army Docs scanned
for structural abnormalities.
EEG was normal.
So was--
do you need me
to sign for this?
Let me know
if you need anything.
Like a transfer.
Typhus?
(House)
Patient has no hair.
Probably means no lice.
Leishmaniasis.
No fever.
Why couldn't they
take care of him
at a military hospital?
I think because
they wanted to annoy you.
Any other
conscientious objectors?
So I'm the only one
who has a problem
when someone
whose duty's to protect
our country blowing--
Blowing the whistle
is honorable
precisely because
it's not dutiful.
Sorry, you said blowing.
Maybe you were going
somewhere else with that.
He's a coward.
He risked his freedom.
He anonymously downloaded
a computer file
from a secure page
and uploaded it
to an unsecure page.
Not exactly storming
Omaha Beach.
The EEG was normal
because he was faking it
to avoid going
to prison.
Let's treat him
with not medicine.
Give those back.
Why?
You got 28.
You can share.
Something's going on
with House.
He just seemed off.
Didn't even notice
that I walked out
of the room
with this.
You began to suspect he was off
when he didn't notice
the mug you stole
to see if he was off?
What else didn't he notice that
you don't want us to notice?
Those are the same clothes
you wore yesterday.
And you got very defensive
when House took
your birth control.
Who was he?
Or better yet...she?
Do I need to explain the
physiology behind birth control?
Attention deficit in a man
who has no attention deficits
has to be symptomatic
of something.
You're right. I'm thinking
either massive brain tumor,
or his soap got canceled
and he's distracted.
Could be dietary.
Refsum.
Or maybe he thinks
you just have
more than one
non-descript white blouse.
Or serotonin syndrome.
I'm not saying
he's definitely sick.
I'm just saying
we should look into it.
No, we shouldn't.
If you believe House is sick,
it's only because that's
what he wants you to believe.
(Park)
Let's go.
We think the long flight home
allowed clots
to form in your leg.
Take this pill.
If you feel any numbness
in your leg after a few minutes,
it means we're right
and you should get comfortable,
because you're gonna be here
for a while.
While we wait,
can you tell me why?
It was the right thing
to do.
There are reports that
insurgents are using your video
to recruit new members.
Making the voting public aware
of what's really happening
on the ground
will help bring
our troops home fast.
[Sighs]
My brother's grunt
means he disagrees.
I think you're being naive.
And I know you took an oath.
If you want to influence policy,
run for office.
Dad raised us to believe
that exposing the truth
is honorable.
Hayes likes
to follow the rules.
Yeah, because that's what Dad
taught us was honorable.
You were ten when he died.
You couldn't possibly have
any idea--
If dad always believe
in blindly following the rules,
how do you explain Tora Bora?
My dad was commanding
a Special Forces unit.
He lost communication
with his men.
They were assumed dead.
He was ordered to abandon them
and focus
on the primary mission.
He disobeyed that order,
went and found his men
still alive and fighting.
He saved their lives.
Did he die in service?
If it was something genetic,
it could help us.
(Hayes)
It won't help.
It was a one-car accident.
That's the army's
official story.
My brother's naive
on this and...
I can't feel my leg.
I'll get the discharge papers.
I have
a blood clot.
No, you don't.
We gave you a placebo
to see if you'd fake
another symptom
to delay going to prison.
Wait a second.
He's not faking.
Because that's not the way
your Dad raised him?
Yes.
(Brant)
My stomach hurts too.
What's going on?
He's not faking.
(Chase) Just because he's got
abdominal bruising
doesn't mean
he wasn't faking the numbness.
(Adams) He's not contesting
the treason charges.
If his code of honor
is that strong,
he's not gonna bother
faking symptoms.
[Pills rattle]
Pleading guilty
is not honorable.
It's just stupid.
A distal esophageal rupture
can lead to compartment syndrome
in his thigh--
explains both symptoms.
No pain
when he swallows.
(House)
What is honor?
Dying for your country?
Getting straight As?
Killing your daughter
because she had the audacity
to get raped?
Ruptured triple-A.
Doesn't explain
the seizures.
Pancreatitis.
Gallstones obstructing
his pancreatic duct.
People define honor
as whatever makes them
feel honorable.
It's a circle going nowhere.
Which I guess
is what circles do.
We'll ultrasound his belly
and look for the obstruction.
I need your signature
on this order.
The Army's leaning
on Foreman to make sure
this is done
by the book.
Didn't need an order
for his last treatment.
This last treatment
wasn't a treatment.
- Forge it.
- I will.
From now on.
But I need the original
so I know what to forge.
We were having coffee
when the dizziness started.
Business meeting?
Date.
Our first.
We met
at the 98 Cents store.
We were reaching
for the same tube of cheese.
[Knock at door]
Huh.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I need to talk to you.
Just about done.
Good news, based
on her thrifty shopping habits
and taste
for artificial dairy,
she's clearly
not a gold digger.
Bad news:
Based on his rhinotillexomania,
he is.
Compulsive addiction
to nose-picking.
A small cut on the inside
of the left nostril
led to an infection
in the cavernous sinus.
It was very nice
meeting you, Mel.
It's not true.
Gloria, wait,
I can change.
My PPTH contract.
House signed it
six months ago.
He signed this today.
His hands are unsteady.
Given his Vicodin abuse,
I think he has
hepatic encephalopathy.
[Laughs]
He's been forgetful,
inattentive.
Dominika's been trying out
new knish recipes.
One of them
didn't agree with him.
A little sleep deprivation
could account
for his forgetfulness
and inattention.
He loads up on caffeine.
That explains a jittery hand.
Maybe.
But if I'm right,
his liver's in decline.
It's curable, but
if he doesn't get treatment,
it could actually be fatal.
This happens
all the time.
One of the symptoms
of working for House--
you start seeing zebras
everywhere.
There's nothing wrong
with him.
House.
Shh.
I'm with a patient.
Sleep study.
You drugged him?
I didn't say
the study was voluntary.
I think you're sick.
What, 'cause I'm sleeping
in the clinic like I always do?
Slow reaction time.
Because I just woke up
from sleeping in the clinic
like I always do.
You're forgetful.
Sorry.
What did you say?
You forgot that we were
supposed to have lunch.
I didn't forget.
I was sleeping
in the clinic--
I'd like to run
some tests.
For what?
Where's this coming from?
Hepatic encephalopathy.
I've watched you destroy your
body with Vicodin for years.
I'm surprised your liver's
lasted this long.
I'll do the examination
myself.
While having you juggle
my jewels sounds interesting,
there's no such thing
as friends with benefits.
It always gets weird.
Your friends out there
are getting a little handsy.
Get enough death threats,
eventually they start taking
them seriously.
A convoy was hit
outside of Kunar Province.
Eight American soldiers
were killed.
Army spokesperson's claiming
that it's revenge
for the attack
that I made public.
Better me take the blame
than them.
You don't think
you're to blame at all?
And you do.
Like everyone else.
A strike like that would take
more than three days to plan.
So the next one might be
your fault?
Lateral view looks good.
If you have such
a negative opinion of the army,
why did you enlist?
I needed to find out
what really happened to my dad.
There were two redacted pages
in his service record.
Going into intelligence
was the quickest way
to up my security clearance.
Then why would you leak
that video?
Part of my job was to grab
a cup of tea with the locals.
The face time is supposed
to make them more likely
to trust us
with sensitive information,
but they became
my friends.
If there was another attack,
civilian casualties,
and I had done nothing...
Your spleen,
it's enlarged.
We should do a biopsy
and look for any--
He's got urinary bleeding.
(Park)
Not just urinary.
Call the blood bank.
(Hayes)
What's happening to him?
His spleen must be sequestering
platelets.
[Machine beeping]
He's bleeding too fast
to wait
for a platelet infusion.
We need to squeeze his spleen
to release the ones he's got.
Tell the O.R.
we're on our way.
(Taub)
Pressure's dropping.
(Chase)
Almost there.
BP's 70 over 40,
and he's hypovolemic.
[Machine beeping]
(Adams)
Pressure's rising.
And he's starting
to clot.
Good news is we can control
the bleeding.
Bad news is...
Bleeding's not the problem.
Unless spleens are supposed
to be lumpy.
(Adams) He's clotting,
but CT confirms
splenic nodules.
Dr. Taub has
an interesting theory.
No, I don't.
You're forfeiting?
'Cause if you can't play
the game and work...
Extramedullary hematopoiesis.
No history of anemia.
She's right.
You're an idiot. Try again.
Where I come from,
this is called cheating.
Where's that?
Stickford-upon-anus?
TB.
PPD's negative.
Could be bru--
Don't interrupt Dr. Taub.
Brucellosis.
You just took out
a family of four.
They were clearly
armed insurgents,
and anyone who claims or proves
otherwise is a traitor.
No rash or back pain.
You defend the patient
for being a whistleblower,
then attack him for being
an honorable whistleblower.
Now you defend him for being
a maligned, honorable
whistleblower?
(House)
Adjectives matter.
Hate nurses,
love naughty nurses.
Taub, pitch again.
- I've pitched like five--
- It's your turn.
Lymphoma.
(Adams) If cancer caused
his seizures,
we would have seen
cerebral masses on his head CT.
- Yes!
- Taub, pitch again.
Now.
The nodules in his spleen
were granulomas.
He's got sarcoidosis!
Someone tell him
he's wrong.
Sorry, House.
Sarcoid does explain
the seizures.
And the bruises.
Say bye-bye, House.
Yes!
[Grunts]
Sarcoidosis it is.
Treat with steroids.
Then come right back here,
'cause I'm not gonna rest
until I've made orphans
of all your virtual children.
House never loses.
Seriously?
Me beating House
is medically significant?
It could be.
Reduced fine motor control.
Add that to inattention
and liver flap.
It does make sense.
We have to talk
to Foreman.
No, we don't.
First of all,
because I can beat him
in that game.
And, second,
even if you are right,
there's no reason to believe
that House's medical judgment
is impaired.
So we should wait
until he kills someone
for confirmation?
You really think
it's a coincidence
that we're treating
a whistleblower
and now talking about blowing
the whistle on House?
You're right.
Playing dumb,
messy signature,
losing a video game--
it's way too complicated
to fake.
No.
I won't take it.
Without this injection,
you could have
a fatal arrhythmia.
Tell Major Mathewson
that I'm not taking
any more treatment
until they give me
a live television interview.
You can't really think
they'll agree to that.
People need to know the tape's
not the reason
for that attack.
They need to know
why I did this.
The people who think
you're a traitor
will still think
you're a traitor,
and the people who think
you're a hero
will still think
you're a hero.
The truth makes a difference.
If Dad were here, he'd be
begging for you not to do this.
If Dad were here,
he'd be proud of me.
The conspiracy theorists
are gonna go nuts
if the patient dies.
I told him that,
and he told me
that option
is still less damaging
than giving the kid
a national platform.
So what do we do now?
You explain
to your brother
that he overplayed
his hand.
That won't make
any difference.
The idiot thinks
he's doing the right thing.
What if we convinced a court
that his refusal
is part of an underlying
psychiatric disorder?
They assign a conservator.
We do what we want.
Fraud.
Great.
Narcissistic personality
disorder.
Both the leaking of the tape
and the refusal of treatment
indicate that he has no fear
of consequences.
(Foreman) So instead of defrauding
the court,
you'll waste their time?
No way a judge classifies
a personality disorder
as a mental illness.
If a decorated military officer,
who happened
to be the patient's brother,
corroborates, they might.
So you want me to sign
a piece of paper
that says my brother is crazy
for doing
what he thinks is right?
I want you to save his life.
His heart could go
at any time.
He's a fool.
But he's not crazy.
The patient
was refusing treatment
because of honor,
and his brother
is refusing
to be his conservator
because of honor.
Oh, good.
Taub's cured the patient.
I had to go
to the bathroom.
Bathroom's that way.
You just ran in from that way.
That one's been out of order
for two days.
I had to go up
to the third floor.
I'm not lying.
It's out of order.
I believe you.
I'm gonna fix it.
We could treat if he doesn't
know he's being treated.
Lace his sponge bath.
It would take too long
to reach his bloodstream.
What if we aerosolize steroids
and blast the room?
Speaking of which...
It'd be too hard to get the
prednisone concentrations right.
No one fixes anything
unless they have
a compelling reason.
If we're gonna treat,
we have to give him
a compelling reason,
something that he wants more
than an interview.
Fire in the hole!
(Chase) A signed order
from Major Mathewson.
They've agreed to declassify
the redacted pages
from your father's
service record.
In two days,
you'll have all your answers.
But the only way you'll live
long enough to get the truth
is by accepting treatment.
I don't trust the Army
to follow through on this.
But you trust me.
I'll make sure
those pages get here.
Okay.
Selfishness
is apparently honorable now.
He wanted to create change.
Instead, he's just satisfying
his own curiosity.
He's getting the truth.
Most he could hope for.
I need to take a dump.
Specifically,
House's dump.
You set this up?
All it took was showing up
two minutes late
and a $2 sign.
Bile deposits are irregular.
House's liver is failing.
Cognitive impairment
will get progressively worse.
[Pagers beep]
[Brant groans]
What's going on?
My foot.
It's killing me.
(Adams)
It's completely cyanotic.
This isn't sarcoidosis.
Cholesterol embolization.
Are you gonna even acknowledge
what we just told you?
That you pilfered
my poo-poo?
Yeah, I was thinking
it would be less awkward
for all of us
if we could just pretend
that never happened.
(Adams)
It's not an embolization.
No instrumentation
inside the arteries.
Thank you for
getting us back--
And if we start you
on treatment now,
get you off Vicodin--
What's the opposite
of "thank you"?
I'm pretty sure
it ends in "you".
I know my body.
I'm fine.
Methemoglobinemia.
Army tests
for G6PD deficiency.
If you're not sick,
then our test,
accurate 99.5% of the time,
yielded a false positive
three separate times.
The odds of that
are 1 in 8 million.
The test is accurate.
The diagnosis isn't.
Sample was obviously
contaminated with other foods
interacting
with my liver enzymes.
Now could we talk
about the sick patient?
His clot dissolved.
That could have caused
the vasospasm.
D.I.C. could have been caused
by Bernard Soulier syndrome.
And you're sick,
and you have to
do something about it.
If we had a patient file
with the same symptoms
you're exhibiting...
And the symptoms
I'm not exhibiting?
Jaundice, ascites,
fetor hepaticus.
We can't tell
if your breath stinks
because you've been popping
mints like they're Vicodin.
You'd still diagnose
hepatic encephalopathy.
I know that because
four doctors you trained
have unanimously diagnosed you
with hepatic encephalopathy.
Park's right.
Treat the patient
with Heparin.
We'll have
a stronger argument
if we go to Foreman
as a united front.
We'll have a stronger argument
if we have an argument.
If House is sick, it's
his business, not Foreman's.
Foreman's business is to make
sure his doctors are able
to do their jobs,
that lives aren't put at risk.
Telling Foreman
will put lives at risk.
We tell Foreman,
House either agrees to treatment
or get suspended, which means
House gets suspended.
And considering House
at 90%
is better than any other doctor
at this hospital at 100%,
that means our patients
get a lower standard of care.
House could be at 90%,
he could be at 60%,
we don't know.
And until we do,
there's no reason
to do anything more
than what we've done.
[House, yelling]
Blurry vision...
headache,
a bit of nausea,
and dizziness.
I am completely baffled.
I only had eight beers.
Sophomore class
pong tournament's in a week.
I'm working on my tolerance.
Hop on one foot
and singe the iCarly theme song.
Like you don't know it.
♪ I know,
you see ♪
♪ somehow the world
will change for me ♪
♪ and be so wonderful
♪ live life,
breathe air ♪
Damn it, man.
Can't you see I'm doctoring?
♪ We're gonna get there
and be so wonderful ♪
If you want to talk to me,
you can buy me
a sandwich in an hour.
Or I could just hover here
until you're done.
♪ These--
Heard enough.
Just never could figure out
the "breathe air" part.
Next year,
stick to whiskey.
Or at least stay away
from week-old green beers.
A lot less likely to contain
tartrazine-laced green food dyes
for which you apparently have
an intolerance.
Once you break the seal,
it'll be out of your system
in 48 hours.
What are my choices here?
If I tell you I'm fine,
you won't believe me.
I've scheduled
a liver function test.
If I ignore you, then you'll
just ignore my ignoring.
Which is rude, frankly.
Depending on the results,
we'll customize
a treatment plan.
If I tell you I think I'm sick
and I need your help
and we need to set up a time
to talk about it,
you'll just assume
I'm lying.
Again, rude.
Also hurtful.
Why is it that you can find
the smallest thing wrong
with anyone else,
but when it comes to you...
I really don't have
a choice here, do I?
No, you don't.
I'm on the list.
But he's not.
You can't ignore me forever.
Well, if you're right, that's
not gonna be all that long.
Do it slow.
Who are you?
Well, considering
the only people allowed
in this room are your doctors
and your family...
I'm your long-lost
cousin Ralph.
So glad to finally meet you.
Are you gonna check on me?
It's gonna be
at least two hours
until we can tell
if the Heparin's working.
Then what are you
doing here?
You know, my father taught me
that it's dishonorable
to interrupt someone
when they're reading.
Honor's not a punch line.
Get out of my room.
So was it worth it?
Best case, you spend the rest
of your life in Leavenworth.
Worst case, you spend the rest
of your life here.
Justice for 34 deaths outweighs
anything the Army can do to me.
They got justice?
Do they know that?
What if only ten people
had died?
Four?
Even one civilian death...
What if they just maimed
a few guys?
Would that have been
worth it?
My job was to log that tape,
get all the details
in the official record.
After the tenth time
of watching it,
I stopped trying
to convince myself
that the shovel could have been
mistaken for a gun.
'Cause all I could see
were the victims' faces.
All I was doing was trying
to read that kid's lips
to make out his last words.
I couldn't sleep.
Couldn't eat.
Think I like the cue ball look?
My hair turned gray
in three days.
My body was telling me
I had to do whatever I could
to make sure
that something like this
never happened again.
Your hair turned gray
in three days.
Loss of hair color indicates
an autoimmune condition,
likely Grave's disease.
Hyperthyroidism leads
to a hypercoagulable state,
which causes thrombosis.
Start him
on antithyroids.
You want to reject
our current diagnosis
because he had
a few gray hairs,
panicked,
and shaved his head?
I want to reject
our current diagnosis
because I think
we're wrong.
And treating
for wrong diagnoses
can result in side effects
like death.
Even if he did full go gray,
stress seems way more likely
than Grave's.
I haven't read
any journal articles
proving that veterans have
a higher incidence
of depigmentation.
Of course, that could be
the hepatic encephalopathy
talking.
Our treatment for Bernard
Soulier hasn't had time--
so you all just want
to ignore the new symptom?
It's not grave's because
it's not a symptom at all.
And the antithyroids you want
could reduce his blood pressure
and his ability
to breathe.
Which can result
in side effects, like death.
Small soda.
Grave's it is.
Start him
on antithyroids.
I know we disagree
with House all the time,
but, before I could say,
"okay, he's a genius."
Now...maybe
he's just really smart.
We're not gonna give him
the antithyroids.
Everything okay?
Any better?
Pretty good.
He did just ask me
for a blanket.
You're cold?
A little.
For how long?
It's really nothing.
Maybe an hour or two.
[Thermometer beeps]
He's at 104.
It's not Bernard Soulier.
Bold move.
You've gone from
speculating I'm sick,
to acting like I'm dead.
We acted like
we don't trust your judgement,
because we don't
trust your judgement.
Why don't you start
by not trusting your own.
We did more blood work,
it's not Graves either.
Talk to you for a minute?
Anything you have to say to me,
you can say to them.
It's only fair. Cause
anything they say to me,
they also say to you.
Jiggle your pockets.
Whose got the silver coin?
Until you receive
a clean bill of health,
I'll be authorizing
all treatment orders.
Well, I would say that that was
an incredibly stupid mistake,
but apparently I'd have
to clear that opinion
through Foreman first.
White count is high.
So all the infections
we ruled out
when he came in
are back on the table.
Legionnaire's.
Unlikely without pneumonia.
(House)
Taub.
Loyalty issues
in his personal life.
Makes sense that they'd cross
over into his professional one.
I was hoping we can get
a diagnosis
before the witch hunt.
The patient's infection
is an inherently
less interesting puzzle
than the stab wound
to my back.
Fine.
I told Foreman.
Can we move on now?
What about dengue?
Patient
isn't in enough pain.
No.
I don't mean about dengue.
I have no idea.
Taub's only confessing
because he wants us
to focus on the patient.
I told Foreman.
I did.
The next person
to confess is fired.
Or Spartacus.
For clarification,
no one's getting fired.
Who else has a pitch?
And then...there's Park.
The only one
who didn't confess.
The same cowardice
that makes someone unable
to move out
of mommy and daddy's home
might also make someone
a tattletale.
You threatened to fire
the next person who--
And it's malaria.
No, it's not.
The Army issues
anti-malaria medication.
And has done
for ten years.
That's the equivalent
of 5,000 generations
of the Afghan mosquito,
anopheles gambiae.
That's plenty long enough
to develop a resistance.
Anopheles, by the way,
is Greek for "useless."
Cover for intra-abdominal sepsis
and treat with antimalarials.
And was I also right
that it was a stupid idea?
We believe you have malaria.
These pills--
I don't want
any medication.
My dad's file
should have been here.
Brant, I told you,
I looked into it.
There's just a delay.
I believe
that's what the Army's saying.
I don't believe it's true.
If they're not going to keep
their end of the bargain,
neither am I.
So we got groped
for nothing.
If he doesn't want
to stay alive--
Hold on.
Is it too late
to become his conservator?
I know what I said before.
Right now I don't care.
Of course not.
We'll get the paperwork
drawn up.
He changed his mind?
Why?
His brother's dying.
He needs
a more substantial reason?
His brother was dying
the last time
we asked him
to be the conservator.
So instead of pushing the issue
with the Army
to get the file, he just decided
to give up on his code?
Apparently.
So where do I sign?
We don't need you to.
The Army gave the file
to you yesterday.
Major Mathewson had
another copy sent over to us.
You know, there's a reason I
didn't want that file released.
I know.
I read it.
I'm gonna treat
my patient now.
[Door slides]
I was right.
Wasn't I?
How did he die?
What did they cover up?
They didn't cover up
anything.
I did.
Dad died in that car accident
because he was drunk.
Killed a pedestrian too.
What are you--
what--
He drank, Brant, a lot.
You were too young
to see it.
I, uh, I had
some of dad's buddies...
take care of his files.
It was the only time
I ever broke the rules.
I'm sorry.
Can I begin treatment?
(Taub)
Fever hasn't broken.
White count is still up.
Renal function
is declining.
(Foreman) So he has all the signs
of malaria,
except the antimalarials
aren't curing him.
Gonorrhea?
If it got into his heart...
We did an echo.
His valves look good.
What about--
you bastard.
You were faking.
Yesterday, House stole candy
by putting it into a cup.
The cup was too small,
so his solution
was to remove
some of the candy.
But the obviously logical thing
was to just get a bigger cup,
which he did today,
because he's no longer faking.
He couldn't have faked it.
We tested your--
I took St. John's Wort
to alter the way
my liver metabolized
acetaminophen.
Then some n-acetylcysteine
just to finish it off.
You tortured them
to torture me
just to see
who you could trust?
I did it to save lives.
God, I wish I could rationalize
that one.
And now you're going
to brilliantly deduce
which one of us
is the rat?
What makes you think
I haven't already?
To be continued.
I need to brilliantly cure
a patient.
No hair usually means
no lice.
What we didn't account for
was that it wasn't your hair.
Tea was not the only thing
that your Afghani neighbors
shared with you.
I'm sure
they were generous enough
to let you sit
on their furniture,
which was infested
with rat lice.
You have typhus.
Caused the vasculitis
and explains
all your other symptoms.
But here's
where it gets interesting.
One of those symptoms,
a lawyer might argue,
was leaking the tape.
There are psychiatric issues
associated with typhus.
If you change your mind,
plead not guilty,
you've got a case.
I'd be undermining everything
I've been trying to do.
You did what you thought
you had to do.
Going to jail proves nothing.
It proves
I still have my honor.
You're not doing this
for honor.
You're doing this
to please your father.
And the pathetic thing
is that the man
you're trying to please
never existed.
Traitor.
You've been avoiding me
for two days.
'Cause, when I stranded you
behind the barricades,
you went straight
to Foreman.
I've been avoiding you
because you're an ass.
I've been an ass my whole life.
I can't get rid of you.
You can get rid of me now.
Just turn and limp away.
Huh.
Your whiny righteousness
has the stench of sincerity.
Fine. I have to punish
my whole team
so that one of them
will step forward.
Makes sense.
Damn.
Now I'm gonna have to punish
my whole team
so that one of them
will step forward.
You just said that.
Yeah, but I meant it
this time.
First time
I was just testing you.
Either you were gonna
genuinely confess
or falsely confess
or actually...
[Marching footsteps]
[Rat squeaking]
His name's li'l Chase.
He's a rat.
You're a rat.
Get it?
Taub confessed to telling
Foreman to protect the patient.
Adams confessed
to protect Taub.
But your confession
was just piling on.
There's no rational reason
for you to have done it.
And my punishment
will be nothing.
You wanted me
to tell Foreman.
Your ability
to solve puzzles
is the only thing
that matters to you.
And you're smart enough
to know
even you'll lose your edge
at some point.
You want to make sure
someone's there when you do.
If that were true,
why are li'l Chase's
li'l cousins
scurrying through
your apartment's floorboards
right now?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net