Who are you?
What are you doing?
Get out of here!
Mom!
Lue? Lue?
You okay?
Okay, honey.
Calm down.
It's all right.
You're just having
another bad dream.
I can't breathe!
Yes, you can.
You're fine.
Just relax.
Just take slow,
deep breaths.
Nice and easy.
There's nothing
to be afraid of.
I'm...trying...
But I can't!
Relax.
Slow, deep breaths.
I...can't.
Lue?
Oh, my God.
Lue, wake up!
Wake up, Lue!
Come on!
Lue!
♪ House 8x18 ♪
We Need the Eggs
Original air date on April 23, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
[Massive Attack's Teardrop]
♪
Been paging you
for over two hours.
I must've been
in the shower.
Then I had to
moisturize.
Eight-year-old boy
was brought into the ER
last night with
acute respiratory distress.
No history of--
no histories
of asthma or allergies,
and his chest
X-ray's clear.
Actually, I had
to moisturize twice.
Dominika made oysters
Rockefeller last night.
Kid's been having
night terrors.
Woke up in the middle of one
in full respiratory arrest.
Stress induced panic attack.
Tell the parents
to lay off the grades.
The world
needs fry cooks too.
Does great in school.
The parents are divorced,
but it was amicable.
And the dad's
moved out of state.
Have you seen
Wilson around?
The dreams are about
an ugly, old hag
trying to strangle him.
The family's Hmong.
SUNDS--
sudden unexpected
nocturnal death syndrome,
aka BS name for no one's
figured out why they died.
Over 100
in the early '80s.
Only male.
Only Hmong.
Healthy right up
until the moment
they died in their sleep.
What was he dreaming about?
It doesn't matter.
It's a dream.
It doesn't
mean anything.
If the nightmare's
scary enough,
meaningful or not, it could
cause a catecholamine surge
and ventricular
fibrillation.
An ancient demon
called a Dab
was sitting on him,
strangling him.
I think that qualifies.
Except in the rational
part of the file,
where it says his EKG's
within normal limits.
It's not his heart.
What about obstructive
sleep apnea?
Sleep apnea wouldn't
have caused breathing problems
after he woke up.
What did you dream of?
I never remember
my dreams.
But you're certain
that they're insignificant.
Defensively so.
I was defending science.
You were defensively
defending science.
Lung damage
from inhaled toxins
could keep causing problems
after he woke up.
Or an upper respiratory
infection.
Okay, Chase and Park,
start iv antibiotics
for pneumonia.
Taub and Adams,
go check the home for toxins.
Could I go with Taub?
It was my idea.
Right...
'cause for a moment there,
I thought you were
uncomfortable around Chase
because you'd had
a nocturnal Australian.
You can go with
whoever you want.
But all of you,
read all of these files.
Do you believe a spirit
could be hurting your son?
No, of course not.
Because if he's been taught
to believe that,
it is possible
for the fear alone
to affect heart function.
I'm an engineer.
I know illnesses aren't
caused by evil spirits.
I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to,
I just...
had to check.
Anything else
you need to check?
No.
I had a dream.
House...
We can talk later.
Relax, I'm a Doctor.
Your spectacular breasts
mean nothing to me.
House...
House!
Later.
I had sex with Dominika.
In a dream?
It wasn't literally sex.
Technically,
it was flossing.
You know,
teeth, testicles.
I think the symbolism
is pretty clear.
"Later" just changed
to "never."
I'll tell you
what would be weirder,
if you didn't dream about
having sex with Chase.
Have you?
No.
But I've dreamed
about having sex
with a lot of people
I work with,
and it didn't
freak me out.
That's different.
How?
'Cause you've
actually had sex
with a lot of people
at work,
and that hasn't
freaked you out.
Good point.
So you're worried
about what it means?
I'm not worried.
It means nothing.
It means something,
doesn't it?
I work with him.
I can't want
to sleep with him.
Maybe Chase
just represents work.
You're just falling in love
with your job.
It has been
very satisfying lately.
You smell that?
Yeah.
Smells like wet dog.
It's mold.
It's not mold.
It's definitely mold.
I don't see
any sign of water damage.
Holy crap.
It looked like
a slaughterhouse.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
It was clean
when we left.
You're telling us
some random person
broke into your house
to dismember a pig
in your son's bedroom?
A pig?
My father-in-law.
What did you do?
What you should have
done weeks ago,
when the dreams started.
I'm saving Lue.
He's coding!
Need a Doctor in here!
V-tach.
No pulse.
Oh, my God!
Push 1 milligram EPI!
Paddles. Charge to 50.
Charging!
Clear!
Baby...
Still V-tach!
Charge to 100!
100!
Clear!
Charge--
wait!
Normal sinus rhythm.
Oh, God!
He's stable,
but we've obviously
got a second symptom.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
kid in V-tach.
Tell me about the luau
in his bedroom.
It's a traditional
Hmong ceremony
that's supposed to call back
the kid's soul.
Hasn't he heard of star-69?
There's more.
The reason grandpa thinks
the kid's soul is stolen
is because he's convinced
his son, the kid's father,
had his stolen as well.
He beat his boss
to death.
The dad
didn't move away.
He's in prison.
PTSD could definitely
cause breathing problems--
It's not PTSD.
Even if the kid
wasn't there,
just hearing
what the dad did--
But he hasn't.
It happened
when he was two,
and all he's ever
been told is that
his parents divorced
and his dad moved away.
The heart thing indicates
a malignant arrhythmia.
He needs an E.P. study.
How many
of the other files
showed malignant
arrhythmias?
None, but--
Forget the E.P.
What about
acute pericarditis?
Explains the dyspnea.
How many
of the other files--
it's exacerbated
by lying supine,
so the symptoms
would get worse
when he goes to sleep.
Just like all 100
of the others.
Do an echo to check
the pericardium.
See if you can find
any cardioactive toxins
in the home samples.
Can I just say that I
very much enjoy my job?
No, no, please.
No need to apologize
for your earlier behavior.
Floss was mint
probably because of
this green G-string
she hangs up to dry
in the bathroom.
My watch
must have stopped.
Apparently
it's already "never."
You might want to
forward your calls.
You do not want
the Reader's Digest
version on this.
There was a very tight
hygienist's uniform,
suggestive use
of the water sprayer--
The floss isn't sex.
It's guilt.
It's tying you up
for throwing away
the I.N.S. notification
granting Dominika
her citizenship.
She can move out,
but she still doesn't know it,
which means you're basically
holding her prisoner.
Tell her the truth,
and leave me alone.
Really?
What?
You startled me.
We work together
every day,
usually under
a fair amount of stress.
It's only natural
I'd pop into
a subconscious thought
every once in a while.
Have you ever dreamt
about having sex with me?
No.
You paused.
No, I didn't.
You think I'm lying?
No, I think you're
fighting the urge
to snap the word "no"
because your subconscious
finds the idea abhorrent.
So if I snap,
it's offensive,
and if I don't snap,
it's offensive
for the exact
same reason?
Talk to your
subconscious.
This is becoming weird
because you're making it weird.
So you don't find
the idea abhorrent?
I work with you.
I don't have to answer
that question.
You just did.
What happened?
Echo was negative,
but he has severe
abdominal pain.
Ultrasound didn't suggest
any intestinal blockages,
but he's severely
constipated.
No spores, clostridium,
or organic toxins
in the kitchen samples.
Nothing in the bedroom either.
We need to scope him,
and we're gonna need
to clear his bowel first.
We should biopsy
his thyroid.
For an impacted bowel?
Hashimoto's thyroiditis
would explain
his lung, heart,
and intestinal involvement.
And if you think we still
need house's approval,
it also explains
dying in your sleep.
Nice call.
When you invite me
for dinner,
I thought maybe you
take me to a restaurant.
Or have plates.
Yeah, sorry.
Idiot delivery guy
forgot them.
Mm...the idiot
delivery guy,
or the idiot guy
whose food you stole
from lounge
refrigerator, huh?
You've gotten to know me
pretty well.
My citizenship
depends on it, right?
Yeah...
that's actually why
I wanted to talk to you.
You heard news?
Yeah.
So what news?
They want us to come in
for another interview?
No.
Since we hadn't
heard anything,
I--I called,
and they said
it's gonna be
a couple weeks,
maybe a month
till they finalize
their decision.
A month?
Yeah, I know.
It sucks.
No, it's--it's not suck
to live with you.
It's been fun, but...
you know, I just
want to be legal.
And you will be.
Absolutely.
In the meantime...
Hmm?
You ever shot anyone?
No, get away.
Look, this needle
isn't nearly as big
as the one in your arm,
and that didn't hurt,
did it?
I don't want it.
They need
to do it, Lue.
You'll only feel
a little pinch
as we give you
the numbing medicine,
and after that,
you won't feel a thing.
No!
Lue, calm down.
It's gonna be okay.
What's he saying?
What's the problem?
I don't know.
He's saying
it's too late.
There's nothing
we can do.
It's Hmong.
He doesn't speak Hmong.
He's never even
heard it.
It isn't him speaking.
It's the Dab.
He's seizing!
Oh--!
Oh, my God!
Need some
Lorazepam in here!
Seizure
rules out Hashimoto's.
Yeah,
that's the issue,
not that we have
no rational explanation
for how the patient
spoke a language
he's never even heard.
I've got one.
It means "you're a bunch
of pathetic idiots" in Hmong.
Or it doesn't.
But you wouldn't know because
none of you speak Hmong.
Kid, on the other hand,
is presumably fluent
in gibberish.
The grandfather
speaks Hmong.
He translated.
He heard what
he wanted to hear,
'cause if his grandson
really is possessed,
that means his son
which is a giant step up
from being
a sledgehammering
psychopath.
Whatever it was
preceded a seizure.
It's obviously
a neurological symptom.
Scleroderma,
advanced to the point
that it's affecting
his brain?
Interesting.
So we should
start treating--
Interesting
that you keep
falling for it
when I say "interesting."
The scleroderma part
was idiotic--
we'd have seen
skin involvement.
The interesting part is
that you and Park agree,
but you're not able
to look at each other.
Um...
I'm looking at her.
I'm looking at him.
Good,
now lick your lips.
Rasmussen's encephalitis.
Diffuse spotty
inflammation
could hit the autonomic
centers of the brain.
It's Hmong for
"get an MRI to confirm."
Rasmussen's encephalitis.
But he'll be okay?
With treatment,
it's manageable.
And it explains
all the things
that have
happened to him?
We think so.
You are wrong.
And you are wasting
my grandson's time.
Neurological issues
can cause a person
to speak in tongues,
speak with an accent--
He wasn't
speaking in tongues!
In times of stress,
our senses can fool us
into believing--
I know the difference
between science and faith,
and when my son started
having the same dreams
my grandson is having,
science couldn't help him.
I'm sorry if your son
suffered from mental illness.
Kao was not crazy.
He was bright,
caring, happy,
until the bad dreams came.
I don't want to watch it
happen again.
Please don't
scare the boy.
It won't help him
get better.
Axial view of mid-brain
level looks good.
Moving on to thalamic.
I had another dream
last night.
This time
it was about you.
Really?
See, that's how
you're supposed to react.
When a woman tells you
she's dreamt about you,
you should be thrilled,
even if you're not interested
in her whatsoever.
You're an idiot,
you know that?
Well, I definitely won't be
dreaming about you tonight.
I'm jealous
of you two.
You couldn't be
more different,
and yet you have
this good thing happening.
You support each other.
You like each other.
Don't let House
screw it up.
We're not
that different.
Yeah, you are.
Apparently, there are
some things about you
I don't know.
I served one year
in police unit.
And you're just telling
your husband now?
Immigration
doesn't know.
No need
for husband to know.
What is happening
to boy with demons?
Absence of evidence
on an MRI,
which my team has mistaken
for evidence of absence.
This is what
I am not understanding:
How can you believe
in dark matters
but not in
dark spirits?
Is--is the idea
of demons
so different than
the higgs boson?
We can't see it,
but we can see
the impact
of its presence.
I borrowed
your physics book.
I read while in bathroom.
You're a dead-eye shot
and enjoy reading
quantum physics
on the crapper?
I read in bathtub.
Better image.
Thank you.
The doctors say
my brain is sick.
Your doctors
are trying their best,
but they're not looking
in the right place.
You know, I know
this is a lot
to put on
an eight-year-old,
but you have angered
our ancestors
by ignoring them.
Now do you remember
how to talk to them?
Yeah, that's right.
Good.
Now close your eyes,
and we will ask
for forgiveness together.
You're doing good...
But we have to do more.
The evil spirits
are in the air,
and the only way
to stop them
is by stopping the air.
You have to be brave.
I'm not trying to hurt you.
This will help you.
I know it will.
Lue?
You okay?
I can't wake him up!
Lue!
Lue, you're safe.
You're in the hospital.
Get grandpa away!
He's not here, honey.
It was just a dream.
He was choking me!
No, Lue,
it wasn't real.
It was!
He grabbed my neck!
Those bruises
weren't there before.
He had the dream,
and then he had the bruising.
More likely--
and by "likely,"
I mean "rationally"--
it's the other
way around.
His brain felt
the pain in his neck
and created the dream
to explain it.
Coagulopathy.
Lung problems cause
a clotting disturbance.
He would have
bruises everywhere.
Is it really
preposterous
that dreams can have
physical manifestations?
Well,
short answer is--
Thoughts during sleep
can and do cause
physical changes.
Is that right,
Dr. Park?
Did you wake up
this morning
experiencing
physical changes?
It's medically relevant.
Her dream
doesn't mean anything.
Can we start acting like
it doesn't mean anything?
Sure.
We could also start
acting like walls
don't mean anything,
but then we'd
hurt our noses.
You've been taking
the high road.
You haven't been teasing in
an obviously teasable situation
because you know
it does mean something.
She hates the dream
because it makes her
feel vulnerable.
You love the dream
because it makes you
feel superior.
The poor lass
who can't help
but fall sway
to your charms,
and you're
bestowing upon her
the gift of
illusory irrelevance.
Can you please
hint to House
that you
had a sex dream?
I'd really prefer
not to get distracted
with trying to cure
the patient today.
I refuse to divulge
my dreams
about girl-on-girl
loofa action.
The bruising
could indicate anemia,
a vitamin C deficiency,
or even leukemia.
That is so weird
that you and I
had the same dream.
I assume yours also ends
with me achieving ecstasy
while simultaneously
placing third in
the New York City marathon.
Third?
I'm a realist.
Liver failure can cause
gibberish from encephalopathy,
constipation, bruising,
and breathing problems.
Hepatic fibrosis
could hit someone his age.
So let's hit his liver.
Get a biopsy.
Angle a bit
more superiorly.
He keeps having
these nightmares
that become real.
They really hurt him.
I don't want to believe
that a nightmare
can do that, but I--
I'm struggling
with it too,
but these things can be
explained medically.
But you haven't.
Every Doctor,
every idea they've had,
it's been wrong.
Liver biopsy's back.
Team's about to meet.
Back to avoiding
eye contact with me?
House got to you again?
Want me to gaze
longingly into your eyes
as I tell you
the test results?
I want you to treat me
like a friend,
which means
getting over the fact
that you like me
more than I like you.
Yeah, egotism and preening
really turn me on.
Too bad I'm not attracted
to androgyny and self-pity,
or you'd have it made.
Because anyone
who hasn't gotten wet
from your petri dish
of STDs
clearly has
low self-esteem!
Bitch.
Dick!
You coming?
Why didn't your lips move
when you said that?
Chase!
You coming?
Liver biopsy's back.
I'll be right there.
Biopsy was negative
for fibrosis.
So once again,
you don't know
what's wrong?
It's always good
to rule out the bad things.
Doctors!
God!
Was he?
Yes.
He was levitating.
Cool.
So the one thing
we know for sure
is he was not
levitating.
He was floating
6 inches off the bed.
He could've just been arching
his back off the bed.
Yes, but then I would have
come into the room
and reported
that the patient
was weirdly arching
his back off the bed.
It was his whole body.
He was levitating.
So many questions...
Starting with why did Chase
address his comment
to someone who wasn't
even in the room?
Hocus pocus,
on my feet
you idiots must focus.
The kid's
not a magician.
Of course not.
He's the lovely assistant.
'Cause grandpa pig sticker
is waving the wand.
Middling with...
is Chase trying
to avoid Taub,
or is he trying
to prove
that he's not
avoiding Park?
We checked the bed.
There were no platforms
or wires.
This wasn't a trick.
Tetanus could cause
muscle rigidity.
Maybe he was propped up
by his heel and elbow.
Except he wasn't!
Tetanus wouldn't cause
that kind of
breathing difficulty.
And ending with...
if Chase is trying
not to avoid Park,
why is he doing this
today and not yesterday?
But hypocalcemia could,
and the enema
we administered
to cure
his constipation
had a high
phosphorous load,
which could make him
transiently hypocalcemic.
It's a long shot,
but at least
it has the benefit
of being rational.
Go pump up
his electrolytes
and start
beta-blockers.
And good news
for Park:
I think Chase
had a sex dream about you.
Dreams don't
mean anything.
I don't know.
Nothing you've done has helped.
If we don't start
and he has another seizure,
the neurological damage
could be permanent.
My father-in-law--
he thinks
the calling ceremony
didn't work because Lue
wasn't there.
And you think
he's right?
I don't know.
I'm sorry,
but there's no way
we can allow him
to perform an exorcism
in your son's
hospital room.
Then I will have
to take him home.
A day ago,
you were insulted
I'd even think you might
believe that stuff,
and now you're willing
to stop all treatment,
so you can try it?
Maybe Xang
was right about Kao.
The man I loved
wasn't evil
and would never do
what he did.
He was...possessed.
And my son needs
his soul back.
Why not?
As long as he doesn't
feed the kid anything
or put anything on his skin
that we haven't
verified is harmless,
what's the problem?
I agree.
And since we're
establishing a new policy
of "What the hell,
we'll try anything,"
I'd like to hire Shakira
to belly dance
while singing Waka Waka.
As long as you get the mom
and Shakira to consent.
It's no different
than having a priest
or rabbi
lead a prayer vigil.
The mom is scared
and confused
and desperate for anything
that'll give her hope.
True.
But in the long run,
I think you'll be happier
having our lawyer
declare her unfit.
That way you won't be ratifying
superstition over science,
and I'll still
be working here.
And why would that
make me happier?
You're not going anywhere,
and we're not "ratifying"
their beliefs,
we're respecting them.
You do realize it may
involve animal sacrifice.
People who live
in glass hospitals
should not
throw exorcisms.
I'll talk
to the mother.
I don't want to deny him
the medicine,
I just...
want to make sure
I try everything I can.
I understand that,
but you have to understand
that we're a hospital,
not a temple.
Then I'll
take him elsewhere.
No, you won't.
He's sick.
We can't let him leave here.
I'm sorry, you really
have no choice.
I spoke to a lawyer.
He told me as long
as I wasn't saying no
to your treatment,
you couldn't say no
to my religion.
Give me 24 hours.
This came
in the mail today!
I'm sorry.
I should've told you.
Told me what?
I don't understand.
What's the letter?
It's from my Uncle
in Poland.
My Aunt Luba, they put her
in nursing home two months ago!
That's too bad.
My mother, I talk
to her twice a week
and she never
even mentioned it.
Wh--what does she think?
That I can't handle?
I am 29 years old!
I am not a child!
Were you going out
tonight?
I could stay.
He's still
barely breathing.
Lue?
How you feeling?
Any stronger?
Lue, can you hear me?
What's wrong?
I'm not sure.
Lue, I need you
to squeeze my hand.
He's not responding.
Get me an amp of D50!
You were wrong again?
I'm calling
his grandfather.
Genetic tests for Brugada
and long QT variants
came back negative.
What about
a carotid aneurysm?
We should do
an angiogram.
He's got normal
carotid pulses.
Who cares?
Mom's given up,
why shouldn't I?
I'm sorry,
do we not treat idiots?
Because I thought--
Her kid levitated.
That happens to my girl,
I'm expanding
my diagnostic horizons.
All the more reason
why we should shut down.
We cure this kid now,
crazy grandpa
and his magic beads
get all the credit.
And since when do you care
about credit?
Since when do I care
about this kid?
All I care about
is sending mommy
out into the world
having faith in faith.
Kid's better off dead.
As soon as she's done
appeasing the Gods, let's talk.
What about Kawasaki?
It explains
the irregular heartbeat,
respiratory distress,
and seizures.
It fits.
Which means he needs
a coronary bypass.
It can't be Kawasaki.
Echo would have
shown it.
But a patent ductus
arteriosis--
it can't be a PDA.
He's not an infant,
nor has he had any symptoms
for eight years.
Maybe he has.
Maybe he had
an infected ductus,
which we inadvertently
treated with antibiotics.
So no evidence
is evidence of evidence?
I'm just saying,
it's consistent.
It's a billion-to-one.
Which means there's
seven people in the world
who fit the diagnosis.
I thought we were
looking for 100.
Well, maybe PDA
is more common
than we thought.
With idiot doctors
like you--
You're wrong.
But the treatment's
just ibuprofen.
Closes
the malformed duct.
Worst-case scenario,
he just doesn't get better,
No, worst-case scenario
is you piss me off--
You're not gonna let us
save an eight-year-old
because one more person
might embrace religion?
Does anyone here think
my diagnosis is right?
Well, then
I have decided,
for today only,
to respect your opinions.
We will proceed
according to your diagnosis
and nothing else.
That's an order.
Good luck.
We need to put him
on the O.R. schedule.
His B.P.'s dropping.
He's crashing.
Call a code!
You need to stop this!
I'm giving him
the ibuprofen.
Dinner's almost ready.
I think I'll stick with
the fluids tonight, thanks.
Why are you sulking?
I'm not sulking.
Oh, my mistake.
Mmm.
Either religion
is killing a kid,
or I am.
What are you doing?
Comforting my husband
after a bad day.
If this is not
what you want,
I go back
to making dinner.
I'm not
gonna answer that.
Oh, smart man.
This is killing mood.
U.S. citizenship!
I'll get it.
This is Mrs. House,
please give good news,
so my husband and I
can go back to sex.
Budmo! Is fantastic!
How many notices
you send me?
O-okay, I--I come pick up
naturalization certificate.
Thank you for calling.
I'm sorry.
Dr. Adams, Dr. Taub?
His vitals are improving.
He's stabilizing.
He's gonna be okay.
It worked.
Um, no, it didn't.
Mrs. Cheng, the medicine
I administered
was a long-shot treatment
for Lue's heart,
but that's
what's helping him.
Ibuprofen?
That's for headaches.
I know it seems
hard to believe,
but it's true.
And I know this seems hard
for you to believe.
Honey...
Grandpa was right.
He saved you.
There were two things
we thought were impossible.
One of them wasn't.
That's all we know.
[Wilco's Black Moon]
♪ ♪
♪ I was always right ♪
♪ about the morning ♪
♪ okay, I'm an old shoe ♪
♪ danced above the blaze ♪
♪ never stopped crawling ♪
♪ over ♪
♪ The black dunes ♪
♪ ♪
♪ and I'm waiting
for you ♪
Was I good?
Doesn't mean anything.
Idea got planted.
It was probably inevitable.
It means something.
What?
Well, it could
mean the obvious,
that you want
some of this.
When will you learn that
that look is insulting?
Or it could just mean
that we like each other.
I'm weird,
and you're pretty,
but we connect.
We feel safe.
We trust
each other.
Maybe.
Just testing
my theory.
Adams defied me.
There's one more zealot
in the world.
And Dominika moved out.
She was fun.
She was hot.
She fixed my blender.
That is not
a metaphor.
You know any good
fake divorce lawyers?
I am surprisingly
depressed by this.
I have cancer.
You were a little short
with me the other day.
You do need an excuse.
Cancer may be overplaying it.
Stage II Thymoma.
I didn't want to tell you
until I had it confirmed.
I got the tests back
this morning.
I have cancer, House.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net