[Television droning]
[Creaking]
[Television turns off]
Billy?
Is anyone here?
[Phone ringing]
(Man)
Hey.
Hey. I just noticed
the front door was open.
Maybe you left it
that way?
I don't know.
I thought I heard something.
I know the whole house
creaks, but I was just--
if you have any doubts,
go to the Cassano's.
I'm in the car.
I'm a few blocks away.
No, I'm sure it's nothing.
Love you.
[Creaking]
[Shifting noises]
[Banging]
[Loud bang]
[gasps]
[Gasps]
Oh! Uh, the--
the door banged shut.
I'm sure it was just
the wind.
Oh, God.
It's okay.
It's okay, it's just me.
You all right?
Uhh!
Margaret...
Hey...
Margaret!
Oh--
oh, my stomach! Oh...
♪ House 7x04 ♪
Massage Therapy
Original Air Date on October 11, 2010
[Massive Attack's ♪ Teardrop ♪]
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
♪
[radio traffic
and weather reports]
I get it.
You're jealous
of my new cane,
so you hired a new doctor
that you could lean on.
Exactly.
Nothing to do with the fact that
you instructed me to hire one.
Dr. House, this is
Dr. Kelly Benedict,
your new fellow.
Nice to meet you.
Um, I just finished
my psychiatry residency
at St. Jude's.
And I loved studying
the mind,
but I thought I could make
more of a difference,
or at least--
man, you're hot.
I mean, seriously.
30-year-old female--
I know what you're thinking.
She looks like Cameron,
and he's hired her
solely to sleep with her.
No, none of us were
thinking that.
Well, you should have.
But you'd be
foolishly wrong.
Yes, he's been dating
at a near-Clooney pace recently,
but at this point,
the only hole he's trying
to fill is the one in his soul,
which means it's
the emotional connection
with Cameron
that he misses.
Did you ever marry
a dying man?
And if so,
did you freeze his sperm?
Okay, so Cameron's
his ex.
But sperm...
She's not like Cameron.
Then why'd you make her
wear Cameron's clothes?
No, I'm wearing
my own clothes.
(Foreman)
-Year-old female.
Severe vomiting
and abdominal pain
preceded by three days
of moderate pain.
Slightly elevated lfts.
Could be lead poi--
uh, uh, uh!
If I know Dr. Shameron--
and I think I do--
she'll want this chance
for a little
stuff-strutting.
Okay, hepatitis "A."
Serologies are negative.
Right...
Appendicitis--
that hasn't ruptured by now?
It's hepatic fibrosis.
(Taub)
At the risk
of having Foreman
snark at me too,
lead poisoning could
also work.
Liver angiogram
to check for fibrosis.
Search the home
for heavy metals.
What's you position
on the legality
of illegal break-ins?
(Chase)
That's more of a second week
type activity.
We'll do the angiogram.
I'll meet you in radiology,
third floor.
She was nervous.
Give her a break.
Oh...And she's not
like Cameron.
True.
Cameron had
much smaller breasts.
By which I mean
she was smarter.
[Rock music]
♪ ♪
(Wilson)
How are things going
with Cuddy?
Great.
We've gotten
to fifth base.
That's two home runs,
and then she
gives me back a triple.
I could see you
on this one.
Am I wearing a dashiki?
[chuckles]
Easy Rider auditions ended
four decades ago.
Are you sleeping
over there yet?
Nope. She comes over,
we hook up, she leaves.
Whose idea was that?
Mine. But I let her think
it's hers.
That's the fun
of a relationship.
You get the sex,
the dinners...
Video game partnership.
I also get
a full-night's sleep.
Okay, taking it slow.
That could work.
You are spending time
with the kid?
As little as possible.
That is one boring child.
House, she's a toddler.
I know.
I'm grading on a curve.
It's that bad.
Oh, you think you were
the scintillating wit
at two and a half?
I wasn't trying
to eat shoes.
Cuddy could have adopted
a golden retriever.
Oh, yeah, things are
definitely going great.
We'll get to it
when we get to it.
You really like these,
or are you just avoiding
a touchy conversation?
Nah. This one's
too metrosexual.
This one's
too heterosexual.
They're identical.
Do you even want
my input?
No.
Then why did you
invite me?
Who'd drive my car home
if I buy a bike?
[Monitor beeping]
(Chase)
You did fine.
House is just trying
to get at me.
And he's wrong,
by the way.
I hired you because you're
the most qualified applicant.
Injecting dye.
Dr. Foreman didn't seem
to like me either.
Oh, well, he takes
a little while to warm up.
In my case, I'm hoping
year seven does the trick.
Tapering cutoff
in the left branch
of the hepatic artery.
Tumor?
Looks more like
scar tissue.
From what, surgery?
Probably.
Look at her rib cage.
(Benedict)
She broke, what, five or six
bones at some point?
She didn't tell us
about this?
No, she didn't.
I checked the pipes
and the paint.
It's not lead poisoning.
You got anything?
Yeah...
I was looking around
in the corner over there.
I found a question about
why you have a problem
with our new doctor.
Sorry, we should all be
super-polite in the ddxes,
fail to correct each other,
and then treat patients
for diseases they don't have.
Dude, is this about
Thirteen?
[Scoffs]
No. Why are you
calling me "dude"?
Maybe it's hard
seeing House replace her
when you've still got
feelings.
One--I don't have feelings
for Thirteen beyond friendship.
Two--it's a temporary
replacement.
And three-- dude?
It felt right.
The day the patient collapsed,
she say where she was working?
Cleaning job in summit,
then she went straight home.
Then why's she got
a credit card receipt for lunch
from a cafe in Trenton?
(Margaret)
I'm not hiding anything.
I just got the days wrong.
I worked in Trenton
on Tuesday.
I worked in summit
on Monday.
I guess it slipped
my mind.
And breaking eight ribs?
That slip yo mind too?
You know how I was
on the cycling team
when I was at U mass?M
Well, during training,
I fell off my bike...
Right onto a sprinkler head.
Why didn't you tell us?
It was ten years ago.
I didn't think it could be
related to my stomach problems.
We're going to need to see
the records from the operation.
You think it is related?
The strange stuff we found
in your liver,
it's probably
hepatic fibrosis,
but it could also just be
a screw-up from the old surgery.
The operation was done
at the University Hospital.
Hopefully they still have
the records.
(House)
Come back.
Just one more time.
You'll love it.
My wrists are tired.
I can't defeat the new
decimator 98 all alone.
Come on,
we're a team.
You understand, right?
The babysitter's leaving
in half an hour.
[Video game alarm sounding]
Oops, you're right.
Scram.
I've got a massage
coming by in five.
It was at that moment
she realized
the romance was
already gone.
Head shot!
[Video gunfire]
[Chattering and shrieking]
Oh...Hi.
Hi.
I called U Mass.
There's no record of
any surgery for Margaret.
You use her maiden name?
No. Kelly knows nothing about
the concept of married names.
It wasn't covered in her
psychiatry residency.
Margaret was never even
registered at the university.
Call the other hospitals
in the area.
Done. Nothing.
So I ran her social
security number
through one of those
websites.
Her number matches
her name,
but she's got
no credit history
until three years ago.
And based on her number,
she was born around 1945.
She stole someone's
identity.
[Pagers beeping]
[Monitor alarm beeping]
(Taub)
Supraventricular tachycardia.
150 bpm.
(Chase)
Carotid massage?
Not responding.
Get the adenocine.
We've tried already.
Get the pacemaker.
We can overdrive her.
[Monitor alarm beeping]
Dorothy.
Dorothy, dear...
It's aunt Em, darling.
What's--
what's wrong with me?
(House)
Well, on the one hand,
you've got some mysterious
heart and tummy problems.
On the other, you look great
for a 65-year-old.
So who are you?
And, no, that's not
some weird
Canadian pronunciation
of "how."
They're saying you changed
your identity.
What are they
talking about, Margaret?
I don't know.
Well, that falls in the
obviously stupid lie category,
which you're familiar with
from the one you told us
about your bike accident.
You thought
we'd never check?
Five years ago...
I was married.
Who was he?
Just a guy.
I met him in high school.
He was older.
He...Used to get jealous...
Do drugs.
Those broken bones?
He...
He would tell me to
take off all my clothes
so he could inspect me.
Then he would hit me.
I got a restraining order,
ran away,
but he found me anyway.
That's when he broke
my ribs.
So I moved away again
to Arizona.
Came back from work
one day...
He'd broken in,
fed pesticides to my dog...
Killed her.
I bought a dead woman's
identity,
changed my name,
moved here.
Is this related to why you were
in Trenton yesterday?
There's a support group
for abused women
at Trenton General.
I go a lot.
What's his name?
Please, don't do this. I don't--
just--just tell me.
Carl.
Carl what?
This is why
I didn't tell you.
'Cause you go confront him,
he'll kill you.
Well, I've got another name
you can tell us instead.
Yours.
It's Jenny.
Now, some person
seemed to think that
I was not being fair to you
in our last ddx
because I made you nervous.
So this time,
I'm gonna put you at ease.
It's just you
and old doc House.
A couple of pals
chittin' the chat.
(Chase)
Why not just place a chair
above a trap door
with a shark tank underneath?
Wednesday is when
I get my shark tank cleaned.
Also because
I'm giving her a chance.
You're giving her a test.
This whole job is a test.
I'm giving her the chance
to fail it sooner
rather than later.
Or pass.
Arrhythmia and elevated lfts
rule out hepatic fibrosis.
So heart and stomach.
Gastritis.
Explains the stomach, not the heart.
Atrial fibrillation?
Explains the heart, not the stomach.
Sorry, sorry. Cystitis.
Explains the...Nothing.
I meant cholecystitis.
It would have showed up
on the physical examine.
Do we have to sit here
all day?
You got a better answer than
she does, then let's hear it.
I'm sure she's already
starting to think how,
if we put the symptoms together
with the abusive ex,
the fact that she'd just eaten,
the open door...
Rhymes with moison...
You think her ex-husband
tried to poison her?
Even if he found her
somehow,
these abusers have
a pattern.
He beat her with his hands.
Poison's too impersonal.
It doesn't fit.
Exactly.
The counterargument
is woof!
Her ex poisoned her dog.
Oh...Right.
(Foreman)
She said he used pesticides.
He could have stuck some
in her dinner.
Treat with pralidoxime.
"A" for effort?
[Elevator dings]
House was wrong
trying to come up
with a complicated reason
you hired Kelly.
Thank you.
It's actually quite simple.
You think she's hot.
You u want to sleep with her.
[Scoffs]
Well, it was nice
to see you finally
taking an interest
in my life.
We should go bowling
sometime.
I'm just saying
if you spend
all your off-work time
and energy getting laid,
it's gonna spill
into your work as well.
She's smart.
You didn't interview her.
I did glance
at her resume.
Middling grades,
middling med school.
She was Editor for Rutgers'
daily undergrad newspaper.
That shows a lot more guts
and determination
than med school grades.
Uh-huh.
How long did you
interview her?
45 minutes,
at least.
How much of that was after
you decided to hire her?
You saw what you wanted
to see.
This guy broke into
our house?
That's the theory.
I don't know,
it could be true.
And you didn't tell me
out him
because you didn't
trust me?
I just didn't want you
to get involved.
I'm already involved.
We're married.
It was the worst time
in my life.
I wanted to block it out.
I'm sorry.
I gotta get out of here.
Where are you going?
I don't know.
Hey...
So I'm seeing you tonight
yes. And you would have
even it you hadn't
told me that.
I was just wondering,
your masseuse...
Brandi.
I'm sure I'm imagining this,
although I'm not as sure
now that I know her name,
but she seems a little...
How do I say this?
I don't know.
Um, a bit slutty.
She is a hooker.
If she's not slutty,
she's doing something wrong.
What?
Did you have sex with her?
Yesterday?
Ah, you're getting
confused by the hooker thing.
No, of course not.
I'm dating you.
But you used to
have sex with her.
Well, it was a massage
plus happy ending
sort of thing.
Now it's more of
a sad ending.
Because of you!
I've tried 15 different
massage therapists
over the last few years.
I don't know why,
but she's the best I've found.
She makes my leg
feel better.
So you really think that
I would be okay
with you getting a massage
from a hooker
you used to have sex with?
You don't mind
the massage part,
you mind the sex part,
which doesn't exist anymore.
I know a great
physical therapist.
I will give you
her number.
Why would I give up one
who definitely works
for one who might work?
Because I asked you to.
That's not really
an argument, now, is it?
I won't see you until
you stop seeing her.
Well, that's an argument.
How's our patient doing?
Well, she's stable,
but it's too early to tell
if the pralidoxime
is working.
Come on, go home.
You can't re-cram
all of med school right now.
I'm feeling a lot
of pressure here.
You were the Editor
of your school paper.
I think you know how
to deal with pressure.
No, I wasn't.
On your resume it said
"Rutgers Daily Herald Editor."
Didn't it?
I wasn't head
of the paper.
That's called
Editor in Chief.
I was just a writer.
We're all called Editors.
Ah.
Did you hire me
because of that?
Not entirely.
Look, if you're having
buyer's remorse...
Oh, no, uh, I'm not.
You might want to check out
volume two
on infectious diseases.
[pager beeping]
Patient's husband just got
admitted to the E.R.
Let's say you had
a really fantastic handyman...
I was hoping you'd
interrupt my cooking
to ask about handymen.
Do go on.
Would Sam ask you
to stop using him
because you might have had
a sexual relationship
with him in the past?
Ah, yes, the age-old
hooker massage conundrum.
Cuddy might have mentioned
something about it.
Let's say you're right.
Completely right
about everything.
Give in anyway.
This is not a point of pride.
This is a point of principle.
Right, you're the Rosa Parks
of hooker massages.
The principle is
she's being irrational.
If I give in on this,
it sets the stage
for the whole relationship.
Putting up with
irrationality
is the foundation
for every relationship.
I agree with Sam when she's
calling her father a monster.
I agree with her when
she's calling him a Saint.
And in exchange, I get
to have sex with her.
And I'm sure she has
similar tradeoffs with me.
Relationships are hard.
You have to make sacrifices.
So sacrifice being crazy.
Go get her a gift
and apologize.
You finally made a good point.
Which, clearly,
you have misunderstood
based on how quickly
you agreed.
The kitchen's burning.
Oh...
We've got to get you
thinking like House.
The husband's in the E.R.
if he's got similar symptoms,
it could mean environmental.
Which helps
organophosphate theory.
Or maybe it's an infection,
which would mean we were wrong.
Exactly.
Or maybe he just got sick
with something else.
Coincidence?
Yeah.
All right, here's one
big piece of advice.
House doesn't buy
coincidences.
Okay, it's not
environmental.
What happened to you?
What's it look like?
Looks like someone
kicked your ass.
What happened?
I looked in her address book.
There's a guy named Carl
in Brooklyn.
She told you to
stay away from him.
I'm not so good at following
direction sometimes.
I found him, I got angry,
which I also do sometimes.
He said he didn't know
what I was talking about.
He wouldn't let me in.
I got more pissed...
Next thing I know,
I'm on the floor
and he's called the cops.
You get arrested?
No, he didn't
press charges.
Well, you should
If he tried
to poison her...
No, he really didn't know
what I was talking about.
He's just some guy
that Margaret--
damn it, that's
not even her name--
Jenny just--
some guy that Jenny
used to work with.
I was stupid.
I just assumed that
the name Carl was...
I just wanted to find the guy
that poisoned my wife.
[Cell phone ringing]
What's up?
Pyrexia.
103 and rising.
I'll be right up.
Your wife just spiked
a fever.
What's that mean?
She wasn't poisoned.
(Chase)
What are you doing?
Just letting you all share
in the joys
of my last trip
to Carlsbad Caverns.
Which the husband probably
would have beaten up
if he'd found it
in the address book.
Would you mind standing
next to the screen?
Yeah, she'd love to become
a target for your ridicule.
She is not ready?
Endocarditis?
Normal EKG.
No osler nodes.
Right, Dr. Kelly!
Kelly's her first name.
What's your point,
Dr. Robert?
Run an echo.
I already did.
No vegetations.
Valves are clear.
Snapilicious!
But as I always like
to say,
it's better to be a helpful
Helen than a negative Nelly.
So while you're cooking up
some ideas of your own,
allow me to present theory 2.0
of why Chase hired you.
Dr. Kelly,
meet your doppelganger.
Oh, no.
Hold on a second.
(Chase)
Oh, come on.
House...
(Taub)
Is that...
That's baby Chase and his mom.
That's adorable!
Never mind the baby,
peep the babe.
Note the cheekbones
and eye shape.
They do actually
look alike.
(House)
I know what you're thinking,
Chase wants to sleep
with his mom.
But who wouldn't hit that
if that looked like that?
It's a classic case of what Freud called--
stop.
This isn't about
Chase's mother.
You're wrong.
What do you mean he's wrong?
It is about your mom?
No.
So it's about...
I'm assuming he thought
I'd be a good member
of the team.
And on that subject,
what about Legionnaire's?
Taub said he saw a rattly
old air conditioner
in the patient's house.
I don't care
if he saw her licking
a petri dish of bacilli,
there's no lung involvement.
All we know is
we don't see it.
Dehydration from the fever
could hide the pneumonia.
Okay, forget
the mom theory.
Now water the patient,
treat for Legionnaire's.
(Foreman)
Hey, Taub.
You didn't write up
the AC system.
Did you mention it to Kelly?
No.
Did you mention it
to Chase?
Yeah.
Whose idea was Legionnaire's?
Dr. Chase's.
Well, you get major points
for trying to trick me.
Unfortunately, you lose 'em
all for failing.
Hold that. Hold that.
See, now you're frowning.
You can really see
the resemblance.
So who gives a crap
if I prepped her?
Uh, House. And that's just
off the top of my head.
Why are you doing this?
You trying to
make me look bad
so you look better...
Or you don't like her,
or you're angry at me?
What?
We hire someone unqualified,
it's just dead weight
we'll all be pulling.
Me especially.
You especially why?
What do you mean why?
Because I'm--
you're what?
You're my boss
or something?
Something like.
So that's what it is.
You're angry that House
gave me the chance
to hire someone
because you still think
you're at a different level
to everyone else.
That's just pathetic.
I am at a different level.
Which is reflected
in what, exactly?
Your title? No.
Ur salary?
Not really.
Your responsibilities?
Hardly.
Your attitude?
Ah.
I think we finally
found it.
It doesn't change the fact
that you made a bad decision
because you want
to get laid.
Or the fact that you're
courageously picking on Kelly
because you're scared
to take on House.
Congratulations.
You're a real leader.
[Typing on keyboard]
[Door opens]
[Thick latin accent]
I am Felipe.
Oh, you've gotta
be kidding.
Dr. House was worried
how you left things.
He's giving you
a massage.
As an admission he was wrong?
Yes.
Well, tell him thanks,
but I have a meeting
with Dr. Schatz
in 20 minutes.
He says you would say that,
and to say no, you don't.
Well, tell him ne needs to
stop canceling my appointments,
because I will just
reschedule them.
He says you would say that,
and to say...Uh...
That "Dr. Schatz is a fat,
lonely moron who,
"in an effort to have contact
with human female,
"makes the same
exact complaint
"about parking spaces
every month.
And you know you have to
stop enabling him."
I have great fingers.
[Sighs]
That's so nice.
Thank you.
How long have you been
a masseur?
What is that...
"Masseur"?
A massage therapist.
Oh, no, not long.
How did my boyfriend
find you?
Boyfriend?
Dr. House.
He is your boyfriend?
Why is that surprising?
I just mean,
if he found me,
I do not think he's got
no girlfriend.
Are you a prostitute?
Are you a cop?
[Whispering]
Then no.
Get your hands off me.
I didn't know you smoked.
I don't.
I don't mind
screwing up.
I've screwed up
in my life,
and I've gotten over it.
But I'm not a cheater,
and I'm not a liar.
And now I feel like both.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
You work with House
and you kind of get
a messed-up perspective
of what's permissible
in the workplace.
Maybe I should just quit.
No. You're smart.
You're hard-working.
Yeah, but I'm not like
you guys.
Use what makes you different.
A lot of this job is
reading people,
dealing with them.
You're a psychiatrist...
Use your skills.
Are you okay?
I checked with
Trenton General.
There's no support group
for abused women.
Maybe it was just--
if she was lying about that,
what else is she lying about?
I mean, maybe she wasn't
even abused.
Maybe she's a criminal.
Who the hell knows?
You don't know.
That's the point.
The way she's acting,
that's the way
abuse victims act.
Their personalities
are affected
by what they went through.
They find coping mechanisms.
I gotta talk to her
about this Trenton thing.
If you wake her up,
make her feel defensive,
it'll go bad.
She doesn't need
any more hostility
or aggression in her life.
Okay.
Seriously?
A massage
from a male hooker?
He was? Huh.
That doesn't bother me
at all.
I guess we both learned
a valuable lesson.
Except that I didn't used
to have sex with him, you idiot!
Plus, he was a gay hooker.
Do you have any idea
how hard it is
to find a straight
male hooker?
Oh, come on.
It's a massage.
I don't care
who gives it to you.
Why not treat me
the same way?
I'm sure that
some part of you
believes this idiocy.
But you can't possibly
be stupid enough
to think that you can convince
any part of me.
And that can only mean
you're trying to sabotage
this relationship.
Why would I do that?
We're doing fine.
Because the next step
from fine is serious,
and you can't handle that,
so you're trying to keep me
at arm's length
with all this crap.
How about you?
I have been completely
open with you.
You won't let me
sleep over.
You basically haven't
introduced me to your daughter.
But do you want to
spend time with her?
Honestly...Before this,
I'd have said no.
But...Yeah.
How are we ever
gonna be a couple
if you keep hiding her
from me?
House...
I need to protect her.
I let you into her life,
and you go away...
Call it what it is.
I'm not the only one
who's holding back.
Hey, baby.
I am not getting mad.
I'm just trying
to understand you here.
There's no meeting
like you talked about
at Trenton General.
You see, it turns out that--
it turns out--
the turnout--
the turnout...
It's been turned...
Turn--turning...
What?
It's turning--
hey...
The turnout--
the turnout is turning...
You're going to burn.
[Breathing erratically]
What's happening to her?
[Muttering quietly]
(House)
It's hit her brain,
whatever it is.
Opacity in the left
temporal lobe.
It could be nothing.
Which would
get us nowhere.
So let's assume
it's something.
What kind of something?
Abscess.
Or lymphoma,
or wegeners.
We'd have to biopsy it
to be sure.
Any of them could explain
all of the symptoms.
You know, we're assuming
everything is connected.
Because it probably is.
But her delusions
are consistent
with mental illness.
Bipolar disease, for example.
She's 30.
It could he hitting her
right now for the first time.
So her mind just happens
to fall apart
right after her body?
Wow, I thought I was
having a bad week.
I know it sounds coincidental...
You know what, I'm back
to the Cameron theory.
That you hired
the dumb version of Cameron
so that you could fire her
and get revenge.
Give her a break.
Oh, you've switched sides?
Let me guess,
Chase represents
the dumb version of Thirteen...
I realized if we all
just keep pressuring Kelly,
of course she's gonna
get stuff wrong.
It's irresponsible of me
to let that happen.
You are a true leader
of men.
Get someone to cut
into her head
and get me a biopsy.
[Drill whirring]
Chase...
Just say "hold on"
next time!
Her temperature's normal.
So what. She was on
the cooling blanket.
We took her off
an hour ago.
She should be febrile
again.
Tell House one
of the patient's symptoms
just disappeared.
(Taub)
Could it be Legionnaire's,
and our treatment worked?
I wish, but no.
We've been hydrating her,
and there's still
no lung involvement.
So relapsing,
remitting fever.
Malaria.
Dengue.
(House)
Why wasn't she frozen?
This morning?
Put a healthy person
on a cooling blanket,
they'd be chilled
like a fine Chardonnay.
She's a nice warm Merlot.
98.6 all day.
I didn't want her to freeze.
So you titrated the blanket.
As her fever dropped, you lowered the power.
Exactly.
So it's been on
the lowest setting since when?
Yesterday afternoon.
Which means we could have known
that her fever was gone
yesterday afternoon.
(Taub)
The fever was brief.
Sounds like a reaction
to the medication...
The antibiotics.
Without vomiting?
When did she last puke?
Not since
she was admitted.
Two down.
Shooting for three.
(Benedict)
You're gonna turn
her pacemaker off?
You sure that's
a good idea?
Nope. But it might be.
No tachycardia.
There's only
the delusions left.
If they're even still there.
Maybe it is
a bipolar disorder.
She's female, she's 30--
it's not a coincidence.
You've gotta stop doing this.
But it could have been prompted
by the physical symptoms.
You couldn't be more wrong.
You've got the cause
and effect backwards.
Start her on haloperiodol
and lorazepam.
Give it a few hours
to take effect.
Call me when she wakes.
Still hallucinating.
Can you hear me?
What are you looking at?
The table, it's on fire.
If it was, think I'd
be able to do this...
Without screaming
for my mommy?
Thank you.
Don't be too impressed.
It's mostly the happy pills
you put her on.
But she can talk
to us now.
The obviously stupid lie
you told us
about your hospital records,
it turns out to have been
un-obviouslyn-stupid.
You thought you wouldn't
get caught
because you thought that
you'd be cured and back home
by the time we spoke
to the other hospital.
Because you knew
what was wrong with you.
Your doctor was treating you
with risperidone, right?
That's why you were
in Trenton.
You got the stomach pain,
you went to see him,
he wanted you
to taper off.
Her doctor's not in Trenton.
Not the one you know about.
If you haven't
figured it out by now,
your wife has a secret.
What the hell is he
talking about?
Is it about your ex?
The ex was not so much
a secret, more of a lie.
You weren't married
before, were you?
I'm sorry.
I didn't want you
to know about it.
Know--know about what?
(House)
She's sick.
She's been sick for years.
Maybe it put you
on the streets.
Maybe that's where you got
the broken bones.
She's only suffering
from one condition.
Everything else is
side effects
of the drug that was
treating it.
She stopped taking the drug,
the side-effects faded.
But the underlying disease
is still there.
Why don't you tell
your husband.
Billy...
I'm schizophrenic.
That's the kind of thing
that a recent
psychiatric resident
might have figured out.
What the hell am I
supposed to do now?
Nothing.
Her physical symptoms
are gone.
We'll put her on a different
anti-psychotic
for the mental ones.
You can take a nap.
This is not who I married.
Of course she is.
You just didn't know it.
I don't know if
I can stay with her.
Sorry, as your
marriage counselor,
I'm not allowed to talk to you
without your wife present.
Just--just tell me
how hard it would be
for us to handle this.
Medically.
Look, if you want me
to give you a reason
to leave her, fine.
Apparently you haven't
noticed,
but she's got a serious
mental illness.
It's too hard.
It's always hard.
Okay, so I made
a mistake.
Kelly will make
a fine doctor,
but she's not ready
for the team.
Up to you.
What?
You like her now?
Nope. But she got me
to the right answer,
which none of the rest
of you did.
If you want to give her
another shot, go for it.
Okay. I will.
Great.
It'll make it easier
for you to sleep with her.
Come on, why else would you
have hired her?
Th's not why
I hired her!
♪ At the end
of a long, long day ♪
♪ ♪
♪ come go with me
in the blue and the gray ♪
♪ there's no up
there's no down ♪
♪ and there's no way around ♪
what are you doing?
I got bored with the porn
on my computer.
You got any girl on girl
on girl on vibrating object
on girl stuff?
I wouldn't have to do this
if you gave me the name
of that physical therapist
you like.
You done with Brandi?
Ehh...Knobby hands.
I will get you the name.
Let's stay at my place
tonight, okay?
Will you get cable?
No.
Then we'll have to have
more sex.
Okay.
♪ When the well runs dry ♪
What are you doing?
Quitting before House
fires me.
Hold on.
We both know he is.
But maybe there's
a bright side.
What?
You really looked out
for me.
You seem like
a really good guy.
And...
I never date anybody
who I work with.
But...
Yeah...
Sorry it didn't
work out.
You want to get dinner
tomorrow night?
♪ See the sunlight combed
on the shapes at the freight ♪
♪ ♪
♪ at the end of the day ♪
♪ gonna get by ♪
♪ gonna get through ♪
You want some more meat?
This is meat?
Yes, please.
♪ There's no up
there's no down ♪
♪ and there's no way around ♪
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Come on, kid.
Come on, come on.
Come on. Come on.
Hey, hey, hey.
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
Aren't you adorable.
www.tvsubtitles.net