[Ominous music]
[Male announcer]
This election day,
the fate of our borders
is in your hands.
John moreno wants to invite
illegal immigrants
into our country.
He wants to give them our jobs.
He wants to give them
our healthcare.
John Moreno wants to give them
the American dream,
and he wants you to pay for it.
[People yelling]
Whose side is he really on?
[Beeping]
It's a valid question.
He favors easing restrictions.
So do I.
Shh.
Come on, Hal.
Your position on work visas
is irrelevant.
He's talking about
a path to citizenship.
I'm telling you,
this ad wins you the election.
By insulting one
of my core constituencies.
Come on, in '04
I had 45% of the Latino vote.
And this year you're running
against a guy named Moreno.
This isn't one of your races
in south Carolina
or Oklahoma, Joe.
This is New Jersey...
People vote for me
because I'm a moderate.
Well, that's great.
You can be the most moderate
ex-senator in the country.
Hal, the election
is seven days away,
and even our own internals show
you down six points.
We've always been the underdog.
And we've always found a way to win.
I know.
Because you have always let me
do what's needed to be done.
Now, I can have this
on the air tomorrow.
No, no.
Come on, Hal, let me do this!
No, absolutely not.
This could totally
galvanize the left.
You all right, Joe?
Yeah, I think I got
some kind of a rash.
What the hell?
That's not a rash.
Maybe I should call a doctor.
You better call an ambulance.
[Massive Attack's Teardrop]
Sync for www.addic7ed.com
(House)
Look at it like this...
Of all the ways to rupture it,
nothing honors
the real Achilles more
than blowing the dismount
on a keg stand.
What's that smell?
Is it onions?
Peppers?
Oh, I know...
It's a sausagefest.
Sausagefest implies multiples.
Now, if you're talking
about yardage,
I'd have to agree.
I'm talking
about your department.
You still haven't
replaced thirteen.
It's coming along.
You've had plenty of time
to find someone.
I've found plenty of someones.
Just haven't kept them.
It's time to end
the cycle.
Meet your new team member.
Her name is Martha m. Masters.
This doctor is not a doctor.
She's a third-year
med student.
She graduated high school
when she was 15.
She filled out the time
before med school getting PhDs
in both applied math
and art history.
She'll be incredibly useful
if my next patient
is an Escher drawing.
Those things
are seriously screwed up.
This isn't a suggestion.
Just because my sausage
has been filling your bun
doesn't mean you get to decide
what flavor chips I nosh on
during the day.
Nope, I get to do that
because I'm your boss.
Patient is Joe Dugan, 42,
political consultant.
Presents with palpable purpura,
and alt and ast
are through the roof.
Otherwise known
as rash and liver damage.
Fascinating.
Senator Anderson
sent this case to us,
and personally requested
we take a look.
That's reason enough for me.
Black guy campaigning
for the opposition?
Does Obama know about this?
I tried calling him
on the brother hotline.
He didn't pick up.
[Knock on door]
Martha m. Masters.
I'm Dr. House.
This is the rest of the team.
Boring, bimbo,
and bite-size.
Martha enjoys
quadratic equations,
Italian frescoes,
and her turn-ons include
learning to be a doctor.
Take a seat.
She's a med student?
Cuddy thinks
she's some kind of genius.
Say something brilliant.
Oh, I... I don't...
Capital of Azerbaijan?
Baku.
Year Beethoven died?
1827.
20th decimal of Euler's number?
Six.
[Masters giggles]
It's my favorite constant.
(House) She's like the
Internet with breasts.
Oh, no, wait...
The Internet has breasts.
(Foreman)
Our patient's liver damage
explains the rash
and cryoglobulins
we found in his blood,
but we can't explain
the liver damage.
Shows no other signs
of drug or alcohol abuse.
Now all we've gotta do is figure
out which one is bimbo
and which one is bite-size.
Also, which monster truck
won the 2004 thunder nationals?
Hep c makes sense.
Test came back negative.
Same for hep a and b.
The answer we were looking for
is Virginia giant.
Feel free to chime in
on either conversation.
Hate to steal the spotlight
from small wonder over here,
but what about toxic exposure?
Tetrachloroethylene.
Could even be pennyroyal
or sassafras oil.
Go to his house,
get me some chemicals.
You wanna stay on this team,
have an opinion.
[Car driving]
(Masters) Oh, cool!
Tudor revival architecture.
Steeply pitched,
asymmetrical roof
over the entrance.
But it doesn't have
the half timbering
over the facade.
Doesn't say anything
about medicine,
can't shut up
about architecture.
Great.
I know.
I don't know what happened.
Being around House...
He's such a legend,
he's so intimidating.
I'm not like that
around ordinary people.
[Chuckling softly]
Uh, not that you guys
are ordinary.
It's just that
he's so brilliant
and you work under him,
so you're not as imposing.
Um...
I'm gonna be quiet.
Good idea.
Dugan didn't give you a key?
If patients know we're coming,
they can hide something
relevant to their illness
intentionally
or unintentionally.
Their knowledge changes things.
Are you a vampire?
It's okay.
We're inviting you in.
But our patient didn't.
I can't do this, I'm sorry.
(Taub) Well, she's
gonna be a big help.
(Foreman) Yeah, what a rube
being uncomfortable breaking
into a stranger's house.
Part of our job description,
not the most morally
ambiguous part.
(Foreman) Give her a chance.
She's fresh, enthusiastic,
has no bad habits
we need to reteach.
She's a med student
with no practical experience.
That means every procedure,
every blood draw,
she needs one of us there
to supervise.
Is this attitude about her
not having an m.D.
After her name?
Because I wonder
if it has more to do
with her being a brainiac.
That's not it at all.
I'm not thrilled
someone else
might be the smartest person
on the team now.
I can only imagine
how you feel.
You're not smarter than me.
Oh, yeah?
You find this?
(Foreman)
A jug of unpasteurized cider.
It could be tainted
with e coli,
and that's what's causing
the liver to shut down.
E coli is found in animals.
So unless he's drinking
pork cider...
Pork cider!
I need the number
of the patent office.
There are indirect ways
of attracting e coli.
Masters refused
to go on the search with us.
Interesting.
Which raises the question,
what is your problem
with her?
He is intimidated
by her intelligence.
(House)
Why would that bother Taub?
He's been working
with people smarter than him
for a long time.
I think perky new girl
makes him feel old.
She's basically the same age
as thirteen.
Yeah, but she's a student.
Makes you contemplate
your med school days.
Back when you had hair,
muscle tone,
and no need
for a regular prostate exam.
Makes sense.
Just like e coli.
Orchards make cider
out of apples
they can't sell otherwise,
like if they've fallen
onto the ground.
Like, to some cow feces.
Which would mean
our esteemed patient
is literally
full of b.S.
Cool.
Go get the ingenue,
start the patient on aztreonam
and plasmapheresis.
[Loudly] He said to start
the patient on aztre...
[chuckling]
The cell sorter
separates the plasma
from the remaining
cellular components,
thereby removing...
the toxins,
antibodies, cryoglobulins.
I think we should
tell our patient
about breaking into his house.
Why would we do that?
Because the reason
not to tell him
was that he might
hide something.
And now that rationale is moot.
The rationale now
is no upside, big downside.
How can we ask our patients
to trust us
if we're not honest with them?
How can we ask the patient
to trust us
after we tell him
he can't trust us?
Fine.
Tell him.
Clear your conscience,
because that's
what's important.
(Dugan) Well, if you would
let me run that ad,
everybody would be talking
about immigration instead.
All right, look,
here's what we're gonna say.
Yeah, he was in Iraq,
and we're all grateful
for his sacrifice.
You chose to honor your country
through public service
and have voted 46 times
to expand the Pentagon's budget
for programs which, oh, by the
way, Moreno wants to cut.
All right. I'll draft it up,
send it over.
[Phone beeps]
(Masters)
You should probably slow down
until you're
out of the hospital.
It's a busy week.
Aren't you curious how we
came up with this diagnosis?
You're doctors.
Isn't that your job?
But how we knew
you were drinking apple cider?
Well, you had to have
found that at my house,
so I guess you guys
broke in there.
That doesn't bother you?
Medicine's like politics.
At the end of the day,
all that matters is results.
That's not true.
Respect matters.
Honesty
and integrity matter.
Have you ever thought about
running for public office?
Because I would love to have
someone like you
as an opponent.
Watch the replacement
fluid line.
Oh, right, sorry.
(Masters) You ever wonder
why American voter
turnout rates
are among the lowest
in the developed world?
Mr. Dugan?
What's wrong?
Can you hear me?
He's paralyzed.
Call foreman and chase,
get them down here.
[Beeping]
Mr. Dugan!
(Chase) We thinks it's a
transient ischemic attack.
The clot must have broken up
before we could find it.
He was temporarily paralyzed,
but he's regaining
mobility and speech.
(House) So, what causes rash,
liver failure, clots,
and the uncontrollable urge
to rat out your coworkers?
Oh, no, wait...
That last one was you,
not the patient.
I wasn't trying to rat.
I was clearly trying to honor
my ethical obligation.
Portal vein thrombosis
could be caused
by Wilson's disease.
Hooray!
You popped your cherry,
diagnostically speaking.
Unfortunately,
the first time always sucks.
Pitch doesn't make
any sense.
Dugan's cornea was normal.
You're obviously brilliant.
So why would you
hide your mind?
I was brainstorming.
I'm not talking about your
stupid ideas about the patient.
I mean your stupid ideas
about morality.
My stupid ideas are what
most doctors consider
the rules
for professional conduct.
What about
a neuroendocrine tumor?
Not without
diminished mental capacity,
loss of judgment.
(Taub) Disseminated
intravascular coagulation,
however, fits.
Rules are just helpful
guidelines for stupid people
who can't make up
their own mind.
You obviously don't fit
into that category,
so why put yourself there?
Masters is right
about a neuroendocrine tumor.
Because yes, Dugan has had
a loss of judgment.
He made this totally
inflammatory
anti-immigration campaign
commercial for Anderson.
It just got linked online.
(Foreman)
You're arguing Dugan's politics
are a sign that
he's mentally compromised?
No, his tactics.
(Chase) He's most likely
the one who leaked it
and all the commentators
are saying
and honesty's a great idea
until your patient asks
if her distended abdomen
makes her looks fat.
(Foreman) House, I hate to
interrupt your ethics debate,
but we have two solid ideas
on the table.
[Sighs]
Ct from his neck to his abdomen
for neuroendocrine tumors.
Run a d-dimer
and fibrinogen
for D.I.C.
(House) Masters.
If lying to a patient
saved their life,
would you do it?
No.
That's a lie.
If your grandma gave you
a really crappy tea cozy
for Christmas, would you
tell her you liked it?
Yes, but that's different.
So, you lie
when it doesn't matter
but you won't
when it does.
How'd you get so screwed up?
(House) How mad would you be
if I fired masters?
Very.
Unless you had cause.
Real cause.
Cause that a human being
would consider cause.
Never mind, then.
She's got principals.
She's like the love child
of Einstein and Mary Poppins.
Didn't even get
Einstein's hair.
It's worth having
someone on the team
who doesn't see the world
entirely as shades of gray.
It is gray!
To you.
[Elevator dings]
She has a fresh perspective.
Unless that threatens you.
It does not...
You thought
I'd get defensive,
keep her out of pride.
A girl can hope.
House, I gave this
a lot of thought.
She deserves
a chance.
A real chance.
House is gonna fire me.
No, he isn't.
Because you told him not to?
Butting heads with House
is par for the course.
House has strong beliefs,
and he respects other people
with strong beliefs.
It's not my beliefs
that are the problem.
It's my personality.
I'm not good at working
with other people.
You've been in there
for less than a day.
I wasn't looking
for encouragement.
It's a fact.
Growing up,
my whole life, really,
I-I spent
a lot of time by myself.
And no one in high school
wants to hang out
with a kid that's
three years younger than them.
And studying Anosov
diffeomorphisms,
determining whether
an unattributed landscape
is a blakelock or a ryder or...
I'm actually
boring you right now.
And yet you chose medicine
which is a team activity.
It's pretty gutsy,
stepping so far outside
your comfort zone.
I'm not trying
to prove anything.
I just wanted to be a doctor.
It was stupid.
Nobody can do everything.
I was vain to think
I could be the exception.
House doesn't care
if you're a team player,
or how ethical you are,
or how high your I.Q. Is.
It's all about the cases.
You help him crack this one,
you two are gonna
get along just fine.
(Foreman) We gotta give
masters some pointers,
help her figure out
how to deal with House.
Why would I do that?
The entertainment factor
is off the charts.
It's like watching
a bunny hop into a buzz saw.
Repeatedly.
And if we don't help her,
she's out of here.
No, something else is stopping
House from firing her.
I'm guessing it's his desire
to keep having sex with Cuddy.
(Dugan) You guys ready to
admit you were wrong yet?
Excuse me?
This tumor you're looking for...
you're not gonna find it.
My judgment
is completely sound.
So when you leaked that ad,
you were trying to torpedo
the senator's campaign?
All right, one,
I told you before,
I didn't leak that spot.
Uh-huh.
And two...
Whoever did leak that ad
had nothing wrong
with their mind either.
It's gonna save Anderson.
(Chase)
That commercial...
Everyone sees through it.
You're just trying to play
to people's fears.
You say fears.
I say rational,
protective instincts.
And judging by your accent,
immigration probably
isn't an issue
you can be
real impartial about.
I waited five years
to get my green card.
If there's anyone
who would resent
someone trying to skip
the queue, it'd be me.
Just because Moreno
favors amnesty...
He doesn't.
You know that picture of him
with the Mexican flags
that seems to be
from a pro-amnesty rally?
That's from an amnesty
international speech
protesting the imprisonment
of priests in Oaxaca.
Yes, you did just prove
that that ad
is even more disgusting
than you thought.
You also proved
that ad is effective.
You still think
my judgment is off?
Not anymore.
There's no sign
of a tumor.
That leaves d.I.C.
I'll go check how Taub is doing
with the blood work.
I guess when you
get on in years,
it takes a little longer to run
a few simple blood tests.
This whole "Taub's
an old man" thing
kinda rings hollow,
considering I'm in better shape
than you are.
Pass the dye.
You're in rounder shape
than me.
Tonight after work,
meet at the basketball courts
in the gym.
You do realize you're
two and a half feet tall, right?
And white.
And Jewish.
It'd be very embarrassing.
I get why you wanna say no.
Tonight after work.
[Beeping] Crap.
(Anderson) Did you hear
Moreno's latest stump speech?
He's gonna clean up Washington.
[Scoffs] Yeah, right.
Like any politician
from New Jersey
has ever cleaned up...
Who else knows
that you leaked that ad?
You and I had
the only two copies, Hal.
I don't care that you did it.
I just want to
make sure it worked.
This morning's tracking
has me within two points.
Told you.
We're gonna
pull this thing off.
Your blood test for d.I.C.
Came back completely normal.
That's good news, right?
(Taub) That means the two
things we thought it could be,
it's not.
We checked your home
for toxins and didn't find any.
But it's possible you might've
been exposed on the campaign.
(Foreman) Have you visited any
industrial or agricultural facilities?
There was a tomato farm
in Lumberton.
They take you into the fields?
No one wants a photo op with me.
I never leave the bus.
Were the windows open?
Certain pesticides...
Foreman.
What?
What is it?
It's not just your liver
we have to worry about.
Looks like your kidneys
are having problems, too.
So this guy spends
his entire life
campaigning against
bleeding hearts.
And it turns out he has one.
Bloody urine actually
is a renal problem,
not a cardiac one.
Yeah, if I say
something inaccurate,
assume it's for comic effect.
Then laugh,
because it's funny.
Ttp makes sense.
What're his platelets?
200,000.
It's not ttp.
What about henoch-schoenlein
purpura?
H.S.P. Doesn't cause clots.
H.S.P. Doesn't
usually cause clots,
but it can.
And the vasculitis
would explain
the kidney problem.
(House)
She can't diagnose a joke,
but she's making progress
on the patient.
We treat with chemotherapy
or steroids.
We treat with chemotherapy.
I said chemo.
Then you said, "or."
Once again,
the bunny meets the blade.
(House)
The road to dead patients
is paved with "or"s.
Chemo is the more
effective treatment
which means it'll confirm our
diagnosis more quickly.
I agree,
but there is another option.
There are lots
of other options.
There's bloodletting,
crystals, prayer...
Another medically accepted
option.
Which is both less effective
and less scary.
So the patient
might just choose it.
Unless, of course,
we don't mention it to him.
We can't withhold information.
If we explain
both the benefits
and the risks
of each treatment
I'm sure Dugan
will choose chemo.
Well, as long as you're sure.
The better option
is chemotherapy.
It's faster and more likely
to completely cure you.
I'll take the steroids.
Oh, my goodness!
If only someone
could've predicted
that you'd make
that incredibly stupid decision.
The nausea and fatigue
from chemo
will only last a few weeks.
Our poll numbers have stalled.
That's five days
till the election.
Doctor, can you
talk some sense into him?
Would that I could,
but ethics dictate
that it's his decision.
So all I can do now
is return to my office
knowing, even as my patient
endangers himself,
my integrity remains
unblemished.
Please.
Take some time
to think about this.
I don't need any time.
I want to start on the steroids.
Game to 11 by ones.
Uh, hold on.
Wanna shoot for outs?
You can have it.
[In feeble voice] One, nothing.
[White denim's I start to run]
You gonna guard me?
Can't hit two in a row.
♪ ♪
Two, nothing.
You gonna wuard me now?
You can have that shot all day.
♪ Daytime I walk street ♪
♪ daytime I'm walkin' street ♪
♪ I'm walking street yeah ♪
Three, nothing.
♪ Somebody's listening ♪
♪ I feel
like someone's listening ♪
♪ to the song in my head ♪
♪ I start to run ♪
One, three.
♪ ♪
[grunting]
♪ Whoo ooh ooh ♪
♪ ooh ooh ♪
♪ whoo whoo whoo whoo ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I start to run ♪
♪ daytime I'm walkin' street ♪
♪ I'm walkin' street yeah ♪
♪ I start to run ♪
♪ ♪
Ten, seven.
[grunting]
♪ ♪
(Taub)
Seriously?
You're gonna beat me with that?
[Panting]
Well...
I was wrong.
You're not so old.
Thank you.
Now all we have
to do is figure out
why masters is making you
feel insecure.
[Sighing]
I was just down
by Dugan's room.
They were ready
to give him the wrong medicine.
I tried to change the order,
but I'm not a doctor.
Good.
The wrong medicine
is the right medicine.
But he wanted steroids,
not chemo.
He wants to live.
I'm gonna tell him
what's going on.
No, you're not.
I don't mind your morality
in theory.
But in practice, you're risking
my patient's life.
So you're fired.
You think that's gonna
stop me from telling him?
If you do, I'll get you
thrown out of medical school.
I haven't done anything
that would merit that.
I know.
But unlike you,
I'm willing to lie.
(Foreman)
Firing her was a mistake.
We need someone like her
on the team,
keeping us all in check.
You're incapable of noticing
when I do something
inappropriate?
We're like the frogs who've been
in the pot for a while.
We're used to the heat.
Things have been just fine
without Pippi Longdivision.
(House) Your opponent's
out of the race.
You can drop
the smear campaign.
(Chase) Dugan developed
pulmonary edema.
It's not h.S.P.
(Foreman) Masters was right.
He didn't want the chemo.
He didn't need the chemo.
Masters was wrong.
He doesn't have h.S.P.
And masters is gone.
Could be an infection.
We had him on aztreonam
for the e coli.
He didn't respond.
Schistosomiasis wouldn't
respond to aztreonam.
(House)
That's a great idea
if he was running
a political campaign in Africa.
The guy hasn't been
out of the country in years.
Who needs to travel when
you've got a giant fish tank
loaded with tropical fish,
tropical snails
carrying tropical bacteria
like schistosomiasis.
Well, break into his home,
get me some escargot.
Unless you wanna
ask the patient's permission
as a tribute to the departed.
Need a minute.
You said you were gonna
give her a chance.
I did!
She used that opportunity
to endanger our patient's life.
By insisting he receive
the treatment that he asked for.
That's what I just said!
Your team is there
to challenge you.
I didn't fire her
because she's a challenge...
I fired her because
she's an immutable obstacle!
You gonna make me hire her?
How do you think
that'll work out?
He's right, I'll just...
You will not quit this job.
What is going on?
I want her gone,
she wants to be gone.
Why do you care?
You don't actually think
that she's a younger
version of you?
Because let me tell you,
you're not that smart
or moral.
Socially awkward, maybe.
She's a potential star,
and I want her in my hospital.
No problem.
Just find her
a different department.
(Chase)
I think I've figured it out.
Why Taub didn't like masters.
Now you're getting
involved in this, too?
My previous source
of entertainment just got fired.
Exactly.
She's gone.
It's over.
She's totally moral
and uptight,
which made Taub feel badly
about his cheating.
Can we get a move on?
(Foreman) You didn't like her
even before you knew
about her morals.
It's from the minute
he saw her.
So...
It's something about
how she looked.
All right.
No snails.
Let's get out of here.
Hello?
[Phone ringing]
Yeah. [On phone]
It's foreman.
What'd you find?
Nothing helpful, but...
(House)
There's gotta be something.
Dugan's going
completely downhill.
Now fluid's collecting
in his chest.
Where the hell are you guys?
In jail.
You gonna come bail us out?
(House)
Uh...
Kinda busy.
[Anderson on TV] Thank you all for
coming down here at this late hour.
I assure you
I will be brief.
There has been
a lot of discussion
about an attack ad that leaked
online earlier this week.
As I said many times
over the past few days...
There you are.
I was starting to think
that my holier-than-thou-dar
was malfunctioning.
Our patient's liver,
kidneys, and lungs are failing.
I need you to help me
figure out why.
As I recall,
you have three actual doctors
you haven't fired today.
They're in jail.
What? Why?
Prostitution.
So you're rehired.
It all started in the liver,
but where in the liver?
If in the ducts, then primary
biliary cirrhosis...
Yeah, I don't need
to hear your ideas.
Just return the volley.
Primary sclerosing
cholangitis.
Nope.
His vitamin a level is normal.
Gall bladder problems
can affect the liver.
Cholecystitis?
Shh!
He's talking about our patient.
Did you just shush me?
Shh!
And thought he was a friend.
That is, until...
He leaked this hurtful,
hateful ad.
I think he's lying.
Dugan said...
The technical term is speaking.
Dugan violated my trust.
And therefore,
I have no other recourse
than to fire him
from my campaign.
Thank you, and there will be
no further questions.
Thanks for your help.
Oh...
And you're fired again.
He screwed you.
(Dugan)
That was a hell of a move.
Use the ad
to shore up the base,
fire the extremist
to hold the center.
No, I mean
he actually screwed you.
Taking weekend trips
down to Bunbury.
He's got a red blotch
on his hand.
That's palmar erythema.
That, and the fact
that he's got
a permanent sheen
of nixonian flop sweat.
He's got hepatitis c
which explains
all your symptoms.
That's great,
but the senator and I
have not had sex.
Well, then the two of you
shot up together.
How many high-functioning
heroin users do you know?
Actually, quite a few.
Look, I know you've got hep c.
So either you shared
a bed together,
you shared a needle,
or you shared a straw.
I'm talking about coke,
not coke.
You can get hep c
from doing cocaine?
Look, I will deny it.
Don't care.
They tested me for hep c
when I came in here.
I don't have it.
Apparently your liver picked up
a few of your campaign tactics.
It's hiding all your secrets
by producing cryoglobulins
so the hep c tests
come back negative.
Now, I could look
for all the associated toxins,
but the plasmapheresis
got rid of those.
So basically,
you've got a disease,
but there's no way to prove it.
It's pretty cool, huh?
What is that?
This is interferon.
It delays the onset
of rigor mortis.
[Door slamming]
[Keys jingling]
When did your lawyer say
he was coming to get us?
He said,
and I'm quoting here,
"soon."
I know.
The reason you hated masters
from the moment you saw her.
Come on.
That was not
the first time you saw her.
That is brilliant.
It's really not.
Is that guy seriously
using the toilet?
Oh, my God, he's sitting down.
Don't try
to change the subject.
Did you sleep with her?
No wonder he's in jail.
Anyone who would do that
has no shame.
Or maybe he tried
to sleep with her,
and she shot him down.
[Sighing] I don't know her.
[Man grunting]
Is he grunting?
I think I hear grunting.
You realize
we're not gonna drop this.
[Man grunting]
I didn't sleep with her.
I interviewed her
for Hopkins med school.
So you're holding a grudge,
because she chose
a different school?
We talked for an hour.
She didn't remember me.
She remembers the 20th digit
of some math constant,
but she doesn't remember
a guy she had
a one-on-one meeting with.
Well, I barely remember you.
Mystery solved.
Now we can all
go back to our lives.
[Toilet flushing]
Great news.
I've decided to rehire you.
Find another sounding board.
Dugan's got hep c.
I'm not doing this.
He's not responding
to interferon.
You must think I have
absolutely no self-esteem.
Ethics and self-esteem?
You really are
a pain in the ass.
What treats hep c
besides interferon?
Now you want me to talk?
Yeah.
[Scoffs]
Come on, stop pretending
you're not gonna do this.
As much as you hate me,
you hate failing more.
I didn't fail.
You fired me.
Repeatedly.
But if you walk away now,
after I just rehired you,
that's quitting.
A German research study
showed that 15%
of patients with hep c
were cured
after contracting hep a.
Of course, other studies
have shown
that up to 85% of
doubly-infected patients
die very quickly.
So, in theory, if we can find
something that mimics hep a...
There's one thing
that mimics hep a...
Hep a.
Good work.
You're fired.
No!
Hep a could cure him.
Better chance it'll kill him.
Tell the lab to release
a hep a culture to me.
We'll see who's right.
It's not an approved treatment
and exposes us to liability.
There's no way
I can let you do this.
That's an extremely
cowardly position.
Listen to the genius.
You're the one that insisted
he run this by me.
It's proper protocol
for an unconventional treatment.
But we shouldn't compromise
patient care
just to avoid lawsuits.
What about the fact
that we don't
have any proof
he actually has hep c?
That is a perfectly
valid objection.
Don't listen to her.
She doesn't even work for me.
If you really think that this
is the only way to cure him,
I will risk the lawsuit.
But I need to know that he
actually has the disease.
Get me proof.
I've given you...
proof!
Get me proof he has hep c,
and then you can
give him hep a.
I can't.
You'll figure
something out.
The two of you have combined
I.Q. North of 300.
That's also true
of five morons.
Go. Work.
(Masters) So what do we do now?
Well, considering the fact
that I'm about to do
something unethical...
Oh, right, yeah...
I'm fired.
(House) Missed you.
We need a false positive
hep c test.
(Foreman) And why would
we want to do that?
The world changes
when you're on the inside.
You just gotta roll with it
once you get out.
(Chase) You think he
contracted hep c
from the senator, right?
Test Anderson.
If it's positive, that's
evidence dugan has it, too.
Evidence, not proof.
Are we presenting this
to a jury of our peers?
That should be enough
for Cuddy.
Should be, but it won't be.
(Taub) The test for hep
c is 99.9% accurate.
That means one
in every thousand tests
is a false positive.
We do enough,
maybe we get lucky.
I smell like jail.
False false positive.
That's the best we can do?
Okay, go do it.
I have a problem.
A medical problem
which could become...
I have lied to Cuddy
10,000 times.
How do you think she'd feel
about 10,001?
I think you probably
already know the answer.
But it doesn't make any sense.
You don't understand
why a woman might be upset
because her boyfriend
lied to her?
I wouldn't be lying
as her boyfriend.
I'd be lying as her employee.
That's not
how relationships work.
My patient is gonna die.
Does the lie guarantee
he'll live?
No.
You got two choices:
To be honest and face
the medical consequences,
or lie and face
the personal consequences.
Now that you're my doctor,
you, uh...
You can't tell anybody, right?
Who'd leak a story
about a sitting senator
who got hep c
from doing cocaine?
You didn't fill out
any paperwork.
I'm gonna run this test
under an assumed name.
Trust me...
No one will ever know
you were here.
Blood test confirming hep c.
He got sicker,
his viral load came up,
finally showed up on the test.
Thank you.
There was a time
when you would have
completely ignored my request.
That means a lot
that you respect me enough
to do this.
I've come a long way, baby.
Now, if you would only
hire a new team member.
I'm on it.
[Dishes clinking]
[People talking]
[Footsteps approaching]
How'd you like
to come work for me?
It's like I'm on
a mobius strip.
We've had this conversation.
You want this job.
[Sighs]
Prove yourself to me,
no more games.
At least,
the current game ends.
Others may start.
You have my
deeply-flawed word.
What do I have to do?
Get dugan
to let us give him hep a.
And while you're figuring out
the best way
to coax a patient
into a treatment
that has an 85% mortality rate,
here's some advice:
Don't.
I'm not gonna lie to him.
You have a math degree.
So let's see
if you can follow along here.
You lie to him,
he definitely consents,
he might live.
You tell him the truth
like last time,
he might not consent,
he definitely dies.
Remind me what's so wrong
about lying?
We're going to inject you
with hepatitis a.
That doesn't sound
like medicine.
I know it seems
counter-intuitive,
but in some people,
the virus can enhance
immune function
and clear out the hepatitis c.
Some.
How many we talking about?
A fair amount.
Give me a percentage.
What are the odds
of this thing working?
[Breathes deeply]
There is an 85% chance
that this will kill you.
(Dugan)
So, you wanna
give me something that works
15% better than arsenic?
Well, technically,
it works infinitely better
because arsenic has
a 0% ch... chance.
This is your only shot.
Both Dr. House and I
believe that.
He faked a blood test
in order to get you approved
for this treatment.
And then he tried to bribe me
into lying to you
about the risks.
If either of those incidents
came to light,
he would be suspended
and probably lose
his license.
Oh, I'm sure some other people
would suffer.
He's risking his career
to give you this chance.
He wouldn't do that
if there was any other choice.
I did it.
And I didn't have to lie.
And you feel good about that?
Yes.
So I'm hiring an idiot.
You can pretend
you wanted me to lie,
but you didn't.
You want the people on your team
to challenge you
otherwise you'd just be a bully
instead of a great doctor.
You hired me because I don't
compromise my principals.
Or I want a front row seat
when you wake up
and realize how useless
your principals are.
I don't want you
to just lie to a patient.
I want you to want
to lie to a patient.
It's not gonna happen.
See you tomorrow.
[Exhales]
I heard dugan is already
responding to treatment.
Yeah, his alt level is already
beginning to normalize.
I wanted to apologize
for the way...
Uh, wait...
You interviewed me, right?
For Hopkins?
Oh, my God, you're right.
[Laughing]
Wow, that memory of yours.
I wanted to say something
the first day.
I felt really awkward
about the whole thing.
Don't worry about it.
Is this grandma's tea cozy?
What?
Nothing.
I'll see you upstairs.
If I knew hiring her
meant dealing
with medical school paperwork,
I might've reconsidered.
You really got
nothing better to do
than watch me sign this?
And miss the ultimate admission
that I was right
about masters all along?
She had me when she
called you a coward.
You heading out?
I have to work late.
Gloating requires
a lot of paperwork.
[Smacks]
[Cheers and applause]
[Anderson on TV]
Thank you, New Jersey
for reelecting me
to the United States senate.
[Cheers and applause]
We ran a positive campaign,
a campaign about the dire issues
facing this great nation.
[Cheering]
There are many people
who gave their all
for this campaign.
But there is one person
that stands out among them.
My beautiful wife, Loretta.
Loretta.
[Applause]
Thank you.
Do you know where
the senator's records are?
House was treating Anderson's
campaign manager,
not the senator himself.
Oh.
Why did you think he
was the patient?
House saw him in the clinic.
I guess it wasn't medical.
When?
Friday.
Around 3.
House's team ran a hep c test
on Joe dugan on Friday.
Can you look up the time?
Chase, Taub, and foreman
were running tests all night.
All negative.
Positive test at...
3:17 P.M.
House ran it himself.
Is everything okay?
I don't think so.
Sync for www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net