♪ ♪
Move it!
Faster! Push!
- Quit slacking!
- I'm not slacking.
Is that how you talk
to your drill instructor?
Sir, I'm not slacking.
You stand up.
You look me in the eye!
I feel lousy.
I can't.
"Can't" doesn't exist here!
Now, you finish this course,
or you're in isolation the rest
of the day, you hear me?
MacDonald, you ready
to make Parks eat your dust?
Sir, yes, sir!
Ready, go!
Are your ears malfunctioning?
I said go! Go!
Go! Get down!
Get down!
Belly down!
Belly down.
Move it!
Get up on there.
You've gotta push.
Move it.
Don't you dare fall.
Grab the bars.
Grab there!
Move it!
Move it! Knees up.
Knees up! Move! Move!
Find the wall!
Hit that wall! Hit that wall!
Move it.
Get up on there.
Don't you fall on me.
Faster! Move it!
What's the matter, Parks?
You got a boo boo?
Sir, I'm bleeding, sir.
- Is your life in immediate danger?
- No.
Then you get your ass
up over that wall!
I said get your ass
over the--gaaa!
Aah...
What's going on?
My back hurts.
I can't move.
Help. Help.
I can't get up.
"Can't" doesn't exist here.
Get--
♪ I need it, I need it ♪
♪ I need it ♪
♪ House 7x10 ♪
Carrot or Stick
Original Air Date on January 24, 2011
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
♪ ♪
We should not be looking at this.
He sent out an alert.
It would be rude
not to look.
Though I am straining
my eyes.
What are we checking out?
Your profile page.
Why? I haven't--
that...is not me.
That is you.
That's me, but that
is not.
Whoever did this
made it smaller.
Much, much smaller.
Whoever did this has
a bone to pick with you.
Ironic, since
your bone is--
is not in that picture.
My proof is right here.
You really want to see it?
Oh, whoa.
Convinced.
You have any idea
who did this?
I don't even know where
the original picture is from.
The bathroom
at the Carlton Hotel.
The towel.
Hotel logo's reversed.
Shot must have been
taken in the mirror.
We were there
for Sanford Wells' wedding.
That must
narrow it down.
He slept with
three women there.
Oh, you're a whore.
♪ ♪
38-year-old former marine
came into the E.R.
with back pain.
Now his bladder aches
as much as his back
because he can't
empty it.
What are we looking at
this morning?
Up-skirt celebrity?
Endearingly funny cat?
Another study about
gays being better parents.
We were lured in
by the word "lesbian."
Has he taken any antihistamines
or anticholinergics?
Nope. And the E.R. ruled out
enlarged prostate,
stopped colon,
and spinal injury.
Military history--
in suspiciously good shape
for his age.
Makes a living
bullying kids.
I'm thinking...Steroids?
Fascinating.
Thanks.
We can wean him off--
steroids isn't fascinating,
it's moronic.
There's no other sign
of hormonal imbalance.
What's fascinating is
that you equate
discipline with bullying.
Which means that your parents
either disciplined you
too much or too little--
I'm guessing too little.
It's hardly surprising you agree
with our patient's philosophy.
You run your department
like a boot camp.
As if cruelty ensures
performance.
Oh, is this where I'm supposed
to disagree with you?
The diagnosis of urinary
retention depends on
the particular
mechanical cause.
We need to know if there's
a blockage in the urethra
versus a nerve or a muscle
problem with the bladder.
Fascinating...
Without misdirect.
Cath him and see
what's stopping him
from emptying his bilge.
Oh, not you, Chase.
Sending Captain Micropenis
to deal with
what is probably
normal-sized equipment,
it's too cruel,
even for me.
Good morning.
And what brings
the lesser Cuddy to these parts?
Pediatrician appointment
for an s-h-o-t.
Waldenwood insists
vaccination reports
go in with
the application.
Honey, finish
your oatmeal.
Waldenwood.
Is that by any chance
a boarding school
or a work camp?
It's our first-choice
preschool.
Blocks made of gold...
Kids don't have to pick
their own noses...
Great facilities
and teachers.
And they're known
for their gifted program.
You sure that's
the right place for her?
Sounds a little snobby.
I've done my research.
We visited.
It's a perfect fit.
You'll feel pressure.
I need you to tell us
when the urge to void
becomes unbearable.
Mm-hmm.
Sorry, can't make you
feel better
till we make you
feel worse.
I get it.
Goes for what I do too.
We cause pain
when it's the only option.
The kids I work with
at the camp are there
because a judge
sent them.
I can't teach them
good behaviors
without first getting rid
of all their bad ones.
That's not gonna happen
unless I push them.
I don't see why
metaphorical pushing
has to involve
actual pushing.
I may work these kids hard,
but I never hit them.
You march them into the ground
instead of knocking them there.
Yeah, well, it beats
the alternatives,
which is ending up in jail
or in a gang or...A coffin.
How often do you
pull that off?
Two-thirds
never re-offend.
That's better numbers
than juvie.
She's brilliant,
but new to the real world.
Yeah.
Hey, doc,
I gotta go.
Let's empty you out.
Take this urine to Taub.
Have him screen it
for bacteria.
I'll analyze this data.
Half hour on the phone,
no go.
Website won't take down the picture.
I thought their policy
doesn't allow nude photos.
Now tap the tube gently
against the table
to re-suspend the cells.
They don't.
Technically...
I'm no longer nude.
Maybe you should
shut down your account.
I tried, but whoever did this
changed my password,
so I can't even prove
it's my page.
Well, there's a clue.
She's got serious
text skills.
My password was "password."
You're a dumb whore.
Do any of the three seem
like a more likely suspect?
Maybe one was clingier?
I don't even remember
their names.
Listen, this is
a tough time for me.
Breaking up with Rachel,
moving into a hotel.
I want you to know
how much your humiliation
has eased my burden.
Urine is clean
for bacteria.
Not surprising, since
his bladder tests show
that his pain problem
is really a nerve problem.
Neurogenic bladder.
Could mean spinal cord tumor,
cerebral palsy.
House is gonna go
right for syphilis.
How can he be so sure?
Rare complication
of an embarrassing illness.
It's practically
a House special.
I want to get ahead.
Let's go test his blood
for syphilis.
Okay, I'm gonna take
some blood.
This will only hurt
for a second. Ready?
Stop it!
Stop trying to kill me.
Hey, let her go.
That girl was trying to kill me!
Let her go.
Security, get some help in here!
Let me go.
Let me go!
She's fine.
How 'bout we get back
to someone who isn't?
The patient's in restraints
and on Haldol,
- which seems to have made him lucid.
- Differential diagnosis.
Back pain, neurogenic bladder,
psychosis.
A symptom which we learned about
when he choked me.
Hate to slow us down
by acknowledging it.
And yet you have.
Tertiary syphilis fits.
The tests came back
negative.
Several meds could
cause those symptoms.
Tricyclic antidepressants,
ritalin.
Also other native plants.
Wormwood,
jimson weed.
The amount of jimson weed
or ritalin he'd have to ingest,
seems like he would have
mentioned it.
Unless he didn't know
about it.
Maybe one of those kids
at the camp
got tired of Driscoll's lessons
and poisoned him.
Go to the camp.
Check for potential
poisons.
I all but ignored
your assault,
showed you no compassion
whatsoever,
but you came up
with a good idea.
Score one for tough love.
Glad to hear you met
someone you like.
Weddings are good
for that.
I was hoping
to get in touch.
The thing is, I'm
a bit fuzzy on names.
Sorry.
Open bar.
She was sitting
at Dr. Simpson's table.
Brunette, purple dress,
low-cut.
That's my niece,
Winn Phillips.
Your niece?
Fantastic.
Her info is
in your email.
Also, there was a blonde.
Green dress.
You want me to hook you up
with two women?
Actually, three.
How do you cheat
on a test
when there's no test?
Sorry, not playing.
Go away, House.
I am not
giving you advice
just so you can
distort it
to suit your own
warped world view.
But it's been working
so well.
Cuddy wants to get Rachel
into Waldenwood preschool.
The problem is, Rachel's
dumber than a paste sandwich.
And her not getting in
bothers you.
You care about Rachel.
That was not advice.
Cuddy cares about her.
When Rachel gets rejected,
Cuddy will be upset.
And as the boyfriend,
I will be expected
to be supportive
and consoling.
Not your strengths,
I grant you.
Leave it alone.
It's just a play date.
It'll be fine.
Play date being
their code for
way to weed out
the paste sandwiches.
They'll hand her puzzles
and counting games,
and Rachel will just sit there
and eat the pieces.
Oh, crap! Crap!
I'm such a sucker!
Thanks for the advice.
That's the isolation area.
Kids who've behaved badly
go there,
sometimes 23 hours a day.
Sound like a pretty good
incentive to behave.
Yeah, by treating the symptom
instead of the disease.
Basic systems theory.
Troubled kids are produced
by troubled families.
This place doesn't even attempt
to change the environment
that damaged them
in the first place.
So there are no bad kids,
only bad parents?
Then why is my brother
an ex-con?
Treating kids decently
doesn't mean identically.
Some kids need more
structure or discipline.
Nobody needs this place.
Maybe we're coming
at this wrong.
We find a poisoner,
and let them point us
toward the poison.
Driscoll's got 24 kids
in his troop.
You want to interview
all of them?
Maybe we don't need to.
Driscoll sent me
to isolation all the time.
It doesn't mean
I poisoned him.
He's the psycho,
not me.
Tell 'em.
D.I. Driscoll's
way harder on him
than the rest of us.
Maybe because he's
a bigger pain in the ass.
What are you in here for?
Shoplifting.
You ready to upgrade
to second-degree murder?
Spend ten years in jail?
If he dies because of
whatever you gave him,
that's what'll happen.
That supposed to
scare me?
My mom's dead, my dad's
never been around.
And after this,
I'll get bounced
to another foster home.
My future's
not exactly bright.
Prison now or later
doesn't make that much
of a difference to me.
Dude, I'm not mopping
the whole floor by myself.
Your eyes are red.
Might be an allergic reaction
to the cleaning solution.
It's just my allergies.
Do you take anything
for them?
Not right now.
Why not?
These IV fluids will help
flush the drugs
out of your system.
You know which
of the kids dosed me?
It's not medically
relevant.
Look, I'm not gonna hurt him.
But I get why
you're scared of me.
I'm real sorry
about this morning.
No apology necessary.
You're ill.
You didn't know
what you were doing.
I used to be
a real screwup.
The military taught me
that actions
always have consequences.
Part of being a man is
accepting them.
And after all the times
I've said that to the kids,
an apology is necessary.
Are you okay?
My heart's kinda racing.
I got it.
Heart rate is 170.
P.A.T. until proven otherwise,
we've gotta slow it down.
Six milligrams
adenosine, IV bolus.
Tell the nurse to get in here
with the crash cart.
Pushing fluid sent his heart
into overdrive.
It took three doses
of adenosine
to get it under control.
Treating him for
antihistamine toxicity
revealed a new symptom,
Which revealed that
he didn't have
antihistamine toxicity
in the first place.
House, where are you?
Playground.
Great place to meet chicks.
Their moms too.
Tachycardia could be
a humoral effect--
mastocytosis.
We'd see other GI
or cutaneous symptoms.
Pancreatic insulinoma.
It would cause
bladder problems,
unlike pheochromocytoma.
Well done, Chase.
Now, turn off your phone.
You heard that?
It's on vibrate.
I'm assuming it's been ringing
almost nonstop since you
changed your status update
to "nothing lights my fire
"like a lady of size--
less than three bills,
don't bother calling."
Followed by your cell number.
No, no, no, you're right.
This is in no way clever
and hysterical.
Before you start rolling
anyone in flour,
work the patient out
for a pheo.
Adrenaline pituitary scans,
24-hour urine collection.
How soon after
the admissions session
did the child get sick?
The kid barely got home
before she collapsed.
Her parents are a wreck.
Desperate for answers.
Have you experienced
any symptoms,
or does someone else
oversee these sessions?
The teachers supervise.
No one's mentioned
feeling sick.
I'd love to call the family
and offer my support.
Sorry, I can't
reveal names.
Doctor-patient
confidentiality.
So this is where all the
admissions play dates happen?
She wouldn't have been
in another room?
This is where
we have them all.
Maybe, to be safe,
we get rid of these toys.
No, no, no,
don't do that.
I'll tell you
if anything's toxic.
For now, you should
minimize your exposure.
I'm supposed to be
supervised.
The scan is pre-programmed.
There's no risk
to the patient.
You're literally gonna
sit here, watch the monitor,
and chat with him
if he gets lonely.
Uh...Still.
Report me.
How you doing in there?
You shouldn't bother
trying to protect Landon.
I know he's the one
who drugged me.
The antihistamines aren't
what got you sick.
Doesn't change the fact
that he did it.
I tried everything
with that kid.
I just...
Can't break through.
It's clear you care
about him.
Have you tried
telling him that?
You gotta
understand something.
These kids, they're all
manipulators.
As much as I care
about all of them,
I can't--
I can't show them that
unless there's some
mutual respect.
Otherwise--
forget those other kids.
Think about this kid.
He watched his mother
get sick and die.
He's never known
his dad.
Who knows how long
it's been
since anyone's
taken care of him,
or if there's ever
been a man around
with any degree
of consistency?
I believe that
you're on his side.
I'm betting it would help
if he did.
You are a beautiful man.
Can I leave now?
I know where
all three women are,
but I'd like to avoid
the additional humiliation
of falsely accusing
any of them.
You I.D.Ed the hotel
off this.
I'm hoping there's another clue
in there somewhere.
We could enhance the image.
Maybe her face
is reflected
in that gleam
off your butt cheek.
Or maybe it's time
to chalk this up
to the hazards
of being a player.
Your zipper problems
just blew up your marriage.
Don't move.
Unlike me,
you've had the decency
not to cheat on anyone,
but you haven't been
giving much thought
to who these women are,
how they might feel.
Obviously,
you hurt one of them.
Emotionally, you hurt her,
because physically,
how would you even know?
Looks like your shorty
is a shorty.
You're early.
Dinner's not ready.
Oh...Okay.
Rachel and I will
go play in her room.
Really?
I'm hungry. Go cook.
All right, you little
lump of clay...
Rachel. Rachel...
It's a new toy.
What kid doesn't like
new toys?
A moron, that's who.
Okay, look at
the pretty colors.
Now, what color is this?
Hmm?
Orange.
Yes, that is orange.
What color is this?
Okay, blocks going away.
Bye-bye blocks.
Next time,
reinforce the levees.
Bad Corps of
Army Engineers. Bad!
What's this?
Rings!
Look at the rings.
Now, the goal
of this game is...
To not kill you.
Why are you here?
Wait, did you give me
an std?
No, I did not.
Don't deflect.
That picture was taken
by someone your height.
Just take it down.
What picture?
Fine.
Play it that way.
So, uh...
You really like kittens,
huh?
Yeah. You said
you did too.
No wonder you're pissed.
'Cause that is not you.
And I didn't take it.
Did you mean my height
with heels or without?
You weren't wearing heels
when we were in that room--
oh, yes, you were.
I started
to take them off,
and then you asked me
very nicely not to.
Why would I do this?
I mean, I'm not mad about
what happened with us.
Or apparently with you
and any other woman
at that wedding.
Sorry, I guess
my forensic analysis
wasn't as advanced
as I thought.
Wait. You know, you don't
have to rush off.
I still have those heels.
Everywhere you looked,
gingham and stuffed animals.
How did you
get out of there?
I didn't...
Right away.
Wasn't anything wrong
with her physically.
One down, two members
of the threesome to go.
You should flip a condom
to choose.
We checked his adrenal,
pituitary, and thyroid glands.
Monitored his catecholamines.
It's not a pheo.
We had to put him on
a diltiazem drip
to regulate his heart.
That means he's
running out of time.
It means you are too.
Your campaign
to soften him up
so he would go easier
on the kids...
All in a pointless attempt
to validate your own upbringing.
Another cardiac
arrhythmia?
Not our patient.
It's the E.R.
That patient
House admitted
with back pain
and urinary retention...
How do you feel about
a matched set?
We need to track
your common exposures.
What shampoo
do you use?
Whatever crap
the camp gives us.
Same here.
We need things
exclusive to you,
but not the rest of the camp.
Otherwise, a lot more people
would be sick.
Toothpaste,
deodorant.
Can't be deodorant
making him sick.
He doesn't wear any.
Smells like a--
park, shut your mouth.
You're not my drill instructor
in here, okay?
Doesn't mean
you get to be disrespectful.
I can do whatever
the hell I want.
You're not in charge.
There's gotta be a link.
Diet, sexual history,
drug abuse.
No. Believe me, I asked.
Those were some
fun conversations.
Do you believe the answers?
I know the answer to that
is always supposed to be no,
but I did.
Not like the kid has had
much unsupervised time
lately.
Delivery for
Dr. Robert Chase.
That's me.
The camp is in the woods.
There are tons of
opportunities for infection
that not every person
will pick up.
Legionelosis from water,
toxoplasmosis from dirt,
brucellosis from animals.
Too bad none of those explain
his symptoms.
"Casey and Sanford Wells thank
me for my extraordinarily
generous donation
to their wedding charity.
Aww.
Oh, God.
She must have gotten access
to my credit card.
Nocardia fits.
Bacteria lives in the dirt.
They both--
nocardia starts in the lungs,
not the bladder.
How generous is
extraordinarily generous?
Call the charity.
Explain the donation's
a fraud.
And take back Wells'
wedding gift?
You are extraordinarily
screwed.
Bushes can make a happy hunting
ground for ticks, lyme disease.
Neither of our patients
have a rash or tick bite.
40% of lyme patients
don't develop a rash,
and a bite is easy to miss.
Start him on doxycycline
for lyme.
$2,500?
Cancel your credit card,
find that girl,
and marry her.
Chris Stroud,
he approaches the 17th.
Stroud...
Go back.
That was Jersey Shore.
I'm not watching
that crap.
No, let him be
your Guinea pig.
You can dose me after
you're sure you're right.
The side effects
are fairly limited.
And it would be better
to treat you
before you develop
any more symptoms.
I want to wait.
I'm not your drill instructor.
Not trying to break you.
My only job is
to make you better.
I truly believe this medicine
is our best shot.
But whether or not you take it
is up to you.
Is there anything else
i can do for you?
Another pillow would be cool,
if you don't mind.
Hey.
Your turn to pick.
Ready, set,
feed the monkey!
Well, this isn't weird
at all.
She's got the fine
motor skills of The Hulk
in oven mitts.
Do you want a doodle?
Do you?
Feed the monkey.
Cuddy puts her to bed
at 7:30,
which cuts way into
our training time.
Play date's on Friday.
What is that?
Dog training clicker.
Gives immediate
positive reinforcement,
bridging the precious seconds
between desired behavior
and treat delivery.
House, she's not a dog.
It really seems
to be working.
Does Cuddy know
that Rachel's here,
and that you're turning her
into a schnauzer?
I told marina
that Rachel and I
are working on a secret
art project for mommy.
Which means that
some pedes patient
is about to be short
one art project.
The sacrifices we make
for our children's education.
Who's a good girl?
It had to be you.
I gave you my credit card
to pay for drinks.
And I gave it back.
I didn't take the picture.
Now go away.
Well, forgive me
if I'm not convinced.
You're obviously
pissed at me.
Because I thought
we totally had a connection.
And then when you didn't
ask me for my number, I--
a connection?
It was a threesome.
Yeah, but you were obviously
more into me
than you were into Nika.
Kenzie, honey,
you have a phone call.
Just a minute, dad.
I didn't want to
say anything in front of her,
but you could have.
You live
with your parents?
Just until graduation.
College?
How old are you?
18...Next month.
Relax, it's not illegal
or anything.
Look, I just need this
to stop.
Would you give it up
already?
I told you,
it's not me.
My parents won't even let me on
social networking sites.
Too many sexual predators.
Stop him.
Hey, hey.
Where you going?
Hey, you're sick.
You need to be
in the hospital.
There's a million hospitals.
Ones that won't send me back
to that camp!
Landon, what's going on?
Please, help me.
Don't send me back.
Those are my car keys.
You stole them out of my pocket?
No bad kids, huh?
Did you stop Landon?
Yeah, yeah.
What's wrong?
Oh, my legs, they hurt.
The muscles are in a vise.
What does it mean?
I'm not sure yet.
Ten Diazepam.
40 potassium.
The leg pain was caused by
a muscle cramp from low sodium,
which was caused by
kidney dysfunction.
Landon didn't respond
to doxycycline either.
I think we can
rule out lyme.
I thought I was
getting through to him,
and he just wanted
to steal my car keys.
If only his previous
behavior
had given you a reason
to expect that.
Why are you putting
hot sauce on a toy?
Maybe you don't care
if children chew
on your caterpillar.
I think it's wrong.
What causes kidney dysfunction
on top of everything else?
Arsenic poisoning.
And people do change.
Driscoll took it
to heart
when I asked him
to think about
Landon's history.
He was much nicer,
and then--
Wow, two ideas that
don't make any sense.
If it was arsenic,
they'd be puking and pooping.
And conversations
with moralizing strangers
do not make people change
their behavior.
Rachel is not gonna do that
more than once.
Whipple's could affect
the brain, kidneys, heart.
Not without G.I. involvement.
Why is it impossible
to believe
I made a compelling
argument, and he--
if he changed, it's because
something besides you
made that argument
compelling.
Compromised kidneys
secondary
to bladder issues
points to botulism toxin,
which lives in soil.
Got into the kid's bloodstream
through the cut
on his forehead.
Got into the drill
instructor's
through some abrasions
on his feet.
Good idea.
Give 'em both
the antitoxin.
I saw my chance
to get out of here.
I had to take it.
Don't make excuses.
You tried to steal
from me.
Oh, these kids are
manipulators.
You can't let
your guard down.
What do you mean
"all these kids"?
Don't lump me in with
the losers at that camp.
Seems like you
belong there.
It may be
your only chance.
Look, I've screwed up,
but I've never been
in trouble with the law.
You said you were in
for shoplifting.
Store owner caught me trying
to boost some chips and stuff.
Called my DCS caseworker.
I thought all the kids
were there under court order.
That's usually how it works.
So why is he different?
Why would I take
a naked picture of you?
You're cute,
but you're not that cute.
Now please go.
You're the only one left.
You're pissed off.
I'm pissed off because
you're in my apartment,
and my boyfriend might
be here any minute.
Boyfriend.
Last thing I want to do
is publicize
that I cheated on him,
so why would I prank you?
And where was this boyfriend
at the wedding?
Out of town.
Conveniently.
It's from my sister's
birthday last month.
And before you suggest
he's my brother,
note how I'm kissing him.
You used me, I used you.
It was a mistake.
Now I just want
to forget about it.
I just got off the phone
with Landon's DCS caseworker.
You were right.
I'm not what made
my argument compelling.
Where are we going?
To give your bladder
an antibiotic wash
to protect against
infection.
Who are you?
I'm Dr. House.
And that boy is the spitting
image of his mother.
Of course,
I've never seen her,
but his care worker told
my lackey
that you paid his
enrollment fee at the camp.
That could mean that
you're a family friend,
but then, why hide it?
The only person
who'd want to hide it...
Is his deadbeat dad,
who has decided not
to be a deadbeat anymore.
Please, don't tell him.
We spend days looking
for a link between them,
and he doesn't tell us
the kid is his son.
We were looking for
exposures.
He didn't think
it was medically relevant.
Soon, he won't have to worry
about his kidding finding out.
Being dead makes
keeping secrets much easier.
Neither one was responding
to botulism treatment,
and the boy started
having seizures.
And Driscoll might
have been right
that their biological
relationship doesn't matter.
Genetic illness emerges
when people are the same age,
not during the same week.
Unless there's a trigger.
Genetic conditions
can be set off
by things in the surroundings,
and these two obviously
share surroundings.
That's a relatively
rare phenomenon.
Which is our specialty,
I know.
Our patients are related.
That can't be a coincidence.
I just had an idea.
Relevant to our case?
No.
Sit.
Wegener's can be brought on
by exposure to heavy metals.
Did you see anything at the camp?
Near the isolation hut,
there were some old
generator batteries.
Could have leaked
into the soil?
Seems like someone else
in the camp
would have had lead poisoning.
You got anything better?
Treat with cyclophosphamide.
Go find your bliss.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have a play date.
Why didn't you step forward
when his mom died?
I found out she'd passed
months later.
By then, Landon was already
in the foster system.
I was figuring out
a way to approach him
when he got into trouble,
so I brought him
to the camp.
You need to tell him.
I can't.
Not now.
If I die, the only thing
I'll ever be to him
is the hardass who made him
run obstacle courses.
You'll apologize to me
for something done
in a psychotic state,
but you won't own up
to being his father.
What happened to
"actions have consequences,
a man accepts them"?
I'm in his life,
and I am working to get him
on the right path.
He doesn't need
a drill instructor.
He needs a dad.
It's so sweet of you
coming to this.
Just trying to be
supportive.
I've heard that's
what boyfriends do.
Hi, honey. Hi.
Did you have fun?
Yeah?
Rachel had a great time.
Played with everything.
She's a very clever girl.
I'm sorry to ask this,
but we've had some problems
with parents coaching kids.
Rachel caught onto our toys
unusually quickly,
and she even knew the game
was called "Feed the Monkey."
Uh, well, as eager as I am
to have her go here,
I promise you
I would never do that.
Hey, Rachel,
have you ever played
"Feed the Monkey" before?
No, mama.
She seemed so dumb,
but when the pressure was on,
she knew what had to be done,
and she did it.
You're pumped
'cause your kid lied?
She's not my kid.
She's a pain in the ass.
And she's a better liar
than you are.
You didn't cut your leg
getting into your truck.
The abrasion has dirt
and gravel in it.
A bit of fertilizer too.
Tripped in my greenhouse.
Growing my own
organic veggies.
Didn't ask.
Not gonna tell.
She didn't hesitate.
She didn't oversell.
Took me years to learn
how to lie like that.
And Rachel has it
on instinct.
Sounds like you're
real fond of that kid.
You're really not good
with nuance, are you?
I admire her talent.
I'm just gonna
numb you up...
I gotta go.
Latest kidney function test
shows no improvement.
Nice stitches.
Do they hurt?
No. They gave me
a shot of something.
That was Lidocaine.
It triggered an underlying
genetic condition
called variegate porphyria.
That would explain
their symptoms.
But I didn't
have any Lidocaine.
But you had a handful
of antihistamines,
courtesy of the deviant
in the next bed.
It's also a porphyria
trigger.
Wait, so we have the same
genetic thing?
Yeah...
Small world.
This is good news.
We can manage the condition
with hematin.
A liver transplant
could cure it.
Sometimes two patients share
one donated liver.
Would that work for us?
Possibly.
We'd have to test your blood,
tissue type.
And if they matched--
why would they?
Just because we have
the same thing making us sick...
Also...
I'm your father.
I don't believe you.
You don't think a white guy
can be a bad father?
Happy to check your DNA.
Do you really think he'd say
he's your dad if he isn't?
It's not like you're a catch.
You're evil.
Barely recognize you
with your clothes on.
You were at the wedding
with your sister.
Shared a room
with her too.
I came by to change
my shoes, and...
I found you
in the bathroom.
It took you long enough
to find me.
Because when someone
starts pranking you,
the logical suspect is
the overly protective sister
of the woman
you slept with once.
This has nothing to do
with my sister.
Then what does it have
to do with?
If you really have
no clue,
then you so deserve this.
All that creativity
and energy
you put into
pranking me...
It seems like you were
trying to make a point.
You really don't want
to tell me what it was?
You're a really big fan
of John Hughes movies.
You inexplicably prefer
Some Kind of Wonderful
to Sixteen Candles, though
that's probably because...
Mary Stuart Masterson looked hot
in those leather gloves.
We talked
at the reception.
That's why you hate me?
It was fun.
It was great...
Until I mentioned that
I don't sleep with guys
on the first date.
And then you said you had
to go to the bathroom,
and you never came back.
Actions have consequences.
Do you seek vengeance
on every guy
who acts like an ass?
Could be a full-time job.
When we were talking,
you seemed like a nice guy.
So either you're
a great actor,
or you're a nice guy
who lost his way.
Whatever the reasons,
a little negative reinforcement
seemed to be warranted.
Oh, currently, your password is
"great big ho."
Change it back to anything
but "password."
Hey, I'm--I'm sorry.
Let me prove it to you
by taking you out to dinner.
Followed by not
sleeping with you.
I'm serious.
Not on your life.
♪ all his life ♪
♪ owned by wildfire ♪
♪ like a spark ♪
We need to talk.
Nothin' to say.
♪ ♪
Okay.
I'll wait till you're ready.
You're my son.
I'm not going anywhere.
♪ ♪
Wait a minute.
What is that?
A doggy.
What does it say?
Ruff!
That's right.
Waldenwood called.
They love Rachel,
but they have no room.
Something about more
siblings than usual.
We should apply
next year.
She's a smart kid.
She'll be fine.
You mean that?
Yeah, I do.
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
www.tvsubtitles.net