♪ Bum bum bum bum bum bum ♪
♪ bum bum bum bum
bum bum bum bum bum ♪
♪ bum bum bum bum bum ♪
♪ Mr. Sandman ♪
If you're going to dress
like an Italian hooker,
at least let it be
this year's Italian hooker.
She's not telling us
we look fat.
That's a major
breakthrough.
If you didn't want
to be insulted,
you wouldn't have invited me.
Would anyone like
some champagne?
- No.
- Yes, three glasses, please.
Mom.
Yeah, it's not-- it's not even lunch.
If you'd prefer,
I'll make it a mimosa.
What do you think?
Perfect...
For a night on the town.
Perfect
for breast-feeding.
♪ Please turn on
your magic beam ♪
♪ Mr. Sandman,
bring me a dream ♪
My heart's doing
that weird thing again.
Beating?
That's normal for humans.
Come on, Lisa, take her
seriously for once.
♪
♪ Mr. Sandman,
bring me a dream ♪
♪ make him the cutest... ♪
What?
What is it?
I think we need to get you
to the hospital.
♪ Mr. Sandman,
bring me a dream ♪
♪ House 7x11 ♪
Family Practice
Original Air Date on February 7, 2011
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
I'm dying to try it.
- Is no one gonna tell me...
- Shh.
How delightful.
Why we're in the morgue?
House is on the lam
from someone.
Taub's got his money on Wilson,
but I'm pretty sure it's Cuddy.
Fool's bet. There's a whole
world of angry patients,
creditors...
She needs a doctor.
Yes, just not me.
Your mom is
a 65-year-old woman
with high
blood pressure.
- What about the macrocytic anemia?
- Borderline,
which is the lab equivalent
of imaginary,
which, by the way,
matches the rest
of her medical history.
You really think
she's psyching herself
into atrial fibrillation?
So get her a cardiologist.
You don't want me
involved.
You don't want
you involved.
All that ethics stuff
that I don't give a crap about
suddenly makes sense.
If you're
emotionally invested,
you cannot make
rational decisions.
You know this would be
a disaster.
This is my mother.
Treadmill test
went well--
no chest discomfort
or ischemia.
The abnormal rhythm
will probably resolve itself,
and if not, a daily pill
will keep it under control.
I will follow up
later today.
Is it connected
to my other symptoms?
Which other symptoms, mom?
Aye...
Not her fault.
This "Dean
of Medicine" stuff--
very impressive at parties.
But she's forgotten
how to be a real doctor.
It's all in my file.
There are 15 years
of clinic visits in this file.
I don't want to be
a bother.
But isn't this what
you do for a living?
So...
We're looking for a disease that
can last a decade and a half,
causes constipation,
diarrhea, flu, cold,
dizziness, rashes,
back and joint pain,
"heart feeling weird,"
"kishkes feeling wobbly,"
one actual hip replacement.
And which has eluded detection
by years of blood work,
X-rays, and MRIs.
Well, one thing does
pop to mind.
We'll monitor you,
and we'll give you
a thyroid test.
And House's team
will do a home search
for environmental toxins.
He seems to know his stuff.
How come he can't afford
a coat that fits?
No radon, no mold,
no lead in the pipes.
Yeah, yeah, great. Have you seen
Cuddy's high-school yearbook?
Okay, that is clearly
not related to the case.
There is no case.
Cuddy won't let House
see the yearbook,
so he figures
there's something to hide.
Any guesses?
It's clearly related
to being a giant
teenage dork.
So you thought I'd have
some insights.
Oh, no, no.
- I didn't mean.
- Relax.
I was crowned
homecoming geek.
I'm sure
you can relate...
Because you knew
some dorks.
I was the class president
and head boy at--
aah!
Oh...
Is that--
is that Cuddy's mom?
Certain parts of her...
And certain parts of some
muscular Hispanic gentleman.
Should we consider STDs?
I think I just caught one
looking at these photos.
What does "azarcon" mean?
I--
it means we might have
an actual case.
Mexican herbal medication
for stomach problems,
but only in the sense
that lead chromate is an herb
and poison
is a medication.
I'll start a chelation I.V.
Thank you so much.
That wasn't too much
of a disaster, was it?
You know...
That's not the only thing
they found in her home.
Not my yearbook...
Nope.
Just some stuff
that could cause
severe nausea and permanent
erectile dysfunction...
And which proves that
your mom is doing the help.
According to her diary, it's
some contractor named Jesus...
Which, granted, was originally
a Jewish name, but...
Go, mom.
So...
Why were you taking
a Mexican folk remedy?
A friend uses it.
A friend?
Mom...
Just for medical reasons,
you should have told me.
If you're sexually active--
at my age, he's more
the active one.
Mom's having a fling.
I know.
You do?
She's been giving me
lousy advice about it
for five years.
- I have physical needs.
- He's a married man, mom.
She doesn't want sex
with him.
I do want
to have sex with him.
Tell me,
who's being hurt?
Hold on.
Five years?
- Why didn't you tell me about it?
- I don't know.
We don't have
that kind of relationship.
Does that really
surprise you?
You said you had two guys
helping you move.
They couldn't get
out of work.
I'm trying
to economize.
This hotel's cheap.
Hi.
I'm sorry. I just wanted
to drop off some mail
and talk to you
about something.
Of course.
Rache...
Chris,
that's not why.
We got to move on.
What does that mean?
Have you moved on?
With who?
Is it Phil?
I don't want to talk
about this.
I know that you're worried
about money.
- You're trying to change the subject.
- Yeah,
which you
could have gleaned
from, "I don't want to talk
about this."
I got you a tryout
to be a part-time medical
consultant on lawsuits.
Wait, with your brother?
Have you completely forgotten
the last time I saw him?
That was five years ago.
Jamie had just found out
that you'd been cheating on me
with your partner's
daughter.
It's a little overreaction.
My--
he broke my nose
and then called me
the most horrible person
he's ever met.
He shouldn't have broken
your nose.
You know, texts,
calls, and emails
all go to the same magic device
these days.
You only got to send one.
Then it's even weirder
it took you so long
to get down here.
Yeah, that's
a crazy mystery.
It's not like I got
a department to run.
This other magic device
tells me that lead poisoning
wouldn't cause all my symptoms.
True.
But it could cause
the 5% that are real.
You think
I'm a hypochondriac?
Well, let me answer this way--
maybe you're imagining
that I think
you're a hypochondriac.
Look, my hand
just started to shake.
It's a side effect
of these arthritis pills.
Read the label.
I did...
When I was typing it up,
right before I slapped it
on a bottle of sugar pills.
You printed
a fake label...
Just to prove
I'm a hypochondriac?
Did it work?
It got you fired,
you schmuck.
An hour to convince her
to go with Dr. Kaufman,
and only then because
he runs internal medicine.
She wanted to leave
the hospital entirely.
My God, a woman
getting better
wants to leave
the hospital?
If she's getting better,
it's not because
you made her feel like a fool.
It couldn't be more because.
If I hadn't,
she'd have diagnosed herself
with six new forms
of cancer.
She'd never leave.
It's hard enough dealing
with my mom being sick.
This juvenile--
Yeah?
Lisa, it's gonna be okay,
but she's in a-fib at 170.
Oh, God.
I think we should cardiovert
while she's unsedated.
I'll be right there.
A-fib's at 170.
Wait.
I'm sorry she's sick.
I'm not sorry
I'm off the case.
You're not off the case.
You don't think
you can convince her--
no, no.
You are staying on.
She just can't know
about it.
Top of the morning,
Dr. Kaufman.
Here's the deal.
You copy me
on all the imaging.
- I'll have my guys run the lab tests.
- No.
I thought you spoke
to Cuddy.
Yeah. Then I spoke
to the elder Cuddy,
who specifically requested
you not be involved.
Listen, Kauffy,
you are perfectly competent,
bordering
on good, even.
But you know I'm better.
If you want,
we can pretend it's 'cause
I got a team
and more resources.
Either way, it'd be crazy
to ignore my advice.
It's not gonna stop
at advice.
You're gonna start
cutting me out,
go behind me
to your girlfriend.
And if something
goes wrong,
still me standing up there
alone at the M&M.
Please...
Stay away
from my patient.
Which button?
The one by your right hand
with the design of the bed
next to it and the arrows
pointing up or down.
You bugged the room?
I absolutely,
without apology, will admit
that someone may have
allegedly done so.
Guess we can pass
unethical
and skip straight
to illegal.
Not according to the recent
Supreme Court case
of bite versus me.
Dr. Kaufman's single.
Did you know he went
to Harvard Medical School?
Mom, stop yenta-ing
for one minute!
If you want gloomy
and unable to commit,
then stick
with the goyishe one.
This is completely unethical.
Why are we listening to this?
I know I'm a pain,
but it's impossible
for me to work with you
if you-- fine, fine!
Instead of a live stream,
I'll get a recap from Cuddy
20 minutes later--
thank you for saving America.
Could be leukemia.
Anemia from
taking over the marrow,
a-fib from infiltrating
cardiac muscle.
Sounds good.
Yeah.
I was really hoping
for a different diagnosis--
one that Kaufman hadn't
already come up with.
He just started
a bone-marrow biopsy.
So we don't need to do anything.
I don't.
You do. Go to admitting.
Find us a new case.
Psst! Whaa!
Ddx.
Um, we just did it.
No, we just did
the fake one.
Why do you think I let the
truth fairy know about the bug?
I was testing her.
She failed.
She's still a narc.
Thiamine deficiency
fits better than leukemia.
You think she's
an alcoholic?
I had dinner with Arlene.
I mixed her a gin and tonic.
And I'd run
out of the tonic,
so I substituted
sleeping pills.
Next morning,
she assumed
the blackout was
from the drinking.
How many old ladies are used
to passing out from boozing?
The answer is the boozers.
We're gonna have to slip her
the thiamine pills.
We've got to run this
by Cuddy.
Why do you think
I'm in such a bad mood?
Alcoholic?
Treatment's very easy,
safe.
It's literally
a few vitamin pills.
It'll fix her heart,
and it won't interfere with
the biopsy Kaufman's running.
Put 'em
in an antacid bottle.
Just tell her
it's for stomach problems.
I have to ask her
about this.
Of course.
Absolutely.
You'll ask.
She'll deny.
You'll push it.
She'll get offended.
You'll be exactly
where you are now,
except it'll be
harder to treat.
You've absolutely
got to do that.
I don't think
she'll lie to me.
She just spent
the last five years
going south of the border
down Mexico way.
We have our issues,
but since dad died,
we tell each other the truth
when asked directly.
It's important to us.
Addicts lie.
Can I speak
to mom alone?
Why?
You're scaring me,
Lisa.
Mom, I think your drinking
is causing your heart problems.
Is this about the champagne?
She ordered--
patsy and Anne
told me last week
you lost control
at the museum luncheon.
You're talking to my friends
behind my back.
We are all concerned.
Just tell me honestly...
How much have you
been drinking?
I may be your patient,
but I am still your mother.
And I'm telling you
I am not a drunk.
Okay.
For your stomach pains.
If something like that
comes up again, just...
Do what you need
to do.
And keep you out of it?
Yeah.
I am being a coward,
which is exactly why
doctors shouldn't treat
their own families.
Congratulations.
You were right,
as usual.
The hitting you
was not optimal.
I was going through
my own divorce at the time.
I have had years
of therapy.
Now when I get mad,
I do some deep breathing,
squeeze my stress ball.
Hey, I kind of
deserved it.
That's for sure.
Here's the deal.
I do a lot
of med-mal insurance.
I need a new
non-testifying expert.
I'll give you one case
as a tryout.
You kick ass,
I put you on retainer.
Average 15 hours a week,
it's 50 a year.
50 what?
You kidding?
$50,000.
I'll take it.
You drive a soft bargain.
You got to sign
an N.D.A.
Sure.
Is this...?
Uh, that's a case
I'm about to settle.
I rep a giant
pizza-delivery company.
Driver hit that kid,
messed up his legs.
And gave him a microbleed
in his brain, right?
What? No.
This little white mark.
Your predecessor checked,
so did the kid's doctors.
I don't know what that is,
but he's fine.
Probably.
But if there's any doubt--
it's a
multimillion-dollar case.
We're settling
in two days.
Lay off it, okay?
Okay.
You're right.
I'm off.
She spiked a fever.
It's 102.
That means I was wrong
about the thiamine deficiency.
You were wrong
about the alcoholism.
True dat.
It's actually looking
more and more like leukemia.
Kaufman rushed the biopsies.
It's not cancer.
So there's
a bright side...
Kaufman was wrong too.
Ddx.
Okay...
What disease can turn
Cuddy's mother
into a coma patient
named Stewart?
Lupus?
We got fired from that case.
We're moving on.
We were already fired.
By the patient.
This time by Cuddy,
so it's real.
She somehow realized that
her completely unworkable system
was completely unworkable.
Okay, pop quiz,
hot shots--
I chose vegetable stew
for a reason.
You got 60 seconds,
no "hintsies."
You're not gonna
talk to us?
Exactly.
You're gonna have to--hey!
You're good.
So this is just a test?
Pupils fixed and dilated--
an addict,
found with an empty bottle
of phenobarb next to him.
How is this a mystery?
It's an overdose.
Glutethimide!
Script filled last year.
Could mimic fixed and dilated
without the brain death...
Except he'll just get better
on his own,
so why would you take
this case?
Because House doesn't care
about the treatment
as long as the case
is interesting.
I'll do a blood draw
and put glutethimide
on the tox screen.
Really?
You thought that case
was interesting?
Oh, guess we're still
on Arlene.
Aren't there other ways
of keeping Masters occupied?
Not according to my
sexual harassment seminar.
Maybe it's not hypochondria.
She said she gets
a lot of rashes.
Add the fever--
sounds like
autoimmune, S.L.E.
Congratulations,
you can think exactly like
a semi-competent
internist.
Kaufman's starting her
on prednisone.
But the heart problems
were first.
Endocarditis.
With no murmurs?
It's usually a late sign.
Echo showed
pristine valves.
Below the resolving
threshold.
Kaufman's prednisone
will suppress her
immune system--could kill her.
You got to tell him
it's endocarditis.
Check the wiretap.
His I.D. guy's been putting
the same argument to him.
He can't convince him.
You think I got a better shot?
So what do we do?
We switch her meds.
We get a solution
of broad-spectrum antibiotics,
stick it in an I.V. bag
marked for prednisone.
Kaufman can only be there
a few times a day.
Tell Arlene you're from
the pharmacy, switch 'em out.
This is nuts.
This is way too complicated.
It's hanging an I.V. bag!
If the attending
doesn't know what she's on,
the risk of drug reaction--
What risk?
We know how he's treating her.
We bugged the room.
This is not
about information!
We're talking ethical
and legal violations
on a scale that should make
even you puke!
She's dying! That doesn't
mean we should all go to jail
to save her!
You're losing control
because...
This is your
girlfriend's mom.
You gonna run this
by Cuddy?
No.
She said to
keep her out of it,
do what we need to do.
Look, I know
what I'm suggesting
is completely screwed up.
That's because
this situation
is completely screwed up.
Do it, or you're fired.
We stick together,
he can't fire all three of us.
Give me a prescription pad.
Why are you doing this?
Because I think
it's endocarditis,
and I think the prednisone
will kill her.
Now, I forgot
my prescription pad.
Am I a horrible person?
I used to win awards
for volunteer work.
I went to Guatemala
and fixed cleft palates.
Now we're sitting back
letting Chase
do our dirty work.
We're doing the right thing--
stay out of it.
I don't know.
I don't know
about anything anymore.
Then this thing with the kid,
Rachel's brother--
stay out of that too.
A--radiologists--experts,
unlike you--said no bleed.
B--you yourself said
it's probably not.
C--you've got
no doctor-patient relationship.
D--you'll lose
your consulting job.
E--your ex will kill you.
F--I'm running
out of alphabet here.
You do it?
Had the bag,
walking towards the room,
and Cuddy's sister says,
"hey, Dr. Chase."
I met her at
that charity event last year.
One of you two
has got to do this.
I met Arlene
at the same benefit.
Conveniently.
Come on, don't ask me.
I don't even know
if I believe it's endo--
Damn it.
It's Rachel's brother.
He wants me to check out
some new case.
Conveniently.
It's a tryout.
I need this job.
I got to do this.
So you're just gonna
ditch us, run off,
and work
on some other case?
Are you Timothy's mom?
Yeah.
My name is Christopher Taub.
I'm a doctor
at Princeton Plainsboro.
I saw your son's file.
I think he might have
a very small bleed in his brain.
Wait, you--
you saw his file?
H-how do you even know
who we are? I--
your son could die
of a brain hemorrhage.
He needs a cerebral
angiogram today.
Get in your car and meet me
at the hospital.
Timothy, we're gonna go see
the doctor.
Another pop quiz.
How many idiot doctors
does it take to switch an I.V.?
The longer we wait,
the more the prednisone
is gonna kill her immune system.
Forget playing pharmacist.
Mom naps every afternoon.
Wait by the room.
When she falls asleep,
get the sister out somehow.
Hi, Dr. Cuddy, is now
a good time to talk?
Not really.
So, um, you know
how you had us consulting
and then stopped
having us consult?
Why are you still here?
Um, well,
I think the stopping
might have stopped.
House put me
on this weird case
where there's
no treatment--
I think maybe
to distract me.
Uh, and they've been
acting odd.
I'll look into it.
Thank you
for coming to me.
Because I'm--I'm worried
that he's switching
your mother's medications.
I checked
with the pharmacy--
Dr. Chase got prednisone
and antibiotics
for my coma patient,
which wouldn't treat him,
but could treat conditions
that cause...
Heart failure.
You told me to keep you out
of it, do what I needed to do.
What the hell
did you think that meant?
I meant, like, if you had
to slip her
a few more vitamin pills
or something.
This is life-threatening!
It's illegal.
I wasn't expecting
something like this.
Only because you intentionally
weren't thinking about it
'cause you don't want to make
any tough decisions.
Are you completely sure
it's endocarditis?
That's not
a real question.
Endocarditis fits
better than the alternatives.
We're having a little trouble
hanging the right I.V.
The fastest way is
with you help.
Where'd Julia go?
She's got a family.
I've got a family.
Three kids and a husband--
that's a family.
You were always tougher
on me than Julia.
Why is that?
I'm not.
I was thinking
about when you made me run
for yearbook editor--
I didn't want to.
I didn't have a social life
my whole senior year.
You let Julia do
whatever she wanted.
We're debating
12th grade now?
Like anything's changed.
What do you want, Lisa?
Do you want to hear
I love you both the same?
Of course I do.
Okay.
But times like this,
when we argue,
it reminds me...
I have more in common
with her.
She's nicer to me.
I love you both...
But I like her
more than you.
I called you three times.
My phone wasn't exactly on.
I figure I'll be getting
some angry calls
once radiology sends back
the angiogram.
They already did.
Here...
This is what you saw.
It's an anatomical variant
of the skull--
the bone in proximity
to a blood vessel.
There was nothing wrong
with him.
That was reason "g."
That's good news
for him.
Lungs clear?
Diffuse wheezing,
tightness, pruritis.
It's an allergic reaction.
Looks like.
Doesn't make any sense.
She's on prednisone.
How could she get
an allergic reaction?
I switched out
the antibiotics,
put her back on prednisone--
her breathing's normal.
But the a-fib's back,
and her fever's up.
Allergy's got to be due
to our antibiotics.
Does Kaufman
know what we did?
That's good.
No, that is terrible!
He doesn't know that
she got worse on antibiotics,
so now he's thinking
endocarditis.
He'll put her back
on the antibiotics
that almost suffocated her.
What do we do?
We push through this.
It started in the heart.
Endocarditis still fits.
It's just got
to be fungal.
We have to switch
Kaufman's antibiotics
for amphotericin "b."
I don't know if you're right.
I don't care.
But we are gonna end up
killing this woman
if we keep confusing
her attending
with these secret meds.
I don't care about confusing the attending!
I want this woman--
we're not talking about
simple antibiotics anymore.
Amphotericin "b"
is dangerous in itself.
It's a poison.
That's why it kills fungi.
It'll give her fever, chills--
which she already has,
which will help us
hide it.
I don't think I can take
a risk like that.
Well, then you shouldn't
have let her fire me!
Look, all you have to do
is switch the I.V.s again.
This has blown up on you
once already.
- He's right.
- Yep.
I'm so sorry
I got you guys into this.
You should go.
I'm right.
I know.
And I'll do it, but--
I agree.
Fungal endocarditis fits.
But we still have
to tell your mother.
I don't want to tell her,
not at all.
But the patient
is the highest priority.
I'm kicking you
out of your office.
Yes, you.
This is not her office yet.
If you tell anyone,
I will get you thrown
out of med school,
and I will destroy
your career.
I've thought about that.
Lying about me...
Won't work.
Everybody knows
your reputation.
True...
But I won't have to lie.
Buried in your coma patient's
big, big file
is a form
that doesn't allow treatment
without the expressed
consent of the relatives.
Wait...
You drew blood.
And that's not just
a screwup.
It's criminal assault.
But you told me--
No. As you may recall...
You set me up?
Why?
Because this patient
is the highest priority.
You made her think
I was hiding her son
being sick!
She scuttled the settlement.
She reported me to the bar.
I got to deal
with that crap now.
I will sue you for slander,
for tortious interference,
and anything else
I can use to destroy you.
Oh, and my sister says
stay out of her life...
You failure.
Five years of therapy.
Dr. Kaufman?
I need to speak with you
and the patient alone.
I'm skipping
the credentials committee.
I'm going straight
to the state board
and reporting you for--
what you've done is
so off the spectrum,
I don't know there's
a specific name for it.
I think he's talking
to you.
Marty, calm down.
And you--what you did
is worse.
He's an insane lunatic.
You're the Dean
of Medicine!
I want you off my case.
That's exactly right.
Don't get excited.
You're fired too.
What? I'll never get away
from House or my daughter
if I stay here.
Transfer me
to Princeton General.
Mom...
You're very ill,
and you're very angry.
You really think now
is the right time
to make a decision like this?
You lied to me
and betrayed me.
Do you think
I really care
what you consider
a good idea anymore?
I'll get the ambulance.
Happy?
I can't believe it.
What just happened?
You just killed her.
Are you blaming me?
This is all because
you're so arrogant,
you goaded her
into firing you!
Actually, my mistakes started
a little after that,
when I agreed
to your brilliant scheme
to keep me on the case
after she'd fired me off it.
She would have left
the hospital.
Only 'cause you would have
let her, like you did just now.
You think
I can control her?
I don't know.
I've never seen you try.
I have been rebelling
against this woman
my entire life.
Here's what I've seen.
She insults you,
you complain to me.
I drug her at dinner,
you never let her know.
We slip her medicine,
happens behind her back.
You never confront her...
And it pisses me off.
Are you taking this
personally?
She leaves, she dies.
One day...
Maybe a week from now,
maybe a year from now,
you're gonna decide that
the man sleeping next to you
killed your mother.
Get me my patient back.
This is really bad, Lise.
I swear to God, Jules,
I will call security!
I asked you before
why you were tough on me.
I wasn't.
You were.
And I know why.
You see something in me
that you didn't see in Julia
and you didn't see in you--
a type of ambition,
a type of brains.
That's why you rode me.
You made me yearbook editor,
summa undergrad,
A.O.A. in med school.
The only time I ever see light
in your eyes
is when you hear me talking
about my job.
The reason you keep coming
to see me in the clinic
is because you trust me.
You trust
my medical judgment.
So here it is.
If you transfer
to Princeton General,
you'll be treated well,
and you'll die.
If you stay here
with House,
you'll be treated badly,
but you'll live.
I don't care if I have
to slash the tires
of every ambulance
in this bay, mom.
I am not letting you
leave my hospital.
One, two, three.
I got it.
How you feeling, mom?
I feel a little dizzy.
Your heart's still weak
from the infection.
We'll hang
an antifungal I.V.
If you're so great,
how come you're not running
your department anymore?
What are you talking
about, mom?
That's what he told me.
Two days ago,
I said that I didn't have
a department to run.
I was being sarcastic.
No, you weren't.
Right, because people
who are talking
can't tell if they're
being sarcastic.
That doesn't make any sense.
Of course they can.
But you weren't.
I love A-Rod.
He's so modest.
And I highly respect
the paintings he has
of himself as a centaur.
Question--
do I like A-Rod?
Yes...
Whoever he is.
She can't recognize
sarcasm?
Deficit in the right
parahippocampal gyrus,
which means CNS involvement
before the fever.
I was wrong
about the endocarditis.
I-I don't--
I don't feel--
Mom? Mom!
Heart rate 170.
Nurse!
Do something.
I am.
House!
The fever was hypothalamic.
That means brain, heart,
anemia, allergy.
You hear that, what do you think?
I don't know.
You think heavy-metal toxicity.
It can't be.
You treated with chelation for lead.
She got better, then she got worse.
She never stopped
being poisoned.
What are you doing?
You really want me to stop and explain?
There it is.
Look at that.
The muscle's black.
Necrosis?
Metallosis.
Her artificial hip
"weared and teared"
way too much.
It's cobalt poisoning.
We need Chase
to get an O.R.
I'm gonna start
chelation again.
I thought you didn't want
to see me.
I didn't.
Foreman called me.
I didn't know
that you thought
that little boy had
a bleed in his head.
I will kill my brother
if he messes
with you anymore.
What do you care?
Chris...
You were
a crappy husband...
But you are
a good person.
Once again,
you are unfired.
Why?
You sold me out
even though you knew
that you were gonna get thrown
out of med school.
That's just...
Kind of impressive.
I keep my job
if I stand up to you.
I keep it if I don't.
I...
Don't buy it.
When Cuddy
was protecting me before,
she was protecting
a doctor.
She's now protecting
a boyfriend.
The hospital's not gonna
put up with that for long.
So I need you
to protect me
from doing something
Cuddy will regret.
See you bright
and late tomorrow.
♪
Mom...
Why would you want
to keep this?
So I can mount it
on the wall,
like a moose head.
It says here
cobalt can cause rashes,
dizziness,
and stomach problems.
You still think I've been
imagining the whole thing?
Okay, you might have
a point.
How do you feel?
You know,
a little dizziness...
Some pain.
♪
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
www.tvsubtitles.net