House?
Oh! My God!
What the hell?
Gotcha.
Did you actually
wake up early
and hide under the bed just
to scare the crap outta me?
Set an alarm
and everything.
It's like dating
a ten-year-old.
God, I hope not.
Now that we're down here...
Hold that thought.
Seriously?
I have to pee.
I'll wait.
I brought a book.
I didn't know what time
your alarm was set for.
House?
You know, you can rent
this space out down here.
In Japan,
that would be like a deluxe--
House, shut up.
There's blood in my urine.
d House 7x15 d
Bombshells
Original Air Date on March 7, 2011
-- Sync, corrected by Ntino --
You really don't
have to be here.
You're my girlfriend.
I'm being supportive.
I'm mainly
talking about them.
Well, given that
there's almost certainly
nothing wrong with you,
and my patient definitely
has something wrong with him--
That can't wait an hour?
'Fraid not.
He's...
Chase.
16-year-old male
spit up blood
during a pick-up
basketball game.
E.R. couldn't find
the source in his lungs
or GI tract.
See? Serious.
Could be vasculitis,
bronchiectasis,
inhaled particles.
What about angiodysplasia?
Ready
when you are...
Get them outta here.
My urethra is not
for public entertainment.
But it is
a good-time adjacent.
Feed the kid a camera.
Check his got for
angiodysplasia.
All right.
If you could scoot down.
Hey, I'm, uh,
I'm missing a watch.
So can you keep your eyes open while--
Okay!
You too.
This little camera
transmits images
to the data recorder
so we can see
if you've got any
vascular malformations
in your GI tract.
Your records show
you've lost some weight
over the past year.
- Was that intentional?
- Not really.
Well, he's been
eating less
since he quit the swim team.
You have to get up early
for swim.
It wasn't fun anymore.
I need to talk to your son
about sexual activity.
Generally, it's less
embarrassing for everyone--
We're leaving.
Actually, I've only--
How long have you been
cutting yourself?
Those are from a layback grind
that went wrong.
Came off my skateboard
straight into a fence.
So...no to cutting
but yes to appetite
and sleep changes,
and you quit something
you used to enjoy.
How long have you
been depressed?
Imaging showed no sign
of upper GI issues.
But the kid did admit
to being depressed
and to smoking pot
to take the edge off.
You are very pleased
with yourself, aren't you?
His marijuana could be laced
with formaldehyde or lead,
which could cause
a pulmonary hemorrhage
which could make him
spit up blood.
Yes. Yes, I am.
I thought it was a good catch.
Run a lead level
and push 5 liters IV fluid.
Feel free to tip
your other server.
Cystoscopy was clean.
- Cytopathology was normal.
- Why do you have my lab results?
I don't.
If I did,
I'd know you were fine.
Unless the blood
came from my kidneys.
Come on.
Your hypochondriac mom
had a brush with mortality
last month,
and it's understandable that
you're worrying more than usual,
worrying that you might
turn into her.
You're right.
Odds are,
this is nothing.
Meet me in the cafeteria
in ten.
There'll be a corn dog
with your name on it.
I mean an actual corn dog.
They fixed the deep fryer.
I need to schedule
an ultrasound.
My dad's head's
still in one piece,
so I'm guessing you didn't
mention the pot.
What'd you tell him?
The truth.
You had a...
minor chemical exposure,
and we can't be 100% sure
how it happened.
Thanks for covering.
I know what it's like
to be 16.
You also know what
it's like to be depressed.
You figured out my deal
after only a few minutes,
but I been fooling my friends
and parents for months.
It's my job to notice things.
Maybe talking to your parents
would make things better.
I've tried.
They take it personally
that I'm not happy,
and then I end up having
to make them feel better.
They don't get me.
No one does.
In Med School,
it seemed like
everybody else
could handle the pressure.
I couldn't.
I ended up hurting myself.
Stupidest thing
I've ever done.
You've got red spots
in your eyes.
They weren't there
before.
You have nice skin.
Thank you.
Shut up!
Sorry. Just thought it would
be rude not to comment.
Just treat me like
any other patient.
Right.
Are you sucking in
your stomach?
No.
Hurry up before I pass out.
Wilson?
Ultrasound isn't definitive.
We should run other
tests before--
Stop talking like a doctor
and tell me what you see.
There's a mass
in your kidney.
We still don't know
why Ryan coughed blood,
and now he's got small
hemorrhages in his eyes.
Sounds like an acquired
coagulapathy
which gives us
a pretty wide differential.
Gets a lot narrower
if we factor in
his depression.
Oh, don't do that!
Mood swings can be a symptom
of physiological illness.
I'm not talking to you.
Mood swings are also
a symptom of adolescence
along with emo music
and masturbation.
More importantly,
his weight loss
and sleeping issues
started a year ago.
Infection makes the most sense.
He shoots hoops at school,
showers in the locker room.
- I'm thinking staph.
- Damn!
You don't think--
Not talking to you!
- Everything okay with Cuddy?
- She's fine.
She's just too stupid
to accept it.
Start him on nafcillin
for staph.
All that's in the, uh,
First Mutual safety
deposit box.
The retirement accounts--
You're freaking out
because of one ultrasound
performed by an incompetent
bonobo monkey.
As demonstrated
by my sitting here calmly
going about my business.
Calling a lawyer,
drafting a will!
Okay. I-I...
hacked into your
online schedule.
Look, tests always
show something.
A mass in your kidney
could be a complex cyst.
- It could be benign.
- I'm a single mom.
I need to set up a trust,
appoint a guardian.
It's silly that I haven't
done it before now.
But you're doing it now
because you think you're sick.
The freaking out
can at least wait
until after the biopsy
this afternoon.
The biopsy's
not till tomorrow.
It's the first opening
in the schedule.
For the Dean of Medicine,
the first opening
in the schedule is...
Oh, look! Now.
My worry isn't any more
important than anyone else's.
Actually, it is.
But I'm not sick, right?
Good point.
I want my stuff,
asshat.
I told you, man,
I don't have it here.
Hey...
Guys.
Everything okay?
On my way out.
I'll see you later.
You wanna...
tell me what's going on?
My friend gave me some
leftover Klonopin he had
when he switched
his seizure meds.
I sold them thru Roid Rage
for 80 bucks,
but I landed in here
before I could deliver,
and now he's gonna
rip my arms off.
How often
do you sell drugs?
It was a one-time thing.
I needed the cash,
I had the pills,
so I thought, "why not?"
It was a bad idea.
The pills are at my house.
I could have a friend
go get them.
Give the thug
his money back.
One time only.
I mean,
if you're okay with this.
You have three kids
of your own.
It's not even a question.
Of course I'll be
Rachel's guardian.
And House
is cool with this?
I mean, you guys...
We've only been together
a few months.
Hmm. Seems like
a lot longer.
Probably because you've been
talking about him for ten years.
And by talking,
I mean ranting about
wanting
to smash his teeth in
with a stapler
for being such a jerk.
People change.
I'll get it.
That better be her!
Ooh!
Rachel Cuddy, you were supposed
to be home half an hour ago.
Don't blame me--
he's the one
who wouldn't
run any red lights.
Mouth on that kid
makes Mel Gibson sound like
Nelson Mandela.
Where'd she learn that?
I don't know why
you're here,
but I didn't do it.
What's the problem,
officer?
She was shoplifting
down at the mall.
Aw!
Are either of you
this girl's father?
Nope. But since
her mom died,
she's my favorite
tax write-off.
Officer, you have my word
it won't happen again.
'Cause next time...
she won't get caught!
It's no big deal.
Good for you.
You could have just
assumed he was a drug dealer,
but instead you
took his word for it.
It's nice to finally
see someone
have a little faith
in humanity around here.
Why would you do that?
Ryan, you okay in there?
I'm not sure.
I think I just peed blood.
Looks like peeing blood
is the new black.
Peeing blood after a night
on antibiotics
means we can move on
from infections.
Scoping showed no sign
of a bleed in his bladder,
which points to a kidney problem.
Probably some kinda mass.
Kidney mass wouldn't
explain the coughing blood
or the hemorrhages.
Antiphospholipid syndrome,
on the other hand...
Makes sense.
But doesn't rule out a mass.
You think it's cancer?
Mass doesn't have to be
cancer.
Could be
renal hematoma.
But the patient
doesn't have
any other abdominal trauma.
He's...
not talking about
the patient.
Cuddy has a mass
on her kidney?
It's probably
just a complex cyst
or angiomyolipoma.
It's a mass, not a mystery.
They'll do the biopsy,
then you'll have your answer.
Just...have to wait.
Patient admitted
to using pot.
Who knows what else
he's doing.
This could be
a heroin-induced nephropathy.
I thought
you trusted this kid.
And then you pointed out
how sweet that was.
If it were heroin, he'd be
going through withdrawal.
Antiphospholipid syndrome's
a better fit.
Start the patient
on plasmapheresis.
While he's doing that,
can I at least search
his house for drugs?
Have I ever said no
to that question?
What are you doing here?
Pie-eating contest.
Cuddy's biopsy
is in an hour.
You should be
keeping her company.
Okay. You've been worried
that your relationship
is getting in the way
of your diagnoses,
you're protecting
your patient.
Either that or...
you're an ass.
Three--I hate
the smell of death.
The chances of Cuddy
having renal cell carcinoma--
I'm talking about
our relationship.
She needs support
and comfort,
both things
that I famously suck at.
This will inevitably
lead to--
you know what's good
for that? Practice.
Doing it--I don't know--
once?
I'm not gonna act like
there's a crisis
before we know
there is one.
There's no proof
there's anything wrong with her.
she's being stalked
by Ninja squirrels
either,
but if she's scared
of them...
as her boyfriend,
it's your job to figure out
how to help her
feel better.
You're right.
House told me
to keep you company.
Nurse told me to give you
antibiotics.
Tell House I'm fine.
Mm!
Tom Cruise got married.
Do you want me to quote
from First Corinthians?
'Cause I can do that.
As a Jew,
I'm gonna have
to decline that offer.
Don't know what
you're missing.
St. Paul
was really on his game.
He'll show up eventually.
You don't actually
believe that.
But I do.
All these years,
he's never stopped
trying to annoy me
for more than 15 minutes.
And now he can't even
walk into the room.
Love hopes all things.
What is it with you
and this kid?
He's doggy paddling
in a sea of misery.
I remember what it's like.
How far did you have to
reach back for that memory,
last night?
Sometimes I hear you
in the living room
watching TV
at 3:00 a.m.
That's when classic Dr. Who
comes on the BBC.
Yeah. If only they had
some device
that allowed you
to record them
and watch them
another time.
I'm just saying...
I don't think fixing this kid
is gonna fix you.
Yep?
We're on our way back.
Our patient lost all feeling
in his right arm.
Look at this.
Chase?
How'd it go with Cuddy?
Aah!
Good thing
I brought my ax cane.
House...help me!
I'm coming!
House...please!
It looks like
we got company.
House!
Aah...aah!
d d
No!
Ah...
Are you okay?
I was sleeping.
What could go wrong?
Patient lost feeling in his arm
while on steroids--
rules out autoimmune.
So what causes bleeding,
kidney problems,
and unilateral numbness?
And a complete absence
of any record
of Cuddy's kidney biopsy.
She must have put it
under a false name
so I couldn't
rush the results.
What if we had it backwards
and it's not a bleeding problem,
it's a clotting problem?
There's no patient file
created in the last two days
for anyone having
that procedure.
She backdated the file?
That's very clever.
Hands off.
She's mine.
Clots could explain
everything
including the numbness.
We should do an angiogram
of his brain,
see if we can find it.
House.
We're worried too.
How sweet.
I'm not worried.
I just wanna get the results
so she can stop worrying.
- Okay, but in the meantime--
- Do an angiogram.
You two go to pathology
and look at Cuddy's slides.
You just said you didn't know
which sample was hers.
I guess you're gonna
have to look at them all.
Bigger question--
What's the deal with Taub?
Just because House
is too distracted
to notice your distraction
doesn't mean we didn't.
Clots, angiograms--
I'm focused.
The kid scratched out
the faces of half his class.
You don't think
that's a problem?
It's not our problem.
Why is it anyone's problem?
I violently executed
my tenth grade geometry teacher
about five different ways
in my mind.
I didn't want
to kill anybody.
I just wanted to torture
them slowly in my basement,
preferably with acid.
You guys ever think about
what you might to do House?
Maybe it's no big deal.
Unless it is.
Someone shot House.
What are you doing?
Pie-eating contest.
I was going to send Chase
to tell you what the obvious
right thing to do here is,
but then I realized...
if you were too stupid
to know how stupid that was,
you might miss the irony.
You have to be
with her.
Yeah. I get it.
She needs artificial
support
for an artificial problem.
She's fine.
Chase did an excellent job.
She doesn't sleep
with Chase.
We don't know that.
Hey!
Eating pie in here.
House...
I'm not gonna tell you
a third time.
Do not screw this up.
Because I really don't
wanna clean up the mess.
He's referring to the pie.
14 patients
with kidney biopsies.
I tabulated them against
their urinalysis results.
Six men, three diabetics,
one lcdd, one kid,
two seniors,
and by default,
one...Cuddy.
Uh...the biopsy
was inconclusive.
The mass is near
the center of her kidney.
They couldn't get
a readable sample.
Means they'll have to
remove the mass
to know if it's cancer
or not.
The file says
they're doing
some imaging now,
give the surgeon a better
idea of what he's dealing with.
Can we order pizza?
There's nothing
in the fridge.
At least not anymore.
What's happening
with the patient?
Angio showed a clot
in a branch of his
middle cerebral artery.
Started him on streptokinase
to break it up.
Although...maybe we should
have just played a few rounds
of Savagescape 2: The Revenge,
because that's obviously
the best way to make someone
feel better.
You keep talking like Wilson,
your face will freeze like that.
Look, however bad you think
you're gonna be in that room,
not being in the room
is worse.
When she breaks up
with you...
you're playing by yourself.
Honey, I'm home.
Just in time.
Pot roast is ready.
Smells wonderful!
I cured all my patients,
so I came home to spend
time with Rachel.
And how was your day
today?
It was great, ma!
I got 100%
on my spelling test
and 170 on my LSATs!
Your LSATs?
You're eight years old.
We've been studying
together.
It was supposed to be
a surprise.
Well, that's wonderful.
I think Rachel
deserves a treat.
No, thanks, daddy.
It might spoil my appetite.
Well, who could that be?
Delivery for you,
Mrs. House.
Happy 29th birthday.
I'm not 29!
You're not limping.
This isn't possible.
None of this is possible.
Girl can dream.
You run out of sugar?
Got your scans back
from today.
Yeah.
Okay.
What's going on?
Imaging shows enhancing masses
across multiple lobes
of Cuddy's lungs.
That's what kidney cancer
looks like when it metastasizes.
She's dead.
What's up, losers?
I hope you're enjoying
being alive.
Today's lesson:
Natural selection.
Excellent system.
Made us who we are today.
But then we invented seat belts
and grocery stores,
things that keep idiots
and weaklings alive.
And let's be honest.
Most of you
don't really deserve it.
Here's to the natural order.
Yes!
Whoo!
Copied
from his flash drive.
Do I go to the cops?
Yes. "Officer, I'd like
to report an assault.
The victim
was a pile of leaves."
It goes on.
He talks about
bombing his school.
Which you know because
you stole his flash drive
and broke into his house.
How's that gonna play?
Ryan's not responding
to streptokinase.
We don't have very long
before the damage
becomes irreversible.
So we either up his dosage
or go into his head
and get the clot out.
- Where's House?
- Hopefully with Cuddy.
She did just get
some pretty awful news.
I called her.
She doesn't know
where he is either.
Have you seen House?
No.
He left my place
last night after you called.
No one's seen him today.
Any idea where he'd be?
No.
And you're not...
worried about that?
He's not good
with bad news.
Yes. I'm worried.
But this isn't about House.
It's about Cuddy.
She's the one
who could be dying,
and he's trying to
make this about himself.
I'm not playing.
Okay...
She still believes
he'll show up.
He'll either get over himself
and be who she needs him to be
or he won't.
We'd like to do an embolectomy.
We'll run a corkscrew-shaped
instrument into Ryan's brain
and pull the clot out.
Okay.
Have you talked
to him about it?
Yes. But I wanted
to see you alone.
I saw some videos that Ryan
made a few weeks ago.
He's blowing up pipe bombs
and threatening people
in his school.
Oh, God!
He was probably
just messing around.
Our son wouldn't
hurt anybody.
I'm not so sure.
I know this looks bad,
but Ryan's a good kid.
He's had a rough couple years
since he started high school,
but I really think
he'll come out of it.
He needs help.
Maybe he does,
but if this gets out,
he'll be suspended,
maybe expelled.
How about you focus
on keeping him alive?
What are you
gonna do?
What do you think
I should do?
Pssh. Ha.
So you can do
the opposite?
There are kids
all over the country
doing dumb,
potentially violent things,
but the percentage of them
who would actually kill anybody
is miniscule.
So I shouldn't do
anything.
Mm...while the odds
are low,
the fallout could be...
huge.
Tens or even hundreds
of lives.
So I should call
the cops.
Of course, over-identification
with the subject
could skew the calculation
towards being extra-protective.
Or alternatively--
You suck at this.
Hate the statistics...
not the statistician.
Give me a little more dye.
There's the clot.
It just disintegrated
when you touched it.
What was that thing?
I got a great idea
where we should go.
I don't want
to hear it.
You're gonna love it.
Australia's finest.
There's a great karaoke
bar in Newark--
I hate karaoke.
They got every--
every song
by every Aussie artist.
Midnight Oil, Men at Work,
Olivia Newton John.
I do a mean version
of Physical.
And the barbecue shrimp
is amazing.
What about the fries?
Hot and salty
and delicious.
Talking about food
made me hungry.
You had candy
in my other dreams.
Means you're stressed
at work.
All dream symbols
mean you're stressed at work.
Or castration anxiety.
No.
I was hoping...
you'd figure out a way
to handle all this.
Maybe you can't because
you're still a child.
I can do better.
Might be too late.
House!
Ah...
I should have been here.
Sorry.
I knew you'd come.
What was that thing,
and why did it just dissolve
in the middle of surgery?
Why is his liver shutting down?
That thing
in his brain goes away,
the kid slips into a coma.
We started him on lactulose,
but at the rate
his liver function is declining,
he'll be dead in a day.
Should we page House?
He's busy.
House can't do anything
for her now.
We need him!
By his own logic--
Patient's blood tests
were negative
for barbiturates
or acetaminophen.
He's not on
a high protein diet.
House couldn't concentrate on
the case before she was dying.
You think he's gonna
get in the game now?
If you don't make it,
I won't sleep with anyone
for at least a month.
Make it two.
Bitch.
A.I.P. can cause uremia,
tank the liver.
It causes abdominal cramping,
not abdominal bleeding.
Oh, because fucosidosis
was such a brilliant idea?
Guys!
Type 2 citrullinemia fits.
There are no signs
of hyperlipidemia
or pancreatitis.
Those can take years to emerge.
Closest we've gotten.
Start him on IV
sodium benzoate
to reduce the ammonia
levels in his blood.
Run a genetic test
for citrullinemia.
Forget your troubles.
d Forget your troubles d
d come on, get happy d
Forget your troubles.
d You better chase
all your cares away d
d shout hallelujah d
d come on, get happy d
d get ready
for the judgment day d
d d
d the sun is shining,
come on, get happy d
d the lord is waiting
to take your hand d
d shout hallelujah,
come on, get happy d
d we're goin' to the promised d
d land d
d we're heading d
d across the river d
d wash your sins
in the tide d
d it's all so peaceful d
d on the other side d
d forget your troubles,
come on, get happy d
d you better chase
all your cares away d
d shout hallelujah,
come on, get happy d
d get ready
for the judgment day d
d forget your troubles,
come on, get happy d
d you better chase
all your cares away d
d chase all your cares
away d
d shout hallelujah d
d come on, get happy d
d get ready d
d d
d for the judgment d
d day d
Get happy.
Get ready. Get ready.
Get ready, get ready.
Get happy.
Get ready!
Happy!
Get ready.
d Get happy d
d Forget your troubles,
come on, get happy d
d you better chase
your cares away d
d shout hallelujah,
come on, get happy d
d get ready
for the judgment day d
d the sun is shining,
come on, get happy d
d the lord is waiting
to take your hand d
d shout hallelujah,
come on, get happy d
d get ready
for the judgment day d
d forget your troubles,
come on, get happy d
d get ready for
the judgment day d
d shout hallelujah d
d come on, get happy d
d get ready for the judgment d
d ready for the judgment d
d ready for the-- d
Hm.
Hi.
Guess who doesn't
have cancer?
Me.
Also you.
Actually, you for sure.
Me...
House.
Your tumor was benign.
An oncocytoma.
They cut it out.
You'll be fine.
Then what was
in my lungs?
Once they ruled out
cancer,
I remembered that your mom
was allergic to antibiotics.
So I had them test
your blood,
and your IGE levels
were through the roof.
Because the lung masses
were an allergic reaction.
So now you're off
the antibiotics,
your lungs
should clear right up.
I brought you something.
Say hello to your tumor.
Ugh!
Wait.
There are so many things
that I could be afraid of,
and most of the time,
I manage to...
lock them up behind doors.
But this happens...
all those doors
just burst open.
You just figured something out
about your patient, didn't you?
Go. Do what you do.
Take him off the meds.
He's got a staph infection.
You treated him for
staph three days ago.
It didn't work.
Bacteria already
in his system responded.
Once a door's been busted open,
more just keep coming.
Oh! He's talking about
an abscess.
I got that.
For the cheap seats,
an abscess
is a gooey little cream puff
of infection.
Probably burst when your
little pride and homicidal joy
took a hard foul.
It's good news.
If we can find the door.
I think I know
where it is.
What if...these aren't
from skateboarding?
The kid has been blowing up
PVC pipe bombs.
If he got hit by shrapnel,
the body walls off
the foreign object,
which, because it's plastic,
doesn't show up on imaging
and provides a perfect home
for bacteria.
Antibiotics
attacked the infection,
causing pieces to break off.
Some hit the liver.
One lodged in his brain
and dissolved
when Foreman touched it.
Once we drain the abscess
and remove the shrapnel,
the antibiotics
can do their job.
He'll be fine.
Which just leaves...
what are you gonna do now?
All right.
I put the rest of the soup
in the freezer
so you'll have some
for later.
- Thanks for everything.
- Yeah.
- Here you go.
- I got it.
Okay.
Are you gonna
tell mom?
So she can show up here
to take care of you
by harassing the housekeeper
and criticizing your bathrobe?
Yeah. I think I'm gonna
wait a few years.
Oh, and I moved
your sleeping pills
back in the medicine cabinet
because I just worry.
Rachel always calls them
candy.
You took Vicodin.
When you came
to my hospital room that night,
you were stoned.
How did you know?
How did I not know?
How did I make myself
forget for months
that you're an addict?
My subconscious
was trying to tell me
you could never get
through this without drugs.
It was a one-time thing.
It's not about
the pills, House.
It's about what they mean.
I was scared
because I thought
my girlfriend might die.
No.
You don't take Vicodin
because you're scared.
You take it
so you won't feel pain.
Everything you've ever done
is to avoid pain--
drugs, sarcasm...
Keeping everybody
at arm's length
so no one can hurt you.
As opposed to everyone else
in the world
who goes looking for pain
like it's buried treasure?
Pain happens when you care.
Y-you can't love someone
without making yourself open
to their problems,
their fears.
And you're not willing
to do that.
I ca--I came
to be with you.
But you weren't with me,
not really.
I wanted to be.
That's not enough.
I can do better.
I don't think you can.
You'll choose yourself
over everybody else
over and over again,
because that's just
who you are.
I'm sorry.
No. No, no, no.
Don't.
- Don't.
- I thought I could do this.
Don't.
Please don't.
Good-bye, House.
-- Sync, corrected by Ntino --
www.tvsubtitles.net