[Alarm rings]
Cranial nerves.
On old Olympus'
towering tops
a friendly Viking
grew vines and hops.
Olfactory. Optic.
Oculomotor.
Vagus. Accessory.
Causes of edema: A.L.I.V.E.
Allergic...
Differentials
for swollen scrotum:
T.H.E.A.T.R.E.S.
English spelling.
Torsion, hernia...
Epididymal cyst.
S...Syphilis.
Enough with the drilling.
We're third year.
No more exams.
You don't have to face House
every day.
And after today,
neither do you.
Here's to no more
coming home in tears.
It's kind of like coming
to the end
of an extreme
roller-coaster.
Even with the terror,
nausea, and whiplash.
I'm a little sad
that it's over.
Let's go.
You got
your procedure log?
Oh, I'm not quite done.
I still have
one more lumbar puncture.
It's due today.
Unless you want to blow off
becoming a doctor
and get another PhD.
I know.
I'm gonna get it done.
I thought you'd have
that thing finished
like six months ago.
I've been busy.
Oh, come on, Cruz.
Let me do this.
I need it for my log.
Wait, you aren't done yet?
I've been busy.
What's in it for me?
The satisfaction
that comes
from helping out
a classmate?
How about cash?
Have you talked
to House?
It's 6:00 am.
He won't be in for a few hours.
I keep a roll of quarters
in the car...
I just turned in my log
and guess what I saw.
There's an opening
in the Diagnostics Department.
House wants
an intern?
He's never
had one before.
You gotta figure
he doesn't want an intern.
He wants you.
♪ House 7x19 ♪
Last Temptation
Original Air Date on April 18, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪ ♪
Uh, you must be
Dr. Thirteen.
Remy Hadley.
Nice to meet you.
You're back.
- Hi.
What the hell
happened to you?
Why'd you lie
about going to Rome?
(House)
You'd lie too
if you bottomed out,
ended up in...
drug rehab.
Thank you, House,
for respecting my privacy.
What a perfect reminder
that I'm back.
I didn't even know
you had a problem.
Loved ones are always
the last to know.
Loved ones and robotic,
estranged ex-boyfriends.
Our patient
is Kendall Pearson.
16-year-old aspiring pirate.
She's that Canadian kid
who's trying to be
the youngest person
to sail around the world.
Collapsed yesterday
during a practice run.
Luckily for us,
cameras were there.
Corporate sponsors
want us to check
that's she seaworthy
before the clock strikes
"you're too old
to set a record."
Gives us three days.
You've still only got one,
right?
Uh, last day
of my rotation.
Could be simple dehydration.
She told
the Coast Guard
she had felt dizzy.
Pulse and BP were normal
at the time of the rescue.
It's not dehydration.
What about your internship?
You sign up this morning?
Actually,
I'm still deciding.
Maybe she had a seizure
and that's what caused
her collapse.
Coast Guard report
says no sign of head trauma.
But what about
her back?
Look.
Right before the collapse,
she hit the small of her back
on the railing.
Damaged adrenal glands
caused adrenal insufficiencies,
which caused
the collapse.
Nice.
Blood draws
every 15 minutes
for four hours.
Let's track her cortisol.
Masters,
there's no hurry.
There's no wrong choices.
At least,
that's what they tell people
who make crappy choices.
What's with the sudden interest
in her future?
[Sighs] You know,
a blacksmith who spends
this much time hammering out
a new blade from raw jell-o
gets curious
about who ends up
wielding it.
No reason to be curious
unless you're interested
in wielding it yourself.
You want her
to intern here.
And you're
considering this?
Before I make my decision,
I still have one more LP
I need to get.
So I'd like to go
to the E.R.
Thirteen,
why don't you take Masters
to do the blood draws.
You can remind her
about all the perks
of working for me.
(Kendall)
Behind the deck.
Port side.
(Thirteen)
If her adrenal hormone levels
are consistently low,
we'll replace them.
You'll be ready to launch
Thursday.
Great.
Inside cabin
facing the bow.
Sorry, K,
I need to borrow mom.
The sponsors?
No, Couric's people
kicking up a fuss
about rescheduling
the interview.
I can take over.
Ceiling of the galley.
Right. The last time
I was on a boat
was my freshman mixer
in college.
I didn't so much mix
as hurl.
Too much to drink?
No, I was 13.
And in college?
Yeah, I know. Weird.
I was thinking "cool."
We'll be back
for the next blood draw
in 15 minutes.
Unless, of course,
you'd like to stay
and continue bonding
over your lost childhoods.
(Kendall)
Listen, I have a ton
of prep work to do
to be ready to launch.
Is there any way
we can speed the tests up?
Mm, I'm afraid not.
Unless you're up
for getting on a treadmill.
We could stress her body.
See if her adrenals
respond.
It would only take
a half an hour.
[Pager beeps]
It's about an LP.
Go. I'll handle this.
Um, Dr. Cuddy,
can I come by
your office later?
I'd love
to get some advice.
I'm in meetings
all afternoon.
Try me tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
This is...
This is my last day
as a medical student.
So I've got this decision
to make.
Probably the biggest decision
of my career.
Which means maybe
the biggest decision
of my life.
Although, I guess,
if I get married...
Um, House has opened up
an internship.
You do realize
if you take it,
he'll probably end up
firing you again?
He's always
hired me back.
And he'll continue mocking
and insulting you
whatever chance he gets.
It's certainly
toughened me up.
You're trying to get me
to say good things about him.
No. I'm trying to make you
make your own decision
and leave me alone.
Working with House is great.
And it sucks.
Often simultaneously.
Most people can't work
in that environment.
Question is...
Can you?
Thanks, Dr. Cuddy.
You pad me down here
and now you're doing my LP?
I got bored waiting.
It's been two minutes.
This is your 11th.
14th.
Listen, your roommate,
is she hooking up
with that resident?
I got to find House.
[Chicken coos]
(Thirteen)
Rehab? Great cover story.
Now I can't ever drink
around those guys again,
thus eliminating my main bond
with Chase.
(House)
Save the attitude for someone
who didn't just get you
your medical license back.
Price you pay.
There's a chicken
in your office.
No, there isn't.
You lied about rehab?
- Oh, great.
- Relax.
She's completely honest,
but also completely boring.
Watch this.
Don't tell anyone.
Of course not.
You did an LP?
Why didn't you page me?
Oh, I'm sorry. Did you want
to do one of those?
You should've spoken up.
You want the job or not?
Um, I--
after careful consideration,
I have decided
to accept your offer
for an internship.
Great.
My department
has a slightly different
procedure log.
Uh, you forged
the last one.
I only did nine LPs.
- Do you know how to do an LP?
- Of course.
Do you know
how to do nine LPs
and say it was ten?
It's time to grow up.
Turn that in,
the job's yours.
[Pager beeping]
Stop staring blankly
and go.
No doubt something horrible
has just happened
to our patient.
(Thirteen)
Her hand turned completely blue
during the treadmill test.
We put her on vasodilators.
Restored enough blood flow
so she won't lose
any fingers.
Rules out
adrenal insufficiency.
Where's House?
He said to meet him here.
His chicken's gone.
(Chase)
Probably on the balcony.
You knew he had
a chicken?
How come--?
(House) Down here!
Loss of consciousness.
Plus she's slowly turning blue.
Can we rule out
magical gum?
(Chase)
Low cardiac output
can cause both.
Patient possibly has
cardiomyopathy.
Possibly caused
by Mercury poisoning
from all the tuna fish
she eats at sea.
(Masters)
Uh, why are you putting,
um, chicken footprints
on the floor?
That clever bastard Wilson
got a hold of an Australorp.
Ah.
Hello.
The quietest and calmest
of all the chickens.
Damn him.
Mercury poisoning
is out.
Red blood cells
have normal morphology.
(Thirteen)
Raynaud's.
Vasospasm in the ulnar artery
would explain the hand.
(Foreman)
But not the loss
of consciousness.
Cerebral vasospasm
explains both.
(House)
Cerebral vasospasm
makes sense.
Take Thirteen.
Give the patient a calcium
channel blocker infusion
in the basilar artery.
Masters.
I thought you were going
to turn that in.
Um, I, um,
been busy with my patient.
You're not busy now.
Bawwwwwwk bawk.
(Donovan)
Masters.
Still haven't turned in
your log?
Still haven't gotten
my tenth LP.
I was thinking
maybe you should take
House's internship.
First you act
like it's the equivalent
of volunteering
to be waterboarded
and now
you're supporting it?
You're weird.
You make paper airplanes
for fun
and hang them
from the ceiling.
You have a membership
to the Einstein Museum
and an overbearing obsession
with facial symmetry.
It indicates freedom
from disease.
We're biologically
programmed--
the point is
you rub people
the wrong way.
But House is okay with your lack
of bedside manner.
He's okay
with your willingness
to argue any point
with anyone
even if they outrank you.
He's okay with your peculiar
fashion sense.
It's peculiar?
House doesn't think
you're weird,
which is weird,
but good weird.
Is that a chicken?
I think it's an Australorp.
I'm gonna go check
on my patient.
Can someone please
explain to me
what House and Wilson
are doing
with those chickens?
They have a bet to see
who can keep a chicken
in the hospital the longest
without getting busted
by security.
Advancing past
the vertebral artery.
And why
are they doing this?
The place they bought them
only had one pig.
I'm glad you're gonna be
sticking around after today.
Really?
You want me to stay?
It's good
to add a different perspective
to the department.
Someone who still remembers
there are rules
other than House's.
If I don't play
by House's rules,
he won't let me in.
Find a way around them.
I'd have to lie to him,
which is still lying.
Lying about a lie,
that's practically telling
the truth.
Catheter's in.
Start the calcium channel
blocker drip.
Means I need another LP.
Luckily, I know
where you can get one.
You good here?
Let's go.
Mm.
Decent stick.
Very smooth.
Sounds like you've had
a few of these.
Suppose that comes
with the territory.
I have Huntington's.
No need to get hushed
and solemn about it.
Why are you lying
about rehab?
Because the real reason
I was gone
is not something
I want to share.
Couldn't you just say that?
Should be enough
for Foreman and the others.
How long
have you worked here?
House's people
have personalities
that range from nosy
to "pardon me while I do
this cavity search."
Do you think there's room
for someone
who does things differently?
No.
Not unless House decides
that's what he wants.
(Foreman)
During catheter removal,
I got a good look
at her cerebral midline.
Pineal gland
is calcified.
(Thirteen)
Case closed.
I'll start her
on hormone therapy.
Ship her out.
I handed in my log.
On your way to do that,
did you happen to stop
and give Thirteen an LP?
Thirteen's stiff gate,
small pupils,
and the raging headache
she's hiding gave you away.
Yes.
And I still broke a rule.
My rule.
Told you to defy the man.
Not this man.
Why is it so wrong
that I don't like to cheat?
Can we go?
No.
Not liking it is fine.
Not doing what you don't like
makes you an eight-year-old.
Wastes your potential.
You want me to be like you.
It's not going to happen.
That's the last thing
I want.
'Cause then neither one of us
would be exceptional.
- You think I'm exceptional?
- Not anymore.
I can do my job
without compromising.
No, you can't.
'Cause I'm not gonna let you.
Internship's gone.
It's time for Masters
to say good-bye.
Enjoy being a surgeon.
You'll be fine.
[Alarm rings]
[Clears throat]
Surgery.
Anatomy.
Branches off
the subclavian artery.
Vitamin C and D.
V-I-T.
Vitamin. V: Vertebral.
I: Internal carotid--
internal thoracic.
Internal thoracic.
T: Thyrocervical.
C: Costocervical.
[Camera snaps]
Martha M. Masters.
That's me.
I'm gonna be a surgeon.
Next.
Welcome
to your surgical internship
at P.P.T.H.
The senior residents
stand behind you.
We'll all get
to know each other soon enough.
Grab a donut
and get to work.
We're out of donuts.
Then, uh, get to work.
Little oozing.
Isolated the left subclavian.
Suction.
You got to do better
than that.
Can't see a thing.
Push calcium chloride.
It will supercharge
the platelets
and increase the clotting.
Two amps calcium chloride.
Tell the blood bank
to set up three units
of packed red cells.
Field is clear.
Nice.
Generally speaking,
pledges aren't supposed
to talk
unless they
ask a question.
That's because,
generally speaking,
pledges don't have
anything to say.
Um, K.P.
Is that patient
Kendall Pearson?
I thought
she was discharged.
Mm.
It's a House case.
I never know
what that guy's up to.
I want you to scrub in
on my lung harvest.
But it's my first day.
Yes, I know.
I was there.
Be scrubbed and ready
in 15 minutes.
What happened?
Last I heard,
you were going home.
Kendall collapsed
in the parking lot.
They're doing something
called a "sympathectomy."
She must've had
a hypertensive crisis
caused by a neural
overstimulation
in her kidneys.
So they're cutting
the nerves.
It's like cutting
the gas line
to an engine.
Yeah, sounds like
what Dr. Taub said.
Said it's basic surgery,
but...
It is.
You should still be on pace
for a launch in 36 hours.
Her mom's
packing the boat now.
I'm supposed to pick up
some dry ice.
But...
Nothing you can do
for her here.
[Sighs]
Um...
We're just trying
to help our daughter
reach her dream.
She's different.
So you have to be different.
I'll make sure she's okay.
Thanks.
[Pager beeps]
You can see
the full lobular structure
of the left lung.
[Gasps]
Bifurcate innominate artery.
I've never seen
one of those before.
Hold this, Masters.
Rib spreaders.
You guys okay
if I pull a circulating nurse?
We got a train wreck
in O.R. ten.
You got it.
Proximal end attached.
Can someone take the retractors
from me?
Not really.
I have
to use the bathroom.
I know you're a rookie,
but you got to be kidding.
I'm not.
It can wait.
I'm gonna have an accident.
Next one in line,
grab it.
- What's wrong?
- Hypotension.
Low cardiac output.
Float the swan.
Don't you have
your own surgery?
I took a break.
I told them I had to pee.
You lied.
Small one.
But it's a gateway lie.
I care about the patient.
Another lie.
You care
about being exceptional.
I told her dad
I was gonna take care of her.
A third lie.
Welcome
to the slippery slope.
(Taub)
Ra is 8.
Equalization of pressures.
Means she has restrictive
pericarditis.
Add that to a calcified
pineal gland.
(House)
When is a calcified
pineal gland
not a calcified
pineal gland?
I realize, technically,
it's never, but--
when it's a granuloma.
It's Wegener's.
We should start her on steroids.
(Masters)
But she had a high CK.
Wegener's
wouldn't explain the--
dehydration does.
(Masters)
Yes. But the calcified pineal
could be sarcoidosis.
You had me
at "I had to pee."
But Thirteen's right.
Start her on three fold
immunosuppressants.
Masters, if you want
to fight me on this,
fill out a consult form
so you can stick around.
Welcome back.
I'm not back!
I'll just be staying
for this case.
You got really good
at this lying thing.
Hope it was one hell
of a whiz.
I ran into Dr. House.
He requested a surgical consult
for his patient.
House never asks
for a consult.
Something about this case,
he needed
a little more help.
First day
of your surgical internship,
you want to be loaned out
to another department.
Interesting career move.
Drop the form
by my office.
Don't stay away too long.
I'm already well on my way
to forgetting you.
How about I take
both you lovely ladies
out for a drink?
I'd love to.
Except I think you're a cretin.
And the last time
she was at a bar
was ballet class.
I didn't take--
Oh. [Snorts]
That's funny.
I'm gonna stay and run
a few extra tests
on House's patient.
This one lab value
doesn't make sense to me.
You're back
with House?
Mm. Just this one case.
I'm not staying.
I would kill for a chance
to work with him.
Like, literally skin you
and wear you as a disguise.
[Chicken clucks]
[Door opens]
[Clucking noise]
[Exclaims]
[Door locks]
You want yours extra crispy
or original recipe?
Chickens!
You ever get sick
from poultry?
Um, a few months ago
from this pheasant-in-a-can
my dad got me as a joke.
You think
that's why I'm sick?
I think that can
was chock-full
of a bacteria
called salmonella enteritis.
Likes to hang out
in the bones.
Let me know
if any of this is tender
or painful.
Um, this bacteria thing,
is this good news or bad?
Well, if I'm right,
that means all you'll need
are antibiotics.
And you'll be, uh,
well, shipshape.
Sorry.
Couldn't resist.
Did you always know
that sailing was it for you?
That it was the right thing?
Didn't even start
till I was ten.
And at first,
I was not a fan.
Certainly there's plenty
not to like about sailing.
But now that you're
so into it...
Oh, no, there's still
plenty of things
I hate about it.
I hate being wet.
I hate being cold.
I hate eating nothing
but freeze-dried food.
That is quite
the endorsement.
Sailing is amazing.
But doesn't mean I love
every second on the boat.
Doing what you love
means dealing
with things you don't.
If there were nothing
to overcome,
it might not be that--
[Winces]
Ow.
Salmonella enteritis
is a nice catch.
Thanks. Starting
on the soft tissue windows.
Once this case is over,
you going back to surgery?
That's the plan.
I think that's a mistake.
I think you should go back
to surgery.
I just said I was.
No. You said
it was your plan.
Which means House
might be right.
And you might be lying
to yourself.
Would it be so terrible?
You chose House
over surgery.
My time here changed me
in ways not everyone in my life
thought was for the better.
No masses.
Moving on to bone windows.
Are those people right?
I think when you do change,
it's not so simple
to go back.
There.
In the humerus.
Doesn't look like
an infection.
That's because it looks
like cancer.
You have lymphoid sarcoma.
A cancer in the bone
in your arm.
Am I going to be okay?
It's a treatable cancer.
But part
of that treatment
involves amputating
your arm.
I'm sorry.
There's nothing else?
We can do chemo and radiation
after the amputation.
I don't mean after.
I mean instead of.
If I leave soon,
I still have time
to break the record.
Honey,
you can't be serious.
I feel fine.
Last night, they thought
it was an infection.
We know it's cancer.
We ran the biopsy
three times.
You don't know
how fast--
postponing the surgery
could increase the likelihood
that the cancer will spread.
Kendall, you need to think
about what the doctor's saying.
I'm thinking
about the sail.
Like I have
since I was ten.
Don't take this
away from me.
It's just a month.
I can take extra
precautions.
I'll Skype you every day
and I can fly back
if something goes wrong.
She'll be risking her life.
I think we need
to discuss this as a family.
You're considering this?
Your daughter's condition--
Thank you, Dr. Masters.
She's not budging.
She wants to launch tomorrow.
She's a minor.
You sign the consent form,
we can do the surgery.
Amputation can be an emo--
She's talked my wife
into agreeing with her.
One parent's signature
is enough.
She needs you
to be a parent.
You're asking me
to blow up my family.
I'm asking you
to save your family.
On her first solo
Atlantic crossing,
she scheduled a court date
to become
an emancipated minor.
She'll do it again
and she'll win.
She is gonna do
what she's gonna do
with or without me.
I'd rather have it
be with.
I'm stuck.
No, you're not.
Case is over.
You're back to surgery.
And fetch.
Oh, that's a good boy.
Hey, good boy.
No one will stop
Kendall's sail.
You need to step in.
Sign on the door
says I'm a diagnostician.
Cool diagnosis
means I'm finished.
She could die.
Pretty sure the law
of the land states
that everyone has the right
to be an idiot.
I think it's the second
amendment. Fetch!
Bring it here, boy.
Who's a good boy?
You are constantly railing
against hypocrisy,
forcing people
to face the truth.
This time nothing?
Yeah.
'Cause they faced the truth.
And made a decision
that will in all likelihood
kill their daughter.
I'm fine with that.
I wanted a diagnosis.
I got it.
What do you want?
I don't want her to die.
Break the rules.
I can't.
So coloring inside the lines
is more important to you
than saving this girl's life?
I was wrong
about one thing,
you are not exceptional.
And fetch!
Ho ho ho.
Oh, that's a good boy.
Good boy. Good boy.
[Knocking at door]
Dr. Wilson.
Um, I'd like
to get your advice
about a cancer patient.
Kendall Pearson.
Oncology rounds.
Everyone's talking about it.
[Winces]
Are you okay?
Yeah, my back's acting up.
Oh. Um...
So what would you do?
I would keep trying
to convince her
to have the surgery.
And if she kept saying no?
I would just keep--
[Winces]
Keep--keep trying.
I know there's a chicken
under there.
Oh, thank God.
It's pecked through
one pair of my loafers.
[Chicken clucks]
So that's all you'd do?
That's all you can do.
Is it?
[Chicken clucks]
Isn't that House's chicken?
Disgusting beasts.
I don't know why I ever agreed
to this bet.
So call it off.
And lose $20?
Listen,
House was in
the exact same situation
Kendall's in.
He needed surgery,
but he didn't want it.
Once he was in
medically-induced coma,
his girlfriend signed
the consent form
as his proxy.
They went ahead
with the surgery
against his will.
Probably saved his life.
So she did the right thing?
Depends on who you ask.
(House)
Fetch!
(Wilson)
No! No!
(Man)
Excuse me.
Who's responsible
for this chicken?
Does anyone know
who owns the chicken?
That bird belongs to...
Dr. Gregory House.
[Chicken clucks]
You need
to do this surgery.
I will.
Now.
We've been through this.
I'm leaving today.
It's a stupid record.
It's not about the record.
I used to race
against other people.
I could have the slowest boat
in the fleet and I'd win.
So it's about being better
than everyone else?
It has nothing to do
with anybody except me.
The other racers
would think I was crazy.
I'd set off on some
tacking angle
that made no sense to them
because they couldn't see
what I saw.
I could sense the changes
in the wind
before they even happened.
At the top of the game,
you play by different rules.
Medicine's gonna burn
a little bit.
[Pager beeps]
(Foreman)
Bradycardic arrest.
Third degree heart block.
Likely paraneoplastic
syndrome.
We need to get her
to the O.R.
For pacemaker
or plasmapheresis.
[Alarm beeping]
What's going on?
The cancer is causing
her heart to slow down.
We have to get her to the O.R.
and treat her.
This is what
I was worried about.
If this had happened at sea,
she would be dead.
Oh, my God.
We need you to sign
the consent form.
Authorize us
to amputate her arm.
[Exhales]
(Chase)
Subclavian access established.
Temporary pacer ready.
Don't need it.
Push calcium chloride.
It'll fix the heart block.
Bradycardia was me.
You did this?
Parents signed
the consent form.
Amputate her arm.
What happened?
You had a cardiac episode
that required us to bring you
into the O.R.
That crisis resolved,
but--
What did you do?
During surgery,
we found cancer
in a lymph node
in your neck.
So you cut off my arm?
Cancer was already spreading.
It had to be done.
[Crying] I told you
I didn't want this.
If we had waited
until after the sail was over
you would have died.
[Crying] That record.
That was everything.
(Bobby)
It wasn't everything.
You have a life.
A future.
You weren't supposed to do this.
How could you?
Because we love you.
I hate you.
I hate both of you.
Okay.
My arm.
Dr. Masters, thank you.
[Alarm rings]
Someone has got
their pouty face on.
I did things
no doctor in their right mind
would do.
Good.
I manipulated,
lied, forged, stole.
I don't want to know
the specifics.
Might be called
to testify.
I broke the rules
because I believed I was right.
You were right.
Then why don't I feel good
or satisfied?
Instead, I just feel
like throwing up.
And you're following me to ask
how I break the rules
and maintain
my rosy demeanor.
[Knocks at door]
I didn't do it to be happy.
I just thought I would be.
You can't always get
what you want.
To the victor
of the spoils.
Your bird recover okay?
Physically, yes.
Emotionally,
it was a long night.
Next week: Ferrets?
House.
I can't do it.
I'm leaving.
Surgery?
I...don't know
what I'm going to do.
But I do know
I don't want to be here.
Nothing will ever
be simple again.
I'm fine with that.
♪ You can't always get
what you want ♪
♪ and if you try sometime ♪
♪ you'll find ♪
♪ you'll get what you need ♪
[Chicken clucks]
[Laughs]
♪ You can't always get
what you want ♪
♪ but if you try sometimes ♪
♪ well, you might find ♪
♪ you get what you need ♪
♪ oh, yeah ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net