[tires screech]
[device beeps]
[horns honking]
Darrien?
♪ House 7x22 ♪
After Hours
Original Air Date on May 16, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Massive Attack's ♪ Teardrop ♪
What the hell happened?
We got to get you
to a hospital.
No, you're a doctor.
Just stitch me up.
It's more complicated
than that. We need to--
The cops will be
waiting for me at the hospital.
They're gonna
bust me back inside
just for being with felons.
You stay here,
they bust me.
I can't go back, Remy.
Neither can I.
God forbid you die,
I'm up for manslaughter.
I'll find someone else.
You leave,
you bleed out.
You're gonna die.
Stop.
Promise me you won't
take me to the hospital.
I promise.
Look at how much fun
she's having.
That's because he has
two functioning legs,
capable of supporting
her body weight.
So do I.
You told me
most of your muscle was cut out.
I was going
for the sympathy discount.
Been taking
some experimental medicine.
Yeah,
I got a lot of clients
on experimental medicine.
You want proof?
Okay,
this amp stack
weighs way more
than you do.
[Grunts]
See?
Now, even if those implants
were made of adamantium,
I'd still be able to...
Sorry.
Cramp.
I'm sure.
I'm not gonna be needing
your services tonight after all.
Aah!
Bowel's intact.
Inferior vena cava's fine.
Aah!
Liver got nicked,
but it feels clotted off.
I don't see any other signs
of internal bleeding.
So I'm okay?
Define okay.
And just because
I don't see bleeding
doesn't mean
it's not there.
[Air pumps]
105 over palp.
I'm gonna check your pressure
every two minutes.
If you dip below 90,
it means it is there
and we have a problem.
Okay.
[Music playing in headphones]
Oh. Sorry.
I should get to work.
Wait. Ruby.
We'll talk more
in the morning.
Good night, Eric.
You two breaking up?
She's pregnant.
I need a drink.
There was a raid.
Andre needed to do something
to slow the cops down.
He stabbed you
as a distraction?
Didn't work.
Cops called an ambulance,
left me lying there.
Oh, come on.
Give me crap.
I know what
I  told you about him,
but it's not his fault
I started using again.
It's mine.
What?
According to this,
you're dead.
You have no blood pressure.
Barely have a pulse.
Am I dying?
You're talking and alert,
so your brain
is getting blood.
Pulse in your right arm
is fine.
So is your B.P.
[Cell phone vibrates]
Hello.
Are you busy?
Yeah, I'm, uh,
I'm about to go out.
Great. Uh, can you
do me a huge favor?
I need you
to go to the hospital
and check out a portable
ultrasound machine for me.
Who's the father?
I have a leak in my bathroom,
and my guy won't come
take a look at it
till tomorrow morning,
and an emergency plumber's
200 bucks an hour.
Dr. House.
Dr. Riggin.
Figures you'd be wrapping up
the trial by now.
I just wanted to give you
a hearty mazel tov.
And don't forget
the Nobel Prize
for developing an incredibly
expensive rat poison.
What do you mean?
What happened?
Tumors.
Just look at these things.
Any indication
the rats were getting sick?
Just some cramping.
Their legs would stiffen up.
They were having trouble
moving around.
We just thought their bodies
were adjusting to the increase
in muscle mass,
but within a day or so
they just started dying.
Oh, well.
Get a new compound
to play with next week.
One portable ultrasound.
Extra pepperoni.
Thank you so much.
I might be late tomorrow.
Your socks are dry.
And, unfortunately,
so is your shirt,
which means you either
just changed to greet me,
or you need this
for something medical.
I am a doctor.
She's my friend.
I was in prison.
You killed your own brother?
Yes.
It was awful and devastating,
but it wasn't murder.
He was sick
and he wanted to die,
and I promised I would help.
Now please stop pacing
and help me find this thing.
Have you talked
to anybody about it?
I mean, are you okay?
No, I may have
an aortic arch aneurysm.
Oh, wait, that's her.
Either help me or leave.
Having trouble
getting a clear look.
Try a long axis view
from the suprasternal notch.
Wait! Put on some gloves.
She's got Hep-C.
Wonderful.
Take it
you two were cell mates.
Just friends.
She saved me.
There's a culture in prison.
If you don't have someone
to show you
how to get
the stuff you need
and stay away
from the stuff you don't,
you're screwed.
Her fingers are turning blue.
Can you move those?
My arm's
starting to go numb.
Arch of aorta's clear.
This can't be an aneurysm.
Maybe the wound threw a clot.
Check axillary arteries.
Stop.
Right there.
5 centimeter gooey mass.
Not a clot.
Maybe a lipoma?
What the hell is that?
Fat-filled sack.
Probably aggravated
by the stab wound.
You got any syringes in here?
Give me that.
I was stabbed in my gut,
not in my arm.
You lost a lot of blood,
gave the lipoma room
to swell.
It's compressing
the arteries in your arm,
blocking your blood flow.
Maybe we can suck
some of it out.
You'll be fine.
Little pinch.
That's not lipoma.
[Upbeat dance music]
♪ ♪
I don't know why she's
even considering
having my kid.
She barely knows me.
All she knows is
I'm a short, balding guy.
It doesn't even make
evolutionary sense.
You want her to keep it?
No.
(Foreman)
'Cause you'd make a crappy dad.
I said, "no."
You're too selfish.
That's why you cheated
on your wife,
why your marriage fell apart--
dude, I said--
I know you.
The only reason you're sitting
in a strip club,
ignoring the strip club,
is because you actually
are considering it.
Although without crappy dads
in the world...
Try moving your fingers again.
Good.
Means it's almost drained.
Not good enough.
We don't know
if it's gonna come back.
We don't even know
what it is--
drugs, viruses,
toxins from that crack house
and God knows where else
she's been.
If this were caused
by the drugs,
she'd have kidney failure,
cardiac involvement.
What about her Hep-C?
Could have fried her liver.
Loses its synthetic function.
Then her entire body
would be swelling,
not just her arm.
That leaves us with toxins.
Where exactly were you
when you were attacked?
You're not doing
a home search
in a crack den;
That's insane.
Apparently, we don't
have much of a choice.
It's a crime scene,
and it's not toxins
or viruses or anything
else you mentioned,
because it's not a coincidence.
Her symptoms have
to be related to the stabbing.
What if her body used up
all the clotting factors
dealing with the stab wound?
Explains the bloody mass.
But if you're right, she could
start bleeding anywhere,
like in her brain
or in her heart.
One of those things could start
growing in my brain?
It's time to get you
to the hospital.
Oh, no.
Remy, you promised.
All we'll do at the hospital
is stick her in a patient bed
and give her IV
clotting factors.
We can do that right here.
We could also embalm her
right here.
I'll call the drugs in.
You go pick them up.
If I'm right,
she'll be fine.
Look, I know you
don't know her
and you don't care about her,
but I do.
Please.
♪ ♪
[Breathing heavily]
Lie down,
elevate your shoulder.
[Groans]
You said Andre wasn't
responsible for the drugs.
What is?
Oh, I don't know.
Yes, you do.
What happened to you?
If you don't deal
with the real problem--
I came here because
you're a doctor...
Not a shrink.
[Deep rumbling]
Ugh!
[Screaming and grunting]
Ah!
[Grunts and yells]
[Gasps and whimpers]
[Cell phone vibrates]
Your lap is vibrating.
Oh, sorry.
Uh, it's my boss.
Probably drunk.
Wants a ride home.
He can take a cab.
Do you have any kids?
Why?
You like moms?
I could be your mommy.
Spank your little ass.
Mmm, uh, no.
I--
what would you do
if you got pregnant?
Not by me...at all,
but by some hypothetical guy
who didn't want to keep
the hypothetical kid.
What would be
the least awful way
for him to tell you that?
Don't talk.
Just let mama dance for you.
Should I send flowers?
Maybe write
the clinic appointment
on the little card?
Surprise!
I hate myself.
[Sighs]
There's just no good way to--
how long have you
had this mole?
It's asymmetrical.
No touching.
Sorry.
Have you been to see
a dermatologist?
[Sighs]
Bobby!
Oh, uh...
I wasn't touching her.
I was just--
oh, God.
Oh!
[Cell phone vibrates]
No.
No, please don't.
Please, please...
Put the gun down.
Put it down
on the ground
and get away!
[Gunshot]
[Thud]
Dee?
I'm sorry.
[Sobbing]
Dee, what is it?
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry!
[Crying]
[Breathing sharply]
[Cell phone vibrates]
Mmm.
[TV playing]
Why aren't you in your bed?
(Brownbeard)
Jibber me jabbers.
I'll give ye splinters
in yer arse,
ye mangy bilge rat.
What are you watching?
TV, you bloody scallywag.
[TV powers off]
Mom!
[Cell phone continues vibrating]
[Keypad tone]
Someone better be dying.
[Door closes]
She hallucinated.
I need you to go back out.
I just called in more
clotting factor.
So she's bleeding
in her brain now.
We double up the dose,
she'll be fine.
No.
We bring her to the hospital,
we do a CT scan
to locate the bleed,
drill a burr hole
in her skull,
and maybe she'll be fine.
We can drill
a burr hole here.
You're not just risking
our careers here.
You could go back to prison.
I made a promise.
You made a promise?
I will not take her
to the hospital.
Great.
Then I will.
No.
I'm gonna move you,
and then I'm gonna
pick your friend up,
carry her down to my car,
take her to the hospital,
and try to save her life.
She's staying here.
Move.
Move!
[Grunts]
She's going to the hospital.
Sweetie...
Go wait for mommy
by the couch, okay?
Go on.
I tried calling everyone else.
You were the last one
on the list.
Any reason why 911 wasn't
on the list?
It's not an emergency.
Right.
Are you suicidal?
I'm not attempting
bypass surgery.
The tumors are small
and they're close
to the surface.
I thought it'd be like...
removing a wart.
You couldn't wait
till morning,
bring your CT
to an actual surgeon?
Surgeons are idiots.
They'd just hack away
at the muscle
until they get worn out.
Or you're just ashamed
you've been injecting a drug
that hasn't even
gone through safety trials.
It's never even been
in the human body.
I got one of the tumors.
The second one is close.
You can use the CT
to help you find the third.
I'm taking you
to the hospital.
Just--just excise the tumor.
Absolutely not!
[Horn honks]
Elevate her head more.
Don't bother.
Cops are gonna be waiting
at the front door.
I'll go in first.
I'll find a patient
on life support
who's waiting to die.
We'll use their name
on all your tests.
No one will ever know
you're there.
Thanks.
What happened to your leg?
I was trying
to make it better.
He was being reckless.
Sit back, honey.
This isn't about
making your leg better.
It's about making
your life better.
Here we go.
Wish I had called 911.
Why else would you
risk your life
doing something so stupid?
Well, you know, I've had a lot
of setbacks lately.
Don't blame our breakup
for this.
You're not unhappy
because of me.
You're just unhappy.
Unhappy people
do reckless things.
Darrien!
[Gasps]
(Darrien) Stop screaming.
My head hurts.
I need you to stay awake.
Talk to me.
About what?
When you were screaming
in my room,
what did you think
you saw?
You said,
"put it down on the ground
and get away."
Sounds like a cop.
Old habits, I guess.
You were a cop?
Back when I was
a decent person.
How do I not know this?
You knew everything--
Not a good resume when you're
trying to survive in prison.
So who were you
talking to in my bedroom?
Why did you keep
apologizing?
'Cause I'm sorry.
For what?
I killed a kid.
He was 19.
I went in first.
Saw him going for his gun.
I tried to talk him down,
but...
[Chuckles]
They told me I was a hero.
So that's when you started
using drugs?
I'm sorry.
Darrien?
Darrien!
She lost consciousness.
[Engine revs]
[Turn signal clicking]
There are no cars coming.
Just go.
The light is red,
ye bloody scallywag.
Stop with the pirate talk.
(House)
If you don't want brownbeard
to end up with
two wooden legs,
better get yer ma
to move this ship,
you mangy bilge rat.
[Rachel giggles]
Of course...
You showed her
that filthy cartoon.
What kind of idiot
lets a three-year-old
watch that?
If you want to lecture me
on my poor judgment,
there would seem
to be more relevant examples.
[Muffled dance music]
[Door opens]
There you are.
You were in the VIP room
so long,
I thought you were gonna
pay off that girl's mortgage.
I got tossed out
by Bobby the bouncer.
You touched her?
I was looking at her mole.
[Chuckles]
Genius.
Let's go home.
I want to wait
for the girl,
make sure that mole's okay.
Bobby the bouncer
sees you
standing out here
like a stalker,
he's gonna break open
your skull.
It was asymmetrical.
It could be cancerous.
You want to get your skull
cracked open.
You're trying
to punish yourself.
I want to fulfill
my oath as a doctor.
You think you're a screw-up
because you got
a girl pregnant
and you deserve to suffer.
You don't.
You just need some sleep
and you'll handle this mess.
Let's get in the car.
She's probably
off work soon.
Give me the keys.
I'll drive.
I'll get a cab.
Good luck with everything.
(Chase)
You were defending your friend
beyond all rationality,
granting her the right
to die in your bedroom.
Was it really all
because of a promise?
That word means something
to some people.
Not that much.
I don't see the bleed.
I'm moving down
to the brain stem.
You promised your brother
you'd euthanize him
and you think you won't
feel bad about it
as long as you can blame it
on the promise.
That's why you have
this twisted obligation
to keep all promises...
Or your carefully constructed
defense mechanism
could crumble down.
I saved my brother from
a lot of pain.
Reconstructed image is clear.
There's no bleed
in Darrien's brain.
Image just blurred.
Did she wake up?
(Thirteen)
She's shivering.
She must have a fever.
Infection?
It couldn't be from
the stabbing.
It has to be
from the stabbing.
No, it couldn't
be acting that quickly.
Well, then what's wrong
with her?
Your heart rate's over 120.
You're clammy.
I think you're going
into shock.
Are you lightheaded?
I'm fine.
Did you see
the new Brownbeard episode?
It was so funny.
No, it was so lame.
Got a boat full
of guy pirates
and they make the girl pirate
walk the plank.
She floated.
That's 'cause she had
big boobies.
That's why he should have
kept her.
We've got to get you
into surgery.
Where is that nurse?
Rachel, let's go find
the nurse.
[Cell phone rings]
2:00 a.m.
Nice of you to call me back.
Chase and I are in
the hospital with a patient.
You've completely
run out of ideas
and you're calling me
to bail you out.
I'm touched.
Hit me.
[Muffled dance music]
(Car voice)
Command, please.
Call Ruby.
Would you like to call Ruby
on the cell phone?
No.
[Keypad tone]
She on any medication...
Besides crack?
She was taking Interferon
in prison,
so I'm guessing she's had Hep-C
for at least ten years.
Can I guess stuff too?
'Cause that's gonna make
the diagnosis really easy.
Prison infirmary isn't known
for stellar record keeping.
And we can't exactly ask
the patient.
(House) Yeah, that would have
been pre-coma.
But how could you have known
that it would affect her
that way?
We didn't think we had
anything mysterious until--
How about renal cancer
throwing clots?
Urinalysis was negative.
That's too bad.
'Cause that was
my one big idea.
Really?
House?
House, you there?
[Sighs]
Tell me more about
the patient.
What was she doing
before prison?
She was a cop.
Shot a kid in self defense,
never got over the guilt,
started taking drugs,
and got busted.
Way to bury the lead.
How long ago
was the shooting?
I'm not sure.
Why?
Again, you assumed she's had
Hep-C for ten years.
Find out when she
shot the kid,
you'll find out when
she started taking drugs,
and when she actually
contracted the Hep-C.
And you think
this is relevant?
It's more relevant
than what you got now,
which is squat.
Three chicks just came
into my bedroom.
I got to go.
(Car voice)
Command, please.
Call Rachel.
Would you like to call Rachel
on the cell phone?
No.
What the hell?
I really am a doctor.
I just wanted--
Cop another feel?
Get away from me.
No, that mole.
I just wanted--
please, don't call Bobby.
Just...
Calm down.
Shut up!
Sick perv!
Get down on your knees!
You think I'm kidding?
Turn around and get down
on your knees!
Please don't.
I said shut up!
[Whispering] Please, please please...
You think you're the first guy
who thought he was special?
Please, please, please...
You think you can
do whatever you want?
I am not going
through that again!
Please...
[Gun clicks]
Please...Please...
(Chase)
Find anything?
Shockingly...
A punk kid getting shot
pulling a gun on a cop
did not make
national news.
Is your neck okay?
Yeah, it's fine.
I'll get you some ice.
I said it was fine.
I shouldn't have
grabbed you so hard.
You had to.
You were right...
About everything.
Oh, I got something.
Darrien must have had
a different last name then.
She must have been married.
2008?
Is that possible?
We never actually talked about
how long she'd been in.
House was right.
She could have only had
her Hep-C for a few years.
There's no way the prison
would have prescribed Interferon
unless the lab showed
her Hep-C to be chronic.
So what makes new Hep-C
looks like old Hep-C?
What if she got a parasite?
The Hep-C made her susceptible
and the parasite sped up
the liver damage.
Entamoeba.
If they were
in a parasitoma,
the stab wound could
have freed them,
sent them coursing
through her bloodstream,
wreaking havoc.
A single bag
of metronidazole.
If we're right,
she could wake up
from the coma
in a few hours.
[Footsteps approaching]
They're ready for you.
Wait.
I want you in there.
I'm not a surgeon.
There's nothing I can do.
Well, you can make sure that...
Idiot butcher
doesn't cut more than
he needs to.
You already signed a release.
He's gonna do what
he needs to do.
Yeah, and if that involves
chopping off my leg...
I want to be sure
that that's damn well
necessary.
House...
I don't trust him.
I trust you.
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
You had parasites
in your liver.
Probably from a dirty needle
or prison...
Or who knows what?
The stabbing made it worse...
But you're gonna be okay.
I'm sorry.
We had to.
I told you I couldn't go back.
I shouldn't have trusted you.
I never liked you.
I killed time with you 'cause
I  was locked in a cage.
You were a distraction.
Someone to talk to so I didn't
have to think about...
everything else.
You're lashing out...
I get it.
But in a month,
you'll thank me.
[Scoffs]
Or maybe you won't.
I don't know.
But...
I know I saved your life.
Is he going to be okay?
He'll be fine.
Close your eyes.
I wish House still
came over to play.
Well...
Maybe you should
write him a letter.
Want to do that?
Okay, let's do it.
Ruby.
You look like hell
and you smell like--
I've been doing
a lot of thinking.
Is that glitter on you?
Just hear me out.
Back when I still
had my practice,
this patient came in,
50-year-old guy,
wanted a tummy tuck.
But when we
do some prelim work,
we discover that his stomach
is filled with cancer.
So instead of telling him
that he's gonna look great
at the beach,
I got to tell him
that he's dying.
Were you at a strip club?
Please.
The weird part was
I was more upset
about the whole thing
than he was.
He actually had
to calm me down.
Said he had great kids,
raised them right,
knew that because of them,
he was leaving the world
a better place.
I thought I might die
last night.
At a strip club?
Yes, I was at a strip club.
And while it was happening,
I kept thinking about
that patient
and how I wish
I was like him.
I want to have this baby.
Darrien had to shoot
that kid.
It was the right thing.
Completely justified.
But it didn't matter.
She destroyed her life
trying to forget.
I'm afraid that's what's
gonna happen to me.
You really should talk
to someone.
I've talked to a therapist.
It didn't help.
Well, maybe you should
talk to someone
who isn't a therapist.
Do you really think
you have any idea
what it's like
to live with something
like this?
Let's grab a coffee.
[Flume by Bon Iver]
♪ ♪
♪ I am my mother's only one ♪
♪ it's enough ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I wear my garment ♪
♪ so it shows ♪
♪ now you know ♪
♪ ♪
♪ only love is all maroon ♪
Late night?
No.
Just haven't had
my coffee yet.
[Yawns]
Sympathetic yawn.
♪ ♪
♪ sky is womb ♪
♪ she's the moon ♪
ooh!
Amish kid collapsed
while picking up a hooker.
Top that.
Missed a call from House
last night.
He in?
♪ ♪
♪ I am my mother ♪
♪ on the wall ♪
♪ with us all ♪
You're lucky.
What are you doing here?
You hoping for someone else?
Hot nurse,
candy striper...
Someone who doesn't
speak English.
speak judgmental.
♪ Only love is all maroon ♪
You've got mail.
"I hope your leg
feels better
"and I hope we can be friends
again soon,
you bloody scallywag."
♪ Leaving rope burns,
reddish ruse ♪
I have to pee.
That's a good sign.
I'm a big boy.
Of course you are.
[Gasps]
♪ Only love is all maroon ♪
♪ ♪
You're an ass.
What, for trying to walk
on a freshly mangled leg?
Performing surgery on myself?
For thinking I could
solve my emotional problems
with rat medicine?
If you're gonna nag,
at least have the decency
to be specific.
Come on.
Listen to me.
You can't keep going
like this.
Something has to change.
Can I pee first?
I know.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net