Are we, uh,
almost done here?
I have to call my mother,
get my daughter,
call the hospital.
So he didn't threaten you?
No.
No fight?
Not really.
Sounds like a yes.
Was there any indication
that something would happen?
Yeah...
Every moment
I spent with him.
He's always waiting
for something to happen.
But this...
And no idea
where he is?
No.
These domestic situations,
it's not uncommon
to get cold feet.
Are you asking me
to file charges?
Just give me the paperwork.
If Greg House steps foot
in my hospital again,
comes anywhere near me.
I want him thrown in jail.
♪ House 7x23 ♪
Moving On
Original Air Date on May 23, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
So...
We can use
any of these?
Yeah.
And just do
whatever we want to her?
That's what
they're there for.
Hey. We were just getting
to the good part.
Is there a good part?
It was performance art.
That's Afsoun Hamidi.
She's a genius.
She just won the MacArthur,
legally proving it.
Just had a retrospective
at the Tate Modern.
- Nobody reads The New Yorker?
- Nope.
But I subscribe to her patient file.
House, you should relax.
You had surgery this morning.
Minor surgery, removing a drain.
- Put there during major surgery.
- My doctor says it's okay
as long as I don't leave
my hospital bed.
Which doctor was that--
Seuss or J?
Nurse.
Dr. Hourani wrote it
in his chart.
I'm surprised he approved it.
I'm more surprised
you actually asked.
I do things like that now.
I'm making some changes...
Like skipping ahead
to minute 37.
What is that--
paint thinner?
I'm not gonna watch a woman
get set on fire.
Philistine.
Who's the guy with the notebook
who can't decide what to do?
Her assistant.
He's been instructed
not to intervene.
Spoiler alert--
he does.
For her, it is literally
heartbreaking.
Let the games begin.
Arrhythmia,
high hematocrit,
and inconsistent RR variability.
You forgot about the fourth symptom--
being completely crazy.
One man's crazy
is another woman's art.
Her work explores things like
gender politics and self-image.
And the pressing issue
of shaving your entire body
in public while wearing
a monkey mask.
She saw her mom
commit suicide
and was abused
by her stepdad for years.
Didn't say the crazy
wasn't motivated.
Well, she took that pain
and transformed it into art.
That's better than a lot
of the alternatives.
I still vote for nuts.
We should run a resting-state
functional MRI
to look for increased activity
in the dorsal nexus.
She's not nuts.
The monkey-mask-shaving medium
really speaks to you?
What speaks to me
is she's elevated
being full of crap
to a genuine art form
and made a fortune
doing it.
People that pay 20 grand
for one of her video stills,
on the other hand,
really do need
their dorsal nexi checked.
Maybe the paint thinner set off
an allergic reaction.
Not without bronchospasm.
There was a space heater
next to her in the gallery.
Carbon monoxide poisoning.
It fits.
Put her
in a hyperbaric chamber.
Thank you.
Lisa.
You're Lisa Cuddy.
What's this about?
I'm sorry.
I'm Jerry Barrett.
I recognize you
from the photos.
They barely do you justice.
The usual.
I'm friends
with your sister.
She showed me
your photos.
I-I work at the bank
across the street.
Um, Julia's my client.
She...
wanted to set us up.
Oh, I-I'm afraid you have me
mixed up with somebody else.
N-no,
I don't think so.
I-I've seen many pictures
of you several times.
That didn't sound
the way I wanted--
I guess I just have
one of those faces.
It's nice to meet you.
Yeah, s-say hi
to Lisa Cuddy
when you meet her
in the office you share.
Oh, thank God.
The I.C.U. isn't being attacked
by giant radioactive spiders.
Did I text you that?
That was meant
for my dream journal.
I wanted
to return your stuff.
Don't worry.
I didn't go AWOL.
I had my wife-maid
bring it over.
My sweater,
a coffee mug,
a half-used bottle of lotion,
and a DVD of Marley & Me.
Given your thing
for Owen Wilson,
I thought you might want
those last two back asap.
I don't get it.
You masturbate to Owen Wilson.
I meant the box.
Oh.
It's a symbolic gesture.
I want things to go back
to the way they were
before we started dating--
no more bad feelings,
no more issues,
just work.
Thanks for coming.
I haven't even spoken to you
since you hurt yourself.
I was self-destructive.
It won't happen again.
I'm making changes.
I'm gonna stop doing
stupid things.
Great.
The smart thing to do
would be to talk
about why you did it.
If you don't understand--
I think I could avoid
putting another hole in my leg
without talking
about my mother.
Well, I don't want
to find out you're wrong
by getting another phone call
from you in a bloody bathtub.
I'm a big believer
that the best way
to get past the past
is to shoot it in the head,
bury it in a deep pit,
and pour lye on it.
I'm just asking you
to talk about it.
You owe me.
Forget about saving
your life.
You exposed my daughter
to that obnoxious
pirate cartoon.
Bring me lunch tomorrow,
and we can plumb my depths.
I should have known the gallery
wasn't ventilated enough.
Hey, if it wasn't for you,
we'd be treating her
for third-degree burns, too.
That was a mistake.
He shouldn't have interfered.
I told you I'm sorry.
I want to share
your commitment,
but it's hard
for me sometimes.
Like when she read
your love letters in the middle
of the New Museum?
Yes,
I read The New Yorker.
That was a year ago.
And we're--
we're not together anymore.
Seriously,
you weren't really gonna let
that guy set you on fire.
He was just a plant
to get the crowd going, right?
If that's your interpretation,
I welcome it.
Afsoun believes explaining
her work limits its potential.
But between us,
he was real
and a total dick.
No sane person
would let themselves
be burned alive
for the sake of art.
My work is meant
to force the audience
to break with the rational
and see things in a new way.
Fine.
No sane person
would let themselves
be burned alive
to "break with the rational."
I feel...
Luca, hand me
the oxygen mask
behind you.
Luca!
Congratulations.
It's a gestational sac.
Can't see anything
this early.
I know.
I just figured
this would help me process
what's happening.
- There's a lot we got to figure out.
- We have almost eight months.
You're not having doubts,
are you?
No.
Are you?
Definitely not.
Nice, cozy home
for little Ruben.
It's a family name.
It's a sandwich.
Named for my family.
♪ if you like piña coladas ♪
♪ ♪
It's just House.
I swear to God,
stay out of my personal life.
Where is the downside here?
Huh?
Jerry is cute.
He's a senior V.P.
He kite-surfs
in Costa Rica every winter,
and he loves his mother.
Seasonally?
Or is that
just the kite-surfing?
Is this about House?
What?
Like I secretly wish
I could alter
the laws of the universe,
change who we are,
and magically
make it work out?
Yes, that's exactly
what I'm asking.
My sarcasm indicated no.
No, your sarcasm indicated
you wanted to avoid
actually saying anything.
Look, Lisa...
All I know
is you seem stuck.
And I don't like seeing you
like that.
She got worse
in the hyperbaric chamber.
It's not C.O. poisoning.
I think
we should consider infection
and test the assistant.
I couldn't get his attention.
He was in a daze.
- You think that's a symptom?
- He's in love with her.
He was probably overwhelmed,
couldn't decide what to do.
What's he been doing
since she was admitted?
Did he bring anything
from the patient room
to the treatment room?
A few things--
a handbag,
flowers,
stuffed elephant.
Does she seem
like the kind of woman
who needs a stuffed animal?
Who are you calling?
Oh, of course.
What are you wearing?
Oh, I can see
what you're wearing.
Go to her room.
Now go address
the elephant in the room.
This is a nanny Cam.
The reason Luca
couldn't decide
what to do
in the treatment room
is the same
as in the gallery.
He's been told
not to intervene.
Congratulations.
We've become
her latest work of art.
It shouldn't have surprised us.
All her work
is based on personal traumas.
She's had Luca taking notes,
videotape her treatments,
collect things,
like sharps and bandages.
It'll all go
into a gallery installation.
Well, then I guess as long
as long as the exploitation
is properly motivated,
it's all okay.
♪ If you like piña coladas ♪
Ultrasound showed a cyst
on her pancreas--
we drained it.
Why are we even
discussing this case?
She lied to us.
It's opening us up
to malpractice.
Our practice opens us up
How do we know
she's actually sick?
Her being sick is a clue.
She would have let
that guy
set her on fire
for the sake of her work.
You think she's scared
of a little arrhythmia?
She probably
huffed paint thinner.
She would have let him
set her on fire
because of the honesty
of her work.
- Faking an illness doesn't fit.
- Thirteen's right--
at least her conclusion was.
Everything else
was laughably wrong.
If the patient
induced pancreatitis
and a heart attack,
she'd be suicidal.
Exactly. She's risking
her life all the time.
Exactly.
If she wanted to be dead,
she'd be dead
a long time ago.
Pretending to cheat death
pays better than water colors.
Coxsackie B fits.
But do a spiral C.T.
of her biliary tree
to rule out gallstones.
Fine.
I'll get the C.T.
Sure. I'd be happy
to come with you.
Thanks for asking.
You're supposed
to stay in bed--
doctor's orders.
If you really cared
about me,
you wouldn't be so obvious
when you scheme
to prove me wrong.
You volunteered because
you want to C.T. her lungs,
not her biliary tree.
You want to find fibrosis
and prove
your "paint thinner" theory.
If I don't come with,
when you fail,
you'll pretend
you never tried.
I don't really have
a choice, now, do I?
Since I've seen your paycheck,
I probably shouldn't.
Canned beans
aren't so bad...
as long as they're cooked
over an oil-drum fire
under a bridge
with the king of the hobos.
I feel dizzy.
Pale,
diaphoretic,
tachycardic,
B.P.,
80 over 40.
Internal bleeding?
Get her out of here
and scope her.
I'm so sorry.
Ooh.
The colonoscopy
didn't find the bleed,
so we got to look
by your liver.
Luca, please.
We need to document everything.
Ooh.
Hold this.
I'm just below
the celiac artery.
No blood.
Could it be leaking
into her thighs?
No swelling,
no asymmetry.
So where's the blood going?
Why are you looking down there?
'Cause I don't like beans.
- You stood me up.
- Sorry.
Should have scheduled
my patient's internal bleeding
for Thursday.
You're still playing the same
petty, passive-aggressive games.
Got you to go all the way
to the second floor
of a building
you work in.
Boy, did I screw with you.
You said
you were going to change.
Check the sign.
It says you got to treat me
with intensive care.
I'm expressing my anger.
You should try it.
Right now, let's finally have
our fight.
All we do is fight.
No, all you've done
is pull pranks
or have temper tantrums
th Wilson, never me,
marry mail-order prostitutes,
make me go to your wedding--
Dominika is
a licensed aesthetician.
You cut open
your own leg.
So all this was about you?
You don't think
it was even related?
House, we've never even had
a conversation
about our breakup.
You are obviously
still angry at me.
And it's hurting
both of us.
Wow, I hadn't realized
the incredible healing power
of lunch.
I know one conversation
isn't gonna solve
everything,
but it is a start.
It's a privacy curtain.
It wasn't working.
Lunch at 1:00,
tomorrow in the cafeteria.
You happy?
How many of those
have you had today?
I don't know.
Is "your mother" a number?
The patient is a fraud.
I found a puncture in the
dorsal vein of her left foot.
- Shooting up heroin wouldn't explain--
- not heroin.
She was injecting herself
with her own red blood cells.
It caused her heart issues, and
when her hematocrit evened out,
we mistook it
for internal bleeding.
It must have been
a very distinctively shaped
and awfully talkative puncture
for you to get all of that.
Browser history
on her laptop helped.
She was researching
blood doping
among other things.
- She was researching me?
- For months.
This isn't about creating art
in the moment.
It's about you.
She set you up.
We sent a Uni over to
his apartment and the hospital.
Yeah, he won't be there.
Any ideas?
When you find him,
you're gonna arrest him?
Is there some reason
you think I shouldn't?
Knowing him,
he'll be in a bar.
He'll find one that matches
how he feels inside.
It'll be the most dark,
depressing hole
you can find in New Jersey.
Now you're just
pissing me off.
I'm really sorry. I-I didn't
know she researched you.
I had no idea she--
If you don't know anything,
then why are you talking?
Please don't take
it out on Luca.
I'll take it out
on whoever I think
will irritate you the most.
I thought you would understand
someone who uses their work
to deal with pain.
I didn't realize
that search engines
could look within the soul.
You're standing in front of me
in a hospital gown.
What the hell
was the point of this?
What personal trauma
are you exploiting--
Sorry--mining
for its artistic potential?
My illness.
I did the blood doping
to intrigue you,
but I was already ill.
Wait.
You're really sick?
Why me?
Do you know what you have?
Yes.
So tell him.
If I do, there won't be
any game for him,
and then there won't be
any art for us.
Why me?
I don't answer
those questions.
You know,
there's a lot of games
I could play
that don't involve dealing
with narcissistic,
manipulative poseurs.
But this is a puzzle
tailor-made for you.
You don't know which
of my symptoms are real,
which are fake,
which ones I'm not even
telling you about.
I know that
intrigues you.
Do you really want
to end it now?
No.
You want us to waste a bed
on her?
You took an oath...
An oath to be cool.
At least that was the one
I mumbled under my breath
while everyone else
was doing the boring one.
Even if she is sick,
which I don't believe,
she also says
she has a diagnosis.
So it's either just a lie,
or it's just a game.
So what?
I like the game. It's fun.
Go get a blood culture.
Check for parasites and bacteria.
This is the new House--
half the leg power,
twice the irresponsibility?
The new House is about making
my life healthier.
Never said anything
about yours.
Go get her blood.
I'll do it.
He's going through
a tough patch right now.
If this is the distraction
he needs
to keep him
in his hospital bed,
I'm sure it's better
than any of the alternatives.
That was incredibly
condescending.
Did it work?
♪ If you like piña coladas ♪
Why do you keep ducking
your wife's calls?
Ex-wife.
I'm sure she just wants
to congratulate you
about knocking up
a 22-year-old nurse.
I haven't told her yet.
But you have told her
you're not gonna sleep
with her anymore, right?
How are you planning
on letting her know?
Just invite her
to the bris?
I'm trying
to let her down easy.
Rachel never wanted
to have kids.
I don't want
to hurt her feelings.
Yeah.
You are all about feelings.
I've loved Rachel
for 20 years.
What if she never speaks
to me again?
She's gonna find out.
It better be from you.
You can't cheat your way
out of this one.
What is it?
Oh, just the nausea.
She said her back
was hurting earlier.
What's the pain level
on a scale of one to ten?
Five.
How do we know
we can take her word for it?
We can't.
Fun, huh?
Roll on your side.
Grey Turner's sign.
We're done playing.
Your pancreas is releasing
corrosive enzymes.
It'll eat away
at the surrounding organs.
But you must know that.
The doctor who diagnosed you
would have said what will happen
if you don't get treatment.
Just tell them.
If you know
what's wrong with you,
tell them
so they can fix it.
How many projects
have we done together?
You're always so worried.
Have you ever gone wrong
trusting me?
That pancreatic cyst
we drained--
it's back,
and she doesn't care at all.
You think
she actually is suicidal.
I would, but how did
she give herself the cysts?
Tox screen was negative,
and there's no sign
of trauma.
There is
another explanation.
The reason
she didn't react
isn't 'cause
she wants to die.
It's 'cause she knows
she can't do anything about it.
Whatever she has is fatal.
That should narrow it down.
What are we doing here?
Testing a theory.
It's based on some stuff
you can't understand,
like RR variability,
and some stuff you can,
like the fact that she shaved
her head in an art piece
four months ago.
That was a commentary
on society's--
It was a commentary
on the fact
that it was gonna fall out
anyway,
and she wanted
to hide why.
Cancer?
Are--are you sure about that?
See that tumor-ish thingamajig
near her "brainamabob"?
Oh, God.
Are you getting this?
Game's over.
I won.
Primary CNS lymphoma
with associated
paraneoplastic syndrome.
Is that really what it is?
Yes.
Four months ago,
I had some vision
and balance problems,
and New York Mercy
diagnosed me.
The tumor was too close
to the brain stem to cut out,
so they did a few rounds
of radiation.
But it didn't work,
and they sent me home.
That was around the time
you broke up with me.
We were having a fling.
It wouldn't have been fair
to involve you.
I'm involved now.
You just didn't want
to open up.
Luca, my mind
was not clear then.
And then you cleared it.
Then you realized
you could use your death
to make your magnum opus.
Maybe you wanted to show
that no one can cheat death,
even an entire team of doctors
with unlimited resources.
Or maybe your first doctors
didn't treat you like a person--
just a series of symptoms.
You wanted to re-create
that depersonalization.
And I was the man to see.
If that was what I thought,
I don't any longer.
You spent time with me.
You took this personally.
No, I didn't.
And I don't actually think
your piece is about anything.
I think you just figured out
that you're mortal.
You're just a bag of cells
and waste
with an expiration date.
You wanted to act out.
You wanted people to notice.
Maybe you even prayed for
a different answer this time.
I got a title
for your piece--
"It Doesn't Mean Anything."
You're forging my name
on prescriptions again.
No.
What you just said implies
that I stopped at some point.
20 minutes ago,
I put a notice out
to all local pharmacies
to require verbal authorization
before filling
my prescriptions.
You have any idea how much extra
work you've just given yourself?
You're not gonna
last a week.
I've been dealing
with this for years.
But it's over--
your liver,
your hearing,
never mind the fact
that each scrip you write
is a separate felony.
You will serve time,
so could I.
You've chosen this moment
to give me crap
about my Vicodin use?
You filled this
three days ago.
Now it's almost half gone.
So is my leg.
It's a month supply.
The amount you're taking
has nothing to do
with physical pain.
Okay.
So maybe I am trying to numb
myself a little,
because I'm trying
to change,
trying to stop
being self-destructive.
So you can only handle
not self-destructing
by being self-destructive?
What do you want from me?
I don't know, House,
but I'm worried about you.
I don't know how many times
I can watch you
cut off pieces of yourself.
Now it's the I.C.U.
Next time it'll be the morgue.
You're miserable.
And you're angry.
And I want you
to actually deal with that
and not just try to medicate
the issue away.
No.
You know
what I feel right now?
I don't feel miserable
or angry.
I don't feel good
or bad.
I feel nothing...
Which feels great.
What are you doing?
Moving on.
In the direction of my house,
where I got some more pills.
If you're discharging yourself
against doctor's orders,
you've got to check
that box.
I'm a doctor.
So, technically--
Wouldn't it be easier
if you just checked the box?
Why are you still here?
I'm going as soon
as the nurse brings me
something for my eczema.
I figured it was irritated
by the paint thinner
poured on me
in the gallery.
Does this mean something?
It's not eczema.
And it's not cancer.
It's Wegener's granulomatosis.
Biopsy confirmed
that what you thought was eczema
was actually a swelling
of the blood vessels
in your skin.
It also explains
the pancreatitis
and the mass in your brain.
And it's treatable.
Um...
What's the treatment?
We could do steroids alone
to shrink the growth
in your brain,
but it's much better to add
another course of radiation.
Radiation?
On my brain?
But it made me fuzzy
last time.
It was harder to work.
I am still slowed down
from it.
And it'll get worse.
But, you know,
dying can also do a number
on your ability to think.
I'm sorry.
I can't do the radiation.
They just said
it was a better treatment.
It could save your life.
My life's not worth anything
if I can't do my art.
You have friends,
people who care
about you.
This is my brain,
my work,
and my life, Luca.
You have more.
This is not
some great performance
piece anymore.
This is just crazy.
I'm sorry.
I can't watch you die...
Not when you
can save yourself.
Good-bye, Afsoun.
Good for you.
- So.
Why did I ever ban alcohol
from the cafeteria?
Before I forget,
there's a brush.
Tortoise-shell handle,
natural bristles--
wasn't in the box.
If you could look for it...
Like the Lindbergh baby.
You dating anyone?
We don't have to--
Look, it's just
standard lunch conversation.
Not for us.
Okay, well,
if you've gone over
to the "we don't talk
about things" side,
then I've got a pot roast
in the oven.
No.
I haven't dated anyone
since you.
Well, you know what they say--
once you go gimp...
We s-should talk
about your leg.
You think I have
unresolved issues,
and you are
the unresolved issues.
Yes.
But it's--it's--
I think it's more than that.
It's your life,
your choices.
I did it
to fix my life.
No, wait.
No, I did it because
I'm a deeply unhappy person.
No--no, I did it
to get sympathy from you.
I did it to piss you off.
I did it
because I'm not over you.
Or I was over you,
and I was moving on.
I did it because I wanted
to know what it's like
not to be in pain.
I did it because I want
to feel more pain.
Whatever the reason, it was
a bad reason and a bad idea.
That's all that matters.
Good lunch.
House...
Talk to me!
I already did.
No, you just parroted back
what Wilson and I've been saying
to you the last few days.
- Get out of my way.
- No.
Oh, you pulled a stitch.
House, please
just talk to me.
You want to know
how I feel?
I feel hurt.
I know.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
Did I make
the wrong choice?
Five years,
through every opening,
every installation,
every day
and every night,
he was there the whole time.
Except the first time
you were diagnosed.
You broke up with him,
and you had to go
through all of that alone.
Maybe that's the real reason
you're doing this piece--
so that this time
you can have him with you.
You still could.
Hi.
Uh, Lisa Cuddy.
Nice to meet you.
I'm sorry
about the other day.
I--there were some personal
things going on in my life,
and I wasn't at my best.
Well, in retrospect,
my approach could've come off
as a little creepy.
No.
On a scale from one
to creepy,
you were
maybe mildly unnerving.
Paging Dr. Stateman.
Dr. Stateman, please.
Rache.
Sorry I ducked your calls.
I keep making the same mistakes,
but at some point--
Chris...
I'm pregnant.
I...
didn't expect that.
Sorry.
Just checking the stitches
on my penis.
Your leg okay?
- It's healing.
- Good.
Just came to grab
the radiation-therapy forms.
What?
Afsoun changed her mind.
Get out.
You made a decision.
- I changed my mind.
- Why?
Because there
are more important things than--
Than what--
than your brain,
your abilities?
It's where
everything comes from--
any meaning in your life,
any happiness.
Not all happiness--
He's already left once.
He's gonna leave you again.
You don't need to depend
on people
who are gonna let you down.
If you do this,
you're a pathetic hypocrite.
You're saying that
your whole life, all your work
up until him was a pointless--
Why are you doing this?
House I can hear
your phone ringing.
You alright?
You had lunch with Cuddy?
Yeah.
How was it?
The pasta arrabbiata
was cold.
Why don't we get a drink?
We could go
to the Sawmill.
Cuddy's is on the way.
I need to return this.
You think she's going to have
an emergency tangle?
It was on my mind.
I want to get it off.
Want me to come?
If I get in trouble?
I'm delivering a hair brush.
What just happened?
Get out.
House,
what are you mad about?
Aah!
You're right.
I feel much better.
You want another one?
No, I think
I've had enough.
What do you think
I should do today?
I don't know.
Go home?
Not tonight.
Cheers.
♪ When I'm with you ♪
♪ all my brothers, oh ♪
♪ I feel like a king ♪
♪ it feels like I'm dreaming ♪
♪ when that blood goes rattling
through my veins ♪
♪ my ears start to ring ♪
♪ I notice what matters ♪
♪ and I got nothing
to lose but ♪
♪ darkness
and shadows ♪
♪ got nothing
to lose but ♪
♪ bitterness and patterns ♪
♪ oh ♪
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net