Hey. Thanks.
No, no, no... Here.
You got this whole thing
wrong, Em.
It's the rock star that's
supposed to be late, not
the rock-star photographer.
Sorry. Morning sickness.
Touch the belly.
It's the first time
I've been asked to do that.
Come on. It's good luck.
Okay.
Hit the Kinos behind the drop.
So what do you think?
I think people
aren't gonna get it.
Come on.
"All-American Rejects."
Juxtaposing a classic image
of Americana with
modern pop culture youth.
Oh, yeah.
Everyone loves
a good juxtaposition.
My fans were born in the '90s.
You know what?
You do this picture,
you'll gain 40 years of fans.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I love the Rockwell thing.
I thought so.
Okay. Kill the house lights.
Let's go!
Hang on. Hey, who's in charge
of the backdrop?
Naomi?
Yeah?
What's wrong with it?
Well, the words are
completely jumbled.
What, you can read that?
Of course.
You okay?
No. Oh, God.
I could be having a...
What's the mnemonic?
"F" is for face.
Is my smile crooked?
What are you doing?
"A" is for arms.
Arms.
You should really sit down.
Can someone
get her some water?
"S" is speech.
I'm slurring? I'm slurring?
"F-A-S-T."
"T" is for time.
Hurry. Somebody, call 911.
Tell them I'm having a stroke.
Hi. I'm Dr. House.
My boss says you're important.
Personally I don't get
what's so hard about
making Scarlett Johansson
look pretty.
Arms out in front of you.
Palms up like
you're holding a pizza.
Close your eyes.
It's so easy you should
consider a career change.
Probably make
a lot more money.
Dr. Mackman tell you
the clot was clear?
Yes.
And he said that you
and the fetus are fine?
Yeah.
He didn't mention
your pronator drift?
What's that mean?
Means Mackman is an idiot.
May I?
Yeah.
So,
you take thousands
of photos of someone,
but only one has to look good.
Kind of the opposite
of my business.
It's not about looking good.
People are always
hiding things.
I just keep shooting
until I can see what's
really inside them.
My eyes okay?
Eyes are gorgeous.
The vessels don't look so hot.
Microaneurysms predict
further strokes.
This is gonna happen again?
Unless I can figure out
the underlying cause.
Puff up your cheeks.
You should be able to
keep the air in. Means there's
weakness around the mouth.
So where'd you learn
to self-diagnose a stroke?
Oh, my baby's biological
father is a neurologist.
He once told me the FAST
mnemonic could
save my life one day. So...
Interesting pet name.
Most people go with
"husband" or "pookie."
He's gay.
Just a sperm donor.
So when you...
You turned him
for a night?
Just straight for one date?
Okay.
He took a magazine and a cup
into my bathroom.
A man after my own heart.
Different magazine obviously.
I'm rescinding Mackman's
discharge order.
My lackeys will be in
to do some tests,
take some more blood
and empty your catheter bag.
Not a moment you'll
want to cherish.
This is definitely different.
It looks almost like...
He's caring.
Find anything else
in the patient's folder?
Like a diagnosis?
Urinalysis revealed
excessive protein
and red blood cells.
Chem panel showed
a creatinine level over 2.5.
So first she strokes,
now her kidneys
are shutting down. Why?
Ultrasound showed
no tumors or stones.
No signs of fetal distress.
No urinary tract obstructions.
BP is fine. No pre-eclampsia.
Any of you guys
ever been to the Galápagos?
Was our patient there?
Dengue fever, avian pox,
even West Nile.
No.
I'm looking for
a vacation spot.
That mean we get vacation?
How would that differ
from your current status?
You're gonna do what? Relax?
Visiting family.
My uncle's a giant turtle.
What if the kidney failure
came first?
Kidneys could've
caused the stroke
not the other way around.
Kidneys don't often
get stuck in the brain.
I'm saying it threw a clot.
Early symptoms
of kidney failure are nausea,
vomiting, ankle swelling.
She would've mistaken it
for morning sickness.
Heart's way more likely
to throw a clot than a kidney.
Echo was normal.
The history indicates
no sign of cardiac problems.
No, but if one were to read
the history closely,
one would notice
that she had six cases
of strep.
In her throat.
That's the one about
10 inches above her heart.
Let me rephrase,
six cases of untreated strep.
She was
prescribed antibiotics.
No one takes them all.
They stop when they
start feeling better.
All strep is untreated strep.
What happens when
strep goes untreated?
Leads to rheumatic fever.
Which leads to... Cameron?
Mitral valve stenosis.
Which is a thickening
in the valve of the... Kidney?
No.
The kidney doesn't have
a mitral valve.
We'll go look at her heart.
Be easy to find.
It's the big red pumping thing
about 10 inches
below her throat.
That was weird.
He was the way he always is.
Which is weird.
Very still, Emma.
Sorry.
No problem.
He caught us with your hand
up my shirt. He's gotta have
a reaction to that.
You think that's what
the vacation is?
Yes.
The pain of losing you
is obviously forcing him away.
Coronal slice appears normal.
There's no way House
just lets this slide.
He's gotta be
planning something.
Maybe he just
doesn't give a crap.
Sagittal slice is clean.
You think he just
stumbled into that closet?
He knew we were there
and he wanted us to know
that he knew.
Or you wanted him to know.
Now he does and you're annoyed
because he doesn't care.
Right there.
Trans-axial slice.
Calcified mitral valve.
Barely.
That's not big enough
to throw a clot.
Obviously it is,
because it did.
House was right.
A valve in your heart
is narrowed.
It caused the clot
which lead to your stroke,
and the reduced circulation
caused the problem
with your kidneys.
And this will fix it?
The balloon will
force the valve back open
and you'll be fine.
EMMA: Can we do this without
a sedative?
It's very mild.
There really is no risk
to the fetus.
We'll monitor your baby's
heart rate separately.
We won't allow it to
decrease anywhere
near dangerous levels.
Thank you.
You're both gonna be fine.
Go ahead, Dr. Cameron.
Listen to that heartbeat.
It sounds so...
Start threading the catheter.
No, I don't want a layover
in Frankfurt, Taipei,
Singapore or London, Ontario.
That's why I asked
for a direct flight to
Phnom Penh.
How hard is it to not land?
Does it matter what I answer?
Well, then fine.
I'd be delighted to hold.
What's new?
Can you tell Cuddy
to stop interfering?
It's her job. What's new?
Good news is
Emma's heart is fixed.
Bad news is it's not her
underlying problem.
Her kidneys are still failing.
You're vacationing
in Cambodia?
You gonna unwind
in the Killing Fields?
Nope.
Gonna catch me
a fish this big.
Mekong giant catfish.
Weighs over 600 pounds.
Aren't those catfish
critically endangered?
That's why it's my last chance
to catch one.
All of our operators
are currently...
If the mitral valve had been
properly fixed the kidney
should be getting better,
which leads us to
the conclusion that you
screwed up the procedure.
Or you screwed up
the diagnosis.
The mitral valve thickening
was so insignificant
it probably wasn't the cause
of the kidneys or the stroke.
Probably never would've
been a problem.
She needs dialysis
and we need a new theory.
CHASE: There are only
a few possibilities.
Patient's pregnant,
could be pre-eclampsia.
We eliminated it
before because...
Re-check for proteinuria
and low platelets. What else?
Hypoperfusion.
The fetus is basically
a parasite stealing nutrients,
minerals, blood.
Put her on telemetry.
Or the pregnancy
is irrelevant.
Could be infection,
sepsis, HUSITTP.
CHASE: A cholesterol embolism
is just as likely.
Tiny particles of cholesterol
rain down, clog up the small
vessels of the kidneys.
Get a smear and ultrasound
her vessels for plaque.
That's it.
Has to be one of those five.
You know what would be
even better? If we'd narrow it
all the way down to one.
Thank you for holding.
We are experiencing
extremely high call volume.
Thank you for your patience.
She's 0 for five.
Either the differential
was wrong or she's faking it.
Kidney failure has to be
precipitated by...
One of the five
we've already ruled out.
The body only has so many ways
of screwing with the kidneys.
The labs must be wrong.
We did the labs.
No one else had access.
That's not quite true.
You put all your patients
through this many tests
or just the important ones?
We wanted to explore
all possibilities.
And?
We've eliminated
all the possibilities.
You telling me I'm dying
and you have no idea why?
Your body is
functioning properly.
So why are my kidneys failing?
The other body isn't.
There's something wrong
with the fetus.
Welcome to the world
of maternal mirror syndrome.
Mom's body is like
an intricate
German metro system.
All the trains run on time.
When she gets pregnant,
it's like a new station
opening in Düsseldorf.
Bunch or rookies
running things.
Bound to be mistakes.
Kids play on the tracks,
get electrocuted.
Before you know it,
the trains are backed up
all the way to Berlin
and you've got
a bunch of angry Germans
with nowhere to go.
And we all know
that ain't good for the Jews.
Who are the Jews
in this metaphor?
A few things can happen
to a fetus in distress.
It can become a miscarriage,
stillbirth,
a very sick baby
or on rare occasion
a time bomb
that kills mom
while it's dying.
Good news is,
we fix the fetus,
mom gets better.
It's the diagnostic equivalent
of a two-for-one sale.
I have read the outcome
of mirror syndrome
is almost always unfavorable.
"Unfavorable."
Is that doctor speak
for "dead baby"?
You think she'll be less upset
if you phrase it nicely?
We can tell her the truth,
that she'll be fine
as soon as we diagnose
a person who weighs
about one pound.
Can't touch it,
can't ask where it hurts,
can't see it.
If only there existed
giant machines that could
look through human skin.
Mirror syndrome
has a limited number
of known causes.
Tachyarrhythmia, fetal anemia,
placental chorioangioma.
All of which are fixable.
Which would be
un-unfavorable, right?
Could also be trisomy 13.
Ebstein's anomaly,
an aneurysm of Galen's vein.
And Dr. Storm Cloud
rained all over
the differential
and killed
the beautiful little baby.
Heart's easiest to see,
easiest to fix.
So let's start there.
When you did Mom's MRI,
did you get a look
at the fetus's heart?
It was in the range
but blurry. The fetus
was moving all over the place.
So we need another scan.
Yeah.
We'll just ask the fetus
to lie very, very still.
No need. I'm going to
paralyze it.
You wanna paralyze
Emma Sloan's baby?
Let me guess. Cameron?
Cameron and Chase
both had their concerns.
No, Cameron had concerns.
Chase just agreed with her
because he didn't want to lose
his all-access pass
to her love rug.
They're sleeping together?
If by "sleeping together"
you mean having sex
in the janitor's closet.
Here?
No, the janitor's closet
at the local high school.
Go, Tiger Cats!
Do you have one of those
camera phones? 'Cause I got
a MySpace account.
I will deal with them
after I deal with you.
Oh, come on.
Let's gossip some more.
I'm sure she's into bondage.
Paralyzing a one-pound baby
risks damaging...
Not paralyzing the thing
risks not getting
a clean MRI of its heart,
which we need to
save its life, which we need
to do to save Emma's life.
You're gonna need to
get her consent.
Well, that shouldn't be
too hard.
"Sign here or you
and your baby both die."
I'm going with you.
Oh, good.
You said sedation was risky.
This sounds insane.
The injection goes into
the umbilical cord.
The baby won't feel a thing.
Fetus.
I'm lowering expectations.
It works here and on dates.
The benefits outweigh
the risks
and the paralytic will
wear off in an hour, okay?
Must be easier to hear
you might die
than your baby might die.
But if there's anyone
I would trust to save my baby,
it would be Dr. House.
Fetus.
Hold this.
Dr. Cameron.
The MRI results back?
The fetus's heart
is structurally sound.
The problem's
with the bladder.
It's four times normal size.
Let me see.
The bladder's so engorged
it's taking up
the whole torso,
squeezing
all the other organs.
There's no room
for the lungs to develop.
The baby has a lower
urinary tract obstruction.
We can fix that
by inserting a shunt.
I'll give Emma the news.
Are you taking over the case?
House won't care.
He has his diagnosis.
Doctor Cameron.
Dating Chase can only end
in one of two ways.
House told you?
You get married
and live happily ever after,
or somebody gets hurt
and you two
can't work together,
and I have to fire somebody.
I would hate to see
my personal life become
such a burden to you.
I'm telling you this
for your own good.
I assume you're gonna have
this same conversation
with Chase for his own good.
Chase isn't the one
that's gonna get hurt here.
There's only room for one
but I could skooch over.
My social life
is my social life.
Couldn't agree more.
What goes on in the privacy
of a janitor's closet
is nobody's business except...
She told me to end it.
Is that what you want?
I was actually hoping
she'd fire one of you.
What are you doing?
Trying to avoid
altitude sickness.
Couldn't score a direct flight
to Cambodia,
so I've decided to scale
Argentina's infamous
Mount Aconcagua.
Perfect except for the fact
that you can't walk.
There's a tribe of
Mocoví Indians who actually
carry the elders up...
You're insane.
I'm an insane genius.
I set the chamber
for low pressure
instead of high.
Thinner air builds up
the extra red blood cells,
creates new capillaries.
Few more days in here,
I can save myself six weeks
at base camp.
Where's my MRI?
There's a blockage
in the urinary tract.
Simple terms,
your baby can't pee.
His bladder is swollen
and it's crushing his lungs.
Can you fix it?
We can insert a small tube
in the baby's bladder
that makes the urine
come out straight through
his belly
for the duration
of the pregnancy.
The bladder decompresses
and the lungs will be able to
develop normally.
When the baby gets better,
you should get better.
First we just have to
do a test
to determine whether
the baby's kidneys
are functioning properly.
And what if they're not?
If they're already
too damaged, then there's
really nothing we can do.
If this doesn't work out
you can always try again.
I miscarried twice
when I was married.
After the divorce,
I tried in vitro like
four times before this.
I'm 42. Maybe it's
just not meant to be.
What are you doing?
You're trying to be me,
so I thought
I'd try to be you.
You don't have
the cleavage for it.
But I have a much tighter ass.
Think every day should be
naked Thursday
or is that an oxymoron?
Let me see the results
from the bladder tap.
They aren't back yet.
They're gonna be inconclusive.
You think my diagnosis
is wrong?
Fetus doesn't pee,
amniotic fluid should be low.
Mom's level is fine.
Doesn't mean I'm wrong.
Could just mean
we caught the obstruction
early.
Either way your test
will be inconclusive.
The urine you've collected
has been sitting in that
fetus's bladder for weeks.
As my pappy always said,
"Stale pee is useless pee."
Fine. I'll do another tap.
Just as useless.
Old urine drops down
from the kidney
right after the first tap
'cause it's so backed up.
Bladder tap number three
will give you
the freshest pee.
That's when you'll find out
if this fetus has even
a fighting chance.
Thank you.
I'll run two more taps.
Since when does
the Dean of Medicine
run bladder taps?
She's an important patient.
Because she takes pictures
or because she's you?
Woman in her 40s, single,
using a turkey baster
as a last gasp at motherhood.
Maybe you want to
make sure she succeeds
so you'll still have hope.
You can't be a good doctor
if you're not objective.
It's your file.
I don't want it.
Then why did you just
say all that stuff?
To humiliate you.
You're taking the case back.
I don't want it.
Your diagnosis is right.
I want to go on vacation.
You can go on vacation
after you've cured her.
CHASE: Good news.
The fetus's urine
had appropriate levels
of protein and electrolytes,
so its kidneys aren't damaged.
Oh, wow.
We're gonna put the shunt in.
Your baby's lungs
should have more room to grow
and your symptoms
should go away.
But he'll still need surgery,
after he's born?
That's when we'll
remove the blockage
in the ureter.
You'll be the only mother
on the planet who appreciates
the value of a wet diaper.
Hey, could you hand me that?
I'm keeping
a visual memory book
of this entire surreal process
and this is the best part
of the story so far.
Yeah. Sure.
Thanks.
When'd you take this?
She did the
second bladder tap.
You should keep it.
Oh, I see her all day at work.
I don't need it.
Maybe you want to see her
after work.
I'm right, right?
I saw the way you look at her.
Thanks.
The shunt is
in the right position.
Bladder is starting
to decompress.
No infection.
Did House say anything else?
About us?
I thought you didn't
care about his reaction.
Trying to make him jealous?
I like my job.
He can't fire you
just because we're together.
We're not "together,"
and House can do
whatever he wants.
How's my baby?
Doing just fine, Emma.
So are you.
My stomach's killing me.
That's not her stomach.
Can you open your eyes, Emma?
I just need to take a look.
What is it?
Emma's jaundiced.
Her liver's shutting down.
Figures.
Just booked my trip
to Johnston Strait.
I thought you were
climbing Mount Whatever
in Argentina.
Apparently I'd have to live
with the Mocoví Indians
for 20 years
before they'd consider me
an elder.
Decided to go kayaking
with orca instead.
No legs required.
Can't leave yet.
Liver failure puts her case
back into the unsolved pile.
Increased AST, ALT
and her bilirubin's
off the charts.
Even fetuses lie.
We diagnosed a lower
urinary tract obstruction
because we saw one.
What if that's not
the whole story?
What if the little bugger
is hiding something?
The real reason
for the mirror syndrome.
Have we looked under its bed?
We checked its diary?
If it's not GU,
could be the heart.
Hypoplastic
left heart syndrome.
There were no
structural problems.
The lungs.
We won't be able to
get a good look
until they develop.
It'll be weeks...
She's not gonna last weeks.
What do you want to do?
Maternal mirror syndrome
has one sure fire cure.
Deliver the fetus.
That's not viable at 21 weeks.
You'll kill the baby.
Fetus.
Semantics
make you feel better?
Pretend it's not a person?
Can it play catch? Can it eat?
Can it take pretty pictures?
Who wants to tell her?
The swollen bladder
was not the only problem.
We can't leave it inside you.
We have to terminate.
Well, can't you deliver him?
Put him on a respiratory
machine till you
figure out what's wrong?
We can. And it won't matter.
The fetus is still at least
two weeks away
from being viable.
Well, I'll suffer through this
for two more weeks then.
You're on dialysis
for your kidneys.
Your kidneys can wait.
They don't make dialysis
for your liver.
You're not gonna make it
two more days.
I'm not gonna let you
kill my baby.
It's killing you.
I'm not having an abortion.
It's not a baby. It's a tumor.
I understand
dying for a cause.
Sacrificing your life so
your child might live. But
that's not the choice here.
Either it dies
or you both die.
Or you fix him
and we both live.
I can't fix it.
I'm scheduling a D&C.
I won't consent.
So I guess
you have two days
to figure it out.
Her kidneys are
almost irreparable.
She's developed severe DIC.
You have to force her
to terminate.
Did you give corticosteroids
to speed up the baby's
lung development?
No. I dropped an anvil
on its chest to prevent
lung development.
I'm trying to extinguish
the human race
one fetus at a time.
Give the lungs more time
to expand so you can
see inside them.
See if they're the problem.
My real patient is dying.
Very quickly. Like I wouldn't
advise her to buy
any green bananas.
The fetus is nothing more
than a parasite at this point.
Removing it
is an instant cure.
You're not gonna get Emma
to see it that way.
She's probably already
named the baby,
read him books,
had conversations with him.
See, you get it.
She'll listen to you.
No.
If you let this woman refuse
to terminate, you're helping
her commit suicide.
As her doctor
my recommendation is
against suicide.
If the baby had a doctor,
I think she would recommend
exhausting all possibilities
before taking its life.
Then she'd be an idiot.
Too bad she's your boss!
What if our original
assumption is wrong?
It isn't.
If we assume
she doesn't have
mirror syndrome,
then terminating her pregnancy
isn't gonna
help her liver at all.
We eliminated
all other possibilities.
The fetus is hydropic
and in distress.
Emma's kidneys and liver
are failing.
The diagnosis is solid.
Wow! The ass-kisser
won't agree with you.
You must be even wronger
than I thought.
Fine.
Let's assume she had
mirror syndrome
but we fixed it when we fixed
the baby's bladder.
That means that
her failing liver would be
completely unrelated.
If it is, we can fix it and
we don't have to terminate.
So her theory is
that our patient's
liver problems
were just a giant coincidence.
It's not a surprising
coincidence.
Pregnant women
can develop liver problems.
If this is the case,
we can actually
do something here.
Don't you guys
think that's worth exploring?
Acute fatty liver of pregnancy
would have the same symptoms.
Thank you.
Brownnoser.
Viral hepatitis,
HELLP syndrome.
Oh, look.
Sticking up
for your girlfriend.
Who says chivalry's dead?
He's not joking?
Be patient. She's going
through all of us. She'll get
that jungle fever eventually.
I'm not going through anyone.
You love him?
This can probably wait until
after you biopsy Emma's liver,
right?
We can't.
Her platelets are too low.
Once we pierce her liver,
it'll be next to impossible
to stop the bleeding.
Come in from above.
Instead of going straight in
through her abdomen,
go in through the veins
in her neck.
Transjugular hepatic biopsy.
If the liver starts to bleed,
it'll bleed right back
into her own veins.
Why don't you start
your vacation now?
Threading the guide wire
through the right
internal jugular vein.
So, the sleep lab...
You and Cameron not sleeping.
How serious is it?
It's nothing.
She's only doing it
to make House jealous.
Then why are you doing it?
You kidding?
You're approaching
the inferior vena cava.
Slow down.
You better not hurt her.
She already has a big brother.
She does?
You obviously care
very deeply about her.
I'm not protecting her.
I'm protecting myself.
A heartbroken,
lovesick Cameron
would be even more unbearable
than she is now.
You're through
the hepatic vein.
(MACHINE BEEPING)
I'm firing the needle.
Heart rate and BP spiking.
Get that out of her.
Fetus's heart rate
just dropped to 50.
We've got contractions.
Pre-term labor.
Start a terbutaline drip!
We were able to control
the pre-term labor
with tocolytics.
The contractions
have subsided for now.
And the liver biopsy
was negative. This is
definitely mirror syndrome.
Her baby's doing this to her.
We're out of options.
Did the biopsy cause
the pre-term labor
or did it happen on its own?
It doesn't make a difference.
Pre-term labor
can be a new symptom.
New information gives us
new theories.
Isn't that how it works?
Not in this case.
Her body's trying to do
what you refuse to, get the
baby out and save itself.
Patient's transaminases
are 10 times normal.
Her liver is on the verge
of shutting down completely.
A torch test could...
We don't have time
for more tests.
We have to terminate
or she'll die.
Then let's work faster.
Medicine doesn't work faster
just because you
hope real hard.
But it could help to see
what the baby's been hiding.
The only organ we haven't
been able to look inside
is its lungs.
The problem must be in there.
We haven't been able to
see inside because
they're underdeveloped.
We've already got her
on corticosteroids, but it'll
take weeks for them...
Then let's drown them
in corticosteroids,
multiple courses.
Speed up their development.
Giving the baby more than one
course will suppress
adrenal gland function.
Have long-term adverse effects
on fetal organ development.
Worse than death?
Emma's already on tocolytics.
The combination could put her
into pulmonary edema.
You'll just kill her faster.
It's the only chance we have
to see inside those lungs.
We're just gonna have to
make the baby better faster
than we make Emma worse.
Come on! This is the kind
of thing House does every day.
House thought we should
terminate six hours ago.
I'll do it myself.
Anybody gonna stop her?
Stopping the madness
is her job.
Somebody's got to be
Cuddy's Cuddy.
Nurse!
Pulmonary edema?
Who tattled?
It doesn't matter.
There's a reason we don't give
multiple courses
of corticosteroids.
Gee, thanks.
It's time to terminate.
That's not what she wants.
Look at her.
She didn't want to be
an incubator for a dead baby,
but that's what you've done.
Either get me a laryngoscope
or get out!
You were right.
You were all right.
Now the mom's lungs
are shutting down.
She's dying faster
than the baby's lungs
are developing.
I had to stop
the corticosteroids.
Have you spoken to the family?
The only family she's got
is that baby.
Well, he's biased.
What do you think
House would do?
House wants to terminate.
I mean if he didn't.
If he shared my position,
what do you think he would do?
He wouldn't share your pain.
He'd be objective.
Right.
He would prioritize
his problems.
He'd terminate.
He wouldn't be afraid
of screwing with her lungs
if there was a bigger issue.
There is no bigger issue.
She needs her lungs.
Not right now.
She's already on a respirator.
The machine is
breathing for her.
I can do whatever
I want to her lungs.
If you're playing catch in
the living room and you break
your mother's vase,
you may as well
keep playing catch.
The vase is already broken.
Yeah, except that room
can't breathe
without that vase.
I'm putting her back on
corticosteroids.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
It worked.
What worked?
I got the baby's lungs
to expand.
We should be able to figure...
Cab's on its way.
I have to finish packing.
I have a whole new
appreciation for what you do.
How hard it is to believe
when everyone around you
is telling you
that you're wrong.
Helps to know they're idiots.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
You're not objective.
But you're not an idiot.
These lungs are still
two weeks away
from being viable.
But big enough
for a diagnosis.
These tissue buds are new.
Could indicate
bronchopulmonary sequestration
or diaphragmatic eventration.
I was thinking bronchogenic
cyst or bronchial atresia.
Could be lung lesions, CCAM.
What about...
Move.
Thought you
started your vacation.
Somebody had to save
our boss's rotundous ass.
Latest MRI of the Sloan fetus.
Small buds in the lungs
could indicate...
Thanks.
Got the multiple choice
all worked out.
Question is, how do we pick
between A, B, C, D,
and none of the above?
Portable MRI is in her room.
We could get a current image.
The fetal lungs are so tiny
the MRI won't give us
the detail we need.
What would we do
if this patient were
not just a tadpole?
Say it was an actual person.
He is a person.
Thanks for playing along.
Pretend it's
a one-pound adult.
Forget the mom,
forget the womb, the placenta.
How would we get a better look
at what's in the lungs?
Transesophageal echo.
Can't access his esophagus.
High resolution CT
could give us a clearer...
Too much radiation
for a one-pound person.
You can't just shoot
everything down, Chase.
You're not me. Collaborate.
A ventilation perfusion scan
would be next.
How do we get a fetus
to breathe in
a radioactive isotope, idiot?
If it were really a person
and we had no other options
we'd do an
exploratory surgery.
Cut into its chest
and have a look around.
Let's do that.
You're the one who insists
we treat it like a person.
I'll put it back
when I'm done.
Me again.
It's your friendly
neighborhood belly squirter.
We're gonna do
open fetal surgery.
Open the uterus,
cut out the fetus
so we can look around.
I know you can't talk so
I need you to look petrified
if you consent.
The umbilical cord
won't be cut.
During surgery, your body
will basically serve as
the baby's heartllung machine.
We find what's wrong
and we fix it.
If we can.
Don't lower expectations
if you want them
to do something.
She should know
what she's facing.
This is incredibly dangerous.
It risks both your lives.
The only reason why
we're suggesting
it is because there's
nothing else we can do.
You all here
for the fetal surgery?
'Cause we're
way over capacity.
Mind each other's
personal space.
There are sharp implements
in the room.
Like this one.
Uterus is fully exposed.
And we're in.
Start draining
the amniotic fluid.
Have you never sucked beer
out of the bottom of a keg?
Where'd you go to college?
Give me that.
Affix the pulse ox
to the palm.
House?
Sorry.
Just realized
I forgot to TiVo Alien.
Fetal heart rate good.
Stats are stable.
Position him for the incision.
I see three well-defined
lesions.
It's definitely CCAM.
I should be able to
resect them.
(MONITOR BEEPING)
It's the mom. She's in V-fib.
Charging.
Clear!
I'm clear.
Looks like asystole.
Paddling isn't
going to do anything.
It's fine V-fib.
I'm going again. Clear!
We're gonna lose them both.
Clamp!
The surgery's not
doing this to her.
The fetus is.
Step away, House.
I'm going again.
The only way to save her
is to cut away the anchor
holding her down.
You keep going,
you're gonna get electrocuted.
Clear!
Going again. Clear!
(MONITOR BEEPING)
Heart rate's returning
to normal.
Continue with the lobectomy.
So my kidneys, liver and lungs
are all fine just like that?
Just like that.
That's amazing.
What's amazing
is how blonde your
baby's hair is.
My baby?
The thing in your belly
that tried to kill you.
You've never called him
a baby before.
Any pain?
Nothing I can't deal with.
You can only get out of bed
to pee, pooh or shower.
And absolutely no sex.
So stop flirting with me.
Sorry.
So this really worked?
He'll be normal?
Well, if you call
being born twice normal.
Hey, thank you.
Don't thank me.
I would've killed the kid.
Wanna grab a bite?
In a minute.
Emma asked me to
bring up her camera.
I'll walk with you.
When'd she take
this picture of you?
You look so...
I'm smiling.
I have a nice smile.
No, I've never
seen you like this.
She got you to glow.
What were you doing?
What did she say to you?
I always glow.
House.
Need you to take
a look at something.
I'm off the clock.
Just open it.
A first-class ticket
to Vancouver Island.
Shoot! The wrong envelope.
I think it's great.
Yeah.
Who doesn't like Canadians?
It's big.
You're trying to have a life.
You're trying to
enjoy yourself.
You didn't need to apologize.
I'm not. I told you why I...
Screwed up.
I saved a life.
I saved two lives.
You
let your maternal instinct
get the best of you
and nearly kill two people.
Case like this, you terminate,
mom lives 10 times out of 10.
You do what you did
mom and baby both die
9.9 times out of 10.
Sometimes point one
is bigger than 9.9.
No, it's smaller.
Exactly 9.8 smaller.
Always is. Always will be.
Well, not for Emma.
And not for her son.
Now go away and be happy.
www.tvsubtitles.net