(BEAUTIFUL PLAYING ON STEREO)
(SINGING) To all your friends,
you're delirious
So consumed in all your doom
Trying hard
to fill your emptiness
The piece is gone
Ten-minute warning.
I'm fine.
What about your meds?
Got it, Mom.
(SINGING) You are beautiful
no matter what they say
(GHOSTLY WAILING)
(HOUSE SNEEZING)
WILSON: House!
Need you.
Forget it. I'm going home.
Hay fever?
Oh, you must be a doctor
and everything.
Two minutes.
No.
The purple thingie
on the file means
that whoever is one of yours
which means cancer,
which means no way
it's two minutes.
Fine, I'm Iying.
30 minutes.
(WOMAN CHATTERING
ON PA SYSTEM)
Mystery of Iife.
Benadryl might help.
AIready did
1,000 milligrams.
Steam room?
Why, Jimmy.
We'II talk about this
in the morning.
I got a 9-year-old
with cancer.
AIveolar rhabdomyosarcoma.
Terminal kid
trumps your stuffy nose.
Not yet.
She's hallucinating.
So the rhabdo's in her brain.
Make her comfortable.
She's got about a week.
Yeah, except there is
no cancer in her brain.
Pristine CT scan, blood tests,
protein markers, all negative.
The cancer's in remission.
Which means
the hallucinations
are unconnected.
Fascinating, huh?
And not that it matters,
but if you fix whatever's
going on in her head,
you give her
maybe another year.
Long time for a 9-year-old.
No. It'II just fly by.
Five major surgeries,
a bone marrow transplant,
fourteen rounds of chemo
and blast radiation.
If it was me,
I'd just stay home
and watch TV or something,
not Iie here
under a microscope.
(HOUSE SNEEZES)
Don't worry.
Anything happens to you,
nobody's gonna Iift a finger.
Differential diagnosis.
On your marks, get set...
Hallucinations could be
caused by...
Whoa! Wait for it.
And go.
...Iatent neurotoxicity
from the chemo treatments.
No, patient's Iast round
of chemo was two months ago.
We would've seen it by now.
Genetic component?
Nothing on mom.
Dad split
when she was pregnant.
His medical history's
also clean.
What a guy.
What about graft versus
host disease from
the bone marrow transplant?
Infection
travels to her brain,
she has hallucinations.
BIood work and LP were clean.
But where there's infection,
there's meningeal swelling.
That CT shows no
meningeal involvement.
True.
Get a tox screen and an MRI.
We can do that,
if you wanna ignore
what we just discussed.
Sounds good.
Toxic exposure doesn't make
any chronological sense.
I guess
there is a third option.
She's making it all up
because she doesn't
wanna get in trouble
for breaking a mirror.
Unfortunately
we can't test for that,
so tox screen, MRI,
and you stay away
from the patient.
What'd I do?
Oh, well, you'II just get
all warm and cuddly
around the dying girl,
and insinuate yourself.
Probably end up
in a custody battle.
Chase, you handle the mom.
Tell her
that you'd just sit home
and watch TV and die,
but you've got
to go through the motions
and try to save
her daughter's Iife.
It's a doctor thing.
What the hell is this?
BIack walnut and ginger.
It's nice.
I'II just Iay you down
and I'II attach
this thingamajiggy.
Sat monitor.
Oh, a pro. Don't have to
explain anything.
I Iike it.
Central Iine for the chemo.
Yeah. Doesn't hurt
or anything, does it?
No, it's awesome.
Instead of an IV,
it saves me a Iot of time
and a bunch of needle sticks.
Oh, I don't think I've ever
heard anyone say they Iike
their central Iine before.
AII right, can I interest you
in a walk in the park?
(WATER GURGLING)
No, thanks.
Okay.
Don't want
any butterflies, either.
Doesn't matter what the walls
Iook Iike, you're still
Iooking for cancer.
Not today. We're Iooking
for an infection.
But I get your point.
You comfortable?
Yup.
AII right.
Let's get this over with.
A pro.
I Iike it.
Whoa! Look at the time.
I should've been out of here
20 minutes ago.
You've only been here
20 minutes.
I can't slip anything
by you, can I?
There's a patient in One.
Nah, I'm taking a sick day.
Take some CIaritin.
Everyone's a doctor suddenly.
Patient in One
requested a male doctor.
Balls are in your court,
doctor.
Union rules.
I can't check out
this guy's seeping gonorrhea
this close to Iunch.
Exam Room One.
Well, it's sexist, and
a very dangerous precedent.
If people could choose
the sex of their doctors,
you gals
would be out of business.
Exam Room One!
Sore throat?
Well, it's not Iupus.
Well, not everyone
can operate a zipper.
You know, the up, down,
what comes next?
My new girlfriend
never been with a guy
who wasn't circumcised.
So she freaked, and...
Ah-ha.
And you wanted Rivkah
to feel all gemutlicht.
I get it.
It's a shandah.
(EXCLAIMING)
I got some box cutters and...
Just Iike Abraham did it.
I sterilized them,
which I was told...
Stop talking.
I'm gonna get a plastic
surgeon. Get the Twinkie
back in the wrapper.
FOREMAN: House. Hey, House.
Andie's MRI
and tox screen were clean.
No infection, no neurotoxins.
(WOMAN CHATTERING
ON PA SYSTEM)
Oxygen saturation is 94%.
Check her heart.
Her oxygen saturation
is normal.
It's off
by one percentage point.
It's within range,
it's normal.
If her DNA was off
by one percentage point,
she'd be a dolphin.
We've got a patient
who for no obvious reason
is hallucinating.
Since it's not obvious,
I thought we'd go with subtle.
It doesn't matter.
If her sat percentage is off,
that means her blood
isn't getting enough oxygen.
That's a problem
with her Iungs, not her heart.
And a Iung problem
isn't causing hallucinations.
But the Iungs could
Iead us somewhere that is.
Welcome to the end
of the thought process.
Primary
pulmonary hypertension?
Maybe PE
or pulmonary fibrosis.
Could be some bizarre case
of kyphoscoliosis.
I'm going home.
While I'm resting, you guys
get some arterial blood gases,
once you confirm
that she is hypoxic,
I want a plethysmography,
chest x-ray, CT and V-Q.
But if all that comes back
negative, then snake
a catheter into her Iungs.
Don't worry,
if I don't sleep in,
I'II get bagels.
You ever had
this test before?
What's it for?
This goes
all the way up the vein
by your hip, into your Iung.
If I find something up there
blocking anything,
I pull it out. Simple.
It's gonna be easy.
The doctor at SIoan told me
I had a great aorta.
Oh, you have had
this test before.
Sorry.
I just Iike hearing you talk.
(MONITORS BEEPING)
I've never kissed a boy.
There's time yet for that.
There was a boy Iast summer.
I was at one of those
cancer camps. I just never
had the guts to ask him.
You know, there's
a good chance I'm not gonna
walk out of this hospital.
Even if I do, I'm nine.
Not a Iot of kissing going on
in the third grade.
You will walk
out of here, all right?
And you will kiss a boy.
There you go. A smile.
Will you kiss me?
No.
No one will ever know.
(STUTTERING) I'm sorry.
I can't.
I won't tell anyone.
Listen, you're nine years old.
I'm 30.
I just wanna know
what it feels Iike. Once.
This isn't
your Iast chance for that.
What if it is?
PIease kiss me?
Bagels.
FOREMAN: You didn't sleep in.
Didn't sleep, didn't breathe.
I'm dying.
CHASE: Pulmonary angiogram
of Andie's Iungs was clean.
Arterial blood gases
and CT scan were also normal.
Her heart and Iungs are fine.
Which gives us no explanation
for the diminished
sat percentage.
Yeah, oddly enough,
sometimes normal is normal.
Sometimes we can't see
why normal isn't normal.
Get her symptoms
on the board.
You're Ietting me
touch the markers?
It's written out
in my advanced
health care directive.
Should I be
incapacitated in any way,
you run the board.
Then Foreman.
Chase, you're just
not ready yet.
HOUSE: What else?
Guys, I know we
sort of ruled out infection,
but if we forget the Iabs
for a minute,
there is one infection
we didn't test for
because of her age.
Neurosyphilis.
There's no way.
If the infection dipped into
her cerebral cortex,
all peripheral functions
could be compromised.
No. She hasn't had sex.
She's nine.
Maybe it wasn't her idea.
I mean, she's been around
a Iot of adults.
AII the hospital visits,
the counselors
at the cancer camps.
You think
she's been molested?
And hiding it pretty well
if there's any of that
going on.
Yeah. AII girls
who've been molested
wanna talk about it.
Break out the rape kit.
She hasn't had sex.
Why are you so sure?
She told me
she'd never kissed a boy.
You read her diary, too?
She asked me to kiss her.
HOUSE: I rest my case.
A regular 9-year-old girl
does not have sex
on the brain,
not when a doctor's
threading a catheter
through her vein.
But she's not
a regular 9-year-old.
She's got terminal cancer.
Cancer doesn't
make you special.
Molestation
on the other hand...
She wanted one kiss,
before she dies.
If she's never kissed a boy,
it's a fair bet
she's never had sex.
Tell that to all the hookers
who won't kiss me
on the mouth.
Hey, here's a theory.
She has been molested,
seeks refuge
in romantic fantasies with
older men with great hair,
and I think
you Ieft out the punchline.
Victims of molestation
Iearn to work the angles,
manipulate people.
You did it, didn't you?
You kissed her.
It wasn't sick.
It was one kiss
for a dying girl.
One small...
One small kiss
before she dies.
Thank you. Thanks.
This is exactly why
you can't touch my markers.
Go see if she's had sex.
Okay.
No one's ever touched me.
We just need to be sure.
I Iike your hair.
I used to have
really curly hair. I always
wanted it to be Iike yours is.
Thank you.
AII right, that's it.
You're fine.
With a patient.
She dying?
No.
Then she can wait.
WILSON: Will you excuse me
just two minutes?
If only she'd been molested.
Then we'd have
something to go on.
HOUSE: No forced entry.
One hallucination.
Maybe it was just bad pork,
maybe there's nothing...
She's not fine.
Her sat percentage
dropped another point.
Which could suggest
a tumor in her Iung.
Lung wouldn't explain
the hallucination.
CT scans showed
both Iungs were clean.
Which means
there's a tumor in her heart.
Not a chance! Give me that.
I Ioosened it.
I opened it.
We've got an MRI
and an echo of her heart.
There's nothing there.
Give me one other explanation
for Iow oxygen saturation.
I can't.
There's only one condition
that simultaneously affects
the heart and brain,
but she...
Perfect, Iet's go with that.
Tuberous sclerosis in a kid
that also has
alveolar rhabdomyosarcoma?
Two different unrelated
cancers at the same time
is a statistical no-no.
What's the rate of cancer
in the general population?
One in 10,000?
Don't.
Don't start with the numbers.
Way I figure it,
one in 10,000 of them
should have another cancer.
Little girl
won the Iottery twice.
It happens.
So you're gonna cut her open?
Exploratory surgery.
I gotta find this thing.
You're just gonna grope around
inside an immunocompromised
9-year-old?
She could die on the table.
I know it's somewhere
near the heart.
House...you've got to do
better than that.
(OPERA MUSIC PLAYING)
Why are we here?
Better acoustics.
Now Iisten to this.
(WHOOSHING)
It's a mitral heart valve.
No. Get the wax
out of your ears.
This is the patient's
aortic valve.
I downloaded the audio
of her echocardiogram.
What are we trying to hear?
Tumor.
They tend to keep quiet
on account of them
not having any mouths.
But we could hear
an abnormality
in the sound of the valve,
which would indicate
the presence of something.
The tumor, for example.
If we could tell the surgeon
where to Iook,
this is no Ionger
an exploratory surgery,
it's a precision strike.
Her aortic valve
sounds normal.
Too bad.
Now Iisten to the dulcet tones
of Andie's tricuspid valve.
(SLOW BEATING)
Normal.
And this is her mitral valve.
(RHYTHMIC BEATING)
I don't hear anything weird.
You guys make me sad.
Listen again.
She's had one hallucination.
Why are we operating on her?
Why are we risking her Iife?
Because Wilson thinks
it'd be nice
to give the girl a year
to say goodbye to her mommy.
Guess maybe she stutters
or something.
Now shut up and Iisten.
Tricuspid.
(SLOW BEATING)
Mitral.
(RHYTHMIC BEATING)
Again.
CAMERON: Wait.
There.
There's an extra flap.
I'm gonna ask
the surgeon to Iook
at the mitral valve first.
Chase, I want you there.
I don't Iike
reading surgeon's reports,
they're boring.
I'm not really sure
I should be spending
more time with her.
She'II be unconscious.
You'II be safe.
I'II be there
when you wake up.
I'm gonna be fine, Mom.
(WOMAN CHATTERING
ON PA SYSTEM)
Brave kid.
She even gave her mom
a pep talk.
Mature, brave. She's a wonder.
What's your problem?
These cancer kids,
you can't put them all
on a pedestal.
It's basic statistics.
Some of them have got to be
whiny Iittle fraidy-cats.
You're unbelievable.
If there's not
one yellow-belly
in the whole group,
then being brave
doesn't have any meaning.
Andie handles
an impossible situation
with grace.
That's not to be admired?
You see grace
because you wanna see grace.
You don't see grace
because you won't go
anywhere near her.
HOUSE: Idolizing is
pathological with you people.
You see things to admire
where there's nothing.
Yeah, well, we're evil.
You find things to admire
where you shouldn't
be sniffing at all.
Like Debbie in Accounting.
She's nice.
You shouldn't know that.
You're married.
So, the Iittle kid
dying of cancer,
I shouldn't Iike her?
If you're dying,
suddenly everybody Ioves you.
You have a cane,
nobody even Iikes you.
I'm not terminal,
merely pathetic.
You wouldn't believe the crap
people Iet me get away with.
(MONITOR BEEPING)
They found a tumor.
It's in her Iung,
extending into her heart.
It wasn't visible on the MRI
because it's growing
along the heart wall.
Now, because of the placement,
the surgeon
has to temporarily remove
Andie's heart.
It's called an explant.
They cut out the tumor,
replace any damaged
heart muscle
with bovine patches.
That's a patch made
from the cow's pericardium.
It's a sac
that encloses the heart.
What are her chances?
The problem is,
there might not be
enough heart Ieft
once they remove
all of the tumor.
And if the tumor's
metastasized,
there's nothing we can do.
Dr. Murphy.
Just Iet me tie this off.
Doctor!
What?
She's got a bleed in her eye.
They got the tumor,
repaired her heart,
but she bled out of her eye.
She didn't
bleed out of her eye
from a heart tumor.
True.
The cardiac tumor was benign.
That's impossible!
Statistically...
Oh, shut up.
If the tumor's benign,
that means it didn't cause
her hallucinations.
That's why I'm mentioning it.
So, the tumor's a coincidence?
This is bad.
You're starting
to state the obvious.
No, you said it would be there
and it was there.
It can't be a coincidence.
A 9-year-old
with terminal cancer
gets an unrelated benign tumor
growing in her heart.
Why?
It's benign?
That's impossible.
Talk to Wilson.
And the retinal bleed,
another coincidence?
A clot could create pressure
behind the eye,
cause the bleeding.
A clot could explain the eye,
but doesn't explain
the hallucinations.
A clot could cause
mini seizures.
Great. Another thing
that's not causing
the hallucinations.
FOREMAN: Post-seizure
psychosis.
The brain sort of
corrects itself after
the seizure by hallucinating.
The clot
could explain the eye
and the hallucinations,
but what about the tumor?
Tumors the size of an octopus
wrapped around
a Iittle girl's heart
are not just a coincidence.
She's not healthy,
she's never been healthy.
WILSON: What's the theory
here? This girl's body's
a Iemon?
Faulty manufacturing,
everything's falling apart?
The tumor is Afghanistan,
the clot is Buffalo.
Does that need
more explanation? Okay.
The tumor is AI-Qaeda,
the big bad guy, the brains.
We went in, wiped it out,
but it had already
sent out a splinter cell.
A small team of Iow-Ievel
terrorists quietly Iiving
in some suburb of Buffalo,
waiting to kill us all.
Are you trying to say
the tumor threw a clot
before we removed it?
It was an excellent metaphor.
Angio her brain
before this clot
straps on an explosive vest.
HOUSE: Angio was clean.
There's no clot?
There's a clot,
we just can't find it.
You can't do
exploratory surgery
on her brain.
Are you sure
you're not a neurologist?
(SIGHS)
Okay.
She's gonna die.
Well, the clot's
not gonna go away quietly.
It could blow at any time.
Are you gonna Iet them know?
I guess so.
Can I come with?
To tell Andie she's gonna die?
That's very un-you.
She's such a brave girl.
I wanna see how brave she is
when you tell her
she's gonna die.
Go to hell.
(CRYING)
What would you do
if you were told
you were gonna die?
I don't know,
I'd be devastated.
You'd cry Iike a baby.
Everybody would.
She's not doing anything.
She's a rock.
She's brave.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Why?
She's gone through
more than most people do
in a Iifetime.
So what?
Does that mean
she's ready to die?
What if her bravery
is a symptom?
The clot is causing
hallucinations and messing
with her emotions.
You think her bravery
is chemically based?
It would tell us
where to Iook for the clot.
Where's the fear center?
The amygdala, near the
hippocampus. It's a big area
and a busy one.
You blindly cut in there,
you'II kill her.
Only time you're gonna
see this clot is at autopsy.
Then Iet's do that.
Is it still illegal
to perform an autopsy
on a Iiving person?
Are you high?
If it's Tuesday, I'm wasted.
It's Wednesday.
I want to induce
a hypothermic cardiac arrest.
Once the patient's on bypass,
we siphon off
two Iiters of blood,
perfuse the brain
while she's in an MRI.
You're actually
talking about killing her.
Just for a Iittle while.
I'II bring her right back.
Oh, well, in that case,
go ahead. Why are we
even talking?
If we do nothing,
she's dead in a day,
maybe a week.
The kind that Iasts.
We need FDA approval
for any surgical technique
that's used
for diagnostic purposes.
Absolutely.
If we were doing
anything invasive. But
there's nothing invasive...
You know,
I'm not cutting into her head.
I'm just Iooking for a clot.
Not invasive?
You're killing her.
Don't split hairs.
If it works, she Iives.
(SIGHS)
Make sure the mom understands
that this is
a million-to-one shot.
I'II see that Wilson
passes that along.
The plan is
basically
to reboot your daughter.
Like a computer.
We shut her down.
Then restart her.
How do you restart
a 9-year-old girl?
We cool
her core body temperature
to 21 degree Celsius.
Use blankets, ice.
Sort of Iike hibernation?
Not quite. In hibernation,
a bear's heartbeat
is just very slow.
In cardiac arrest,
there is no heartbeat.
So she's dead.
Temporarily, yes.
By cooling her,
we Iimit the risk of damage
when we remove her blood.
Not all of it,
two to three Iiters.
Half her blood?
Then we put it back.
It's called
perfusing the circuit.
In this case, her brain.
And using an MRI,
we'd have a very brief window
to hopefully see
the outline of the clot.
If it's there,
and it's operable,
we go get it.
And Andie walks out of here.
(DOOR OPENING)
(SIGHS)
Signed consent forms.
Great, thanks.
You sound better.
I stacked a combo
of Mentholatum, a few Vicodin,
and something else
which I can't remember.
Should be able
to ride the high
for a couple hours.
What did Andie say?
About what?
About this?
I didn't talk to her.
She doesn't need to know
the specifics
of this procedure.
What if you're right
about her?
What if
she just is that brave?
That doesn't mean
she's mature enough to handle
this kind of decision.
Either she understands,
or she's not brave.
You can't have it both ways.
If she does understand,
then she deserves to know
what's going on.
(MONITOR BEEPING)
I'm Dr. House.
I've seen you around.
Your mom tell you
what we're gonna try?
Sort of.
Tomorrow's test
could take 10 hours.
Given your present condition,
you might not even
make it through.
My mom's done
a Iot of research.
How do you feel about it?
If we figured maturity came
from how much time
you've got Ieft
instead of how Iong
you've been here,
this would be your call.
I don't have a choice, right?
I could give you one.
I wanna get better.
You've got cancer.
If I fix this...
I have a year.
A year of this.
A Iot of people
wouldn't want that.
would just want it to be over.
Are you asking if I wanna die?
Nobody wants to die.
But you're going to.
The question is, how?
How much
you're gonna suffer, and
how Iong.
I'm asking
if you want this to be over.
What would you tell my mom?
I would give her
10 excellent medical reasons
why we can't
do this procedure.
I can't just Ieave her
'cause I'm tired.
But you can't stay for her,
either.
But she needs me here.
This is your Iife.
You can't do this
just for her.
I Iove her.
Thank you for joining me
for tonight's dress rehearsal.
PIaying the part of Andie
is Morty Randolph.
For his donation to science,
we give our thanks.
Once Andie is cooled
and goes off bypass,
we have 60 seconds
to get two Iiters of blood
out of her body,
back into her for the pictures
to find the clot in her head.
If our star
is bumped tomorrow,
(SHRILL BEEPING)
while my MRI is on,
these red Iights will go off.
Which will mean we have
no usable test results.
No test results,
it's goodbye Broadway.
You guys'II be wearing
bad cat suits in Des Moines.
We'II have neurosurgeons here
with a view of the monitors,
cardiac surgeon there
in case we need
to open her up.
Anesthesiologists, one by
the cardiac bypass machine,
one by the cooling apparatus.
Girls in the chorus,
if you're over 5'10",
stick with me.
Okay, give me 60 seconds
on the clock.
Show time.
A five, six, seven, eight!
HOUSE: Siphon off the blood
through the arterial Iine.
Whoosh.
Sound of blood draining.
More whoosh.
(GULPING)
(SHRILL BEEPING)
And we kill her.
Again.
(BEEPING)
MALE TECHNICIAN: Sorry,
my hand slipped.
How hard can this be?
It's a Iittle busy down here.
Again!
(BEEPING)
ANESTHESIOLOGIST: If we didn't
have to Iavage
her gastrointestinal...
Again!
We could bolt it to the table.
Gruesome and Iow-tech.
Kiss me, I Iove it.
A five, six, seven, eight!
FEMALE TECHNICIAN:
Here you go, Doctor.
This'II make you sleep.
A Iot of people.
Big musical number, kiddo.
A Iot of people here
to make you Iook good.
You're kind of
freaking me out.
He gets that sometimes.
Deep breath, honey.
Okay, go!
Intubate her.
FEMALE TECHNICIAN: Is that one
okay?
FEMALE TECHNICIAN: Charge.
Here.
ANESTHESIOLOGIST:
Body temperature
37 degrees Celsius.
HOUSE: Start the cooling.
You, go.
She's shivering.
200 milligrams of Vecuronium.
ANESTHESIOLOGIST: 24 degrees
Celsius.
(BEEPING)
DR. MURPHY: We have afib.
What?
She's dead,
that's the whole idea.
Go!
ANESTHESIOLOGIST:
One Iiter out.
Two Iiters.
Okay, put the blood back in.
Reperfuse the circuit.
Anything, people,
anything at all.
NEUROSURGEON 1 : Internal
carotid artery in cavernous
sinus is fine.
NEUROSURGEON 2:Ten seconds!
Vestibulocochlear nerve
intact.
Middle meningeal artery clear.
NEUROSURGEON 2: Five seconds!
Nothing.
NEUROSURGEON 2:
We're over the Iimit. We've
got to start rewarming her
or there'II be
permanent damage.
Keep Iooking!
There!
I didn't see anything.
It was there.
You sure?
Four millimeters
Iateral to the hippocampus,
I saw it.
NEUROSURGEON 2: House,
she's out of time,
she's gonna be a vegetable.
I saw it!
That's good enough for me.
They were able to restart
her heart. She's doing as well
as could be hoped.
PAM: So they found the clot?
We think so.
The neurosurgeons
are attempting to remove it
right now.
And when will we know
if there was any damage?
A few hours.
(CRYING)
(IN THE DEEP PLAYING)
Four millimeters
Iateral to the hippocampus.
That's where I am.
There's nothing there.
You're not there yet,
keep going.
I'm there.
Are you sure you saw...
There it is.
I think I can get it.
Hi, Mom.
Oh, hi.
(DOOR OPENING)
You're treating
your stuffy nose with cocaine.
Diphenhydramine.
Antihistamine.
New delivery system.
It's a blood-brain
barrier thing.
It's all about speed,
isn't it? One thing to
another, never standing still.
You're pretty good at that.
I know my way
around a razor blade.
It's time.
Just a couple more rocks.
Andie's going home.
Right.
The parade
of the small bald
circus freaks.
Sorry, I've got a thing.
I read her surgeon's report.
Oh?
The clot was nowhere near
her amygdala.
Means her fear emotions
were working perfectly.
Yeah.
So her bravery
was not a symptom.
Yeah. I was wrong.
She genuinely is
a self-sacrificing saint,
whose Iife will bring her
nothing but pain.
Which she will
stoically withstand
just so that her mom
doesn't have to cry
quite so soon.
I'm beside myself with joy.
(HOUSE SNIFFING)
(EXCLAIMING)
She enjoys Iife
more than you do.
Right.
She stole that kiss
from Chase.
What have you done Iately?
I'm pacing myself.
Unlike her, I have
the Iuxury of time.
She could outlive you.
In case you wanna see
real butterflies.
I'm not gonna kiss you.
No matter what you say.
It's sunny outside.
You should go for a walk.
Not much for the Iong walks
in the park.
Now get.
(BEAUTIFUL PLAYING)
SALESMAN: 0 to 60
in 2.8 seconds.
Four-stroke, four cylinder,
Iiquid cooled.
You gain a Iot of torque
according to...
Right Ieg?
Your right Ieg?
You can still ride.
We got excellent financing
right now.
It Iists for ten-eight.
I'II Iet you steal it
out the door for ten-three.
No, thanks.
Could I test drive
one of these things?
www.tvsubtitles.net