(PANTING)
Good morning.
Hey, Alfredo.
You done already?
No. Not yet.
I finish tomorrow.
Mexico playing Argentina
on TV?
No, no.
(PANTlNG)
My asthma is very bad today.
Six years, Alfredo.
You can't lie to me.
I'm throwing a dinner...
First thing tomorrow...
Party's tonight.
A little rain and I'm gonna
have to put buckets
on the dining room table.
No clouds, no rain.
I'll tell you what.
You take off, but if it pours
into my guests' wineglasses...
Okay. Okay, senora.
I'll do it.
Thank you.
(SPEAKlNG lN SPANlSH)
(COUGHlNG)
(ALFREDO SCREAMlNG)
(ALFREDO GROANlNG)
(SlREN WAlLlNG)
Spinal cord seems intact.
Take a deep breath.
(GASPlNG) It hurts.
Try.
Breath sounds bilateral.
I don't think
he has a pneumothorax.
Just asthma.
That and probably
a broken rib.
Tell me when it hurts
the most.
(GROANlNG)
Your two little fingers
are darker than the others.
They feel funny. Como needles.
How long have they
been like that?
Never noticed before.
Is bad?
CUDDY:
Judging by how it looks,
he could lose his hand.
How does falling off your roof
do that to a guy's fingers?
He could have tweaked
a vertebra in his neck.
Could impinge the ulnar...
Sorry, trouble concentrating.
That tank top
really absorbs moisture.
Could impinge the ulnar nerve,
cut the blood flow.
Or it could be
disseminated intravascular
coagulopathy.
DlC?
Guy falls off a roof,
the first thought is always,
"It's a clotting problem."
Trauma can activate
the clotting enzymes.
Guy could lose
more than his hand.
Thank you very much.
This guy's been working for me
for a long time, and l...
Do I get bonus points
if I act like I care?
Cervical MRl.
Work up for DlC. And start him
on a heparin drip.
Who?
You wanna know his name?
I'm sure it's in the file.
Or you could ask her.
She's his oldest,
bestest friend. They were
in Cub Scouts together.
I'll get started
on the blood tests.
You haven't been a real doctor
in 10 years. You'll make
a mess all over the sheets.
I'll do it.
You have clinic duty.
I still know
how to handle a patient.
Get me blood.
Lots of blood.
They're better.
They've showered.
You don't need to see him.
One-handed handymen
aren't in big demand.
Talking. That's how
lawsuits are lost.
I know you, Lisa.
You go in, you offer
to pay his medical bills,
his wages,
you'll say something stupid
like, "I'm sorry."
You think I'm an idiot.
I think you're not a lawyer.
Don't go in there.
Trust me, House's people
can handle this.
Yeah.
CHASE: This might
sting a little bit.
The medicine
will thin the blood
and help it to circulate.
Those are pretty
nasty scars there.
I work construction.
(GROANlNG)
How long
will I be in the hospital?
Depends how long
it takes us to figure out
what's going on.
I need to work.
I'll get fired.
I'm sure Dr. Cuddy
won't fire you.
I'm a janitor
at fast food six nights.
I need to work.
My mother
doesn't make enough.
I can work. I'm old enough.
You're old enough
when you finish college.
Why? You never went...
I never had a big brother
to tell me to shut up!
I promise we'll let you
out of here as soon as
we're able to.
Look, l... I am fine. Okay?
I feel better. I go home now.
No.
If this is a clotting problem,
it could be very serious.
All right?
Look, you can't
make me stay.
Wait...
You can't make me stay.
Turn your hand over.
I need to see your hand.
Where's Dr. Cuddy?
CHASE:
We've got a third finger
turning dark.
His PTT is prolonged
and the fibrin split products
are off.
He's not clotting properly.
It looks like a mild case
of DlC.
Well, obviously
not that mild.
This keeps up,
his hand is literally gonna
be dead meat.
His hand
is connected to his arm,
and his arm is connected to...
I'm not sure,
but I bet it's important.
All this from falling off
my roof!
Yeah. If only he'd fallen
on his head.
Then he wouldn't have any
of these symptoms.
We need something
stronger than heparin.
Human Activated Protein C.
Looks like Cuddy,
same cleavage.
Protein C is indicated
only for severe sepsis.
How many of his limbs
have to be at stake
for it to be severe?
But this stuff
is crazy dangerous.
It can cause
internal bleeding.
If he bleeds, he could stroke,
he could die.
He could get better.
You know, if I try
to scheme like this,
you get that nasty
wrinkly face and screech
like a hyena.
It's very sexy, I admit.
Do it.
Protein C
is borderline irresponsible,
except that the safe stuff
isn't doing squat.
It's exactly the type of thing
you would do.
Obviously.
It's exactly the type of thing
he'd do.
I know.
I think he's trying
to protect me.
Now, that's not
the type of thing he would do.
I overruled him.
He's the best diagnostician
in this hospital,
and I overrule him.
You care about this kid.
Your judgment
should be worth more than his.
He also pointed out
that I haven't been
a real doctor in years.
Now that sounds like him.
You were
just jerking Cuddy around?
She seriously thought
I wanted to stop her.
One thing Cuddy
is not is clueless.
No.
First casualty of this case
is her sense of humor.
That's weird.
There's nothing funnier than
almost killing a guy.
I'm just having trouble
getting up those steps.
When did you start noticing?
Oh, a week ago.
Your blood pressure's
a little high.
I've got something new
that should help you out.
It combines a nitrate
with a blood pressure pill.
It's targeted
to African-Americans.
Targeted?
Yeah. Well, see,
we tend to have
nitric oxide deficiencies.
And the studies show
this drug counteracts
that problem.
It's the first drug to...
What kind of studies
you talking about?
are there?
They get some patients.
They give them some drugs.
I've had white people
lying to me for 60 years.
You think this is a tan?
You think
they tell you everything?
The trouble
with us black folk,
we can't tell
the difference anymore
between racism
and everybody gets screwed.
Yeah?
Well, how about them
cheap meningitis drugs
they're pawning off in Africa?
Gonna tell me
that ain't racism?
That's just greed.
You really wanna screw whitey?
Be one of the few black men
who live long enough
to collect social security.
Take the medicine.
(ECG BEEPlNG)
(GASPlNG) Nurse.
Nurse! Help! Nurse! Help!
Nurse!
What's up?
I can't move my arm!
Take it easy. Take it easy.
The Protein C side effects
we were worried about,
they happened.
Where was the bleed?
His brain.
It's causing
right side paralysis.
I've stopped the treatment
and called a neurosurgeon.
I can move it now.
It's okay now, yes?
Can I go home soon?
The surgery went well.
But all we did
was fix the problem created
by the medicine we gave you.
(SPEAKlNG lN SPANlSH)
She says you...
You look young.
Are you sure...
There's five of us
working on the case.
The others are older.
Why doesn't Dr. Cuddy
come to...
(COUGHlNG)
That doesn't sound too good.
CAMERON:
His fingers are even darker.
His temperature's 102
and spiking.
And the x-ray
now shows lung infiltrates.
Well, the good news is he
won't be bitching about losing
his hand if he can't breathe.
The trauma from the fall
could have caused acute
respiratory distress syndrome.
Right. I forgot. Your roof.
It would cause
lung infiltrates
and maybe fever
and conceivably
the cyanotic fingers.
The only question is why.
Why what?
Why her weird psychopathology
requires a diagnosis
informed entirely
by personal guilt.
Let's assume
we've been wrong up until now.
Let's assume,
just for one second,
that the earth doesn't revolve
around Cuddy's roof.
What if he was sick
before he had his run-in
with gravity?
He just didn't
notice anything.
Well, pneumonia
can cause DlC which can cause
cyanotic fingers.
Pneumonia doesn't hit
that fast.
Sure.
Only pavement hits that fast.
It's not pneumonia.
He might have missed
a finger turning dark.
He's not gonna miss
breathing problems.
What else?
It's pneumonia.
He wanted to go home.
I thought he was lying.
I told him
I had a dinner party.
I made him go up there.
Well, why didn't you
just take out a gun
and shoot him?
I thought it was just asthma.
You might've mentioned this
earlier, Doctor.
Maybe we could have sent
some blood cultures to the lab
instead of wasting a day
indulging your self-loathing.
If it's just garden-variety
bacterial pneumonia,
he's gonna be fine.
So give him garden-variety
Levaquin, and a garden-variety
echocardiogram.
And go check out
the kid's house.
The blood work
will show us which type
of pneumonia it is...
If he's huffing nail polish
or pulling the wings
off his pet parrot,
this way'll be faster.
And I bet
Julio's just dying to find out
what's wrong with him.
Go with her.
It's Alfredo.
And I can handle
getting a key and...
Rico and I no longer trust you
deciding what's important
and what's not.
You ever think
about writing a book
on office politics?
Trust me,
it would be a lot worse
if I told her that you had
to break into her house.
(STUTTERlNG)
What? Wait, wait, wait...
Cuddy's house?
See? It is shocking.
The guy's
been working there every day
for the last three weeks.
You think
it's impossible he could've
picked something up?
I'm not breaking
into my boss's house.
I'm your boss.
She's scarier than you are.
She's a woman.
Relax. I'm coming with.
House is having lunch
with his juniors now?
No. Not a chance.
Then where do you think
they're going?
I have no idea.
Then why don't you think
they're going to lunch?
Because it's not like House.
That was your point, right?
He had that smug look
on his face.
When he's that pleased
about something
he's gotta tell somebody,
and the only somebody
he knows is you.
(SlGHlNG)
He's breaking
into Cuddy's home.
What?
Why?
Medical reasons?
Why is he so curious
about Cuddy?
Why are you so curious
about his curiosity?
about me...
Because you dumped him
and you're married
and they are neither
of those things.
I'm just curious.
Nothing wrong with that.
No. Nothing wrong with that.
What do you think? Red thongs?
I think red thongs.
Okay, 20 bucks says
I can get through this door
in 20 seconds.
You're on.
Count me in.
No furniture polish,
no paint thinner, nor
anything else worth sniffing.
Nothing in here, either,
except a few cockroaches.
Nice. Someone
should fix Alfredo's roof.
So, why haven't you
fired House?
It's just, you guys are always
screaming at each other,
and I figure
you hate him, so...
I don't hate him.
Why not?
He's a great doctor,
but any other
hospital administrator would
have fired him years ago.
CUDDY: Four of them did.
The question is,
why did I hire him?
FOREMAN: So, how'd you know
about her key?
You been doing
a little handyman work
for Cuddy yourself?
Someone as obsessive
and insecure as Cuddy
probably has three extra keys
hidden away
within 10 feet of the door.
And you consider obsession
a negative quality.
Insecticide is organic.
Soap is hypoallergenic.
I got the bedroom.
This is where it all happens.
You both went to Michigan.
Did you know him
while you were there?
I was still an undergrad,
but, yeah, I knew him.
He was already a legend.
So you just knew him
as a legend?
My God, you're subtle.
Anything on your mind?
More cockroaches?
Worse.
Beautiful.
There's no way
you just deduced
where that key was.
Does this count as red?
You gave yourself 20 seconds
and put money on it.
Oh, my God.
She's got pictures
of you in here.
Just you. It's like some kind
of weird shrine.
You're kidding.
Yeah.
She uses super tampons.
What does that mean?
You two are just
too nasty to each other
not to have been nasty.
I can be a jerk to people
I haven't slept with.
I am that good.
There's nothing here.
You ready to go,
or you got some more stuff
you wanna sniff?
Whoa! Check this out.
It's fuzzy. It's black.
It's alive.
Patient's lung function's
declining rapidly.
Levaquin's not working.
He obviously doesn't have
garden-variety pneumonia.
I'm glad you learned
to take his impending death
in stride.
Guess what he does have.
Rats.
Scars on his hand.
Rat bites.
But he says
they're from construction work
so he won't have to admit
he's got rats at home.
Catholics are right.
Pride will kill you.
He has streptobacillus.
Rat-bite fever.
Boogie oogie oogie.
Fits the symptoms perfectly.
That's certainly
one possibility.
But what about
the aspergillus fungus
we found under the sink?
What sink?
You ought to clean
your bathroom better.
You broke into my house?
No. No. You're wrong.
I had a key.
You had no right
to invade my privacy.
There was no medical reason
for that whatsoever,
and there was certainly
no moral reason for it.
Oh, damn.
You're right.
The focal consolidation
makes fungal pneumonia
far more likely.
You're right I'm right.
On the bright side, it has
the advantage of keeping you
totally responsible.
The treatment for aspergillus
is amphotericin.
That's hugely dangerous.
Yeah? Your point being?
Going the dangerous
and aggressive route
didn't work the last time.
It's bound
to work this time. Start him
on the amphoterrible.
(ALFREDO COUGHlNG)
Dr. Cuddy?
I'm Manny, Alfredo's brother.
How's he doing?
He's worried about money.
I wanna work for you.
(SlGHlNG)
How old are you, Manny?
Fifteen.
Twelve?
I can paint.
I mow lawns. I rake leaves.
I can start today.
Alfredo wants you
to finish school.
Like you care.
Manny, I've known
your brother...
He falls off your roof,
and you don't come
see him once?
Bitch.
(MUSlC PLAYlNG ON TV)
With a patient.
Not according to the log.
It's 3:15.
Is it a commercial?
How's Cuddy doing?
She's not acting like Cuddy.
It's a pleasure.
You know her.
She has trouble
with these situations,
feels personally responsible.
The technical term
is narcissism.
You can't believe
that everything is your fault
unless you also believe
you're all-powerful.
Wow, does she sound messed up.
I don't believe
I can fix everything.
And I don't
lie awake at night,
tormented by that fact.
No. You lie awake
tormented by how...
I thought we were talking
about Cuddy here.
She cares.
She enjoys feeling guilty.
Lisa cares. It's why
she drives you nuts. 'Cause
it's not just a puzzle to her.
The patients
are actually real,
their feelings
actually relevant.
And I'm telling her
she can't even talk to him.
My God, it's contagious.
You're feeling guilty, too.
I'm just saying,
take it easy on her.
You owe her that.
MAN ON TV: From the moment
I saw you at the EI...
Commercial's over.
So glad we talked.
Snap, crackle, pop.
You got some
Rice Krispies in there?
That bad, huh?
You were here yesterday.
I see from the chart
that Dr. Foreman prescribed
medicine, not a miracle.
Got to give this stuff
more than a day.
I didn't fill
that Oreo's prescription.
On the theory
that you didn't trust him
because he's black.
Well, I'm gonna prescribe
the same medicine and see
if you fill it this time.
I'm not buying
into no racist drug, okay?
(SCOFFlNG)
It's racist because
it helps black people
more than white people?
On behalf of my peeps,
let me just say thanks
for dying on principle for us.
Look, my heart's red.
Your heart's red.
And it don't make no sense
to give us different drugs.
You know,
I have found a difference.
Admittedly,
it's a limited sample,
but based on my experience
of the last 90 seconds,
all black people are morons.
Sorry, African-Americans.
I'll see another doctor.
Fine. Fine.
I'll give you
the same medicine
we give Republicans.
ALFREDO: I think the medicine
is working.
They're lighter, right?
They don't look
lighter to me, Alfredo.
How's the tingling?
Does not bother me.
Tell her the other thing.
(SPEAKlNG lN SPANlSH)
He hasn't peed
since yesterday.
Since last night?
Afternoon.
It's not a problem.
I don't drink much.
I think
we'll give you a little rest
from the meds here.
(SPEAKlNG lN SPANlSH)
She says, "That's the medicine
that's supposed to cure me."
Just making
a little adjustment.
Excuse me.
He's not making any urine.
I think we just destroyed
the kid's kidney
with the amphotericin.
I think he's dying.
Dying?
Cheese it, the cops.
(SOBBlNG lN SPANlSH)
I guess she understands
a little English.
CAMERON:
His kidneys are shutting down
due to the direct toxicity
to the proximal
tubule epithelium.
Proof that my brilliant idea
of giving him amphotericin
is killing him.
That wasn't a complete
waste of time.
His reaction shows
that you don't need to clean
under your sink.
It wasn't aspergillus.
And blood cultures
show he was negative
for rat-bite fever.
There's still plenty of other
cool pneumonias.
Tested negative for Moraxella,
Nocardia, cryptococcus.
He has a low titer
for chlamydia antibodies.
Maybe...
No, no.
His chest x-ray's all wrong
for chlamydial pneumonia.
But the titer points to...
CAMERON:
He had an STD last year.
That explains the titer.
He has low sodium.
Maybe it's Legionella.
No. His antigen is negative.
Well, that all sucks.
Maybe we were right
to begin with.
His problems are all caused
by DlC precipitated
by falling off my roof.
DlC wouldn't cause
a fever this high.
See? My lap dog
agrees with me.
How high?
Two hours ago
it was 103 with acetaminophen.
What about on St. Alban's Day?
Only temperature
I'm interested in right now
is his temperature right now.
(SPEAKlNG lN SPANlSH)
Open up.
Okay. Let me clarify.
Open up and keep it open.
Yeah.
Okay.
Under your tongue.
You're using your left hand.
Right one hurt?
No, I feel better.
What, it really doesn't hurt,
or you just figure
if you say no,
you'll get out
of the hospital sooner?
It doesn't hurt. I feel good.
(SNlFFlNG)
You don't smell too hot.
(GROANlNG)
Your hand is starting to rot.
HOUSE: Why are we here?
We are talking about
cutting off a kid's hand.
Yes, we're talking
about cutting it off,
not subdividing it
and putting in condos.
It's not a legal issue.
Are you being
intentionally dense?
I think it's premature.
I've heard enough.
What?
She says one word
and you take her side.
You should at least wait
until she actually gives
a medical reason.
Otherwise I might
take it personally.
Shut up.
If I were to somehow
find out that you two
were in disagreement
over the proper
medical course of action,
it could make it awkward
for my client in court.
My client being
the two of you. So, guys,
I'm a little busy here.
Why don't we
pick this conversation up
in half an hour?
Okay?
All of his symptoms are caused
by his underlying problem
and the medicine we gave him.
What underlying problem?
You have no idea
what the underlying
problem is.
You're the diagnostician.
Fine. It's all my fault.
Does that make you
feel better?
His hand still has
an arterial pulse.
His hand is a cesspool.
And the crap is spreading.
You are being
pretty aggressive about
destroying a man's livelihood.
I don't give a damn
about his livelihood.
He loses that hand,
he loses his job,
all of his jobs.
He's not like us...
Can't work as a cripple?
He loses his home.
His kid brother drops out.
An American dream destroyed.
Very sad, very emotional,
not one medical fact
in the whole pathetic tale.
You have lost perspective,
Cuddy.
You've stopped looking
at this as a doctor.
You're acting like someone
who shoved somebody
off their roof.
You wanna make things right?
Too bad, nothing's ever right.
I am happy to report
that we're now so in sync
we're actually wearing
each other's underwear.
Chop-chop time.
Is this true?
HOUSE: No. I'm lying.
It's stupid to do it with her
in the room, I guess.
This is a big decision.
We made it.
We should convene a meeting
of the ethics committee.
No!
Look, she is making
a medical decision based on
never wanting to feel regret.
You're making a legal decision
based on wanting me
to be wrong.
Greg, you have
a history of aggressive...
You wanted
superficial agreement.
everybody's asses covered.
You got it.
Now can I do the surgery?
Pretty, pretty please.
Lisa,
are you sure
you're okay with this?
I should be the one
to tell the family.
Your hand is dying.
The bacteria are eating it.
When
they run out of food there,
they go somewhere else.
If you cut off my hand,
I'll be cured?
Unfortunately, no.
We still have to find
the disease that's making you
sick to begin with.
But you won't die of gangrene
while we're looking.
(SOBBlNG)
I quit school
when I am 1 2 to get a job,
to help my family.
I know I never get a good job,
never save money
or own my own house like you.
But, Manny, he's smart.
He's the best in his class.
Well, maybe Manny
doesn't have to quit school.
Maybe you can...
Are you sure
I need to do this?
Yes.
Okay.
(SOBBlNG) Okay.
(LUlSA SlNGlNG lN SPANlSH)
(LUlSA HUMMlNG)
I gave
one of my clinic patients
a follow-up call.
Your name came up.
I'm guessing an old black guy
who thinks the ClA invented
rap music to make your people
want to kill each other.
He said you gave him
the white folks' stuff.
This is exactly
why black people
don't live as long...
This isn't about race,
unless annoying is a race.
Is he not getting better?
He's fine so far.
I'm calling him back in.
I'm getting him
on the right stuff.
Relax, Foreman, he already is.
I told him
it was the white stuff.
I gave him the black stuff.
He was right.
You did exactly
what white people do.
You figure we don't need
to know the truth
or can't understand it,
so you just lie to us.
Just a white lie.
Good one, massa.
Right, and I'm a racist.
Too bad that idiot
will never know for the rest
of his long, long life.
Every slave master
thought they were doing
the black man a favor.
Negro can't
take care of himself,
so we'll put him to work.
We'll give him four walls,
a bed.
We'll civilize the heathen.
I'll tell you what.
Stop doing us favors.
If you're right, and we end up
back in the jungle
with lousy
blood pressure medicine,
it won't be on your head.
You okay?
You wondering
if you made the right call?
I've wanted to be a doctor
from the time I was 1 2.
I wanted to be a lawyer
from the time I was six
until my second week
of law school.
Sorry. Your story.
I graduated medical school
at 25, pissed off that I was
second in my class.
Chief of medicine at 32,
second youngest ever,
first woman...
Sad story.
If I had been
Alfredo's doctor...
You are his doctor.
I insisted
on giving him Protein C.
We had to cut his skull open.
I insisted on amphotericin,
killed his kidneys.
I missed the pneumonia
completely.
I would have searched his home
and ignored mine.
I would have watched him die
trying to save his hand.
If I didn't have House
looking over my shoulder...
Are you saying
you're not as good a doctor
as House is?
I'm saying House is right.
I was so anxious to get ahead.
I haven't been a doctor
in years.
His little finger is dusky.
Yeah, that's why
we're doing this.
No. I mean the other hand,
the one we haven't
chopped off yet.
CUDDY:
Hjs O2 sats are down to 88.
His lungs are giving out.
He needs a ventilator.
And dialysis.
You're getting distracted
by the multisystem
organ failure.
Pinkies are supposed
to be pink, right?
I mean,
they're not called "gray-ies".
But the organ failure
is gonna kill him.
But the pinky is weirder.
What does it tell us?
The same thing the right hand
told us before we cut it off.
It's the same symptom.
HOUSE:
But at a different time.
His blood work
indicates mild DlC.
What if it's mild in the way
that when you get out
of the ocean,
the water clinging
to your body makes
the sea level drop?
It's technically true,
but it's completely
irrelevant.
A lack of DlC
would explain everything
if there were also
a lack of anything to explain.
Endocarditis.
His heart's infected.
Little bacteria cauliflowers,
clinging to his valves.
Except sometimes
they can't hold on. They go
swimming in his bloodstream.
Thursday, one breaks off,
goes to his right hand,
black fingers, gangrene.
Friday's child
heads for the kidneys.
And we all know
what Saturdays are all about.
Party with the left hand.
Also explains the fever.
It's perfect
except for the little fact
that we already tested
for endocarditis,
and he was negative.
Which means he either
is negative or...
What infection can cause
pneumonia and culture-negative
endocarditis?
Prize value goes down
with every clue.
(CAWlNG)
You're thinking psittacosis?
Alfredo doesn't have
any pet parrots.
Quit your squawking.
Give him doxycycline.
No! That'll just make
his clotting problem worse.
I liked you better
when you were coming up with
wacky drugs for us to try.
We give him the doxy now,
damn it, maybe we can
save his pinky.
He can teach his brother
to count all the way to five.
If you're wrong,
he'll end up with no hands
and no feet.
Technically, if I'm wrong,
he'll end up dead,
but I take your point.
What's his night job?
He cleans up
at some fast food joint.
What, you think he got it
from a chicken nugget?
Since when do fast food joints
allow 1 2-year-olds
to mop floors?
Alfredo is 20.
Really? Looks younger.
Where were you going
to work tonight?
What job do you do
on Saturday nights?
CUDDY: What are you doing?
Wake him up.
We just cut off his hand.
Yeah. We need
to talk about it.
It's not happening.
(SPEAKlNG lN SPANlSH)
Honest, I've got no idea
what I just said.
Why didn't you say
you spoke Spanish?
Well, because
she'd wanna talk to me.
Or something like that.
(SPEAKlNG lN SPANlSH)
She says he doesn't work
Saturday nights.
Give me the talking juice.
The fact
it doesn't fit your theory
doesn't make it a lie.
When she was out of the room,
the kid brother insisted
he was gonna cover for Alfredo
at work tonight.
(SPEAKlNG lN SPANlSH)
Saturday nights
he goes dancing.
Either it's a lie
or he's dancing with birds.
Give her the talking juice.
She doesn't know
what you're talking about.
Odds are it's gonna be
close to his house.
It's probably an abandoned
warehouse or factory.
Take the Scooby gang
and spread out.
What the hell
are we looking for?
Find somebody
who looks like crap.
Tell him you want
to place a bet.
(SPEAKlNG lN SPANlSH)
(SPANlSH MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(PEOPLE SHOUTlNG)
(CELL PHONE RlNGlNG)
It's Cuddy.
I already put him
on the psittacosis meds.
As soon as you left.
You're welcome.
What do you think the record
for one-handed juggling is?
You can yo-yo one-handed.
Good point.
ALFREDO:
I always wash my hands.
If a bird is infected,
you can get psittacosis
just from breathing his dust.
But then, why do I get sick
and nobody else?
Your asthma
made you vulnerable.
You're gonna be
all right now.
Yes.
(SPEAKlNG lN SPANlSH)
For saving my life.
He thanked me.
He should have.
We cut off his hand.
If we'd figured it out
earlier...
If you'd figured it out later,
he'd be dead.
I never figured it out at all.
Hello.
What do you want, House?
If you're wallowing
in self-loathing, I've got
something that might help.
We're getting sued.
You saved his life.
He admitted that.
We'll settle.
He's got a stub where his hand
used to be. We have insurance.
Case seems pretty solid to me.
The new American dream.
Happy ending.
Kid's gonna be just fine.
Cuddy,
your guilt.
It's perverse and it makes you
a crappy doctor.
It also makes you
okay at what you do.
You figure
a perverted sense of guilt
makes me a good boss.
Now, would the world
be a better place if people
never felt guilty?
Makes sex better.
You should have
seen her in the last months
of our relationship.
A lot of guilt.
A lot of screaming.
I know this wasn't just
because it was your roof.
Cuddy,
you see the world as it is,
and you see the world
as it could be.
And what you don't see
is what everybody else sees,
the giant gaping chasm
in between.
House, I'm not naive.
I realize...
If you did, you never
would have hired me.
You're not happy
unless things are just right,
which means two things.
That you're a good boss,
and you'll never be happy.
By the way,
why does everybody think
you and I had sex?
You think there could be
something to it?
WlLSON: Cuddy feels guilty
about not diagnosing
psittacosis any earlier?
I think so.
There's no way
she could have.
No.
No way she could have.
(SLOW ROCK MUSlC PLAYlNG)
It's raining.
www.tvsubtitles.net