Hey!
Dr. Sebastian!
Two pallets of antibiotics
for tuberculosis.
We’ve got six pallets
worth of patients!
Stoia Tucker needs a math lesson.
I’m headed back tomorrow.
Hey! Hey.
Come on! Come on!
Let that truck though!
Let it though!
Move those boxes.
Quick, quick!  Let’s move!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Let’s go, let’s go, hurry!
I’ve got some very special medicine here;
this is from Hershey, Pennsylvania.
One per person, one per person.
Help, help!
Dr. Sebastian, come quickly!
My son, he fell.
He fell on this rock.
We were just waiting for his friends.
[Speaking in a native language]
I got no breath sounds on the left.
Give me that.
Yeah, he’s gonna be okay.
The fall didn’t cause him to drop a lung,
the lung caused him to fall.
TB chewed it up.
He’ll be lucky to live another year.
Now, this is Sarni.
I picked up the tab
for the back brace myself.
The funny thing is is that the brace cost
more than the medicine that would have
prevented her from needing it.
It’s your medicine.
All of the antibiotics that
we need are right here
in your warehouses, in your factories.
- We provide over 10,000 doses a year.
- Which is not enough.
You know we’d love to do more,
but our hands are tied.
New car, Jerry?
I saw it on the way in,
looks beautiful.
Don’t make this personal.
All the way from Germany, too, I know that’s a lot of red tape.
I’m not like you;
I’m not ashamed of making a living.
And I know you didn’t become
a chem. major for the money.
Now you want the same things
that I want, you just...
You have to,
you just have to push a little,
you have to push
a little bit harder,
harder for them.
Sebastian?
Call 911!
Isn’t someone here a doctor?
2x04 - TB or Not TB
Original Airdate (FOX): 1-NOV-2005
Selling subscriptions?
I heard 20 and you get a new bike.
Dr. Sebastian Charles collapsed
during a presentation at Stoia Tucker.
Really? Crushed under
the weight of his own ego?
Wow. Is there nobody you admire?
Well, there was this gal
I met in ‘Nam who could
blow out a candle without using her...
He thinks it’s TB.
Good thing he’s not the syphilis expert.
- He wants a second opinion.
- Second to his own.
Okay. It’s not TB.
What is it?
Oh, you want specifics?
Lemma. Big Knicks fan.
You’ve never had
an episode like this before?
No. He died last month.
Stupidly tried to share
his meds with his cousin,
and they only had enough for one.
Dr. House,
I’m Sebastian Charles.
Patients aren’t usually
part of the diagnostic process.
Well, I’m a doctor…
Listen, I know you guys
don’t make a lot of money, but...
I wrote your people
a check last month.
Oh, well… write us another one.
Talk to Chase, he’s rich.
My dad, not me.
Every minute 4 people die of TB.
Wow, how can you sleep at night?
There’s people dying in Africa
of a disease that we cured over...
Yeah, I know.
I saw the concert.
Seriously, let’s say you sleep six hours,
that means every night you kill...
1440 people.
I guess you gotta
get some sleep, but come on,
if you’d stayed up another 10 minutes
you could have saved 40 lives.
Do you send notes
to the families in the morning?
That’s gonna take at least 10 minutes
so that’s another 40 dead, another 40 notes….
Why don’t you go wrack yourself
with guilt in your own room?
No, thanks, I’ll stay.
I’d like to hear the differential.
Dr. Cameron, tell the doctor
why it’s not a good idea
for the patient to be here.
He’s an immunologist
and a TB expert.
That’ll be very useful
if we need somebody to say the words,
- “I think it’s TB.”
- [Chuckles]
[Sniffs]
What is that?
Oh that. I’m sorry,
that’s my body powder.
It’s the only thing I’ve found
that works in the Sahara.
I, I’m kinda used to it,
I don’t even notice it.
Who thinks it smells like
an elephant dung smoothie?
- It smells okay to me.
- [Laughs.]
That is exactly why the patient
shouldn’t be in the room.
If you can’t tell a man that
his cologne makes you want to puke,
how are you going to tell him
that he’s an idiot?
He’s not an idiot.
Sure, you say that now,
while he’s in the room.
Sebastian:
Look, I don’t have time for this.
- It’s TB.
- Nope.
The symptoms are too varied.
Well, if you haven’t seen 10,000 cases
I’d agree that’s what you’d think.
Told you he’s an idiot.
You said you wanted
a second opinion.
No, actually. My backers
wanted a second opinion.
Yeah, doesn’t look good if you drop dead
while wearing your shoes sponsor’s logo.
It’s TB, and I’m not dying.
I’m gonna want you to plan a PPD and
induce a sputum to confirm the TB.
Imaging studies’ll
determine the progress, and
I think we should probably
take a CT scan of my lungs just
so that nobody second-guesses us?
Wouldn’t want that.
[Cell rings.]
[On phone] Hello?
No, I’m feeling much better.
Well, what you can do is
you can get your board to approve
the increased med shipments that...
Aha. No, no, no, no, don’t try.
No, no, don’t do your best.
Just get it done, okay?
That’s Stoia Tucker, and they’re
the nice pharmaceutical company.
I’m sorry, but
it’s against hospital regs.
Oh, I need the phone.
[Beeper goes off]
Why don’t we focus on
getting you better right now?
[Beeper goes off]
What are you gonna do,
throw me out?
No, just the phone.
Sorry, we’ve got an emergency.
[Beeper goes off.]
There’s a phone in your room.
Yeah, I figured that there would be.
Right, I just thought,
it’s not like the hospitals that
you might used to in Africa.
I don’t know
what the facilities were like…
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
And thanks for that check.
[Beeper beeps again]
I should go.
The nameless poor have a face,
and it’s a pompous white man.
Yeah, what a jerk,
saving all those lives like that.
What’s the emergency?
I can’t remember
how to do Walk the Dog.
The guy’s sick,
he may be dying.
We’ve forgotten all about
doing a differential diagnosis.
You just sent us off to test him for...
I had to get him out of there.
Now we can all sit around
and call him an idiot.
Who wants to go first?
He’s right!
Tuberculosis could present
in hundreds of different ways!
Well, by that logic, everyone
in the hospital should be treated.
Not everyone in the hospital’s been
exposed to it for the last 20 years.
TB takes years to kill you.
2 weeks ago he was perfectly healthy,
now he’s got a white board full of symptoms.
What about something metabolic?
Welcome aboard
the Good Ship Asskisser.
Nice day for a sail.
Pucker up, me hearties.
It’s not metabolic.
Kidney, liver and thyroid are
all normal. No diabetes.
What about his heart?
Obviously big as all outdoors.
Abnormal heart rhythm.
White form showed P-R variability.
It’s subtle, but it’s there.
You think it’s his heart?
Sick sinus syndrome?
Loose throttle.
Sometimes beats too fast,
sometimes too slow.
Causing him to pass out.
It would account for the episode.
I’ll put him on telemetry,
do a stress test and
an echocardiogram.
Treat him like every
other hospital patient.
I want to see that
pious, body powered toosh
hanging out of his gown.
Could you give me
a hand with this thing?
I don’t recall asking for
a stress test or an echocardiogram.
What are you gonna do, walk out?
Corporate sponsors
aren’t going to like that.
I need your forearm.
What’s House thinking?
Sick sinus syndrome.
Well, that’s a lot
more serious than TB.
Is that a PPD?
If it changes color
in the next 48 hours...
Yeah, uh, if House doesn’t think it’s TB
why would he have you test for that?
Just covering all his bases, I guess.
Uh huh. He doesn’t seem like
a guy who, who does that.
We have you scheduled
for a 10:30 echo.
Good for you.
[Chuckles]
Every minute that
we refuse to love one another,
another puppy cries another tear.
You’re just mad that he’s closer
to a Nobel Prize than you are.
And yet I’ve nailed
more Swedish babes.
Crazy, crazy world.
It’s not just a trip
to Stockholm, you know.
It comes with a cash prize.
Seriously?
No wonder everyone’s
going after that peace thing.
[Elevator dings]
He cures thousands of people
every year, you cure, what? 30?
McDonald’s makes
a better hamburger than your mother
because they make more?
Oh, I see! So you hate him
because the lives he saves aren’t
as good as the lives you save.
Yup, that’s the reason.
Nobel invented dynamite.
I won’t accept his blood money.
The top of my head’s killing me.
Hmmm. We spent a week
doing ‘top of head’ in Anatomy.
I know just where it is.
Ow! That is not the top of my head!
Eh, close enough for clinic.
Your sinuses are clogged.
Judging by the scratches
on your hands,
I’m guessing a new cat.
It was my mother’s.
She’s dead.
You keep a dead cat?
No. My mother’s dead.
Oh. Poor cat.
You’re allergic.
We can control it with
antihistamine, one pill a day.
Pills?
You don’t like to swallow.
Not surprised. Forget the pills.
I’ll give you a nasal spray.
Steroids?
Is there something else
you can give me?
Well, if you lived by the river,
I’ve got a bag.
Hey, stress test was normal.
But his EKG was not normal.
Echo’s normal.
Two for you, one for me.
We need a tie-breaker.
Echo and stress test
are more reliable.
Tilt-table test.
Never works.
Bet you a week’s
clinic duty it does.
Hah hah, you’re on.
You like this guy?
You always tell us our opinion
of the patient is irrelevant.
Medically, it’s irrelevant.
That says something about you.
You figure that
anybody that gives a crap about
people in Africa must be full of it?
Yes. There’s an evolutionary
imperative why we give a crap
about our family and friends.
And there’s an evolutionary
imperative why we don’t give
a crap about anybody else.
If we loved all people
indiscriminately,
we couldn’t function.
Hmmm.
So, the great humanitarian’s
as selfish as the rest of us.
Just not as honest about it.
You also always tell us
motives are irrelevant.
Dr. Charles,
your heart’s handling the changes
in orientation just fine.
No pauses on your EKG.
And House drives up for
the lay-up and oh, rejected!
What does this knobby thing do?
I’m within protocol range,
you’re not going to get a different result.
The way I figure it is,
if this could show you problems at 6,
imagine what could happen
if you crank it to 10.
House, is that you?
Does it go to 11?
Would you stop? You lost.
I’m scheduled for clinic duty
Thursday and Friday.
All right, I’m beginning
to feel nauseous.
Would you turn the damn thing off
before you break it?
Okay, I’m getting dizzy,
I can’t see, I’m gonna pass out.
I win.
At those speeds
astronauts throw up.
I’m not talking
about the nausea.
Foreman:
The test revealed a problem.
Yeah? House is insane?
What he just did...
Abusive and unprofessional.
If he hadn’t done it,
we wouldn’t have seen the problem.
You’ve got
an abnormal P-R interval.
It could be dangerous,
possibly fatal, particularly
if you’re in Africa away
from advanced medicine.
I’m gonna need a pacemaker?
You’re scheduled
for surgery this afternoon.
You’ll be able to maintain
your pacemaker from anywhere,
you just need to get yourself
to a phone line every few months.
Better yet, you could
join me at one of my clinics.
I’m kind of spoiled.
Well, we’ll get you a hut
with a view. You like sand?
I meant medically.
- No PET scans, no MRIs…
- This is ridiculous.
- Dr. Charles, wait...
- I know, I know,
hospital regulations. Darling...
...have a seat. Come on.
You’re smart, you’ll adapt…
we going up or down?
- Basement.
- All right.
You might even find that
without the technological crutches
you become a better diagnostician.
My heart can handle this, right?
So far just carnival rides
have set you off.
When you meet these people
it changes you.
We should talk
about it over dinner.
Are you asking me
to Africa or on a date?
Oh, I can ask you
halfway around the world,
I can’t ask you to
a restaurant a block away?
Well, one’s a job,
and the other’s…
Yeah, hospital regs,
you can’t date patients, right,
I wouldn’t want to risk
your precious objectivity.
You haven’t answered
either question, by the way.
You don’t think
objectivity’s important?
I think doctors like House
cling to objectivity like a
three-year-old to a blanket;
don’t get too worked up,
stay calm, stay cool and
maintain that correct perspective.
The only flaw in their argument is
when you have millions of people dying
the correct perspective is to be
yelling at the top of your lungs.
- Sorry, my head is killing me.
- Here, sit on the step.
So, you gonna go out
with me or not?
Your heart rate’s normal.
Yeah, of course it is,
it’s one flight of stairs.
I’m gonna be fine.
My hand’s a little...
Call a code!
Second floor stairwell!
You were wrong.
Hey, I have feelings.
I’m trying my best.
Isn’t that enough for you?
- The abnormal EKG was real...
- It’s not sick sinus syndrome.
Well, thank God we found out
before we put the pacemaker in.
And thank God
you dragged him into a stairwell
to get his heart racing.
We were taking the stairs,
they keep them in the stairwell.
The guy’s a selfish jerk,
why would you...
Why would you say
he’s selfish?
Because he’s been
talking to Foreman.
No I haven’t,
I’m just giving my opinion.
This kind of altruism
doesn’t just naturally...
[Phone rings]
Excellent briefing.
Hey, the guy’s still sick.
Can we talk about that?
The headaches point to
a neurological problem.
Acoustic neuroma.
Brian tumor causes dizziness,
loss of consciousness,
messes with breathing patterns,
heart rhythms...
Get an MRI.
Hello? Oh, I’m sorry,
I’ll be right down.
No problem, I’ll do
an extra hour to make up.
I’m late for my clinic duty.
Here, go be me for a couple hours.
Explosive diarrhea, fever…
it’s probably the flu.
Wow, you’re good.
You a Harvard boy?
You’re not Hale, Oliver?
No. Carter, Cecelia.
They put you in the
wrong room, Cecelia.
Mrs. Carter.
Sorry. I’ll just be a few minutes,
don’t take these in order
and everything falls apart.
I have cancer.
I felt a lump.
- I’ll go get a nurse.
- Yeah, see you in an hour or two.
Lie flat.
Lift your left arm up
and under your head?
Right there?
Yeah, I felt it this morning.
Oh, my cousin had the same thing.
It’s nothing.
We should check it again
on your next cycle, but
you really don’t have
anything to worry about.
That’s what they told Donna.
She was dead in six months.
Listen, the edges are smooth,
it has mobility, it has all
the earmarks of a benign...
Why should I believe you?
Because you’re trying
to rush me out of here?
The risks of a false positive
on a biopsy outweigh...
Either you do the biopsy
or I talk to your superior.
Which is it...Dr. House?
I’ll arrange the biopsy.
Thanks.
He asked me out.
I’m shocked.
I’m shocked when
patients don’t ask you out.
He also asked me
to come to Africa.
Boy, he moves fast.
I think the two questions had
two different objectives.
Well, do you like him?
Good looking single guy,
genius doctor, cares about the world…
I take it you said no.
You think
I’m that hung up on rules and...
He’s not House.
There’s nothing there.
Yeah, there is.
- Did I ask you to plant a PPD?
- It was positive, he’s got TB!
Well, of course he’s got TB!
The guy’s been in the jungle for 20 years!
If he tested positive
for pink-eye would you think
that was his big problem?
I did a test, it was positive,
why is that a problem?
Because now he’s got
the big red target on his arm,
the stubborn jerk thinks he’s right!
He won’t let us
do any more tests.
Well, maybe he’s not
the only stubborn jerk.
I did an LP2: low glucose and
he has an increased sed rate.
- Everything screams tuberculosis!
- Not everything!
If any of the symptoms
are caused by the TB
it would throw off our diagnosis.
You’re right.
Gotta treat the TB.
Who knows,
maybe he’ll just get better.
You’d like that, wouldn’t you?
So it’s TB, but not TB?
I’m complicated.
The guy does know tuberculosis.
If he says it can manifest itself...
He’s not even a real doctor, he’s a human telethon.
Is that your problem with him?
You see hypocrites every day,
why is this guy so special?
You think I have a
hypocritical attitude to hypocrisy?
The problem is
there are 26 letters in the alphabet
and he only uses two of them.
He treats thousands of patients
with one diagnosis.
He knows the answer going in.
It’s cheating.
So it’s all because he’s
one of them useless specialists?
Oh, did I hurt the big time
oncologist’s itty bitty feelings?
You’re a big help to patients
who actually have cancer.
Other times you’re just annoying.
You’ve outdone yourself.
I’ll say. My salad’s
covering a free t-bone steak.
Cecelia Carter,
remember her?
Last week they said it was
“Mystery Stew”, they owe me.
She was just in my office crying
because of the way you treated her.
That doesn’t sound like you!
Then it probably wasn’t.
I get that you like
to shock people.
Stun them
out of complacency,
out of stupidity.
But this woman thought
she had cancer, she had
a lump in her breast!
What were you
trying to accomplish?
Let me ask you something:
if this were another doctor,
if this patient were
complaining about, let’s say,
I don’t know, Foreman,
you’d just dismiss this
as the paranoid bitching of another
paranoid bitch and file it under ‘P’ for...
Paranoid?
Am not.
- You’re right.
- Good.
Apologize to her before
the end of business today.
- What did you do to Ceci?
- I have no idea.
Just a salad today,
big breakfast.
Hey.
Levofloxacin?
You have a resistant strain of TB.
Wow, you just walk
right in with these.
That’s what we doctors do.
We write down
the name of some medicine
and someone gives it to us.
You know, there’s parts of
the world where you get knifed
walking around with this.
I mean, regular stuff’s
bad enough, but
treatment for the resistant strain?
[Whistles]
I could get $6
a tablet for that one.
And I’d take it
for two years.
Streptomycin,
now that’s two grand…
ten grand, cure one person.
I had a patient in Jani once.
It was a mother, had...
had three little boys.
She had resistant TB,
she couldn’t afford these.
She couldn’t afford bread.
We gave her
the regular stuff, but...
no surprise she died.
I’m sorry.
I’m not taking these pills.
Because she couldn’t get them
you’re not going to take them?
That’s insane!
Why, because I’m
better than her?
Because letting her die was wrong
but letting you die is just as wrong.
Well, maybe I won’t die.
Maybe somebody’ll pay
a little more attention to my story.
He figures the pharmaceuticals need
something big to force them into action.
[The phone rings]
This’ll get a lot more media play
than a thousand African villagers dying.
So he won’t take the pills.
Newsweek’s calling you!
And he won’t agree
to any more tests.
He has his diagnosis.
See what happens
when you don’t listen to me?
- Maybe millions of lives get saved...
- Yeah, that’s my point.
Increased heart rate,
night sweats, loss of consciousness,
besides rough sex,
what do they all have in common?
- T...
- It’s not TB!
- His autonomic nervous system?
- We know that it’s not a brain tumor.
So what else could be
eating his nerves?
Fabry’s, autonomic disregulation syndrome,
shy-drager syndrome, it doesn’t matter.
He won’t let us test him.
[Phone rings again]
[On phone] In my opinion,
Dr. Sebastian Charles is an idiot.
Yeah, you can quote me.
C-u-d-d-y.
[Chase and Foreman laugh to themselves.]
Sebastian is refusing
life-saving treatment.
He’s refusing TB treatment.
You don’t think he has TB,
ergo you should care less.
He won’t let me test him.
And what do you
want me to do about it?
Hold him down.
Have you apologized
to Cecelia Carter yet?
Trust me, she doesn’t
want to hear it from me.
Look, the guy is killing himself,
am I the only one who
realizes this is a bad thing?
If he was a Christian Scientist
refusing meds we’d have 18 attorneys...
You’re putting on make-up.
That’s not a good sign
for my side, is it?
Sebastian has called
a press conference for 3.
He’s asked me to be there
to confirm the diagnosis
on the prognosis.
You are as big a
media whore as he is.
Of course I am.
It couldn’t possibly be
that I think he’s right
and I’d like to be a
small part of what he’s doing.
Oh, whores can like the sex.
Doesn’t mean they’re not whores.
And with that eyeshadow…
I am totally screwed, aren’t I?
Totally.
How’re you feeling?
A little weak.
You’re having a good day.
The symptoms will quickly focus
more and more on your lungs,
you’ll find it difficult to talk
and eventually breathe at all.
I think I know what
I have to look forward to.
I know.
I just came to ask
if you’d be willing to
accept any treatment.
Naw, if you’re trying
to scare me into any...
No. Palliative treatment.
Narcotics, Fentanyl patch,
morphine drip, whatever it takes.
We can make your last days
fairly comfortable.
And if you have another
good day, maybe dinner.
Hmm.
Thank you.
You want third-world treatment?
You got it.
Boy, is it hot here in Jani!
- What are you doing?
- What am I doing?
Putting everything
on the floor of the hut.
Uh oh, wicked magic box
with the moving pictures!
You think he’s a hypocrite?
Hypocrite? No, everyone in Africa’s
got cell phones or running water.
Hah, this thing just will not flush.
Do you really think
that if you come in here
and make it a little hot,
make it smell a little, that
I’m just going to fold and abandon
everything that matters to me?
Lousy sanitation over there, too.
You are not the same as them,
your life is not the same.
And you are cheapening
everything they’re going through
by pretending you are.
I am the same,
I’m not special.
You can’t demand to be treated
like any third-world sick person
and call a press conference!
They treat me special!
That doesn’t mean I am!
Now what kind of selfish jerk
wouldn’t take advantage of that fact?
It’s all preventable.
Stoia Tucker makes
medications right here,
in New Jersey.
They have warehouses
full of the stuff;
there’s more than
enough to go around.
So if I can get them,
why can’t Lemma?
Why can’t Quesmo?
And why can’t Sarni?
[Snaps]
Another person just died.
Where is your outrage?
[Snaps]
[On TV] No, I have no intention
of martyring myself,
I’m just putting myself...
[Keeps snapping]
Sure, they’re dying,
but it’s got a great beat.
Must be hot as hell
under those lights.
Yup.
Hey, why the page? He okay?
He’s in a coma.
I need you to apologize
to Ceci, Cecily...
Mrs. Carter? For what?
- For whatever I did.
- You didn’t do anything.
That has been
my position all along.
[On TV] X-rays are negative,
so he’s not contagious at this point,
his condition’s currently stable...
D’you notice how all the
self-sacrificing women in history...
Joan of Arc, Mother Theresa,
can’t think of any others...
they all die alone.
The men on the other hand
get so much fuzz it’s crazy.
It’s an unfair world.
House, she was scared
and unreasonable.
Insulting a woman with breast cancer...
that’s a move best left to the pros.
Frankly, you don’t have the chops.
I didn’t insult her!
I did the unnecessary biopsy,
like she wanted.
It was negative,
like I knew it would be.
What did you do,
call ‘em perky?
You are years away
from mad skills like that.
I need you to apologize.
You know, Cuddy’s only doing this
because she thinks it’s you.
Welcome to the world.
Everyone’s different,
everyone gets treated different.
You try fighting that,
you end up dying of TB.
What are you doing?
Testing the patient’s
autonomic nervous system.
Of course.
His internal heating and
ventilation should be off,
shouldn’t be able to sweat.
That’s why he’s got that
awful body powder.
Take it away, crank up the heat,
stick him under the lights,
can’t cool himself.
He should be turning bright red.
The picture’s fine.
I’m asking Stoia Tucker
to save these lives, millions of lives.
Including my own.
Dr. House,
I would appreciate it
if you left us alone.
Get that out of my face.
Cuddy:
What are you trying
to prove, House?
Dr. House,
I would appreciate it
if you left the room.
He’s sweating like a pig.
It’s a hundred degrees
in here, House, because
you turned up the thermostat.
Did they hear me?
The media, did they listen?
He’s disoriented.
They, they have to hear me.
His arteries are clamping down.
[A monitor starts beeping]
I want everybody out of here, now!
Get the crash cart,
he’s having a cardiac arrest!
[More beeping.]
Cuddy:
Get them out!
Everyone, I want everyone
out of here now!
Clear.
Come on, Sebastian. Clear!
I’ve got sinus rhythm.
That is not TV!
Compelling television.
Do whatever tests you want.
I want to treat you for TB.
Dr. Cameron found low sugar
in your cerebrospinal fluid.
It’s a classic finding of TB.
And now you think
TB’s the problem?
Nah. TB caused
cardiac arrest on a hot day,
your work in Africa would be
even more futile than it already is.
Can you get to your point, please?
That white board in my office,
we’re up to about a dozen symptoms now.
Cardiac arrest, clearly not TB.
CSF sugar clearly is TB.
The rest of them
could go either way.
Unless we know which ones
are which I can’t diagnose you.
I’ll take any other tests or treatments
you might want to prescribe.
So you’re
not special, but TB is.
People die of TB
because we let them,
it’s our choice.
People die of malaria
because we let them,
they die of dysentery...
Nah, TB’s my disease.
You own a disease?
Well, I’m sorry
I missed the IPO
on dengue fever.
Look, I know
I have a way about me.
I know I piss a lot of people off,
and a whole lot more I just annoy.
But you’re the first person that
I’ve ever met who I think is
actually annoyed by what I do.
Do you think
I’m not saving any lives,
or is that a bad thing?
Right now, I’m just
trying to save your life.
Or do you just have
a problem with hope?
You know,
the difference between our jobs
is not numbers or styles.
It’s that I know
I’m gonna fail.
Even if I save a million people
there’s gonna be another million.
You couldn’t handle that.
I think you resent anyone who can.
Can’t we just agree that
you’re incredibly annoying?
Take the pills or I let you die,
do an autopsy,
call my own press conference,
and make sure the world knows
that you didn’t die of TB.
Corporate sponsors
will be disappointed, but
they’ll find another disease.
Why would you do that?
Because I’m just a
mean son of a bitch.
So we still have to explain
P-R variability, syncope, headaches,
and...low sugar?
- That was classic TB.
- Apparently not.
Cameron: You’ve rerun the test?
Chase: Yeah.
This is good!
Good? This is bizarre.
Bizarre is good!
Common has hundreds
of explanations.
Bizarre has hardly any.
What else could
cause low CSF sugar?
Uh-uh. I get to
ask the questions.
I’ve found you look
a lot smarter asking the questions
than dumbly not answering.
- High insulin levels in his blood.
- They’d have to be very high.
Chase: Okay, very high
insulin levels in his blood.
How could he get
high insulin levels?
We’ve checked
daily blood sugars, all normal!
See how smart she looks?
Cause she asked the question.
And it’s not glucagonoma
because he has no rash.
It’s not self-induced
because he’s not an idiot,
and it’s not a tumor
because the CT and the MRI
were both negative.
Which just leaves tumor.
Why do you do this?
Why do you ignore
what I say like I’m not even...
Small tumor.
Really, really tiny.
So small we can’t see it.
Nesidioblastoma.
An abnormal growth of
the insulin-secreting glands
of his pancreas?
It only intermittently
secretes insulin.
It responds to stress.
Like if, oh, I don’t know,
if someone accidentally puts
the mechanical bull on 11.
Easily removed by surgery.
Except, if it’s so small
we can’t see it,
how’re we even going
to prove it’s there?
“She asked, looking clever.”
We just start hacking away
at his pancreas until he gets better?
How do you prove
something exists
when you can’t see it?
Does God exist?
Does the wind blow?
We know because
the leaves move.
[Elevator dings]
Look for effects.
Uh, we should look the other way.
It’s Cuddy with your patient.
Cuddy:
Dr. House!
Dr. House has an emergency.
- We can’t avoid her forever.
- Eventually she’ll die.
You sure she doesn’t
have breast cancer?
House:
We think you have a tumor,
easily removed surgically.
We’re going to
poke it with a stick.
And if there’s no tumor?
Nothing happens.
Splenic artery,
it’s a hard left off the celiac.
If there is a tumor?
What usually happens
when you poke something
with a stick? It pokes back.
He’s stuck in the
superior mesenteric.
I knew we should have
stopped for directions. Men.
I’m there.
We’re going to inject calcium
into your pancreas.
The beta cells will release insulin.
If there are
too many beta cells
because of a tumor,
your blood sugar will
drop precipitously.
How do we know
it won’t go too low?
Fingers and toes crossed.
Go ahead.
Glucose is holding steady at 75.
No leaves rustling.
Blow harder.
I already gave him 1 amp.
Well, I guess
now would be the time to
give him more than 1 amp.
Cameron:
50. It’s starting to drop.
45.
I think my arm’s shaking.
I’m gonna start him
on a glucose drip.
He’s gonna seize
Not yet.
Foreman:
He’s continuing to drop.
House:
Not fast enough.
[Monitor beeps]
He’s seizing.
We’ve got to reverse this.
Cameron:
He’s at 40, 38, 35...
[Monitor beeps more]
Push an amp of D-50,
you want to kill the guy?
We’re back to 40.
Congratulations,
you have a tumor.
[Elevator dings]
Are you gonna
go out with him?
Is that any of your business?
Nope.
I don’t think so.
Two days ago
you were holding his hand.
What’s changed?
He practically lives in Africa,
there’s no future.
On the other hand,
maybe there’s too much
of a future now.
You weren’t attracted to him
because he was prepared
to die for a cause,
you were attracted to him
because he was actually doing it.
Right. It’s that simple.
That was simple?
I put a label on them
and go from there.
Everybody does it.
We are who people think we are.
People think he’s a great doctor
so they give him stuff.
He is a great doctor.
The reality is irrelevant.
I’ll prove it.
People who know me
see me as an ass,
treat me as an ass.
People who don’t know me
see a cripple, treat me as a cripple.
What kind of selfish jerk wouldn’t
take advantage of that fact?
Ow!
Oh, my goodness,
are you okay?
Yeah.
I am so sorry.
It was completely my fault.
It’s nothing, I’m fine.
Well, I’m very relieved,
I feel terrible.
Don’t worry about it,
I’m fine.
- You sure?
- Mmm. - Okay.
How’s everything?
I’m gonna go.
My foot’s killing me.
- Oh, what did you do?
- It was nothing, it was all my fault.
[On phone]
Yeah, listen Fugawi, relax.
I’m gonna be back on Tuesday.
Tell Sarni I’m gonna
bring her a new brace. All right.
Just in case.
You get ‘em?
Six month supply.
Should fix you right up.
I see you when
you come back for a refill?
Yeah, I’ll see you
in two months.
You’re gonna give them away?
Well, you know
how these things happen,
you leave a bag in the airplane,
drop some pills
down the drain...
I have an idea.
You could bring me
the refill in Africa.
I don’t think so.
You actually like
working for House,
you find this satisfying?
["Stranger in a Strange Land"
by Leon Russell]
# How many days has it been
since I was born? #
# How many days
until I die?   Why? #
# Do I know any way that
I can make you laugh? #
Thank you, thank you,
I appreciate that.
I appreciate the support.
It’s not about the kids
dying every 8 seconds,
it’s about the media stroking.
Adulation and pats on the head.
That’s your problem
with him, isn’t it?
Look at him,
he loves it. Eats it up.
Yeah, the man actually
enjoys what he does.
Listen, I saved his life.
That means
I get credit for every life
he saves from here on out.
I’ll make sure
Stockholm knows.
www.tvsubtitles.net