(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
Hi, kids.
Mommy, Iook what I made.
Oh, wow.
It's a farmer and a cow
and some horses.
It's beautiful.
It's for Ted's office.
Oh, he's gonna Iove it.
And it'd be nice
if you called him Dad.
Give me a big hug.
Secret is the Haas avocados.
I can e-mail you the recipe
if you want.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
It's the third time
they've changed plans
since Friday.
These idiots think you can
just add a 14th floor
and the mayor won't notice.
And I thought turning
the garage into a nursery
was complicated.
Any Iuck on your end yet?
Not for Iack of trying.
MARGO: Ted.
(CROWD CHEERING ON TV)
Come on.
Come on, Margo!
I have to go tell a client
he's an idiot.
Go kick some ass.
I have to take Stella to
karate by 3:00 and a birthday
party at Julia's after.
You okay?
Yeah. I'II be back.
Just make sure she's dressed.
(GROANING)
(MARGO MOANING)
Honey! Honey!
(CRYING)
CUDDY: He's actually on time.
He's six minutes early.
Something's happened.
I'm on it.
Good morning, Jimmy.
Anybody die
while I was gone?
Did you iron your shirt?
I thought about shaving.
Couldn't find a razor.
What the hell happened
in Baltimore?
Sorry, chief.
Never kiss and tell.
I think you just did.
There's no such thing
as "just a kiss."
Did you iron your shirt?
Everybody's flash today.
Has she Ieft Mark?
Is she going to?
I think I can hear
cancer kids calling.
Are you planning on asking her
to Ieave Mark?
Not sure.
Cameron keeps my calendar.
Hey. This is a big deal.
This is an affair.
Have you even talked to Stacy
about what the hell
this means?
Didn't have
a Iot of time for talking,
if you know what I mean.
Great. Breaking up a marriage.
Fertile ground
for high comedy.
We need to talk about this.
Gosh, wish I could.
How did the HIV test go?
You study up?
I rescheduled
for this afternoon.
We have a new patient.
Thirty-four-year-old female,
movement disorder.
Movement disorder?
Fascinating.
This isn't just gonna go away.
No. But maybe you will.
Probably suffered head trauma
in the car accident.
Trauma Ieads
to the dyskinesia.
According to her husband,
the flailing started
before she got
anywhere near that car.
HOUSE: What does
the flailing Iook Iike?
Her arms spasm uncontrollably
and there's
a mild facial twitch.
Demonstration?
You wanna know
what it Iooks Iike,
go see the patient.
Oh, snarky.
Was he Iike this
the whole time I was gone?
The patient's
been on a fertility regimen
for the Iast 13 months.
Excess estrogen
in the system could explain...
Who finished
the animal crackers?
Sudden movement disorder
could be a symptom
of Huntington's.
If you finish something,
don't just put back
the empty box, throw it out.
Huntington's
takes a day to confirm.
We should put her on tamoxifen
in case it is
the fertility meds,
counteract the estrogen.
That's a great idea
if you wanna kill her baby.
Movement disorder can present
in the first trimester.
She's not pregnant.
Peeing on a stick
is only 99% accurate.
Get a real pregnancy test.
You know, the one with
the blood and the hormones
and the rabbit.
Oh, I'm sorry,
it's still your Iimo.
What do you say, Miss Daisy?
Whatever you want.
Lame duck's done quacking.
You quack,
people shoot at you.
Cuddy just put me here
to make you miserable.
Another two days,
you can go back
to making yourself miserable.
Okay, get an MRI.
See if it's in her head
or in her uterus.
You're gonna want
to paralyze her.
You run tests on a flailer,
somebody's gonna Iose an eye.
(GASPING)
Sorry. You think I'm pregnant?
We need to find out for sure.
Would all this go away
once she delivered?
It could also be neurological.
We need to get an MRI.
Can she do that
if she's pregnant?
The risk to the fetus
is extremely Iow.
But there is a risk.
I don't think we should do it
until we're sure.
Ted, I think
you should take Stella home.
I wanna stay here.
We should be with you.
You should take her
out of the room.
We're gonna temporarily stop
Margo's spasms.
You can do that?
Vecuronium.
It's a paralytic.
Essentially cuts off the brain
from the muscles.
Don't worry.
Your mom will be just fine.
It'II make
running the tests easier,
and it won't be
dangerous for the baby
if you are pregnant.
TED: Let's go, Stella.
I want to go with Mommy.
We'II be just outside, okay?
We gotta Iet the doctors
get her better.
AII right?
It's okay, sweetie.
Love you.
Your vitals
will be watched closely.
I'm gonna close your Iids
so your eyes don't dry out.
Just try to relax.
What the hell did you do?
Were you just cold and Ionely?
Of course he told you.
He's an eight-year-old boy.
Hey, you're the one
who kissed him.
Why are you so worked up
over this?
Because you're married.
Not to you.
This is none of your business.
The Iast time you Ieft,
I was the one stuck
picking up the pieces.
Oh, right. He cried
himself to sleep every night.
That so sounds Iike him.
He's been pining
for five years.
You're being dramatic.
No. Actually,
I'm underplaying.
This is me being restrained.
It was one kiss.
Are you being
intentionally thick?
This was not
just a one-night stand.
You can't toy with him.
I'm not.
He's probably toying with me.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Oh, boy.
Welcome back to the world.
You're off the vecuronium.
Could you wiggle your toes
for me?
The MRI was clear.
Whatever this is,
isn't in your brain.
MRI. So I'm not pregnant?
CAMERON: I'm sorry.
So what do we do next?
Well, it could be a variety
of things, some treatable,
others more serious.
Open up.
I'm gonna run a genetic test
for Huntington's.
That one of
the more serious ones?
Yeah.
It's also possible
that this is just a symptom
of the fertility treatments.
And now that we know you're
not pregnant, we're gonna
start you on tamoxifen
to counteract the estrogen.
Will that undo
all the fertility treatments?
For the time being, yeah.
But it could cure you.
You can start trying again
once we get you healthy.
Damn it!
The spasms are gonna get worse
now that the vecuronium
is wearing off.
What are you so scared of?
I'm still your mother.
I'm just a Iittle sick.
Why did you even
bring her here? I told you
to Ieave her at home.
FOREMAN: Hypervigilance,
sudden irritability.
Symptomatic
of Iunch with Cuddy?
The patient
now defines Huntington's.
Then what do you need me for?
Start her
on Huntington's meds.
Before we get
her test results back?
We start her on valproic acid,
it could destroy her Iiver.
Could stroke.
If we wait,
she could progress
to full-blown psychosis,
and then her kid
will never get the chance
to say goodbye.
Wanna tell the class
how that feels?
Huntington's patients
don't progress to psychosis
in a day.
(PAGER BEEPING)
She went from zero to 60
in world record time.
Indicating it might be
something other
than Huntington's.
We got a problem.
Stay away from me!
Where's my daughter?
What's happening?
She's having
a psychotic break.
No! She is not yours!
What do you want with her?
Calm down!
TED: Honey.
Margo,
you're gonna hurt someone.
No.
CHASE: Push two milligrams
of Ativan.
I want my daughter!
She's not yours!
No more experiments!
No!
CAMERON: How can
her Huntington's test
be negative?
FOREMAN: AII the signs
are there. Movement disorder,
psychosis.
It should be Huntington's.
Yeah.
It would certainly
make your job easier.
Well, good news for Margo,
it's not Huntington's.
Bad news for us,
her psychotic break
eliminates fertility meds.
Which means we have no idea
what's wrong with her.
We give you so much,
and you give us so Iittle.
You know, the patient
is prime age to develop
spontaneous schizophrenia.
AImost impossible.
No family history
of mental illness.
How about toxins?
None of her family members
are sick. Nobody at her
office, her volunteer group,
kid's classes,
and PTA members, all fine.
So she raises a daughter,
runs a business,
she does charity work,
she volunteers at school,
attends PTA.
What makes Mommy run?
You're thinking drugs?
Cocaine.
Explains the psychosis
and the flailing.
And the uncanny ability
to bring home the bacon,
fry it up in a pan,
and never ever Iet Teddy
forget that he's a man.
I'II go Iook for her stash.
Take Foreman.
There's gotta be a reason
for the stereotype.
I know you're in there.
I can hear you caring.
The door was Iocked.
It means
I didn't wanna see anyone.
High school reunion?
It's for a patient.
She can't roll.
Hey, I Iocked that door, too.
Paranoia.
Must be the good stuff.
Times Iike these,
I wish I had cancer.
So what did she say?
It depends. What did you do,
and who are we talking about?
We both know
that as soon as we talked,
you ran to Stacy
so you could gossip
and giggle.
I need to know what she said.
I have a crazy idea.
Why don't you go talk to her?
Because my bestest buddy
says that could
Iead to trouble.
She sounds confused,
but I don't think she is.
I think she's waiting for you
to do something,
show her you're serious.
Wow.
It's a big jump from
"infidelity is morally wrong"
to "do her."
I didn't say "do her."
I said do something.
What exactly did she say?
She didn't say
it was a mistake.
She's not gonna Ieave Mark
in the middle of his rehab.
Too much guilt.
She Ieft you.
Harsh toke, dude.
House.
Killjoy.
I could've covered this.
You need to get
that test today.
I wish you guys would remember
my birthday
instead of my HIV test.
Forgive us
for being concerned.
I got a bet with House.
He says
you're too scared to get it.
I say you're too anal not to.
I'II cut you in.
CAMERON: That was
a colossal waste.
FOREMAN: Who would've known?
Searching a high-end family
home for illicit narcotics
was such an obvious choice.
Working moms practically
Iive in their cars.
Little bump on the run.
You were a car thief, right?
Mama's Iittle helper.
House, Ritalin.
Cocaine with a PG rating.
Prescribed to her daughter.
Mommy does everything
for her family these days,
even swallows their pills.
It's possible the kid's meds
are the kid's meds.
Pop enough Ritalin,
it can explain everything.
Well, Ritalin maybe explains
some tics, some involuntary...
No, case reports
have referred to chorea.
She's been cut off
from her stash,
so the flailing's tapered off,
the psychosis hasn't returned.
It's perfect.
Tox screen will confirm that.
Half-Iife's 1 2 hours.
Drugs will be
out of her system.
We're done. Get rid of her.
We're not done.
We have to confirm the
diagnosis before we send her
home to die of something else.
Oh, yes.
The power tastes so sweet.
You just can't resist.
You're Iike a diabetic
at the ice cream counter.
You wanna say no,
but you need
that chocolaty goodness.
Yeah, well,
I'm still signing the charts.
So until tomorrow,
you're not allowed
to kill anyone.
Wuss.
We've asked her three times
if she's on any meds.
So we don't ask her.
Candy striper.
So, you Iike dogs?
(WHISTLING)
That's not a dog.
Smart kid.
Are you always
such a good Iittle girl,
or does Mommy sometimes say
you're the reason
she needs a double martini?
Who are you?
Over here, kiddo.
I'm talking to you. Focus.
Must be because
you're off your meds.
Who are you?
Doctor and candy striper.
She's not on any medication.
HOUSE: Well, that's strange.
'Cause this bottle has her
name on it. And I think these
are medical pills inside.
What's he talking about?
The doctor
prescribed Stella...
A few months ago.
I never told you about it,
because I never gave her any.
That's funny,
'cause the bottle's
almost empty.
You missed a couple of days.
Take five.
Stop.
Why? Unless they're not hers.
You need some water, sweetie?
I'm not taking Ritalin.
Come on. AII the cool moms
are doing it.
And tox screen
says you're cool, too.
You were on drugs
while taking care of Stella?
I'm sorry, Ted.
It's a cafeteria menu.
It should take a couple hours
to process her.
Then you can take her home
and divorce her.
Working Iate?
Or are you just avoiding Mark?
It was one kiss, Greg.
So far. I'm planning
on keeping a chart.
I'm moving back
to Short Hills.
I think it's time.
You're Ieaving?
It was never meant to be
permanent, and now
that Mark's getting better...
Yeah, much better.
Except for the whole
walking thing.
He needs to get back to work.
Right.
Saving the next generation
from making bad choices
about acne cream.
You're running away
because the kiss
meant something.
I'm not running away.
I'm going home.
With Mark.
I Iove Mark.
You Iove me more.
I don't want you to Ieave.
Are we okay?
I'm sorry.
Let's just get you home.
That's a good idea.
Mommy!
Hey!
Call a code!
What's wrong, Mommy?
What's going on?
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
This better be important.
You've gotta come back in.
No, I don't.
Margo's stable, but...
Oh, my God.
Well, I'II be right there.
She had a stroke.
Perfect.
(SIGHS)
Gotta go back to work.
Right now?
Well...
Patient's stable.
Could maybe wait a half-hour.
He should have been here
20 minutes ago.
Doubt if he makes it at all.
I saw him Ieave with Stacy.
He was probably
just walking her to her car.
Oh, yeah.
That sounds Iike House.
He's not an idiot.
He's not gonna hook up
with a married woman.
I hope he is getting some.
Maybe he'II mellow out.
(HOUSE SINGING)
What took you so Iong?
It's midnight.
Traffic. Cinco de Mayo.
You owe me $100.
You didn't take the test?
Fear trumps anal every time.
It's not a big deal.
I had the viral Ioad
and antibody test.
It's 99.9%
that I don't have HIV.
And if you have the test,
and it's negative,
you gain a tenth of a point.
But if it's positive you Iose
nearly 100, right?
No arrhythmia,
so Ritalin
isn't the big problem.
Something else is going on.
Fine, Iet's play doctors.
I removed the clot
which caused the stroke.
Problem is,
we don't know
where it came from.
Did ultrasounds of her heart,
arms and Iegs. AII clear.
Could be
a protein C deficiency.
Wouldn't explain
the movement disorder.
Nothing explains everything.
What if
it's a crime syndicate?
Let's say Ritalin
and the fertility meds
plotted a caper.
Ritalin takes care
of the psychosis,
the flailing.
I still don't think Ritalin...
HOUSE: Fertility meds
are competitive by nature.
They had to do
something bigger,
something really unexpected.
Fertility treatments
have been known
to cause endometrial cancer.
Which could cause clots,
which could have caused her
to stroke.
So ultrasound her uterus
this time.
See if there's something
growing in there that doesn't
Iook adorable in a onesie.
Cameron. I Iove you.
You'II get your test results
tomorrow.
The prescription
for my heart condition.
A bit on the cheesy side.
I was trying for romantic.
Still fits.
Did you tell Mark?
I told him I had to work Iate.
You gonna tell him?
How am I gonna tell him?
Still working
on that phrasing.
How about,
"You know all the stuff you
were worried about when we
first came here, honey?
"You were right."
Pithy.
Everything's easy
when you don't care
if you hurt anyone.
You already
did the hurting part.
He just doesn't know it yet.
If I never tell him,
it'II never hurt.
I want not to Iove Mark.
I wanna hate you.
I want all of this
to be simple,
but it's not.
You can either
have a Iife with me,
or you can have
a Iife with him.
It can't be both.
It's not easy,
but it is simple.
No endometrial thickening.
No masses.
FOREMAN: No cancer.
She's on fertility treatments.
She had a blood clot.
It's there.
Millions of women
are on fertility treatments
and they don't get cancer.
Right. They get babies.
She had a blood clot
and a stroke.
She'II get another one
and probably die,
if we don't find that tumor.
Do an endometrial biopsy.
Biopsy's painful
and unnecessary.
We just did an ultrasound.
What?
(HOUSE SHUSHING)
If you have a personal issue
that's interfering with...
What are we waiting for?
Your four weeks just expired.
Your reign of terror is over.
Mine has just begun.
Now go stick a needle
up her hoo-hoo
and find that cancer.
"Hoo-hoo"?
He went to Hopkins.
COMMENTATOR 1 : Pergasaurus
has got 1,500 horsepower blown
and injected with alcohol.
COMMENTATOR 2: Yeah,
that baby really moves.
COMMENTATOR 1 : Oh, yeah, and
the transmission, two-speed
Powerglide. Suspension...
What are you watching?
TV.
What are you doing here?
Ted's with my mom.
He asked the nurse
to watch me.
What nurse?
She's not really watching me.
I got that.
Do you still
have the balloons?
No.
Do you wanna play something?
Nope.
When can Mommy come home?
Don't know.
What's wrong with your foot?
War wound.
Does it hurt?
Every day.
Is that why you're so sad?
Oh, aren't you adorable?
I'm not sad, I'm complicated.
Chicks dig that.
One day you'II understand.
That's what my parents say
when they don't want me
to know something.
They say that a Iot?
Only when they're talking
about making babies and stuff.
When you catch them fighting?
They don't fight.
Not ever?
People who Iove each other
don't fight.
Right. Forgot that.
What floor was that nurse on
who was watching you?
Two.
Good talk.
At your age, the type of
uterine cancer that develops
is not Iikely to metastasize.
It's very treatable.
Okay, hold still, Margo.
(STAMMERING) I'm feeling
a Iittle bit dizzy.
Oh, my God.
(MONITOR BEEPING RAPIDLY)
BP's dropping.
What's going on?
CHASE: Get him out of here.
CAMERON: Heart rate's 98
and rising.
We've gotta find that bleed.
What'd you do, hit an artery?
With what?
I hadn't even started
the procedure.
(MOANING)
I need some advice.
Whatever it is, can it wait?
Yeah.
What was Greg Iike
after I Ieft?
An egomaniacal
narcissistic pain in the ass.
Same as before you Ieft.
Do you think he's capable
of having a real relationship?
What happened in Baltimore?
Nothing.
Right.
Maybe something.
Technically,
most of the something
happened after Baltimore.
Oh, God, Stacy.
I don't know what to do.
Are you seriously thinking
about Ieaving Mark?
No. I don't know.
I can't.
And you want me
to tell you it's okay?
It wasn't all bad with Greg.
I was with him for a reason.
You Ieft him for a reason.
I could swear
I remember him being fun.
Sorry for the scare.
Just tell me she's okay.
UItrasound showed the bleed
was coming from her Iiver.
It's rare, but the blood
got into her fallopian tubes.
In a way, it was Iucky.
Let us know we were Iooking
in the wrong place.
The tumor's in her Iiver.
Is it cancer?
We're running some more tests.
There it is.
It's a Iiver tumor.
Well, if it's malignant, at
Ieast she's only gonna Ieave
one child without a mother.
Do a biopsy.
We can't. It's vascular.
MARK: House.
What?
I'm here about Stacy.
What about her?
I think I'm Iosing her.
Your wife, your problem.
She won't talk to me.
So what?
You gonna talk to me instead?
Talk to your shrink.
She keeps saying
everything's fine.
Find a bar.
Talk to a stranger.
You're the only one
who's been through this.
I'm shutting her out.
I'm saying things
and then hating myself
for saying them.
How did you get past that?
Didn't.
Can you please be
a human being for one minute
and talk to me?
Sorry. Gotta go. People dying.
You're not gonna outrun me.
House!
You're not ready for this.
I've seen the way
you and Stacy
talk to each other.
You're an idiot.
You probably
just set your rehab
back three months.
Let go. Get off of me!
Liver tumor
doesn't make sense.
You saying the CT was wrong?
I'm saying the symptoms
don't add up. A plus B
does not equal Iiver tumor.
We gotta solve for X.
We gotta Iook at this
differently.
What do we know about her?
The side effects
of the Ritalin caused the...
No. We've examined the file
up and down.
Come on, give me that.
Why do you people
always overlook
the human element?
What do we know about her?
Margo...
Dalton. The woman.
She's a people-pleaser.
She doesn't Iike
to Iet people down.
Never fights with her husband.
She turned to drugs
instead of asking for help
to manage her Iife.
So if she can't manage now,
why does she want another kid?
Foreman,
I need your help here.
You wanna pull a bank job,
would you go it alone?
If you gonna rob a home, sure,
that's a one or two man crew.
But a bank,
you need a Iookout,
a getaway driver.
I'm not saying anything
until the metaphor
plays itself out.
So here's the caper.
Fertility meds
create a distraction.
Mommy had three refills
on Ritalin
in the Iast three weeks.
That team goes straight
for the top floor.
No trouble taking out
communications, but they need
the specialist, a safecracker.
AII he does is stroke,
blood clot, Iiver tumor.
Foreman was right.
This badass
even does flailing.
Come on.
There's only one guy I know
who does that kind of work.
Birth control pills?
While the surgeons
are cutting out
a chunk of your Iiver,
should I have them do
a hysterectomy, too?
A hysterectomy?
I'm trying to get pregnant.
You don't have to Iie to me.
We're not married.
You're Supermom.
You can do anything.
You work seven days a week,
you volunteer,
you raise a kid.
Yet you still
somehow find the time
to Iie to hubby number two
that you really, really wanna
give him a child with his chin
and pretty brown eyes.
What makes you think
that I would...
Because it fits.
Birth control pills caused
a hepatocellular adenoma.
Explains all your symptoms
that aren't explained
by your other Iies.
That's it?
AIso...
I'II have the tuna on rye.
Would you Iike
to Ieave my room now?
Your tumor is benign.
Stop taking the pill,
and it will go away
on its own.
I'm canceling the surgery.
What are you
gonna tell my husband?
That I'm canceling
the surgery.
You can do the explaining.
It's tricky, huh?
It's one thing to say
you can't have a baby.
It's another to say
you don't want one.
Personally, I'd make up
some other Iie.
Could...
Could I die on the table?
Could you die
if you tell him the truth?
I need this surgery.
I'm not on the pill.
You can't cancel the surgery.
If she goes off the pill,
the tumor
goes away on its own.
You have no proof
the birth control pills
caused this.
You have no proof
she's even taking them.
If we do the surgery
maybe we'II kill her
on the table.
Then I can prove
I'm right at the autopsy.
Or we can forget the surgery,
Iet the tumor grow,
and kill her.
Why don't you take it up
with Stacy, see which option
minimizes your risk?
Here's what I think
she's gonna say,
"Oh, I Iove Greg.
"But if you go against
the patient's wishes,
you're calling her a Iiar.
"And if something goes wrong,
I end up in court
"having to defend
the big mean doctor,
albeit with dreamy eyes,
"who wouldn't believe
the nice suburban mom.
"And even though
his cane makes me melt,
do the damn surgery."
HOUSE: Shocking.
It's benign.
People do
crazy things for Iove.
No, crazy is hanging out
in the park all day
talking to pigeons.
Margo knows what she's doing.
She gave up half her Iiver
to save her marriage.
No, she surgically removed her
fingerprints
to cover her pathetic Iie.
It's twisted and manipulative.
I get that. But it's also
romantic.
I'm barely willing
to put the seat down
after I pee.
Do we need to talk?
Nope. I'm fine.
So the surgeon
got the whole tumor,
and it was benign.
That's good, right?
Yeah, benign is good.
How could a benign tumor
have caused all the symptoms?
We believe
all your wife's symptoms
will go away now.
Oh, thank God.
Look,
I'm gonna pick up Stella.
I'II call you
after I get the babysitter.
Dr. Foreman,
you can help me.
You could tell my husband that
because of all this,
I can't take
any more fertility treatments.
Confidentiality rules stop me
from telling your husband
the truth.
But my obligation to Iie
ends there.
Are there...
Is there a birth control
method, something
that won't make me sick?
Margo,
you're gonna have risks
with everything,
especially
if you're not telling
your fertility doctor.
If you keep doing this,
it's gonna kill your marriage
and kill you.
You don't know.
In a few years,
we'II give up.
Stop trying to get pregnant.
We'II hug, cry.
Eventually Ted will stop
thinking about it, and he'II
appreciate Stella even more.
And we'II Iive
happily together
for the next 50 years.
Something you need to see.
Knowing is always better
than not knowing.
It's a referral request.
Right.
The HIV thing came in earlier.
You're fine.
You won't read your mail,
but you'II open mine?
It said "confidential,"
and I wanted to know.
The most important Ietter
of my Iife,
and you're still an ass.
Comforting, isn't it?
(DOOR OPENING)
Hey.
Hi.
I'm gonna talk to Mark
tonight, and I'm gonna
stay here with you.
Don't do it.
This isn't funny, Greg.
I know.
You
spent all these months
chasing me.
Now I'm here
and you start running?
What the hell changed?
Nothing.
Nothing changes.
I'm not gonna change.
Who asked you to?
Mark is willing to do
whatever it takes.
I'm not.
Never was.
Now you're introspective?
Weren't so analytical
the other night.
You were happy with Mark.
You'II be happy again.
Shut up about Mark.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
I can't make you happy!
What?
How do you think
this is gonna end?
We'II be happy, for what?
A few weeks? A few months?
And then I'II...
I'II say something insensitive
or I'II
start ignoring you.
And at first it'II be okay.
It's just House being House.
And then,
at some point,
you will need something more.
You'II need someone
who can give you
something I can't.
You know I'm right.
I've been there before.
Oh.
It doesn't have to be.
It does.
I don't wanna go there again.
I'm sorry, Stacy.
(DOOR CLOSING)
(SIGHS)
$50 says they're
divorced in a year.
Six months, tops.
I'II take that bet.
It's the perfect marriage.
There's nothing to fight over
if you never
talk about anything.
What did you tell her?
I told her
she's better off without me.
That's probably true.
You're an idiot.
You don't think
she'd be better off
without you.
Right.
I sent her off on a whim.
You have no idea
why you sent her off!
Don't do this.
This was no great sacrifice!
You sent her away because
you've got to be miserable!
This kind of psycho-crap
help get your patients
through the Iong nights?
Or is it just for you?
Tough Iove make you feel good?
Helping people
feel their pain?
You don't Iike yourself.
But you do admire yourself.
It's all you've got,
so you cling to it.
You're so afraid
if you change, you'II Iose
what makes you special.
Being miserable
doesn't make you better
than anybody else, House.
It just makes you miserable.
www.tvsubtitles.net