# Down in my heart #
I have a joy joy joy joy
# Down in my heart to stay #
[All whoop in joy]
Do you feel the spirit?
All:
Yeah! Halleluiah!
And in the 39th year of his reign,
Asa was diseased in his feet,
until the disease was exceedingly great.
Yet...
he didn't seek help from the Lord,
but from the physicians.
Now, there is nothing wrong
with seeing a doctor.
But can a doctor heal through the power
that Jesus gave his disciples?
Men of science can walk
through life with blindfolds
never knowing that you or I
could not take a single step
if we were not uplifted by God.
Agnes,
thank you for letting me
an instrument of God's love for you.
In faith...
Oh...
all things are possible.
My friends,
I want you to let Agnes
feel the wave of faith
in this church here today
lifting her into God's hands.
[All cheer]
You can do it.
Come on, sister.
"Oh Happy Day"
Praise Jesus.
# Oh happy day #
# (Oh happy day) #
Thank you, God!
Thank you, Lord!
Thanks be to God!
Thank you, Lo--
Oof!
Oof, oof!
No!
Son!
Dad, I think I need a doctor.
Agh!
2X19 - House vs God
Original Airdate (FOX): 25 APR-2006
Did you remember my DVD player?
Well, if you wanted it,
you shouldn't have left it behind
when you moved out.
Now I get it.
It's a drag watching porn on VHS.
I'll call you
as soon as I'm done with it.
That's if you ever
get a phone installed.
Oh, forget it.
I'll come by and get it myself.
After work? Thursday?
Won't be home Thursday.
No problem, I still have a key.
I can let myself in and out.
I guess maybe I could
bring it in tomorrow.
After all, how many times
can you hit pause
at the part where Lindsay Lohan
wins the spelling bee?
What is it about
girls who can spell?
It's math contest.
What is it about girls
who can count?
It's poker night, isn't it?
[Elevator dings]
You said weeks ago
that I could play.
- Stop making excuses.
- Gotta go.
Building full of sick people.
If I hurry,
maybe I can avoid them.
The abdominal series showed
no evidence of obstruction.
What'd you have to eat?
Chicken sandwich.
We travel. Lots of fast food.
Thank you.
I barely felt it.
You're welcome.
God told me you were kind.
You talk to God?
God's presence often descends on Boyd
to help him guide others.
This been going on long?
Since he was ten.
God told me
I would meet a woman healer...
who was harboring vengeful thoughts
about a man she works with.
That's God's job.
I'll keep that in mind.
- His urine is dilute.
- What does that mean?
It could mean that for some reason
his kidneys aren't purifying
the way they should,
which would let toxins
accumulate in his body.
We'll run the blood work
and see what it tells us.
Thank you, I appreciate it.
God talks to him?
It's not psychosis,
he's just religious.
The only medical issue that
showed up on the blood work
is low sodium.
No, you talk to God, you're religious.
God talks to you, you're psychotic.
A lot of people experience their religion
as something more than symbolic.
- That doesn't mean--
- God ever talk to you when
you where in the seminary?
No.
God's loss, our gain.
He's either psychotic
or a scam artist.
He was actually
really impressive.
Well, yeah...
with the burning bush and all,
it's quite the show.
He was intelligent, polite, dignified.
He's not a typical 15-year-old.
And he told Cameron God wants her to stop being pissed at me over the article.
God  knows you stole
Cameron's article?
He knows she's
"harboring vengeful thoughts."
I'm over it.
Yeah, I can tell that from
the Berlin Wall of body language
between you.
I'm shocked
that he picked up on it.
Low sodium.
Check for Addison's?
No pigmentation and
potassium levels were normal.
Cirrhosis?
Liver feels fine.
Transaminases are normal.
[ Sighs]
We should monitor his saline intake
to correct the low sodium.
No more than one MEQ
per liter per hour.
And let's push the patient history.
See if there's any evidence
of drugs or other delusions.
I'll take care of it.
You're gonna talk to a patient?
God talks to him.
It'd be arrogant of me
to assume that I'm better than God.
So, you're a "faith healer."
Or is that a pejorative?
Do you prefer something like
"Divine health management"?
I though God might have
mentioned that I was coming.
I'm okay with"faith healer", Dr. House.
Oh! That's a nice one.
You  didn't even go with...
"I see an H and a medical coat."
The nurses talk about you a lot.
Ah, don't believe them.
I keep a sock in my pants.
Faith, that's another word
for ignorance, isn't it?
I never understood how people
could be so proud of believing in
something with no proof at all.
Like that's an achievement.
God's asking for our trust.
You can't love somebody
and not trust them.
Trust has to be earned.
You can't trust someone
hiding in a closet.
You don't trust anyone.
You seem lucid.
There's no confusion,
no lethargy.
What drugs
have you been taking?
Nothing.
Uh, some aspirin. I...
get focused on something,
I forget to eat-- Next thing you know,
I've got a hunger headache.
So aspirin and hospitals are okay.
That's an interesting attitude for
someone who's kept any number of people
from getting medical help.
Just because
I believe in prayer doesn't mean
I don't believe in germs and toxins.
That bottle's been opened before.
You refilled it
at the water cooler.
Yes.
How often do you do that?
A few times an hour.
He likes to stay hydrated.
You think germs
might have gotten in?
I think water
might have gotten in.
We can adjust your pain meds.
Again?
Suppose we increase
your Oxycodone.
We both know the only reason
I'm talking lucidly now
is because I did not take
my full dose this morning.
You've done your best.
And I have been
a good soldier.
It's time
we accept it's over.
What about the trip
you were talking about taking?
You've wanted to see Florence
since you were a teenager, right?
Yeah, go now.
All drugged up.
It's not exactly the trip
I've been dreaming of.
Okay, but you're strong.
You're dealing with this.
And there is the right combination of
pain meds out there. And we'll find it.
Don't give up on us.
And don't be startled by
the sound you're about to hear.
[Bangs at a door]
Excuse me.
I have a friend
with boundary issues.
[Crow caws]
Can this wait five minutes?
Is she dying?
Yeah.
Before the end of this consult?
They could build monuments
to your self-centeredness.
Patient. 15-year-old.
Faith healer. Hotline to God.
- What are his symptoms?
- He is not a saint.
He figures out what's going on
in people's lives by watching,
listening, deducing.
And you're worried about
trademark infringement?
Then he passes on advice from God
so he can watch them jump.
It's a power trip.
Ah, and there the similarities end.
Why is he here?
I fear for the human race.
A teenager claims to be the voice of God and
people with advanced degrees are listening.
The majority of Americans
believe in a personal God.
What are his symptoms?
Massive cramps, low sodium.
Turns out he's been
drinking water non-stop.
God told him to purify his body.
Huge water intake
would cause low sodium.
Which would cause
the cramping. Yeah, I got it.
What, that's it?
You solved it.
You just brought me out here
to rant because faith annoys you?
Mm-hmm. He's all better.
You know, I'd get it
if people were just looking
for a way to fill the holes.
But they want the holes.
They wanna live in the holes.
And they go nuts when
someone else pours dirt in their holes.
Climb out of your holes, people!
# Go tell it on the mountain #
# Over the hills and everywhere #
# That Jesus Christ is born #
# Go tell it on the mountain #
# Over the hills and everywhere #
# That Jesus Christ is born #
Boyd, are you all right?
# Go tell it on the mountain #
Boyd.
# Over the hills and... #
Come on.
Let's go.
Can you tell meyour name?
Do you know where you are?
Boyd?
God doesn't want you to be afraid.
He sent me here to heal you.
You think he hasn't heard you prayers,
but he heard them all.
Even the ones you didn't say.
Sorry. Boyd, come on.
Let's get you back to your room.
In faith,
all things are possible.
Let's go.
Lord...
I call on you to relieve
the suffering of your daughter.
- Grace?
- And make her whole again.
Hey, hey!
What are you doing? What is this?
He's just had
a complex partial seizure.
His disoriented.
He doesn't know what he's doing.
Well get him back
to his room--now.
You okay?
Are we certain
he even had a seizure?
Hymn singing and healing.
He does it all the time, doesn't he?
Isn't it interesting
that religious behavior is
so close to being crazy,
we can't tell 'em apart.
The repetition,
the lack of affect and awareness.
- It was a seizure.
- Infection?
No fever.
Could be Wilson's.
Or maybe it's
a glycogen storage disease.
- Or a brain tumor.
- Or tuberous sclerosis.
Hmm.
How to settle this?
We could ask our patient to ask God.
Or we could MRI his brain.
Which way do you wanna go?
- 'Cause I'm open to all possibilities.
- House!
Why the hell do you
let an unstable patient
wander the hallways?
His leash broke.
The last thing a terminal patient needs is
to hear somebody taunt them with a cure.
She was freaked,
she was angry.
And now she's
not freaked and angry.
And you are.
She says
she's "feeling better".
Maybe not singing and dancing, but
she's feeling just a little bit happy
for the first time in months.
Sudden drop in pain
can create euphoria.
You shouldn't let her
have her vacation?
Oh, that's great.
And when the vacation's over,
when she crash lands from all this denial?
She was dealing with her illness.
Now her expectations are rising.
And you're not the one who
has to be there when all that false hope
gets yanked out from under her.
Don't you guys
have anything to do?
How long have you
been healing people?
You believe
that's what I'm doing?
I'd like to.
But you don't.
Why do you always do things
you don't wanna do?
It's okay,
I don't expect a real answer.
God would probably want you
to take that stick out of your butt
and get over this.
If there is some higher order
running the universe,
it's probably so different from
anything our species can conceive,
there's no point
in even thinking about it.
But I doubt it gives a damn
about my butt.
So you believe God might exist,
but you don't think about it?
It's the most important issue--
I think penguins might as well
speculate about nuclear physics.
Why are we having
this conversation?
What? I'm curious.
You cannot tell someone they are
your colleague and not a friend and
then casually chat about the afterlife.
You actually keep score?
Your MRI results aren't done yet.
Go back to your room.
No singing.
Well, you would get a point
for figuring why the low sodium.
What are my guy's points for?
Your trick about the spat between
Dr. Cameron and Dr. Foreman
apparently impressed someone.
And the second point?
Do you think it could be
because I healed Grace?
She's  been back
to see me. I like her.
You like messing with people.
That's why you're here now.
Maybe you think that
your batteries are powered by God,
maybe you don't.
Either way,
you enjoy what you do.
Yes.
I like helping people.
I get a rush when
I see the look on their faces when
they realize their burdens are gone.
Mm, but you make sure
you're in the next state
by the time the endorphins wear off
and the arthritis comes back.
That doesn't happen.
Oh, you do extensive follow-up studies?
God told me.
See, that's not fair.
We were having fun.
It's hard to keep sniping rationally
when you throw a bomb like that in there.
He spoke with me about you too.
Forgive my enemies?
Never date a Taurus
when Mercury's in retrograde?
Yeah, I learned that one myself--
the hard way.
God says you look for
excuses to be alone.
See, that is exactly the kind of
brilliance that sounds deep,
but you could say it about any person
who doesn't pine for the social
approval of everyone he meets.
Which you were cleverly able to
deduce about me but not being a moron.
Next  time tell God
to be more specific.
God wants you to invite
Dr. Wilson to your poker game.
Don't talk to my patient.
What are you talking about?
You get all huffy when my patient
stumbles into yours in the hallway.
But you got no qualms
about chatting my guy up.
This is fun,
it's like "Password".
Keep talking, I'll jump in
when I get a clue what the hell
you're talking about.
God knows about
my poker game.
You think I told him?
Either that or I start
going to church every Sunday.
That would mess
with my bowling league.
House, aside from yelling at him
to get back to his room,
I've never spoken to your patient.
MRI shows an abnormal area.
Tuberous sclerosis.
It's the right neighborhood.
Accounts for all the symptoms.
All of them.
Leading cortical tuber's
identifiable.
We can do this surgically.
Tell our patient congratulations.
Soon these chats with God
will be a thing of the past.
Tie goes to the mortal.
Did you know the Catholic Church
keeps a doctor at Lourdes?
He hears
the same thing every day.
But out of the thousands of cases of
people who have claimed to feel better,
the Catholic Church has only
recognized a handful as miracles.
But they do recognize a handful.
Well, they're a church.
It's  what they do.
Look, for the past couple of years,
the world's been getting smaller.
Eight months, six months.
I watch a trailer for a movie...
and I think, am I gonna be here
when that comes out?
But maybe there is still
a horizon out there.
You know, maybe...
Maybe I can make plans
for a year from now.
Two years.
I like the view.
The view is a lie.
And if you believe it,
you're going to crash so hard...
Let me take
new images of your liver.
You can't accept
that it could be true.
Well, if it is true,
you shouldn't be afraid of proving it.
Tuberous Sclerosis
is a genetic disorder.
It causes small, benign tumors
to grow in various parts of the body.
In this case, the brain.
You said benign.
They probably are.
But benign or not,
they're not in a good location.
We need to remove them.
You're talking brain surgery?
His symptoms are getting worse
which means the tumors are growing.
Surgery will correct it all.
The chemical imbalance, the seizures,
the auditory hallucinations.
Hallucinations?
Without the surgery,
it's just gonna get worse.
It might even be fatal.
With the surgery, your son should be
a perfectly normal 15-year-old boy.
I'm not normal.
I need you to talk to my patient.
I'll get this one.
Why do I have the feeling
you're plotting world domination?
Moses is refusing surgery.
You have a gift.
People thank you for
telling them they're gonna die.
If I can get him to agree to surgery,
I want in on the poker game.
You would let this kid die
just to get into a stupid game?
You'd let him die
just to keep me out?
Hi.
I'm Dr. Wilson.
I knew
they'd send somebody else.
That God has a big mouth.
House.
Can I ask why you don't
want the tumors removed?
God put them there
for a reason.
You think God needs a telephone
in your head to talk to you?
Isn't he everywhere?
It's not a long distance call, is it?
This is the way
God does things.
Through natural law.
If he went around doing
big, flashy miracles all the time,
- nobody would need faith.
- How come everyone else needs faith,
but you just get the guy
screaming his existence in your ear?
Your turn.
Do you think
God wants you to die?
This is the way that the Lord
often is with his chosen ones.
He gives the most trials
to those that he loves the most.
How sweet.
You abdicate your authority.
Avoid those tricky parental issues
like whether to let him drive at 16.
Just let him die at 15.
So you believe
your son is... um, a saint.
The way I understand it,
one of the hallmarks
of a saint is humility.
Someone with true humility would
consider the possibility that...
God hadn't chosen him
for that kind of honor.
He'd consider
the possibility that...
he just had an illness.
You have a gift
for manipulation.
I listen. I have an actual
conversation with people.
Which, shockingly, does raise
the odds they'll be cooperative.
That's what I'm saying.
You read that kid, and
you manipulated the hell out of him.
Bring pretzels.
Hosue plays
"What a Friend We Have in Jesus"
on the piano
[Knocks on the door]
I know that knock!
Use your key,
I'm not getting up.
Game's not till tomorrow night.
And those aren't pretzels.
I took some images
of Grace Palmieri's cancer.
Yeah?
Her tumor has shrunk.
[Stops playing piano]
Don't tell my patient.
I want all records
on miracle woman.
Every test, every treatments
he's ever had.
Every question she's ever
answered in this hospital.
And anything sent
from previous doctors.
Go back to neonatal
if you have...
Which part of
"Keep them away from each other"
confused you?
They're friends.
She thinks
he saved her life.
And we've obligingly offered
medical proof that his delusions are true.
They've withdrawn
permission for the surgery.
I've put the lawyers on it.
Her tumor shrank?
I'm on it.
Tell Jesus that
we need another 24 hours
to normalize his sodium level.
He's already normalized.
Actually, tell Joseph.
Jesus'll know you're lying.
And I want you and Foreman and Cameron
to go over every line of every file on that woman.
Isn't he the one
we're supposed to save?
The only way to save him is
to prove that she is still dying.
MRI machine checks out.
Maybe the radiologist mischarted
which machine they used.
I checked both. This is insane.
We're diagnosing a recovery.
What about six months ago?
Maybe there was a malfunction
on her before pictures.
Some shadow that made the tumor
look bigger than it really was.
I'll go see
what I can find out.
Maybe it's a delayed effect
from radiation.
Sometimes it can take a while.
She hasn't had radiation
for six months.
- Here.
- Nowhere. Her records...
There's about a dozen appliances
in every home that give off radiation.
Dosages that wouldn't hurt a hamster
if it was tied to the machine for a year.
If the machine's operating properly.
Sometimes remissions just happen.
You think
House will just shrug and say that
if one of us doesn't check the home?
[Radiation counter buzzes]
Kings on 9s.
Thank you.
Wilson, this is... uh, dry cleaner,
tax accountant, guy from the bus stop.
This is Wilson.
How comehe gets a name?
Seniority.
Hello.
[Phone rings]
Find anything?
You have any idea how many
electrical devices give off radiation?
All of them.
I'm gonna be here all night.
Everybody's a whiner.
Be a doer,
not a me too-er.
Raise.
I'm out.
Chase:
She's got at least four different types
of pain pills here and an LED device.
I'll raise your raise.
Keep looking.
Fold.
[Laughs]
You were bluffing.
He knew you were bluffing.
Your luck's changing tonight.
So did they find anything?
Or are you gonna have to accept the fact
that every now and then remissions happen?
[Phone rings again]
This call had better
be worth my time.
This is what happens
when it's not our patient.
We don't know enough.
That's why you're there.
She's got a boyfriend.
Unless you think
he's radioactive...
He could show up any minute.
The honor of working for you
is not worth a felony charge.
Give me a minute.
I'm saying the odds of you having
a straight flush are pretty low.
House!
I'll fold.
Fold.
I'm screwed, aren't I?
[Chuckles]
Nine bucks
for a straight flush.
He's not coming home.
Relax.
There's nothing in this universe
that can't be explained...
Eventually.
Take this game.
Only two people knew
that you wanted in on it.
I didn't tell him.
I told you,
Why would you?
The only person he's been getting
all intimate and conversational with
is your cancer chick.
How would she know?
The subject of my poker game
isn't likely to come up
in the course of a patient interview.
No, that's the kind of thing
you mention to someone you're used to
sharing the details of you day with.
Don't.
Your rabbi...
A guidance counselor.
A parent.
She's not your mom, is she?
I'm seriously saying don't.
You've been having sex...
This is so not the place.
With our miracle woman.
[Knocks on the door]
Excuse me, may I...
May I talk to you?
Of course.
Boyd's getting dressed.
He's ready to check out.
He can't check out
without your permission.
His sodium level
still isn't normal.
I told him.
He said that God said
it was okay, he was fine.
Could you talk to him?
Tell them
my name isn't Wilson.
Most people in your situation
just have their careers to worry about.
You've got that
and divine retribution.
Tell them.
Tell me how it happened,
and I'll tell them whatever you want.
She'd had a bad day.
Pain-wise.
Her ride didn't show up
to take her home.
So you offered.
Yeah.
She didn't have any groceries.
She was too sick to go out. I...
figured I could afford
to take a half hour.
- Pick her up and few things.
- And stay and make sure she's okay.
Yeah.
And never leave.
You told me
you got an apartment.
But you moved in with her.
You lied to me.
Tell them.
His name is not Wilson, and
he's screwed up worse than I am.
Okay, yes, I lied to you.
I'm sorry.
Half the doctors who specialize in oncology
turn into burnt out cases. But you,
you eat neediness.
Lucky for you.
Thanks for the game, guys.
I don't think I'll be coming back.
You're a functional vampire.
Sure, you're heroic, useful to society.
But only because it feeds you.
There's nothing worth stealing,
so don't even look.
You don't just have a fetish
for needy people, you marry them!
- Here we go!
- You mean it!
And then time passes, suddenly
they're not so needy anymore.
Your fault.
You've been there
for them too much.
They're getting
healthy, independent.
And that's just ugly.
God, you must be
pissed at God right now.
Making her all happy.
Why are you doing this?
Because you're being stupid.
[Laughs]
You know what you're risking
by sleeping with a patient.
Oh, that's crap. You're not mad
because I'm risking my job.
You're not even mad
because I lied to you.
You're mad because I lied to you,
and you couldn't tell.
Yeah, you got me nailed.
Yeah, that's why you didn't
want me in your poker game.
Because when it comes
to being in control,
Gregory House leaves
our faith healer kid in the dust.
And that's why
religious belief annoys you.
Because if the universe
operates by abstract rules,
you can learn them,
you can protect yourself.
If a supreme being exists,
he can squash you any time he wants.
He knows where I am.
[Phone rings]
I think it's yours.
Yeah.
I'll be right there.
Jesus is spiking a fever.
He's delusional.
Tuberous sclerosis
doesn't cause fever.
I know.
I'll drive.
Pick any random guy off the street.
Bring him in here,
examine him exhaustively.
You will find at least
three things wrong with him.
This kid has
tuberous sclerosis.
- A mild case.
- But his tumors are growing.
We assumed that
the tumors were growing.
'Cause he's getting sicker.
But he could have grown old and died
and never known about them
if he hadn't come here.
We were looking for
something that was more or less
in the right part of the brain.
It's like we found someone
standing over a dead body holding a gun.
We arrested them,
didn't look any further.
Well, sometimes
people really do just stumble
into a murder scene.
His fever is 103 and rising.
If we don't do anything,
he's gonna be chatting with God
face to face real soon.
Fevers don't come from
a long-term underlying condition.
He's a garden variety religious nut
who happens to have an infection.
It's lumbar puncture time.
No.
No, God told me
no more of man's medicine.
If we have faith in him,
he'll make me well.
It's just a test.
We just wanna
find out what's wrong.
God knows what's wrong.
God will take care of it.
He's delirious, and he's a minor.
This is your decision, and not his.
The kingdom of heaven is
like a treasure hidden in field
which when a man finds, he hides.
And for joy he goes and sells
all he owns and buys that field.
Buy all the land you want!
Don't blow your brains out.
You're watching your son kill himself!
He's out of his mind with fever--
Dad, if your faith is weak,
I will fail.
I need you.
I'm sorry.
You don't even know
what's wrong with him.
God knows the answer.
And I would rather leave it
in His hands than yours.
Wilson.
I need you to do your thing.
You do know that I don't
actually have magical powers.
I have faith.
You're better off trying to slip
some antibiotics into a meal...
Which antibiotics?
We don't know what infection he's got.
- Go as broad as you can.
- Forget it.
Our best hope
is your silver tongue.
What if it's not an infection?
Where you not paying attention when
I was doing my murder scene metaphor?
What if the tuberous sclerosisis guilty?
It had the gun in its hand,
it was standing over...
Doesn't cause fever.
It causes everything else.
What if the fever's
the innocent bystander?
Fever could have been set off
by something he picked up anywhere.
Could have been
a bug he got here.
Or a bug he gave here.
He gave it to your patient.
That's why her tumor shrank.
The virus went after the cancer first.
Are you saying
a virus attacked her tumor?
For 200 years,
there have been reports of
wild viruses that target tumors.
Early 1900s,
an Italian medical journal wrote up
a woman with cervical cancer
who was injected
with a weak strain of rabies.
I have no idea why they did that,
but her tumor shrank.
You think
he gave her rabies?
One of the virus types
most prone to go after cancer cells
is herpes.
Herpes encephalitis.
It would fit.
Seizure, low sodium.
Even the blurred vision.
And it would mean if you're right,
Grace's cancer is coming back.
You're not gonna
be able to convince them.
They don't want any more tests.
They don't wanna...
They can't argue
with the mark of Cain.
I'm not gonna
change my mind.
No more tests.
God knows the way.
Okay, let's start with his shirt.
What are you doing?
I'm on a mission from God.
If you won't let me
undress you, then strip.
What's he doing?
What's going on?
That woman you helped,
you gave her a virus.
No, she's healed.
I have a gift--
A gift is jewelry, socks.
What you have
is herpes encephalitis.
The only way you could have transmitted it
is by scratching one of your own sores
and touching another person.
Herpes, that's something
you get from sex, right?
Either that or cold sores.
Your kid got it from the sex.
No, no sores.
No, my body is clean.
They examined me
when I came in. No sores.
Herpes hides.
You have an outbreak, it goes away,
comes back, goes away. Strip!
You didn't have a sore
when you came in,
but you've got one now.
Dad, I've never ever--
You ever wonder why a perfect child
of God should feel so desperate
to purify his body that
he needed to scarf  down
a dozen gallons of water a day?
- Boyd, is he right?
- Dad, no, he's crazy.
Help me.
Dr. Wilson, help!
God said no medicine,
no procedures.
Taking off your clothes
doesn't count as either of those.
This one's your call.
Son...
Dad, you have to
have faith in me.
I have faith in the Lord.
You, I trust.
As much as you can
trust a teenage boy.
Take off your clothes.
Relax.
A few Hail Marys,
a little acyclovir.
You'll be picking up angels
again in no time.
Come in.
My father told me
I have to apologize to you.
Still hearing voices?
You're lucky.
You go through life with a certainty
that what you're doing is right.
I know
how comforting that is.
Good luck.
You're not gonna
give me my final point?
You knew it was me?
Who else?
You don't think God
should get a point knocked off?
- The tumor shrank.
- Because of a virus.
Do you know what the odds are?
She had to have the right type of cancer.
He had to have the right type of virus.
The exposure had to be--
- She won the lottery.
- You say won the lottery,
- he says... miracle.
- Yeah,
the hand of God reached into this kid's pants,
made him have sex so he could scratch a rash,
stick his fingers
in some woman's face,
give her a few extra months.
Come on, he's just another
liar and manipulator.
Well, nobody's
as perfectas you are.
It is possible to believe in something
and still fail to live up to it.
So, how's your girlfriend?
She got a little extra time
out of this. Not a lot.
She didn't crash?
No... She says she's happier
when she believes in
something bigger than she is.
She still believes.
Faith.
She's going to Florence.
You moving out?
Yeah.
Moving back in with me?
I don't think
that's a great idea.
But we're okay.
House, you are...
as God made you.
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : Vaccine
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net