[A baby crying]
Honey?
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Yeah. I'm just fighting
off a stomach bug.
I'll be fine.
Did he sleep okay?
Great, as long as
I was holding him.
I can't wait
for colic to be over.
Oh, shh.
There you go, Mikey.
Bath time's coming.
He lifted his head yesterday.
Take the day off.
I mean, you're sick anyway,
and you hardly ever see him.
Or me.
I can't.
I got a meeting
with Crandall's Kitchens.
I think that deal's gonna close.
They called about
the car payment again.
It's 2 months late.
We're gonna be fine, honey.
Enjoy your bath,
little man.
You know, honey...
Honey, I'm not gonna go in.
I'm coming down
with something.
Honey?
Kara.
Kara?
Kara!
Mikey!
2X22 - Forever
Original Airdate (FOX): 9 MAY-2006
Before we called in
*** merged in the bathtub.
Don't know how long.
Non-responsive at the scene.
[Crying]
Obviously breathing now.
Continue the blow-by.
Stat portable chest.
- Caucasian, female, 32.
- Where am I?
Tonic-clonic seizure
in the bathroom.
Where am I?
Come on, one, two, three.
On three-- one, two, three.
You're in the hospital, honey.
Mikey's here,
and the doctors say
he's gonna be okay.
Hopefully.
He needs to be checked out
by the NICU.
What happened?
- You passed out.
- What?
Mikey fell.
Has your wife had
a seizure before?
No.
I can't mve my head.
I want to see him!
He's right here, honey.
He's right here.
Tonight...
L Word marathon.
You watch The L Word?
On mute.
I'll pass.
Dinner with Cuddy.
Still sucking up so
she'll fund your play space
for the chemo kids?
They really ought to save their energy
for other things. Like crying.
[Elevator dings]
She's the suck-up.
She asked you?
She's smart. She knows if
she buys me enough alcohol,
my defenses just
might be weakened.
Doesn't make sense.
Unless she ran out of batteries.
Hey...
I'm recently single.
She's single.
You're too nice
for her to like you.
She's not needy enough
for you to like her.
She's got an agenda,
just not one that includes
an appearance by little Jimmy.
I'll poll my peeps.
How many of you think
that Cuddy asked--
Or rather, "peep."
Chase caught a case in the E.R.
He wants us to take a look.
Unless Chase broke his neck
falling off his polo pony,
he had no reason to be in the E.R.
Cuddy put him
on a two-week NICU rotation.
Patient had
an unexplained seizure.
Seizures are cool to watch,
boring to diagnose.
How about Foreman?
He needs to get
his malingering butt back here.
He almost died.
Almost being the operative word.
Hey.
How are you doing?
You look great.
Thanks.
I feel great.
Glad you're back.
Cameron makes lousy coffee.
I take mine black, the way I take
my brain-damaged neurologists.
Happy to help.
How you coming along?
Tell  her everything's great.
Neither of us wants
to deal with her guilt.
- I don't feel guilty.
- Of course not.
Hell, if people felt guilt every time
they accidentally lobotomized a guy...
- I was trying to save his life.
- Yeah.
Your heart was
in the right place.
It's just his brain is not quite
where it's supposed to be.
Tell her everything's great.
It's true.
No  more left-side,
right-side reversals.
Still some short-term memory loss
and spatial processing problems, but
trying not to be
too hard on myself.
Yeah.
Might pull a muscle.
We have a case?
Seizure that can't be
explained by epilepsy.
And accompanied by
elevated calcium levels.
Still bored.
Tell her why.
Because seizure with
mildly elevated calcium is...
diagnostically simple.
It's either hyperparathyroid, cancer,
or calcium-mediated neurotoxicity.
Well done.
But until you can remember
how to make coffee,
hands off the patients.
H ouse.
All those reasons
this case bores you...
The ER has already
ruled them out.
Lungs are clear.
Get an EEG confirming
brain function's okay.
Can we focus
on the task at hand?
Why did mommy twitch so hard that
she tossed the baby in with the bathwater?
You don't need me for this.
Of course I need you.
We're a team.
Polyarteritis nodosa.
Inflamed arteries in the brain
cause seizures.
Inflamed arteries in the kidneys
cause calcium buildup.
You're a moron.
Did you even look at the file?
Kidney function's fine.
- Whipple's.
- What?
Whipple's.
Test her.
Cameron thinks
it starts with a "W."
I'm thinking "V."
Dad vomited this morning.
Maybe they've both got strep.
Think you can do
a strep throat culture without the swab
ending up in the guy's poop chute?
- "V" for vasoconstriction.
- It got to be my guess.
Excess calcium makes blood vessels
in the brain clamp down.
Best-case scenario: seizure.
Worst-case: stroke.
Do a digital extraction angiogram.
Foreman can't tell up from down.
Cameron's a girl.
- All that mechanical stuff.
- Sorry, Cuddy says I'm stuck here.
You're late.
And you are
in my locked office.
Again.
Whatcha got there?
Special panties
for your date with Wilson?
It's not a date, and
it's none of your business.
If it's not a date,
it is business.
And if it was business,
you wouldn't say
it was none of my business.
What do you want?
I wanna talk about
your date with Wilson.
- It's not a date.
- This is fun.
Spring Chase from NICU,
and I'll shut up about your date.
NICU is short-staffed.
You suddenly lost
the ability to lie.
Nobody's quit NICU
in two years.
And if you're making up reasons,
that means there is no reason.
Which means he asked
for the assignment, didn't he?
If Chase needs a break
from you, he should take it.
Absolutely.
Both mom and dad
are negative for strep.
You'll be back playing
with the big toys soon.
Or not.
Either way, I'm fine.
You don't have to say that.
It's okay.
I can always work
in a research lab or teach.
And you'd be
okay with that?
Why wouldn't I be?
You were planning on
pursuing grants of your own.
Running a department.
I'm alive.
Changing jobs,
not making coffee--
if that stuff bothers me now,
I don't deserve the second chance.
Ungaa.
They say that physical contact
helps the healing process.
[Alarm starts beeping]
What's happening?
Your son's not
getting enough oxygen.
Take Mr. Mason outside.
Uhh! Uh! Ahh! Uhh!
Lung's collapsed.
He's not getting any air.
I need an IV catheter!
Uh!
Aah! Aahh!
You have a seizure?
Her chest muscles are contracting.
It's something else.
Aah!
Her whole back is spasming.
I need 2 milligrams Lorazepam, stat.
He's okay.
His lung wouldn't collapse
if he was okay.
What is happening?
I have no idea.
Aah! Aah!
House:
So...what causes seizures,
hypercalcemia,
and the thing where
mommy bends like Gumby?
Little busy here.
Uh-oh...
baby's lungs are gonna
conk out any minute.
Probably wanna deal with that.
I'll get right on it
as soon as I finish
indulging my boss.
Multitask.
Chemical pneumonitis.
Bubble bath got into the baby's lungs
when he was underwater.
Start him on prednisone.
Keep him on high FI-02.
Let the indulging commence.
Lithium could cause all three
of the mother's symptoms.
No record she's on lithium.
And tox screen was negative.
Lithium doesn't show on
a basic tox screen, Scarecrow.
Myelomatous meningitis
could also cover everything.
Rare complications
of a rare blood cancer.
You're not totally hopeless.
Get an S-PEP and an MRI
for myelomatous meningitis.
Search the patient's place
for lithium.
Baby's lung problem is
bacterial, not chemical--
start ECMO.
While you're searching
for the lithium, take a water sample
and check the pipes.
You want me to
write this down for you?
I ask you,
is almost dying any excuse
for not being fun?
I'm not putting
that baby on ECMO.
The chance of there being
bacteria in bathwater--
Why don't you
wanna work for me?
I'm nice,
and fun at parties.
I'm not working NICU
because of you.
The baby's X-ray suggested
chemical pneumonitis.
Not to me.
X-ray was too consolidated.
So why are you down here?
Hoping to expand your make-out pool
to include the preemie to
nine-year-old demographic?
I needed a break.
From the patients.
They lie to us all the time.
Foreman almost died trying
to save a drug-dealing cop.
I just wanted to get away
from that for a while.
What a complete load of crap.
What am I, a nurse
you're trying to prep with
this vulnerability thing?
ECMO could kill him.
You don't start him on ECMO, and
that infection could rampage through his body
like Pistons fans after a championship.
[Elevator dings]
But you do it your way.
Nothing more honest
than a dead baby.
ECMO stands for
Extra Corporeal Membrane Oxygenation.
Basically, we remove
your son's blood--
All of his blood?
We run it through a machine,
which takes out carbon dioxide
and adds oxygen.
Then we re-warm the blood
and run it back into his body.
There is a significant risk
of internal hemorrhaging,
and he may also suffer--
You put him on antibiotics.
Won't that take care of the infection?
Not fast enough.
Are you sure this is
Mikey's best shot?
Absolutely.
- Cuddy's trash.
- Not anymore.
Paid good money for it.
Look at what she bought.
Red clover.
What is red clover
used for, Dr. Wilson?
It's also used
to treat asthma.
Psoriasis... joint pain.
She doesn't wheeze,
flake, or ache.
And she didn't ask a pulmonologist
or a dermatologist for dinner.
She invited an oncologist.
It's not a date.
It's a consult.
Mom's MRI was negative
for masses, abscesses.
- There's no sign she has--
- Fascinating.
Call me when we have--
She has a subarachnoid bleed.
So why is our patient
bleeding into her brain?
Her blood workup shows
her Pro-Time's elevated.
She's bleeding
because she's not clotting.
So why is she not clotting?
What'd you bring us, daddy?
Only mood-altering drug
was vodka. The back of a drawer.
Hiding booze is
classic alcoholic behavior.
That'd explain the bleeding.
What bleeding?
You don't remember?
She  bled all over you
this morning.
Kidding. Idiots are fun.
No wonder every village wants one.
If she's an alcoholic,
she would also be more prone
to hypercalcemia.
But the tox screen
was negative for alcohol.
Hey, it was your idea.
Now it's even better.
Mommy quits, she gets the DTs.
Even explains the seizure.
Also fits
conversion disorder.
They're deep in debt.
He's working round the clock.
They got a new baby.
I think the seizure was
a physical response
to psychological stress.
Boozy mommy covers
more symptoms.
Put her in a nice
Phenobarbital coma
before the DTs kill her.
Where are you going?
To put her in a pheno coma.
What if I'm wrong?
What if daddy's the drunk?
You want us to give her
the pheno or not?
I want him
to argue his point.
I assumed you considered
the father and ruled him out.
What's that saying?
"When you ass-sume,
you become a pain in the ass to me."
Why should I argue?
You'd just overrule me.
Enough! Get a pony
or a watermelon farm.
House!
I  need him to react.
I need him to act
like a human being.
I need him to get over
this boring near-death rebirth.
I have changed.
It's not something you get over.
Nearly dying changes
everything forever.
For about two months.
Two months is too long.
I need the guy
I hired back, now.
Now matter how much
your misery loves company,
it's not getting mine.
I'll talk to the dad.
Cameron can take the mom.
We'll figure out if mom was a drinker.
Waste of time.
Put her in a coma
before the DTs kill her.
So...
Is this a separation or...
Well, lawyers have been hired.
Friends divvied up.
Oddly, she didn't
fight me for House.
[Laughs]
At least there aren't...
kids involved.
You just have each other
to deal with.
Hmm.
If there had been kids,
maybe we would have
done more of that.
Do you want kids?
Listen, is there
anything in particular
you... wanted to--
Hospital business or--
Catching up.
I mean, you know,
it's not like...
Either one of us has
anybody to run home to.
No.
How are you feeling?
Okay.
A little groggy.
There's  somebody
here to see you.
Hey, Mikey.
Mommy's awake.
Oh, Mikey.
Oh, gosh,
I was so scared.
Oh.
Oh, I love you.
I love you so much.
Ohh. Shh.
I'm sorry.
You don't have anything
to be sorry about.
You were sick.
Turns out
she and her husband
met in AA.
Obviously, she slipped.
Good call.
It wasn't hard,
considering my other choice
was your stupid psych theory.
Which was not stupid.
I tell you, I'm gonna
drop the N-bomb if I have to.
You're addicted to conflict.
Did they change the name?
You could have handled this patient
without dragging Chase in.
But that fact that
he didn't want in, killed you.
Just like the fact
you can't get a rise out of me.
Where's the baby?
Get off me!
No! I have to do this!
No breath sounds.
Crash cart and epi, stat!
Uhh! Uhh!
Told you your psych theory
wasn't stupid.
Your son is stable.
But the lack of oxygen
damaged his kidneys.
She must have rolled over
on him by mistake.
Mr. Mason...
I was there.
Your wife tried
to smother your son.
That's impossible.
Kara would never hurt Mikey.
He knows.
They said Mikey knows.
You hear voices?
They wouldn't quit saying that
Mikey would be better off if...
They were right.
We've been trying to diagnose
a seizure that didn't exist.
She faked it when
her husband caught her.
I don't think
she faked it.
She just happened to seize
right in the middle of
drowning her child?
Good break for the kid.
Hey, take it easy on Foreman.
He's playing with one lobe
tied behind his back.
Postpartum psychosis
makes her want to drown her kid.
The internal conflict
triggers a seizure.
You know what else
might be a trigger?
Physical illness.
It's a wild idea, I know.
Especially since she doesn't have
any obviously physical symptoms.
Like internal bleeding or excess calcium.
I'll draw some blood.
Test for a--
Uhh!
Jeez, you've done it again!
Will you argue with me?!
Drinkers don't eat right.
Explains the bleeding and the calcium.
This might just be some crazy drunk,
and I'm telling you that she's about
to die of myelomatous meningitis.
- We already tested for--
- Exactly! It's an insane idea.
Okay.
What do you want me to do?
Have an original thought.
In the meantime,
stress her into having
another seizure.
We can't,
she's on haloperidol.
You also can't because
it's dangerous and highly unethical.
Therefore, if you get caught,
pretend you can't make coffee.
Mental defectives get tons of slack.
Take off the haloperidol.
Hook her up to an EEG,
flash some lights. Make her pant.
Shoot her up with a placebo.
When she starts twitching,
if the machine twitches along, it's real...
if not, call the cops,
'cause she's a psycho killer.
- Stop pushing him.
- Stop protecting him.
He needs it.
- Not if he wants to get better.
- He might not be able to get better.
Well, then, I need
a new neurologist.
He got sick doing his job.
If he got killed doing his job,
I wouldn't keep him on the payroll.
I don't care how guilty you feel or
how touched you are by his reborn spirit.
- I'm not touched.
- Then you're guilt-ridden.
- I'm not guilt-ridden.
- Then you're pathetic.
Right now, I'm annoyed!
Keeping him up all night in a seizure lab
is not the way to advance his recovery!
- It's too much!
- You're right.
You should stick around.
Make sure he doesn't screw up.
Foreman:
Kara, look directly into the light.
Keep looking.
Thought you'd be
gone for the day.
Thought I'd wait for
the bone marrow biopsy results.
House sent you
to baby-sit me, didn't he?
He asked me to wait
for the results.
- Oh, Cameron, it's fine.
- Of course it is.
Look. A few weeks ago,
you were upset that
I didn't consider you a friend.
Now you're upset
that I'm happy?
What can I say?
Apparently, I'm a bitch.
[Laughs]
I didn't say that.
It's annoying.
Insisting every day of your life
is a blessing is basically
calling everyone else shallow.
- It gets old.
- Sorry.
Oh, give it a rest.
How was dinner?
Cuddy did not mention cancer.
She lost her nerve.
It was a date.
What are you doing?
PCR test.
You're doing it yourself?
In the middle of the night.
On a spoon.
Cuddy's spoon.
I'm checking her saliva
for cancer markers.
Yeah...
I do that
after all my dates too.
People think
you're the nice one.
Why are you so
worried about Cuddy?
You go first.
You desperately
want this to be a date.
Because the alternative
is cancer.
Just admit
that you like her.
She's smart, funny.
Got a zesty bod.
It's great you can look
beyond the fact she's the devil.
I stole a spoon.
You stole her garbage.
She's my boss.
She gets sick,
the hospital might replace her.
Especially if she dies.
I'd have to learn
how to manipulate someone new.
Whoa.
I think I'm gonna cry.
Find me when
the results come in.
Mr. Mason...
because of the damage
done to your son's kidneys,
his potassium is climbing.
It's causing
irregular heartbeats.
I'm doubling the meds
and starting him on dialysis.
Unless we get
his potassium down...
he's gonna have
a heart attack.
Kara, just another few minutes.
Biopsy's back.
She's negative for
myelomatous meningitis.
And she's not seizing.
So we're wrong
and House is wrong.
And you're okay with that?
[The alarm beeping]
She's seizing.
She's not doing anything.
Brain activity isn't accelerating.
It's slowing down.
Cameron:
Muscle rigidity, involuntary grasping
and sucking motions.
She's in an encephalopathic delirium.
Mmm, a genuine physiological illness.
That rules outa few things.
Like what, I wonder?
Postpartum psychosisand conversion disorder.
Thing about being a good loser...
you're still a loser.
Ouch.
The delirium means her brain is shutting down,
reverting to its most instinctual functions.
Since it's progressing, maybe
we can assume it's progressive.
Which means it won't be long before
the brain closes shop altogether.
Ideas?
[The alarms beeping]
He's in V Fib!
Potassium's still too high.
No pulse.
Get him off the machine.
Charge at 10.
Clear.
Still in V Fib.
Another amp of epi.
Damn it, Chase shouldn't
be wasting his time in NICU.
Could be Wernicke's.
No, treatment for Wernicke's is thiamine.
We gave her that together with the pheno.
Delirium points to lithium.
I know we didn't find any, but--
She's have to be smuggling it in
to be getting sicker.
Whipple's causes
encephalopathic delirium.
Test was negative.
The test could have
been wrong.
Ideas are not soda cans.
Recycling sucks.
We need something new and shiny.
Or go retro. Take an old idea,
shine it up, add a new symptom.
Encephalopathic delirium.
Pellagra.
She drinks.
Alcoholics get pellagra.
They eat lousy diets,
so no niacin.
He agrees with me.
What a shock.
Well, you're right.
Lack of niacin starves the brain.
Neurons shut down, causes seizures,
encephalopathic delirium, and psychosis.
We give Kara niacin,
she'll come out of her delirium
and she'll be totally sane.
Don't think she's ever gonna
be sane again.
Her son just died.
How do you feel?
Um...
My... stomach kind of hurts.
I need to ask you some questions.
See how you're doing.
Mm-hmm.
Tell me your name.
Kara Mason.
Is my son here?
When were you born?
Please... where's Michael?
Is he okay?
Do you hear any other voices
besides mine?
No! Answer me.
You've been suffering
from delusions.
They were caused
by a vitamin deficiency: pellagra.
It made you believe
things that were not real.
Like the voices.
I, uh...
remember doing things to Mikey.
Were those real?
I'm afraid so.
So I...
You tried
to suffocate your son.
But I...
you...
you stopped me.
And, uh...
that other doctor.
He got Mikey breathing.
Your son's organs were
damaged too severely.
He passed away
this morning.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no!
No!
Oh, my God! No!
Oh, my God.
Foreman:
Pellagra doesn't cause
bloody vomit.
She's still sick,
and getting worse.
House:
So what causes pellagra
and crimson spew?
Whack!
Dead baby, while sad,
not our problem.
I should have given him
more polystyrene.
You killed him.
If you don't get over it,
you're gonna kill mama too.
Cameron:
Her alcoholism caused the pellagra.
Maybe it also explains the vomiting.
- Gastritis.
- Gastritis meds aren't helping.
Which may confirm her story
she only slipped once.
You remove the drinking from the equation,
internal bleeding, hypercalcemia,
seizure, and pellagra are all back in.
Chase, will you get your head
out of the dead baby's butt
and focus on the barely alive--
How much polystyrene
did you give the kid?
1 gram.
His potassium just kept rising.
I need your son.
Who are you?
Your wife's doctor.
Your son may have had
the same condition she does.
My son didn't have a condition.
She killed him.
If I biopsy her intestine,
she'll bleed out.
He obviously won't.
You're not using
my son's body to help her.
Okay. How about
trading him for a beer?
Or maybe you're
more of a whisky guy.
You didn't have
strep or a stomach bug
the morning you came in.
You puked because
you were hung over.
Accuse a recovered drunkof slipping,
most of the time, you'd be right.
So I drink.
You're acting like
this is my fault.
People are gonna
feel sorry for you.
They'll tell you that you can't
anticipate the unthinkable.
The fact is, you can.
It's just not all that pleasant.
You don't know
anything about--
I know that people don't get
crazy enough to kill someone
without first being crazy enough
for someone to notice.
How many times
did you go out for a drink
because she was crying?
How many times
did you stay at work because
you couldn't listen to her telling you
what a bad mother she is?
You were relieved
when she shut down.
Just sat staring
for hours at a time.
She held the pillow over his head.
You slept while she went nuts.
- Not exactly a draw, but--
- What is wrong with you?
What kind of a person
says those things now.
Let me do the test.
It'll be one less thing
for you to feel crappy about.
Got a dead baby
for you to biopsy.
Let Cameron do it.
You love working NICU?
I could get you transferred.
I told you, I just
wanted to trust patients.
You don't give a crap
about patients.
Your paycheck.
You've been double-dipping.
Taking your vacation time here
while drawing a salary in NICU.
Strange.
Rich boy doing all that
for some extra cash.
I'm not rich.
But your dad was.
Now he's dead.
If you're not rich,
that means that daddy cut you out.
I'm not rich.
Don't let it change you.
And do the test.
"Over Yonder"
by The American Boy Choir
God of confession,
take Michael into your arms.
Welcome him into paradise
where there'll be no sorrow,
no weeping, and no pain.
Peace and joy forever more.
I'm sorry.
It was a date.
Cuddy's negative
for all cancer markers.
It was a date.
Baby's intestines shows
light villous atrophy.
Why would a baby
have flattened villi?
He was being treated
with polystyrene.
- Polystyrene shouldn't--
- It didn't.
Question is, what did they use
in the NICU to bind it together?
- Wheat gluten.
- That's great stuff.
Unless your body
can't tolerate it.
The baby didn't have colic,
he had celiac disease?
Just like mom.
Celiac can be triggered
by all kinds of stress.
Bills, childbirth,
drunk husband.
Every time she had a bowl of pasta or
a slice of bread or a slosh of soy sauce,
her small intestine
became more damaged.
Less able to absorb the vitamins
and minerals into her bloodstream.
Her body couldn't
absorb enough niacin.
Caused the pellagra.
Couldn't absorb Vitamin K.
Caused the bleeding.
And celiac is why
the baby's meds didn't work.
His body just
couldn't absorb them.
Switch mom to IV nutrition.
It's gluten-free.
It'll spruce her villi right up.
No, celiac causes
nutritional deprivation.
Our patient has excess calcium.
Tell them what causes
excess calcium.
With a chaser of bloody vomit.
Celiac patients are susceptible
to cancer of the stomach lining.
- She has MALT lymphoma.
- Well, she's your patient now.
And it wasn't a date.
You don't have cancer.
You don't have dwarfism.
You have no proof of that.
I, on the other hand, have this.
You ran a PCR on me
without my consent?
Hey, it's good news.
Really? It's just hard to access
because of this overwhelming sense
of personal violation.
Deal with it
on your own time.
Bad news...
estrogen is too high.
No matter how many people
you tell otherwise,
I am, and always have been,
a woman. Estrogen is normal.
Not this much.
Not for at least another week.
That's when you ovulate.
What?
You monitor my periods?
Based on...
when I get bitchy or...
Once a month, when
you leave the kids'cancer ward,
your eyes glisten.
And about three days later,
you break your ban on sugar and
chow down a bucket of frozen yogurt
in the cafeteria, sprinkles included.
Based on the last yogurt sighting,
you've got another week before you ovulate.
You're on fertility meds.
With red clover
as an herbal booster.
And that dinner with Wilsonw
as an audition.
It's too bad he didn't land the gig.
He would have had fun.
I was considering a donation.
Not a party.
So...
When is our... "dinner"?
Ooh, he's gonna be
so disappointed.
Right. You two are gonna have
a lot of fun with this.
Your patient won't
let me touch her.
I killed my son.
Is it my turn to say
something obvious now?
Oh, I know.
You were insane.
I did it.
I chose to do it.
Yeah, like diabetics choose
to not produce insulin.
Listen, someone got sick.
Someone died.
It happens every day.
The only difference in this case is...
it wasn't the same someone.
I could have stopped.
I didn't have to
listen to those voices.
Spoken like a true sane person.
This is not your fault.
You're healthy now.
Except for the cancer.
Those voices...
felt as real to me as...
as Michael's hand.
Right here,
when he nursed.
And... the smell of his hair.
You do not...
deserve to die.
Maybe.
I don't wanna live.
She said no.
So we gether declared unstable,
appoint a medical proxy.
She was unstable.
Now she's sane.
She's entitled
to refuse the treatment.
You have to change her mind.
You can't just walk away.
Fine! Go on in there and tell her
that every day is a blessing.
"So you killed your baby.
Shake it off. Think positive.
At least you're alive."
Hmm.
Kind of hard to sell
when you don't believe it, huh?
And you never believed it.
You just wanted all that crap
you went through to mean something.
Well, it didn't mean anything.
It never does.
Welcome back.
Why are you doing this to me?
I was happy.
You were aspiring to be content.
Don't give mea semantic argument.
I was content with the way things were!
That's what happiness is.
Yeah, if we were all
just satisfied with what we had,
what a beautiful world it would be.
We'd all slowly
starve to death in our own filth,
but at least we'd be happy.
Listen, I need your self-worth
to hang on this job.
For kicking ass here to be all that
lets you rise above miserable.
If waking up in the morning
is enough, I don't need you.
I can live with that.
No, you can't.
Not anymore.
If you got treatment,
then maybe we could...
When you see Mikey...
Tell him
his dad says he's sorry.
Hi.
- Night. - Night.
- Good night.
Did you tell Cuddy
we tested her for cancer?
Yeah.
And?
It wasn't a date.
Turned out
she had some skin lesions.
Guess there was
no genetic predisposition.
You TiVo The L Word?
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : Vaccine
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net