We just arrived.
Yeah. Kids okay on your end?
Good.
Yeah, yeah. He's very excited.
Hey, hey. Listen, I gotta go,
okay? I'll call you tomorrow.
Excuse me.
Get away. Get away.
Sorry about that. Sorry.
What's wrong with him?
Excuse us.
I ought to go back and kick
the hell out of that guy.
She was old enough, she didn't
have to scream like that.
It's okay, Dad. It didn't bother me.
For the first time, none
of these people bother me.
I just think, "36 more hours. "
Thirty-six more hours? How
do you figure that, Kenny?
Tomorrow at this time,
I'm scheduled for surgery.
It's a 10-hour procedure,
throw two in there for prep,
thirty-six until I'm just
another face in the crowd.
Kenny has a frontonasal encephalocele.
It's a midline deformity.
He's here to undergo
a facial bipartition.
And what does that mean?
Well, we have five
surgeons, four nurses.
He's going to require
six units of blood.
Will it fix him?
It'll repair a lot of the damage done...
We need a sound byte.
Would you say, "He'll be
ready for the junior prom"?
Yeah, yeah. That's probably true.
No, I mean, I need you to say it.
Dr. Chase,
we got an issue.
Heart rate's skyrocketing,
he's over 180.
He's in v-fib. Paddles!
Charge to 300.
Turn that camera off.
Is this a reaction to anesthesia?
Haven't given it yet.
Clear!
Crank it to 360.
I said turn that damn camera off! Clear!
A teenage boy with a cranial facial
deformity was about to undergo
a reconstructive procedure, when he
had an unexplained cardiac arrest.
Good.
Good?
I mean, go on.
We have the patient on a pacing wire,
it's the only thing
keeping his heart going.
Yeah, we know. We're doctors.
Right, it was meant to be just for them.
Just be yourself.
Until we are able to figure out
exactly what is causing the heart block,
the reconstructive surgery
is on hold, obviously.
That's "yourself"?
Fascinating case.
I will see you again after
I have saved his life.
Have a warm bath waiting.
Are you following me?
Darnell will be trailing
you throughout the case.
Pretend we're not here.
But if I do that, won't I bump into you?
We'll stay out of your way.
No, it was a joke.
See, I became a doctor because
of the movie, Patch Adams.
Listen, do you wanna get
ahead of me and maybe back up,
I don't know, low down,
so I look more powerful?
That's perfect. Yeah?
Also, my eyes look better
in rooms with summer colors.
You know what? It's black and white...
You think I like the cameras?
You think I want the whole world
watching you check out my ass
and question my wardrobe?
Would it be better if I checked out
your wardrobe and questioned your ass?
A little part of me...
There is no little part of you.
...thought that maybe you would see
what great PR this
could be for the hospital
and not make me force you
to act like a human being.
You using force on me is intriguing.
On the other hand,
cameras make people act.
Sometimes like human
beings, sometimes just weird,
sometimes they wear open-tip bras.
It's cold in here.
A less obvious point is that I need my team
to be unafraid of the metaphorical fart.
That production company is covering
all the medical costs for this kid.
So either you let them continue filming
or the kid goes home with the same face.
Sorry about that. Private.
She waxes her moustache once a month
and sometimes gets some
pretty gnarly ingrown hairs.
So, did he hire you flat out or are
you competing for one of the spots?
I'm not sure what you mean by that.
She's not competing.
She was handpicked by House.
She's safe, like Foreman.
So that takes three spots down to one.
Where's Foreman?
He's in the bathroom. Good.
Come on. Let's go for a walk.
Walks look good on camera.
They give the illusion of
the story moving forward.
New patient.
Sixteen-year-old boy with
second-degree infranodal heart block.
Post-arrest.
Any reports of
light-headedness or syncope?
Certainly not light-headedness.
Why did you hire her?
Not in front of the company.
Are we gonna be on TV?
I'm making a music video.
Come on. A little faster, more energy.
Why are you glad Foreman's not here?
Because he would object
to what I'm about to do.
Oh!
Sorry.
Hey, buddy.
You stay in there, we'll be out here,
making sure he doesn't move again.
God! Finally I hear myself think.
Our patient has...
Why did you hire her?
Because she has way more
diagnostic experience
than the other swimsuit
models I was considering.
Our patient has a frontonasal
encephalocele with a midline cleft.
Don't stare directly at it.
So what caused "Big
Head's" heart to stop?
Simple. His big head.
Increased intacranial pressure
would cause heart block.
Wrong. Sixteen years they've been
testing that insane noggin to death.
What about a congenital heart defect?
He has a midline anomaly on his head,
makes sense he'd have a midline
anomaly in his heart, too.
The 16 years of testing didn't show?
Why did you bring her in
so late? It's not fair.
The rest of us... Hey,
hey, hey! You wanted fair,
you picked the wrong
job, the wrong profession,
the wrong species.
Forget the deformity.
Treat the patient like he's any
other really, really ugly kid.
Infection? Could be endocarditis.
Well, since he doesn't have
a prosthetic heart valve,
I assume you're thinking
he's an IV drug user?
House said assume he's normal.
Dealers don't ask for ID and
don't care what you look like.
Nice. You're right about the habit.
You're wrong about the substance.
Blackened skin under the nose
equals frostbite from huffing Freon.
Freon's toxic, it damages the heart.
Discoloration could be
acanthosis nigricans.
It's a common side effect
of these deformities.
There's also discoloration
on the cheeks and forehead.
Do a nuclear study.
If I'm right, you'll see
scarring of the heart.
I'm not part of some game, am I?
I gave up a career because I
thought this was a firm offer.
Yes, this is a real offer.
I think she might be an idiot.
Who?
No, she can't be an idiot.
I mean, she was in the
CIA, for God's sake.
And the Bay of Pigs
was a daring triumph.
She had good ideas in Langley.
All your ideas.
She was able to identify
that they were good ideas.
Stab in the dark here, is she pretty?
She's new.
She's nervous. She's a C-cup.
She said one dumb
thing in a differential.
They all say dumb
things in differentials.
A D-cup?
If she's no good, just fire her.
I can't. I just hired her.
She left a career.
Wow.
Either that's actual guilt, or
I have got to see this woman.
My son is not huffing Freon.
Mr. Arnold, Dr. House is like a
savant when it comes to diagnostics.
What's his genius theory?
Because Kenny's not normal, he's
doing drugs to deal with his pain?
Maybe the way to look at
this is that you are normal.
And what's that supposed to mean?
You're like any other parent who
thinks his kid can't be doing drugs.
Doing this because my
dad thinks I'm on drugs?
I was doing drugs behind my
parent's back at your age,
and I had a lot less reason to be.
Not that your life must be miserable.
Not that I'm suggesting that
you should be doing drugs.
How's school going? I'm home schooled.
Really? You're lucky.
Going to school was boring.
My dad took me out, and it
wasn't because it was boring.
I had a rough time in school, too.
Maybe not like you, but, you know...
I don't mean to compare our situations.
Actually, I guess I am
comparing our situations,
but only to show you how yours is worse.
You can edit that out, right,
so I don't look like an idiot?
Relax. Everyone acts
like an idiot around me.
Makes you think it's not an act.
Can I have something for my headache?
Yeah, is that new?
Sixteen years old.
Has the same birthday I do.
I'm gonna start the test now.
Study showed no signs of
scarring on Kenny's heart.
It wasn't drugs.
Well, then, give me something better.
What's causing heart block?
It could be toxoplasmosis.
We should do an LP
to test for infection.
If it was toxoplasmosis, we'd
have seen enlarged lymphs,
and because you're not pretty enough to
be an idiot, you must know that already,
which means you just said it
because you want to do an LP
to look for intracranial pressure.
Because it is intracranial pressure.
Wait, I'm not done.
You thought I wouldn't catch on,
which means you either think I'm
an idiot, which is flattering,
I've been doing my hair differently...
The kid's got headaches. He's been
popping acetaminophen like peanuts.
How could you possibly
think that I was done?
I prefaced that with an
"either. " It needs an "or. "
Or, you are an idiot,
which is possible, I'm not
great at judging men's looks.
The OR?
And the MRI room.
Yes...
Dr. House frequently conducts differential
diagnoses in a variety of places.
He feels that a change in venue
often leads to a change
in thinking processes.
I have to go take
care of something else.
Just let me do a CT
scan, see if I'm right.
The sooner we fix the problem,
the sooner we can get to
his reconstructive surgery.
Yeah. Who cares if you're
dead? It's how you look.
Well, since you've given me
nothing better, we're back to drugs.
The one thing we know it's not.
Decreased uptake on
the membranous septum.
Could be an artifact.
We can redo it, but...
Nothing's nothing. Do an EP study.
EP study means we have
to stop this kid's heart.
I'll set it up.
House, do you have a
minute to be disemboweled?
I'm gonna thread this catheter
through different areas in your heart,
and once I've found the right pathway,
I'll apply some electrical energy.
It'll stop my heart?
It sounds worse than
it is. You'll be fine.
Is it gonna hurt?
There'll be some discomfort.
If you've done drugs, I understand.
Being different's really hard.
Kenny, it's more important
for you to get better
than to worry about getting in trouble.
If I did drugs, that could
explain my heart problem?
It could.
And then you could do the
surgery to fix my face?
That's why we're here.
You know how famous people,
everywhere they go people
are watching them, staring?
They never have a chance to just be,
you know? And a lot
of them turn to drugs.
And people stare at them because they're
beautiful, but, me they just stare...
You okay?
I need to know what kind of
drugs, Kenny, and how much.
Coke, mostly. A lot of coke.
And then when I run out, I
usually go to LSD or acid.
Those are the same thing.
They are?
You don't do drugs, do you?
I drank from my dad's
liquor cabinet one time...
We're not gonna do this test. No...
I need you to turn on your side.
We need to intubate. I
need some help in here!
Too bad you guys are going
for a theatrical release.
Vomiting blood would
have made a great act-out.
Likely causes?
Mallory-Weiss tear.
No pallor, no melena.
Why are you wearing a tie?
I always wear ties, I'm a doctor.
Please don't look at the camera.
Sorry.
Nasal papilloma.
Hemorrhage could have
overwhelmed the heart.
Nice lipstick.
Thank you.
Bad idea.
The hemorrhage came after the block.
House, let them do their job.
Is anybody here more
interested in the medicine,
a little less interested
in the paparazzi?
Upper GI bleed.
Could be something he ate or
drank. Maybe a peptic ulcer.
Good.
Except no abdominal pain,
patient hasn't lost his appetite
and the last I checked, the gastrointestinal
tract isn't connected to the heart.
Yeah, but other than that, real good.
Nasopharyngeal angiofibrosis.
I just said it wasn't a nasal tumor.
Stomach cancer. Tumor causes bleeding,
body's reaction to the tumor
causes paraneoplastic syndrome,
which leads to heart block.
Finally, someone who is
not just a pretty face.
You and Taub, run the
scope, find the tumor.
Could be dangerous. If the
bleeding was caused by liver failure
as a result of the
intracranial pressure...
Liver is the one organ you can't
ascribe to intracranial pressure.
True.
Intracranial pressure
can cause liver problems.
It causes an increase in the cavernous
sinus pressure, which causes pressure
in the superior vena cava,
which shuts down the liver.
Did you just think of that? No.
Then why didn't you say anything in...
Think it would've changed
his mind? Not a chance.
House would have undercut me,
and forced me to do a
procedure I just argued against,
and then I'd look like a hypocrite
in front of the thousands of people
and potential future
employers watching this film.
If you're right, and we stick a scope
back down a kid with liver failure,
he could bleed again.
I know.
He just vomited blood.
Isn't that dangerous?
No. You're in good hands.
Okay. All right.
Well, it's great how he
rebounded from that setback.
What setback?
He didn't tell you about the...
Well, that's his right.
The records were sealed.
Personally, I think he
was just tapping his foot
and reaching for the toilet paper.
Obviously it was a witch hunt.
You think they singled
him out because...
No. Literally, a witch hunt.
Dr. House is a practicing Wiccan.
It's a beautiful
religion, it's very caring.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You have an all-access pass to
the case, not my Fave 5s. Now, go.
Come on! Come on! Let's go!
I think I'm going blind.
Hairy palms, too?
She said something idiotic again
and I didn't even notice it.
Foreman had to point
out that it was idiotic.
She's making me an idiot.
It's cute. You have a crush.
No, I think it's something systemic.
Thirteen's pretty.
You're obviously okay with her.
She killed a patient.
The bitch is pretty.
The bitch is a bitch.
Ask her out.
The bitch? She's a bitch.
No, the one that's making you an idiot.
It's the story of life. Boy
meets girl. Boy gets stupid.
Boy and girl live stupidly ever after.
Pretty girl kill again? No.
Elephant boy just
vomiting up blood again.
No tumors in the
patient's stomach, so...
But the scope caused variceal bleeding.
Took 20 minutes of banding to stop it.
Taub was right about the liver failure.
Yeah.
His craniofacial deformity is
causing intracranial pressure...
No. ... which is causing...
Where are the nosebleeds?
Where's the labored breathing?
You were right about me being wrong.
You were wrong about you being right.
I need new ideas. Anybody?
Does it bother you that
this kid's gonna die
because you won't put down
that camera at all? You know?
Your people should be extra motivated.
I'm sure they all wanna
look good in the film.
No, 'cause now they're too
worried about looking bad.
Dr. House, heart block plus liver
failure could mean autoimmune.
Maybe scleroderma.
Foreman? Does that make sense?
Not without tight skin on the hands,
muscle weakness and
a 30-year-old patient.
Liver failure plus heart block
could be a mitochondrial disorder.
Hey, say what she just said.
Liver failure plus heart block
could be a mitochondrial disorder?
Go look for signs of
retinal degeneration.
No, it's ICP. You're
only gonna see swelling.
Take him with you, so he can
see the degeneration, too.
So before you worked here in the
ER, you worked for House, right?
Three and a half years.
Why did you leave?
Hey. I don't wanna be on TV.
I'm not signing a release.
We'll blur you out.
Take off your pants.
You gonna be able to use any
of this if I start swearing?
Did House treat you as badly as
he treats his current fellows?
Loaded question.
That's not even a word.
Fork!
Very clever.
I learnt how to be a doctor from House.
Or at least a doctor who learnt
how to be a doctor from House,
if that makes any sense.
And you left his team because
you couldn't stand him anymore?
No, no. I love Dr. House.
Now, that's something we haven't heard.
I mean...
What did you ask me again?
Why you left.
I loved being around him,
professionally.
You know, he was always stimulating.
Not in an erotic sense of the word.
Fork. They forked,
and then they spooned!
Lean forward, and place
your chin on the rest.
I can't reach it.
Skooch in a little.
I'll take care of it.
Just like last time?
Maybe we should try this
the old-fashioned way.
Okay, look up to the ceiling
and try not to blink, okay?
Okay, good. Now straight ahead.
There it is. Swelling, no degeneration.
It's not mitochondrial.
Swelling proves there's
increased pressure in his brain.
Absolutely.
So, now we can schedule
the reconstruction?
Absolutely not.
Your test proved you wrong.
We found exactly what
I predicted we'd find.
Swelling means there's
increased pressure.
You get a gold Star
of David for proving,
yes, this kid has a big head
and big heads cause pressure.
Doesn't explain the liver.
Too much acetaminophen does.
JRA explains all of
it, including the liver.
One theory's better than
two. Treat with steroids.
If you're wrong, steroids are
gonna mess with his immune system,
put off his surgery for months.
You really wanna lose this
argument in front of the camera?
I'll speak to the father.
Dr. House believes that Kenny has JRA.
Juvenile rheumatoid arthritis.
We need to start administering steroids.
Will the steroids fix it?
I don't think he has JRA.
I think Dr. House is wrong,
and that the steroid
treatment could be dangerous.
I think I can get House
thrown off the case,
and get Kenny the
facial surgery he needs.
The father refused steroids until
we're sure about the diagnosis.
I am sure.
It's JRA.
And why would he even doubt that,
unless a former fellow of
mine was chirping in his ear?
The decision was his. I
merely voiced my concern.
Why did you take this job?
He's got a bulging cyst.
Perfectly good plastic surgery
practice, lots of money.
Fluids aren't draining properly.
Temptation to come screw
with me just too much for you?
There's gotta be a better reason.
He needs surgery to drain it.
Oh, and I think I mentioned
this earlier. You're fired.
What you did was over the line. Get out.
But don't go anywhere.
You're not fired, yet.
No one is firing anyone
in the middle of this case.
Not while those cameras are here,
and not while Taub is the only
person that this father trusts.
Where are you going?
To do what I always
do in these situations.
Treat my patient behind his back.
That's one option.
Or you can do a CT
scan of the kid's head.
If there's no midline
shift, we know Taub's wrong
and you get your consent
to give the kid steroids.
Just a warning.
If we have to start getting consent
every time we do a procedure,
soon they'll be asking
for informed consent.
Didn't think you had
the guts to stage a coup.
Coup failed. I'm scheduled
for execution at dawn.
No, you're not.
No reprieve from the governor.
You're a test result away from
becoming House's front runner.
He doesn't care about what you said,
or what you did five minutes ago.
He just wants the next good idea.
Show me 20 percent
magnification of the forebrain.
I look at our patient, as soon as
I saw his face, I saw a regular kid.
One thing about being a plastic
surgeon, you don't see what is,
you see what could be.
Talk like that around House, doesn't
matter how many good ideas you come up with.
So,
tell me what you don't
like about yourself.
Gosh.
There's so many things.
Is Dr. Taub available? Because
he was very highly recommended.
Well, he's no longer practicing with us,
but I've taken over all his files,
so if you tell me what needs work...
Do you know why he left?
He had personal issues to deal
with, so if we could just...
My goodness. Is he okay?
Oh, yeah, he's fine. He's fine.
Because my friend had
his ears done by Dr. Taub.
Should he worry that they may pop back?
No, it wasn't a professional issue.
I'm sorry, I really
can't go into more detail.
Shall we discuss your needs?
You know that toe next to the big
toe? Mine's bigger than my big toe.
Is there any way to shorten
it? Or make my big toe bigger?
Like, a toe-gmentation?
Did he lie, cheat or steal?
You're not here for a
consultation, are you?
What gave me away?
Was it my obviously perfect feet?
Hi.
CT shows that...
Let's go.
What are you two doing here?
Skipping three scenes.
CT's back. He's gonna say that
there's evidence of an anomaly,
I'm gonna say, he's wrong.
He's gonna go back to the
father and we'll all end up here.
The defect is pushing on
the right frontal lobe.
This bend is a sign of herniation.
Or, it's a sign of
increased pressure from JRA.
Dr. Taub would rather
distract you from the truth
with sparkly things,
like four karat diamonds.
House.
Your partner said that you
left for personal reasons,
but your wife said you lost a patient.
You son of a bitch,
you spoke to my wife?
See, that confused me.
Why would you give her a diamond
if you screwed somebody else over?
If you screwed her
over, I mean, I could...
Get that camera out of here!
You say anything to her?
Just asked questions.
Get them out of here, too.
We're doctors.
I screwed around with a
nurse. It became a deal.
My partners found out and I resigned.
There. Happy?
If you could be a bit more
descriptive, I'd be happier.
Some people pop pain pills,
I cheat.
We all have our vices.
Taub, I don't see it.
Stay away from the family.
House, start steroids and
stay away from his family.
Wow, you are ugly.
Wow, you're an ass.
I have a deformity.
I know, that's why you're ugly.
But you're a lucky boy.
Anywhere else in the animal kingdom,
your parents would
have eaten you at birth.
Your son needs steroids.
Dr. Cuddy agrees.
Does Dr. Taub?
He's not a real doctor.
He's a plastic surgeon.
All he cares is that your
son looks good in his coffin.
So, I'm supposed to believe you?
The doctor who cares.
You shouldn't care if I care.
I don't trust you.
Because I don't think
the surgery's important?
You're putting your trust in someone
who does think the surgery's important.
You're willing to take chances to risk
his life for something he doesn't need?
I do need it.
I can't have real relationships.
I can't even have a real conversation.
Not even with my dad.
Dad.
I know you love me.
But you don't treat me normal.
You're always protective.
The world can always go to hell.
But you never yell at me.
Even when I screw up.
I wanna be normal.
Take your steroids, and you get to live.
Then you can do your surgery.
But it'll only change your face.
It won't change who your face made you.
We're gonna get caught.
Not on film.
All their camera equipment's in here.
Where did you get those keys?
Blue, the janitor.
What?
That's his name.
His name's Lou.
Owe him an apology.
Just watch 20 minutes of this stuff,
tell me if I'm out of my mind.
Finally, we have video evidence.
Dr. House, heart block plus liver
failure could mean autoimmune.
Maybe scleroderma.
Foreman? Does that make sense?
Not without tight skin on the hands,
muscle weakness and
a 30-year-old patient.
Can I see that again?
What did you miss? She
screwed up, I didn't...
No, just the part
where she leans forward.
I think you can see through her dress.
Upper GI bleed.
Could be something he ate or
drank. Maybe a peptic ulcer.
Good.
You thought that was a good idea?
What am I gonna do?
Just enjoy.
I'm gonna keep her around,
because she makes me an idiot?
Well, you're protected,
Foreman seems immune.
You think he's gay?
Did he become an idiot around Chase?
I just said it's not a nasal...
Wait a minute, rewind
that. Was that Thirteen?
Wow.
I can't believe I'm that guy.
Every guy is that guy.
I'm not every guy.
What is this? Semantics here?
Okay, all guys are that guy.
I'm not all guys!
Cameron was smart.
You know, I'm beginning to doubt that.
I wanted to clarify
something I said earlier.
"I love Dr. House,"
and then I qualified it,
which, after thinking about it,
I didn't really need to do.
I did love being around him.
I guess, I just wanted to qualify
what I qualified before.
I'm looking defensive, aren't I?
No, no. I think that's great.
Clears everything up.
It's no big deal, really...
There's a mass lesion in the left anterior
temporal lobe surrounded by oedema.
Did you just insult me in Pig Latin?
Dr. House, please.
Will you just take a look at this?
The defect is causing this
nodular shadow here, you see it?
You're right, I didn't see that before.
Come on, let's go.
Hey.
I know you think you're feeling
better, on account of feeling better,
but this trusted family doctor
thinks that he's found a mass lesion,
so if you could lie back down
and struggle to breathe...
Okay.
You were right.
I'm thrilled I'm wrong.
This is great, Kenny.
You're gonna get your surgery now.
First person I'm coming
back to see is you,
because compared to me,
you're gonna look like butt.
Hey!
What, no comeback?
Look at that.
What?
His little finger, it's twitching.
No, it's not.
Just give it a second.
There. And?
He's not better.
What's wrong?
My diagnosis.
I don't know what he has.
Cancel the surgery.
New symptom. Involuntary
muscle movement.
Twitching finger is a symptom?
The body doing something
it's not supposed to do
is the definition of a symptom.
Kid's about to have a life-changing
operation. He's nervous.
Or he's not.
Or you were right.
Kid got better when
we put him on steroids.
This is JRA and it's under control now.
Or the steroids have just
tempered his condition.
He got a haircut, but
he's still got bad hair.
What about Lyme disease?
It explains everything, the heart
issues, the internal bleeding,
even why he'd get better on steroids.
On the other hand, if
he has Lyme disease,
there'd be other subtle clues
like a huge target-shaped rash.
But thanks for playing.
Why can't you just accept the
fact that you cured this kid?
You want to stop his surgery!
You're not normal.
So you don't want
anyone else to be normal.
You don't think normal's healthy.
Could be rheumatic fever.
Also explains why the steroids helped.
It's a similar inflammatory disease.
Rheumatic fever doesn't
explain liver failure.
Taub thinks that acetaminophen does.
Fine. Let's test your theory.
Remove his pacing wire.
If he's better, his heart
will be just fine on its own
and then he can have his operation.
If I'm right, his heart will stop.
Kutner, have the paddles on standby.
Another chance to blow someone up.
There'll be some minor discomfort
and you'll feel a slow,
steady pulling sensation.
Are you sure his heart
is ready for this?
Absolutely.
He's convinced he's sure.
Whereas I care about your son,
and have therefore brought
a professional defibrillist.
We're not gonna need those.
Dad, I feel fine, and my
finger hasn't moved in a while.
Okay. Take him off.
Here we go.
Heart rates 85 beats per
minute. BP 110 over 70.
Is he okay?
I feel the same.
He's fine. You're fine.
Thank God!
What do you mean, thank God?
God's the guy who gave it to him.
Thank you. Thank you.
Can you tell us about the procedure?
We have to use both an extra
and intracranial approach
to get enough exposure to
reduce the encephalocele cyst
and do the bony reconstruction.
And how are you participating
in this procedure?
She's not.
They don't want me here because
they think the kid's cured. I don't.
And what do you think the problem is?
I wish I knew.
I just know that if Dr. House is
right, something's gonna go wrong.
Dr. House doesn't think he's right.
Well, then I'll just waste a
few hours watching a surgery.
See, the danger is,
we have to reconstruct
all the way down to the cranial base,
and there are some
big vessels down there.
So, what we'll do is we'll
work our way down to here...
When were these pictures taken?
Well, about three weeks
ago. Why? What do you see?
Well, the acanthosis
nigricans was already there.
It's been there a lot longer than
that, probably his whole life.
What about around his hairline?
What? There's no discoloration.
There is now.
I have a new theory.
Their bad ideas don't indicate
a lack of intelligence,
they indicate an open mind.
The willingness not to be
trapped by conventional...
You've got a problem.
Tell me something I don't know.
You hire beautiful girls, enslave
them, force them to be around you
because you don't know how to
have an actual relationship.
If they're qualified, keep them.
If not, fire them and ask them out.
You do realize that, "Tell me something
I don't know" is just an expression?
Thirteen... You think that just because
she is as beautiful, ergo, you think that
because she hasn't had a decent idea...
No. My point is she's about to enter
your office, so you should shut up.
You were right about the diagnosis.
Yes, it was JRA. I'm very proud.
No, I mean you were right about
being wrong. He's got Lyme disease.
It explains everything.
Could you just hold up some fingers
so I can see if I'm literally blind?
We ruled out Lyme disease hours ago.
All the symptoms fit.
I am so ashamed.
Is she really that good looking?
Apparently.
How many lives have been
lost because of pretty girls?
The target rash is hiding.
No one ever looked
at him closely enough.
She's getting uglier by the second.
We can try and pretend we're above it
and we can try and
intellectualize it away,
but ultimately, shiny,
pretty, perky things are good
and ugly, misshapen,
teenage boys are repulsive.
The question was, do you resent Dr.
Cuddy's interference in your practice?
Oh.
Well, then I guess my answer
wasn't very helpful, was it?
"Mini-stud", stand up.
I spoke to your other partner.
After Cuddy told you...
No, I stayed away. Did
it all over the phone.
I asked for a reference. Said you were
applying for a plastic surgery job.
Oh, God!
Yeah.
He went nuts. Apparently
you signed a non-compete.
Now, why would you agree to that?
I don't wanna practice plastic surgery.
You sign a contract because
someone's making you.
Someone's getting something from you.
What did they give you in return?
They agreed to keep their mouths shut.
So you gave up your chosen
career just so they'd be quiet?
I love my wife.
You risked this job with
nothing to fall back on.
I thought you were wrong.
Sit back down.
You're keeping him
because he's a philanderer?
Where do I sign up?
Ask the Mormon. I'm keeping
him because he's interesting.
Dr. Terzi, would you please stand up?
Nice.
I have treated you unfairly.
Pre-judged you.
And for me to be a better person,
I have to rectify that situation.
You're fired.
You wanna grab some dinner?
Maybe a movie?
Seriously.
Just days ago, with
Kenny's condition worsening.
It was Dr. Gregory House
reassuring Kenny and his father.
I care about your son.
The charming House, who
happens to be a film buff
with a soft spot in his heart for
children told us how he got his start.
See, I became a doctor because
of the movie, Patch Adams.
Determined to save the
boy's life, as well as...
The horror.
Well, it's nice of them
to send us an early copy.
Not so much sent as stolen.
It was Dr. Gregory House who
served as not only a doctor,
but a rock for Kenny and his father.
You're putting your trust in someone
who does think the surgery's important.
House, one of those rare doctors...
God!
...who wears his heart on his sleeve.
I was saying that was
a stupid thing to do!
It's difficult not to be moved.
Oh, stop it.
Suddenly, I don't feel I can
trust Michael Moore movies.
Where are you going?
Kittens to get out of
trees? Deaf kids to read to?
I owe it to the world to make sure
this evil never sees the light of day.
Is there anything else?
Thank you, Dr. House.
Thank you.
www.tvsubtitles.net