I don't know about you, but I'm nervous.
Mazel tov!
Many children.
This is a great thing, Roz.
I am so happy for you.
Thank you, Mrs. Silver.
Yonatan is a good man,
from a good family.
I know you chose well
for me. I've been blessed.
Cross-species mating. I feel
like Darwin in the Galapagos.
Amber and I have a lot in common.
She's a Cutthroat Bitch,
you cry over Dark Victory.
Bette Davis. Another
strong, assertive woman.
You don't like strong.
You don't like assertive.
You like needy.
She's not dying, is she?
Yes. Go away.
I give it two months.
Hundred bucks.
It's not really fair.
You're not objective.
But, I'm all about the teaching, so...
We're at four months.
You hid this from me?
I was wrong. Okay?
I thought you'd be upset.
I thought you'd track
me down in hallways...
I shouldn't have discounted the sex.
She's obviously limber enough to
put off the meltdown for two months.
She's not needy. I don't need needy.
She's scary. Why does
scary need pathetic?
Are you going to talk to her?
I don't see that I have any choice.
You're all right with that?
No impulse to save her from me?
I've broken the pattern, House,
which is why this has a chance.
I know you're too suspicious to accept
that without getting out your ruler
and your calipers and your
scanning equipment, so,
go ahead. Get it out of your system.
Thirty-eight year old female
with loss of bladder control,
blood in her urine and a broken
leg from collapsing at her wedding.
Ampicillin for the UTI,
shiny cast for the leg.
You guys know Wilson's dating Amber?
No. Wilson and Amber?
I knew.
I asked her out. She said she'd
just started seeing someone.
Cultures were negative for UTIs.
No signs of previous trauma or STDs.
Kidney cancer.
CT was clean for tumors
and kidney stones.
I thought Amber scared
you guys. She does.
But she also has legs that
go all the way up to Canada.
So do Canadians. It doesn't
mean I want to date one.
Her sodium's low. Could be
endometriosis in the bladder.
Low sodium could also be from low food.
Hasidic Jews fast on their wedding day.
Or sodium was absorbed by a
toxin already in her system.
Was it just the legs, or did you
detect something resembling a soul?
She grew on me.
If there's a toxin in her,
it could be carbolic acid.
I'm talking about the patient now.
That much carbolic acid, someone
would have had to poison her.
Could have been a Cossack.
If this was 18th-century Poland
and Cossacks were into
household cleansers.
Which is why it's more likely
that the poisoner was poisonee.
Suicide's a sin.
Corollary of, "People lie," is, "People sin.
" And in my world, "People" includes Jews.
She was getting married.
Hasidic women marry young
so they can start pushing
out little "Hasidlings. "
Thirty-eight means a woman not on
anyone's hot list being pushed onto a guy
who's not on anyone's hot
list. No way out. No way out.
Endometriosis fits better than an
epiphany that her life is meaningless.
We should start her on Als
and do a cystoscopy to confirm.
Fine. Check her innards for bad
cells and her home for bad karma.
The carbolic acid should be on the shelf
right next to the regret and the self-loathing.
These people are crazy.
Yeah. She should be self-hating.
I'm not self-hating. I hate religious
people who are out of touch with reality.
You only marry someone
you met three times
if they're carrying your little mistake.
What's their divorce rate?
Cleaners are all organic.
Nothing with carbolic acid.
You like how they hook up?
Romance is just emotional foreplay.
Candlelight meals, flowers... It's as
much a ritual as anything these people do.
Why not go with someone who's pre-vetted,
shares the same values? Cut to the quick.
Values may give you the big picture, but
time together gives you the little picture.
Does she chew her food too loud?
Will she leave you alone
during the Final Four?
You commit to something deeper.
You let the little surprises slide.
Surprises kill,
which is why you only commit
when there are no more surprises.
And you have no more
surprises for your wife.
Do you think this came
up on date number two?
You ever heard of a
Hasidic Jew into hard rock?
She's listed as a
producer on all of these.
Where there's rock and roll and sex,
usually, there's drugs.
I'm Baal T'Shuvah. I became
Hasidic about six months ago.
And before six months ago?
Music business isn't exactly
known for its holiness.
Heroin.
But I've been clean for months.
Yonatan knows
in the broad strokes.
He never actually asked the details.
Says what's important is the person
that I am now, not the person I was then.
How do you go all the way from...
I just took a class.
Then I took another class.
And you just completely
left the music business?
Pop music is considered frivolous.
Same reason we don't
watch TV or go to movies.
Your drug use may have
caused some long-term damage.
We're going to need to take a hair
sample to test for latent toxins.
So, you can never watch Star Wars again.
You figure that I'll hire you,
if you promise to dump Wilson.
How did you... Wilson had a key.
You figure that I'll make
your life hell at first,
but I'll eventually see how
good you are and keep you.
It's a good plan, don't you think?
Perfectly tailored to your personality.
No, it's not. You know it's not.
Means you just want to stay in my orbit,
because you figure I'll eventually
realize that I made a mistake
and you'll be able to rub my face in it.
I can't wait. It's going to be awesome.
No, it's not. And you know it's not.
'Cause you know that
even if I made a mistake,
I'd never admit that I made a mistake.
Which means that you're just
toying with Wilson to toy with me.
Your goal is pure feral vengeance.
Innocent bystander, but
there's a greater good.
No, that's not it.
Because a bag of flaming
poop bypasses the bystander.
So, which is it, House?
Am I in this for you?
Or am I in this for him?
Give him back his sweatshirt.
Pit stains don't become you.
Treatment had no effect,
rules out endometriosis,
and her hair sample was
negative for residue drugs.
This woman lived in the fast
lane till six months ago.
Maybe we're missing something.
She admitted drug use.
Doubt she's holding out on
her days as an asbestos miner.
Cryoglobulinemia might
account for the symptoms.
Except for the one you missed.
Well, there's no
change in her condition.
I'm not talking about a new symptom,
I'm talking about one that
presented six months ago.
Look, she's nuts. But we can't just give
her 10 cc of atheism and send her home.
Religion is a symptom of irrational
belief and groundless hope.
Altered mental status, on the other
hand, is a symptom of porphyria.
She didn't develop uncontrollable
anger, crying, anxiety,
she just decided to go to Temple.
The woman didn't just
choose to keep kosher.
She went directly to the extremes of
Hasidism and a life of stringent rules.
She became a masochist.
She didn't like her old
life, so she changed it.
People don't change.
They might want to,
might even need to, but...
Taub gave up a six-figure plastic
surgery career for this job.
That mean he has porphyria?
He switched jobs to save his
marriage. He did it to avoid change.
He's right. You don't suddenly choose
crazy without suddenly being crazy.
No. No. If she walked
away from everything,
to go base-jumping or live with apes
we wouldn't be having this discussion.
We would if she was also tinkling
blood out of her over-excited bladder.
Pump Hadassah full of hematin
and give her a phlebotomy.
Bloodletting?
Porphyria is a rare genetic disorder
that causes an over-production
of a certain protein.
Draining the blood relieves...
A hair test for damage from drugs
showed she has a rare genetic disease?
Not exactly. We're
testing her now to confirm.
You're treating it
before you confirm it?
Blood test results take 24 hours.
You must have seen something
that makes you suspect it.
Dr. House has a theory.
A theory based on what?
We'd like a different doctor.
I assure you that Dr.
House is our best...
Then we will settle for second best.
Someone who doesn't think my wife
is sick just because she's religious.
If you prefer, I can give your
wife my second-best diagnosis.
Did you know Wilson's dating Amber?
I have reviewed the chart.
Someone on your team
must have pointed out
that cryoglobulinemia
also fits the symptoms.
Yes. It fits many of the symptoms.
My wife's body is sick.
Her mind and soul are fine.
You live according to God's
600 commandments, right?
Six hundred thirteen.
Do you understand them all?
It takes a lifetime of learning.
But you follow the ones
you don't understand,
because the ones you do understand
make sense and you believe
that the guy who created
them knows what he's doing.
Of course.
So, you will trust my diagnosis,
and you'll let me treat her,
because in this Temple, I am Dr. Yahweh.
I want a new doctor.
I'm starting her on indomethacin
for the cryoglobulinemia.
People don't change.
For example, I'm going to keep
repeating, "People don't change. "
So, alcoholics that successfully
go through treatment don't exist.
They're still alcoholics.
If they never take another
drink as long as they live,
it's only because they
didn't live long enough.
If you're dissatisfied with your life,
changing it is a symptom of mental health.
I get why that concept
is strange to you.
O2 sats are 85. She's hypoxic.
We might need to intubate.
What's wrong with her?
Well, it's definitely
not cryoglobulinemia.
Better ask him.
We kept her on oxygen overnight.
Her respiratory rate's stabilized
and her O-sat's back up to 95.
I saw Amber drop off
Wilson this morning.
Yes. The male always drives the female.
So what caused the breathing problem?
Pulmonary involvement
rules out porphyria.
She kiss him or he kiss her?
I missed it. The lab tech with
the tongue stud also pulled up.
Wegener's would explain
her elevated sed rate.
Wegener's wouldn't explain
the changed mental status.
Actually, we've been trying to
ignore that part of the white board.
I wrote it in black. I'm
always serious when I use black.
Lupus would explain...
Maybe she didn't change.
Are you agreeing with me,
or are you making a point?
I'm making a point.
That's going to take longer.
How do we know that the real Roz isn't
who she is now and who she was then?
Can't we say that her previous life was
true, without making her present one a fraud?
The "life is messy" argument. Nice. Explains
everything without explaining anything.
If it's lupus, there's a heart
problem we don't know about yet.
Run her through a stress test. If
she has a heart attack, I'm right.
Or we could wait, hope that...
You're afraid to give
her a heart attack.
Of course we're afraid to...
No reason to be afraid.
Unless you think I'm right.
It's Wegener's.
But we'll have the
crash cart, just in case.
Oh, my God! What are
you guys doing here?
I had a sudden yen for fusion.
I put a different restaurant in my
date book. I'm firing my assistant.
That's okay. Hi, Greg.
And I call you "Greg" because
we're now social equals.
I call you "Cutthroat Bitch. "
Well, quod erat demonstrandum.
And I speak in Latin, because I
don't try to hide what an ass I am.
I assume you'd like to join us?
It will be easier to observe our
interaction if you're at the same table.
If we ever get seated.
Excuse me.
No, no. I...
We've been waiting for...
Any minute now, she's going to hit
him in the face with your testicles.
She tends to treat... She
tends to treat every event
like it's the last
'copter out of Saigon.
She's the anti-Wilson.
She's a force for evil.
She has an annoying
quality. Perhaps even two.
If I was perfect, I would date perfect.
You like that.
It's annoying, but she's good at it.
Wait a second.
This isn't just about the
sex. You like her personality.
You like that she's conniving.
You like that she has no
regard for consequences.
You like that she can humiliate
someone if it serves...
Oh, my God.
You're sleeping with me.
I need you to go faster, Roz.
A little harder.
I am going harder, damn it.
What if Dr. House was right?
And Roz did make a radical change.
Lupus is chronic, but treatable.
And with the treatment,
it would undo the change?
She'll be the way she
was before I knew her?
I don't think it's likely.
Then you don't know for sure.
You'd find someone else.
There isn't someone else.
You've had three dates.
How long have you been married?
Twelve years.
And is she the one?
We wouldn't still be
together if she weren't.
I love her as much now as the day...
Well, you should love her more.
The more you know someone,
the more you should love them.
Okay. That's enough, Roz.
Your heart's as strong as a battleship.
Does this mean Dr. House was wrong?
Oh! Oh, my leg!
Heart's strong enough to prove you
wrong about the change in mental status.
Only proves this isn't lupus,
just as the leg pain
proves it isn't Wegener's.
Leg pain could be from nerve
entrapment. We're thinking blood clot.
Do an MRI to look for
the clot. Then do an FMRI.
An MRI alone will detect...
If the clot hasn't dissolved.
An FMRI could show signs
of a near-ischemic stroke
in post-ischemic parts of the brain.
Give me 10 bucks.
No. I missed lunch.
I thought you went out
with... I missed lunch.
Good symmetrical activity
in both hemispheres.
Caudal structures look
okay. She hasn't changed?
Sex, drugs, rock and roll and the 600
rules of God are all in there somewhere.
We oversimplify people. It's
how the human mind works.
Everything's on or off.
Everything's got a category.
You don't like it.
You don't want to be over-simplified.
Roz, move your right leg.
No one can describe
themselves in 10 words.
Why would we want to
hear anyone else do it?
So you keep it a mystery. No
categories if no one knows anything.
Do you think maybe you're
over-simplifying me, now?
No.
I'm sure you have many reasons
to keep yourself a mystery,
besides the fact that you're bisexual.
A denial would have worked
before the long vacant stare.
Roz, move your left leg just an inch.
People who have a problem with boxes
are people who don't fit in them.
You've been working for
House for a long time.
No need for name-calling.
I would ask if this was going to be
lunchtime gossip, but lucky for me...
I don't give a damn.
How's our mental Yentl?
MRI shows no sign of clots,
FMRI shows no problem areas.
Go restart her IV.
What's wrong with it?
Nothing. But like so many of the procedures
we put patients through, it hurts,
which, if she's enjoying it,
will show up in pretty colors.
This is why you wanted an FMRI?
It showed she didn't have a blood
clot, which is diagnostically relevant.
And it can show that she's become a
masochist. Also diagnostically relevant.
And it will be cool.
Either explain which part of my
analysis didn't make sense, or go do it.
It isn't cool.
I'm sorry.
Heavens. Look at her limbic system.
Her pleasure centers are
lighting up like a Hanukkah bush.
Foreman must have a
touch like an elephant.
Okay, Roz, we've got what we need.
Yes. It was impressive.
Roz? You all right?
Oh, sorry. I was praying.
All through the procedure?
No, when Dr. Foreman apologized, I
knew something bad was going to happen.
She was praying. Could
explain the brain activity.
BP and heart rate are
dropping. She's crashing.
She's stabilizing.
Get her up.
All the way up. On her feet.
Make her do that again.
We've started her on
fludrocortisone and ephedrine.
It's Planet of the Apes.
The apes are the humans.
Humans are the apes.
It's Wacky Wednesday, opposite day.
When you stand up, your BP and heart
rate are supposed to go up. Not...
Got it. So, what causes bloody urine,
loss of bladder control, leg pain,
altered mental status and
pressure-blood in direction-wrong?
Pheochromocytoma?
Low catecholamines in the urine
means no pheochromocytoma in the Jewess.
Could be systemic sclerosis.
Mental status.
She was praying.
She was in pain. You no
longer think she's crazy?
I can see why she'd be
attracted to that life.
You drank the
Manishewitz-flavored Kool-Aid.
I'm not saying I agree.
I'm just saying...
That there's a rational
basis for the irrational.
They have something that we don't have.
Imaginary friends.
If the toaster's not
working, wiring could be bad.
Which debate is that metaphor
supposed to help us with?
Electrical problem in the heart.
Arrhythmia messes with her
blood flow when she stands,
causes low BP and heart rate.
Could also impact mental
status, everybody's happy.
Run an EP study of her heart.
Find where the wiring's verklempt.
I went by your hotel this morning.
They told me you moved out.
You moved in with CB?
No. Apparently, I moved in with you.
The very fact that you're resisting
my insight proves to me that...
House. You're right.
Why not? Why not date
you? It's brilliant.
We've know each other for years,
we've put up with all kinds
of crap from each other,
and we keep coming back. We're a couple.
Are we still speaking metaphorically?
Amber is exactly what I need.
And you would agree if you
weren't mired in self-loathing,
topped with a thin crust of megalomania.
Hey. That's my best friend's
girl you're talking about.
I was wrong.
House. You're right.
She's not me. Well, she is me. But,
that's not why she's attractive.
She's a needy version of me.
It's hard to imagine
such a mythical creature.
You started seeing her
right after I fired her.
I started seeing her four months ago.
She told Kutner it was four weeks.
You lied to me. There
was money on the line.
Because I knew how you'd react and
I knew you wouldn't pay me, anyway.
You knew that I was right.
She wasn't needy. She
was in a bad situation.
There's a difference.
Not to your libido.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Why are you doing this?
Every time I agree with
you, you find a new argument.
What are you trying to avoid?
Well, if you'd looked at me with those
flashing eyes before I was involved...
C'est la vie.
And I use the French
because you're an ass.
Right atrium normal, no arrhythmia.
You can become a D'har Master. Does
that require further explanation?
Right ventricle normal.
In college, I was really
into science fiction.
Not like the guys with
the $600 prosthetic ears,
who could swear in Romulan.
That was embarrassing to the rest of us who
just thought it was good, smart literature.
I went to one convention. By senior year,
I was D'har Master in the Klingon Empire.
I'm not going to become Hasidic.
I'm not even going to
become slightly more Reform.
Coronary sinus normal.
You can't have your eyes opened
to something and not act on it.
I haven't had my eyes opened. I just
don't think they're crazy anymore.
Then they have something to offer.
She's living proof that sane people
can make radical changes, but House...
He thinks that he can bully...
I'm sorry?
I think she's telling
you to stop deflecting.
Evil tongue. Gossip.
It's okay. Thanks to the
sedative, you won't remember it.
Words are permanent.
Someday, you'll say something
that you wish you could take back.
Hiss bundle is normal. Pathways
are all clean. No arrhythmias.
If the toaster doesn't work and
the wiring in the house is fine,
problem's got to be in
the city's power grid.
Autonomic nerve disorder.
Could be Riley-Day Syndrome.
Congratulations on your wedding.
You have a rare and incurable
degenerative disease.
I'll set her up for a
thermoregulatory sweat test.
She's bisexual.
What?
I could hear them talking
from inside the MRI.
Hear who? I heard the word sex.
It was interesting.
What was interesting? It doesn't matter.
We're doctors, we never know what's
going to matter. She said sex.
If she wants to tell
you, when she wakes up...
Yeah. These people aren't
going to change you at all.
I need you to sleep with Wilson.
Good morning.
He's involved with an
inappropriate woman.
His people are sheep herders,
and Amber's are cattlemen?
He's combined two of his worst qualities.
His love for me and his love for need.
And as administrator of this hospital,
you have to save your star oncologist.
Wish I could help. But as administrator,
there are some people in accounting
I'm scheduled to sleep with first.
Wilson has a pattern with women.
He saves them, then he betrays
them, which then causes guilt,
which then causes him
to go save somebody else.
For example, a hospital bureaucrat
nearing 40 who has no personal life.
I suggest you go braless.
I get that "sleep with" is your way
of saying I should talk to him...
No, I really mean "sleep with. "
You're not worried this relationship
will fail, you're worried it'll succeed.
That Wilson will no longer
be at your beck and call 24l7.
That your best friend will change.
People don't change just
because they wish they could.
And it bugs you that he wishes he could.
You'll never lose your friend, House.
You're the long-distance
runner of neediness.
As the chamber heats up, Roz's
body temperature should also rise,
making her sweat and
turning the powder purple.
No change in color means no sweating,
which means her central
nervous system is damaged.
I shouldn't see her like this.
We could have a diagnosis as soon
as she comes out of the chamber.
It might be better if you stayed.
It's disrespectful.
I'm sure she imagined the first time
her husband would see her bare like this,
would be celebrating their marriage.
Given the circumstances, I think Roz would
sacrifice modesty to have you with her.
Please. Don't do that.
What? I think it's
nice that you're here.
I think... You think it's sweet
that I care for her modesty, but that
it's archaic and ultimately irrelevant.
Our traditions aren't
just blind rituals. They...
They mean something.
They have a purpose.
I respect my wife.
And I respect her body.
Her body temperature's stopped climbing.
What's going on?
She's having a seizure.
Need a crash cart!
Blankets, too! She's freezing.
She was supposed to
sweat. And she froze.
Return to the Planet of the Apes.
Hypothermia caused the seizure.
What caused the hypothermia?
Could be infection.
Her white blood cell count was fine.
When she was admitted. She could
have picked something up here.
A complication on a complication?
Her body's doing the opposite
of what it's supposed to.
Her body is Wilson.
How do we respond to that?
We accept that he's happy.
We do the opposite.
So, you want us to what?
Send the patient home?
An infection means that
something's been added to the body.
Something that should be expelled.
What's the opposite of that?
Something missing from the body.
Could be an enzyme or a hormone.
Cortisol. Could be Addison's.
It fits.
Every symptom.
I'll run a cortisol stimulation test.
Are you sure she doesn't want to
just take you back to her lair,
hang you upside-down, and
deposit her eggs in you?
Excellent disguise, House.
You two are really that serious?
She's pretty. She's funny.
Maybe she's a little more...
Evil?
...aggressive than you'd expect for me.
But, I'm happy. Can't I just enjoy
what that feels like for a while?
How many people have
looked at you trustingly
while you gave them a fatal prognosis?
But you knew it was kinder
to tell them the truth.
Amber compulsively
looks out for number one.
You compulsively look out for
the person that you're with.
Your needs are going to feed
her needs until all that's left
is a Wilson chalk outline on the floor.
Sorry.
Wow.
That cortisol stuff is great.
Does it work on everything?
I take it you're feeling better.
Still weak, but, yeah.
You must be so tired. You should
go home and get some sleep.
I'll stay.
I never told you, but you are much better
looking than Mrs. Silver led me to expect.
She never liked me. When I was eight,
I threw up on her shoes
at my uncle's wedding.
Your abdomen's a little swollen.
Is it serious?
It's hard to say. Sometimes it can
mean a liver issue. We'll have to test.
Oh. Oh, dizziness is getting...
She's going into shock, I need another
liter of saline! Type and cross two units!
What's happening to her?
She's bleeding internally.
She's saying the Sh'ma.
She thinks she's dying.
The MRA shows you're bleeding internally,
but not where it's coming from.
The blood can only keep
you stable for so long.
Our best option is to
open you up and search.
But you can fix it.
If we find the leak.
You find the bleeding,
you find the disease?
No.
But it could keep you alive long enough
so Dr. House can find
what's wrong with you.
No.
I don't want to have the surgery.
It's the only chance you've got.
I don't want to have the
surgery until after sunset.
I'm probably going to die, anyway.
I just want to share one
Shabbat with my husband.
Roz, please. The Torah
commands us to preserve life.
I waited 38 years to find what I wanted.
I can wait another eight hours.
And I'll leave the rest to God, okay?
I had her rabbi call. She's adamant.
She's not a masochist. She's suicidal.
Nice work, Chase.
Yeah, I should have had
twin rabbis call. Can I go?
We need you.
So, instead of a few days, we now
have a few hours to figure this out.
Nice work, Chase. Why do you need me?
Saying, "Nice work, Chase" when
you're not here is pointless.
Seriously. We need you.
We should X-ray for malformations of the
rib that could cause arterial twisting.
Malformations don't cause bloody urine.
She's not suicidal.
She made a commitment to a
new life with her husband,
and she wants one meaningful
experience in that life.
She just met the guy.
Taub just met her and he's already
so in love he's ready to let her die
and take her back to the home planet
for a burial in the lava sea of Tormiad.
It's who he might be.
She's connecting with all the
years she's not going to have.
A better way of connecting to those
years is to actually have them.
You want more time?
Joshua got God to make the sun stand
still. No reason God can't speed it up.
And by God, I, of course, mean you.
Told you we needed you.
It's sundown, Roz.
We're taking you back to your
room for your candlelight dinner.
Ready? One, two, three.
It's too early.
Your sense of time is off
because of the medication.
Good shabbos, Roz.
So, you pray, scarf down some
challah, then we can do this?
You wanted to see me?
And you came.
I feel pretty confident it'll
be something interesting.
Solve this case and the job is yours.
Is there a "Drop Wilson"
clause attached to this?
Standard contract all employees sign.
Why do you have to believe
I have an ulterior motive?
For the same reason I believe a crack
whore is going to have sex for crack.
All my life,
I thought I had to choose between
love and respect.
And I chose respect.
And with Wilson,
I know what it's like to have both.
And that beats a fellowship.
Could be DIC.
You've changed.
I hope so.
Normal platelet count rules
out DIC. Good try, though.
I read that a hydatid cyst could...
Would affect the lungs, not the bladder.
I tested her white cell
count again. Normal.
How long till we get to cut her open?
When I left, he was still
singing Eshat something.
It's the husband's blessing of his
wife. He calls her Eshet Chayil.
Woman of Valor. "Strength and honor are
her clothing. She laughs at the future. "
Because she's an idiot.
Volvulus of the small
intestine could cause bleeding.
She would have had constipation.
Her value isn't beyond pearls, either.
Because dead people have no value.
Polycythemia vera.
RBC count would be higher.
I need to bring the light to my face.
Thrombocytopenia. If it's autoimmune...
Titers were normal.
Parkinson's would
explain the hypothermia.
Not the bloody urine.
The woman's not just a
masochist, she's a hypocrite.
The commandment to preserve
life comes before all others.
Actually means she's not a masochist.
She's not following all the rules.
Just the ones that please her.
Right. She walked in crazy and
explained how ritual trumps living,
and you decide it's
a beautiful lifestyle.
I know. She's wrong,
but, if there's nothing more...
Then, the only meaning is here.
But if she thinks God is there for her,
if she lives her life
believing that God is there...
Then, she dies.
Things aren't where we want them to be,
just because we want them to be there.
Of course, that doesn't mean
they're where they should be.
Hey. Stop that Jew.
Chase hates working on shabbos. I'm
going to make this easier for him.
Stand her up.
She doesn't do so well on her feet.
Neither do I. Stand her up.
You can tell all the ladies
at the Mikvah about this.
What did you do?
What are you doing?
Put your hand here. Press hard.
You have nephroptosis. Also
known as "floating kidney. "
The kidney is like a chandelier.
It's attached to a ceiling of
intestines and blood vessels.
But your contractor, I think you know
who he is, he hung it with a cheap chain.
It's been hanging sloppy for years.
Finally, something shook it loose.
After that, every time you stood,
your kidney dropped a few centimeters.
That caused all of your symptoms.
None of the scans picked it up.
Because we do scans
with patients lying down.
She would have been lying down in
surgery, too. They'd never have found it.
Good chance she'd never come out.
She'll be all right?
Ultrasound to confirm.
Then, tell Chase, to put
the kidney back on the shelf.
The bleed will be nearby.
That's it?
Mazel tov.
Couple hours surgery,
you'll be ready to push
out those 14 children.
You do it both ways, right?
What? The ultrasound.
You do it standing up and lying down.
What else would I mean?
I've decided you could do worse
than a female proxy for me.
So, you're going to acknowledge
that people can change?
No. You think I've changed
or Amber's changed? Nope.
Then, you've changed.
If you do change, can it be the
part of you that chases me down halls
trying to change me?
Do you know what this means?
That you made one good dating choice.
The fabric of the space-time
continuum could unravel.
My world could expand. I could form
a long-term connection,
that isn't with you.
And since you put the darkest
possible construction on everything,
you could end up losing a friend.
You've thought of all this.
And yet, you're going along with it.
Are you being self-sacrificing?
I'll sacrifice a lab rat.
I'll sacrifice a fly.
I'll sacrifice $200 on a
mudder at Monmouth Park.
I don't sacrifice self.
Shabbat shalom, Wilson.
Shabbat shalom, House.
www.tvsubtitles.net