He's got a good pulse.
Maintain head
stabilizationand flip him over.
My count, guys. Ready. Go.
Sir, we're paramedics.
The mailman saw you having a seizure.
We had to break downyour door.
Do you know what your name is?
On my count. One, two, three. Up.
We're taking youto the hospital.
No, I can't--
no. No, I can't...
Hey, buddy. Buddy, we're trying to help.
Sir!
Stay out of my house!
You just had a seizure.
You could have a stroke.
A bleed in your brain.
Leave me alone!
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
House Season05
Episode07 'The Itch'
35-year-old male-- crushing headache
and three seizures in the last two days.
so it's a bleed, clot, tumor,
metabolic, or infection.
- Stick him in a ct.
- Can'T.
I'm assuming he has a giant head.
Severe agoraphobe.
The world scares the hell out of him.
So we can only test him with
whatever we can take to him.
Fun.
Agoraphobia a symptom?
Only of being shot.
He and his girlfriend were mugged
seven years ago. That's when it started.
Anybody can hate humanity
after getting shot.
Takes a big man to hate it beforehand.
How'd you get this case if
he didn't come to the er?
I talked to him through his
door when he had flu last year.
I run the community outreach pgram now.
See? Perfectly reasonable explanation.
She's definitely not here trying to work her way
back on the team and steal your job or anything.
It's a legitimate question.
He agreed to meet with us.
But even if I can get inside his
house, his brain is a black box.
We can pick this up in a minute.
what's this?
Take-out menus.
But I'm hoping you'll come up with a better
answer when everyone asks what we're talking about.
- Last night--
- forget it.
I know this is awkward,
but we need to talk.
There's a reason that we've
evolved a feeling of awkwardness.
It tells us not to talk about things.
I was emotional because of
the adoption falling through.
And you actually let your
human side show for a moment.
That is why we kissed.
I just want to say thank you
for not... taking advantage.
You're welcome.
Any time you want to stop
kissing, I'm there for you.
Portable equipment can't distinguish a
bleed or a tumor. Can't see vasculitis.
What did cuddy want?
I kinda hit that last night,
so now she's all on my jock.
She looks pretty good
for someone on roofies.
The only equipment we have is
a sonogram and a portable x-ray.
What part of olivine, pyroxene,
and amphibole don't you understand?
pyroxene.
Pyro means "fire"...
they're indicator minerals.
You can't see diamonds so you
look for the indicator minerals.
I assume the diamond is the
tumor or bleed or whatever it is.
we provoke a seizure.
The indicator is the increased electrical
activity focused around the abnormality.
We do an eeg, see the focus, see where the
problem is, whh tells us what the problem is.
The formster and the camster.
Kickin' it old school.
Thank god she's not
trying to steal your job.
Go do it. And search
the home for toxins.
I agreed to talk, not let you in.
You could be very sick.
We need access.
I'm just not ready.
Why does hhave two locked doors?
He must use this room as an airlock.
Deliveries in. Garbage out.
He never has to go outside.
Just tell us when you are.
We're not going away.
Seriously?
You want her to admit that all he has to do is
ignore us for a few minutes and we'll take off?
He was shot.
Girlfriend killed.
He probably has post
traumatic stress disorder.
He doesn't believe in a just
universe. He doesn't trust anyone.
Give him some hostY.
I shouldn't have implied
we'd wait forever.
We've got a whole
hospital full of patients.
We can give you a few minutes.
But eventually, if you don't let
us in, we're gonna have to leave.
just one person comes in.
No. We've got to search
the whole house for toxins.
How about I examine you in one room
and my colleagues will do the search?
I'm gonna tryto provoke a seizure.
I need youto look straight ahead, okay?
You all right?
Yeah. Uh, I just, um, I haven't been
in a room with anyone for a while.
- Um, can you just give me a second?
- Sure.
You're the, uh, uh, person I talked
to through the door last year, right?
Yeah.
You were, uh, you
were nice... and smart.
Kind of made me expect someone older.
I'm not that young.
Must've been scary being shot.
Don't do that. Okay?
You d--you
don't know me.
I've got everything I want here.
I-I-I make a lot of
money writing tech manuals.
I get stuff delivered. I work out.
I see anything I want over the web.
Um, I'm--I'm
happy here.
Yodon't seemvery happy.
Well, right now I'm not.
Go away.
Did you speak to cuddy last night?
She's fine.
Why would it take anyone more than a
few hours to get over misplacing a baby?
You spoke to her?
Kinda hit that.
So she's all on my jock.
Wha--what?
Everyone else thought I was kidding.
You hit?Like making
out or full-on sex or--
got a chart laid out with all the
bases. I'll take you through it.
Wh--what are
you gonna do?
What can I do?
I'm going to ignore
herfor the rest of my life.
This mosquito bite kept me awake.
Don't careabout the bug bite.
She's your boss.
So now I have two reasonsto ignore her.
It was just a kiss.
There's a reason.
Yes. Those large things in her bra.
You were hiding it from me
means it meant somethingto you.
Yeah, I fiendishly concealed it
within the phrase"I hit that."
Stop scratching. You'll draw blood.
Finally you saidsomething useful.
If I actually break the skin,
it'll let the poison out.
If you... dated
cuddy...there would--
sorry. I get better
reception when you're not here.
What do you got?
his place is totally clean.
No animals. No hidden drugs or
alcohol. No lead in the paint.
and since you're not breathing hard,
I assume you're not holding cameron aloft
in triumph. Which means no seizures.
Speakingof breathing hard,
cameron, you engaged to chase yet?
sorry, we should have clarified.
We're callingabout the patient,
not . Cameron'slove life.
We aren't engaged.
Moves things alongmuch faster
to just give himthe answers.
- Seizures can alsobe induced
through-- - after six years?
A year and a half.
- Through sleep deprivation or-- -
sleep deprivationwould take too long.
You living together?
We spend most nightstogether.
There's a bunch of drugs that
can lower a seizurethreshold.
And cloud the
diagnosis with side effects.
His place or yours?
His usually.
Interesting.
You would've saidinteresting
no matterwhat the answer.
And no matter what the answer,
it would've been interesting.
No engagement. Commitment issues.
His place, control issues.
Not sure whose,but interesting.
Yeah, moves much fasterthis way.
Where was the patientwhen
he had his first seizure?
In his entry hallway getting his mail.
Getting close to the
outdoors spooked him, raised his bp.
Use that fear. Bring him outside.
He punched out a fireman.
We're doctors, not bouncers.
Okay. So bring the outside to him.
Floor is genuine wood.
Why are they here?
They overheard me announce the half price
bank foreclosure in the er waiting room.
Where's everybody?
Cameron'swith the patient.
Uh, everybody else went home.
Because they don't need to be here.
Neither do you.
And yet you are.
This way.
Molding's original?
Original?
They were here before the house.
The shut-in's also original.
Come on. Don't be shy.
House, get themout of here.
easy for you to say.
You're not gonna be makingsome
serious capital gains.
This is cruel.
And leaving him undiagnosed
is what, altruistic?
Procedure worked. He's
seizing. What do you see?
Normal theta.
Normal delta. This isn't a seizure.
It's something.
Mr. Nozick,are you okay?
Stomach's killing me.
See? It's something.
partial small bowel obstruction.
Blockage expinsthe pain.
What explainsthe blockage plus seizures?
Atrial fibrillation throwing emboli.
Crohn's causing an abscess.
Could bea million things.
There's no way to know unless we get him in
for an mri on his head or exploratory surgeryso
we can biopsy his bowels,
which he won't let us do.
Wouldn't.
Pain changes things.
House.
He told you to stay out of here.
He can chase me out once he's
done doubling up in agony.
Whatever yr big problem is, it's caused a
complication we call "colon fos." "Fo," full of.
Since we're in mixed
company,"s" is stool.
Nothing's coming out so the
pain'sgonna get worse and worse.
We need to sticka pooper scooper in you.
We also need to take
a lookat your bowel.
I made my wishes clear.
And if the crazy fairy were
here, she could grant them.
I'm not insane.
I-I feel painwhen I go outside.
So it--it's rationalto
avoid that pain.
Except now you're feeling pain inside.
Not as bad. Nowhere near.
We can give him drugsfor the blockage.
And if it doesn't work?
That blockage will ruptureyour intestines,
spew sewage throughout your body.
Whatever you're scared ofout there,
aren't you more scared of death?
You obviouslycan't stand people.
But for me, it's worse. All right?
I'd rather die in
here than live out there.
If you don't mind floppy
hair and an annoying accent,
I know a surgeonwho will
operate in your home.
Thank you.
With the risk of infection,
chase won't actually--
he's not gonna do surgeryin
some crazy dude's house.
You just
said--
what I said was that chase
would put him under at the house,
we'd take himto the hospital,
open him up,do our thing,
then slip him backinto his room for the post-op
without him ever finding outthat we tricked him.
Some of that was implied.
- It's unethical.
- He'll be asleep.
He gets to makehis own
calls even if he's asleeP.
Why are you sidingwith him?
Oh, yeah, you're that girlwho likes
broken people because her husband died.
And since chase
isn'tall that broken--
hey, why don't we operateon his
infarcted leg while we're at it?
Who cares if he said no.
I was risking my lifeto
avoid becoming a cripple.
He's doing it to
avoidsunlight and fresh air.
We've got to make it look good.
I know I'm a pain in the ass.
I know it would have been
easy just to walk away, but...
you're a good person.
Count down from 10.
10, 9, 8...
let's go!
How you doin'?
- Better.
- Great.
Everything else good?
Uh, everything involving
me kissing house is good.
Oh, god, you dragged itout of me.
You're a genius.
It's no big deal.
I was feeling vulnerable.
He's a friend.
And I leaned on him.
It's funny. I've leaned
on friendsin the past.
Never leaned so far my
tonguefell into their mouths.
I don't think of housethat
way. I never have.
Why not?
You know exactlyhow it would go.
It'd start off exciting.
We'd get caught up in the novelty and the
hostility and the forbiddenness.
And then we'd realize that the
flirty hostility is just hostility
and his inabilityto open up is no
longer exciting,it's just frustrating.
And--and then it'sthe inevitable
blowup and the recriminations
and we don't talkfor two months.
Yeah.
Well, it certainly proves you've
never thoughtabout house that way.
I get your point.
I will be more carefulwith
my tongue in the future.
That's not my point.
Maybe novelty and hostilityand
forbidden-ness doesn't have to end bad.
Gotta go.
What time you done?
We could trythat new sushi
place next to my house.
Why don't we stayat my house tonight?
We always stayat mine.
That's what I mean. We--we
used to split it. What happened?
I don't know. Closer to work.
By five minutes.
Anmy house doesn't looklike it was
decorated by a drunk rugby player.
Well, we can discuss
it.I hadn't really--
why does it haveto be a
discussion? Can't you juststay over?
You do know they page me when that
much surgical equipment is signed out.
He didn't consent. He consentedto the
surgery. You think he's gonnasue over where?
He won't even know where. He'll wake up in his
house. He won't know a thing about what happened.
Until he catchesa post-surgical infection in
his dirty apartmentand finds out we tricked him
and winds up owningthe hospital.
Why aren't you arguingwith her?
Because she's right.
I don't care where he gets the
post-op, just that he gets it.
Keep him here.
House. You okay?
Yes. We don't need to talk.
Your hand.
That's weird.
I usually don't get the
stigmata until easter.
Please tell dr. Chase the
patient's ready for him now.
Stewart, wake up. It's dr. Cameron.
If you can hear me, blink.
We were concernedfor your safety
so we brought youto the hospital.
No, it's okay.
Why--why?
- No, it's okay.
- Why...
I just wantedto keep you informed.
I didn't want youto have a bad shock
while you were recoveringfrom surgery.
Gotta get outta of here.
It's okay, stewart. Calm
down. Calm down. Stewart.
Stewart,I'm gonna sedate you.
I'm gonnasedate you.
No!
Calm down.
I need some helpin here!
Damn it! Somebody get in here!
What did you do?
well done.
Your patientcalled his
lawyer, threatened to sue us.
He's now heading home
completely undiagnosed.
He'll sooneon his way back.
He's sick. He'll crash.
He'll lose consciousness.
I'll declare an
emergency,bring him back in.
Not anymore you won'T.
His lawyer now holdshis
health care proxy.
The next time we havean emergency, larry
ruseckas, esquire,will be calling the shots.
I made the right call.
If he'd flipped outafter major
surgery, it would've been worse.
The benefit of being bossis
that I don't have to argue.
You're all off the case.
What's going on betweenyou and cuddy?
Bad lovin' gone bad.
Seriously. Why didn'tyou argue with her?
She just threw usoff the case.
Because ignoring heris a lot easier.
Convince the patientto
let us back in again.
See if you can clearhis
blockage with lactulose.
If this thing kills himbefore we can
diagnose, it won't be fun anymore.
Okay.
You gonna keepworking on this?
Yeah. I brought inthe case.
There is no case. He's gone. You've
been tossed. This is totally nuts.
He's incredibly
sick.We don't know--
forget about the patient.
What is going on with you?
This is why we lefthouse'team to avoid
this constant floodof pure craziness.
That's why I left house.
You got fired.
I'm sorry. I know I l you down.
But you know who elseI let down, pretty
much everyonewho's important to me.
My boss, my old boss, my boyfriend.
I did that for you.
I'm not gonnalet you down again.
It's like the red badge of idiocy.
If the confederacy had mosquitoes, we'd all have
southern accentsand I'd be paying foreman less.
She kicked youoff the case.
This is what happens
when you don't address it.
She acts weird,things get different.
You understand that
differentimplies difference.
She's tossed mea million times before.
No, she always chastises you.
And you'd always come
runningto mto complain.
So you're actingdifferent too.
You're scared.
You are scaredto get involved.
How is that "scared"?
It's rational.
Emotionally mature people who
work together should not de.
Guaranteed breakup.
Guaranteed ugliness.
Any relationshipthat doesn't
end in a breakup ends in death.
Everything falls apartin the end.
That's your worldview.
The corollary,which you keep forgetting, is
that you have to grab any chance for happiness.
Why does this matterso much to you?
Cuddy and I are fine.
The only persongetting
worked up here is you.
I don't want youto be fine.
I want you to be happy.I
think if you dated her---
are you familiar with
the adverb "vicariously"?
If I wanted to
ask her out--
you did ask her out.Last
year. Whatever happened there?
I don't know. I wasn't interested.
Wrong. You were interested.
But amber grabbedyour genitals first.
But now you're single, and
that makes you miserable
because you think it's too
soonfor another relationship.
So you're gonnamake me miserable.
Please, get a girlfriend,or
a life, or something.
For me.
Better or worse?
worse. Drugs aren't working.
I think we should do the surgery
in his house like we planned.
Well, then one of uswasn't paying attention because
I thought that surgerything was just a trick.
We prepared the room.
We hung the drapes.
It's probably ten timesas sterile as any
mobile operating theater you'd find in a battlefield.
We still need trapper john.
Chase doesn't wantanywhere
near this surgery.
Maybe you could talk to him.
I can't understanda word he says.
Taub.
Doing anything later?
Blood in the field.
Not where I'm looking.
How am I supposedto know
where you're looking?
Here's a hint. It's the bloody part.
The whole thing's bloody. It's
a guy with a hole in his body.
It's like you've neverdone
this before. Use the ction.
I will.
And in fact I'venever done this before
because I went to med school,not nurse school.
Hey, wanna see if your
client's actually made of money?
Cutting out last piece of bowel.
Suture.
Mucosa's pink.
Flattened villi.
Intestinal atrophy.
It's whipple's disease.
Explains the seizureand
the stomach pain.
Little bleeder here.
Cautery.
Hey,
wait.The gas--
That always happensduring surgery.
Just the gas build up in the blockage.
Nothing to sue about.
Treat him for the burns.
Put him on antibiotics
for the whipple's.
He'll be fine.
That's niceof you.
He doing good?
Uh, burns are healing
fine. He's stable otherwise.
Good. So, uh, I could stayat
your place tonight if you'd like.
I can'T.
Well, you're not gonna sleep here again.
You might have
noticedthe lack of nurses.
Because you're not on the case.
You can't really use thatas an excuse...
- dr. Cameron!
- Wait here.
Your stomach?
My legs are numb.
I can't feel them at all.
New symptom. Peripheral neuropathy. Got
worse on antibiotics. It's not whipple'S.
- porphyria.
- liver's fine.
Amyloidosis.
We would've seen iton the intestines.
What did we seeon the intestines?
Pink mucosa, flattened villi.
It's not whipple's,
it's gotta be celiac.
Wheat allergy meanshe's
not absorbing nutrients.
Explains the seizures,stomach,
and now the nerves.
we should run a blood test for celiac.
Not fast enough. Not accurate enough.
Force-feed him wheat then do an
endoscopy as it hits his duodenum.
See if there's an allergicreaction.
His guts just exploded.
It might be a tad
painfulto make him eat.
That's house's point.
There's nothing diagnostic about it.
He's trying to put the patient
in pain, force him to come in.
It is a lid test.
So is the blood test,which is painless.
foreman, listen to that little voice in
your head that's comingfrom the telephone.
Force-feed him.
Don'T.
You know house. You know I'm right.
We'll do both tests.
I'm not here to play matchmaker.
Okay.
House basically...
well, he accused me of
being interested in you.
Oh, he's just tryingto
change the subject.
I know. But I do have...
I've always... had...
some feelings for you.
Are you sayingyou want to date me?
No. I-I--it wouldn'tbe fair to
house and it's too soonafter amber.
But you thoughtyou should just say it.
Yeah. I thought you should know.
Let's have dinner tomorrow night.
Okay.
Or maybe it would be
betterif we just... had sex.
Pardon me?
In front of house's office.
I mean, I don't want to take any chances.
I assume the point of
thisis to make him jealous
and make him realizethat he
does want a relationship with me?
Yes.
You think it'll work?
You're an idiot.
Trust me.
Everybody will be happier
if house and iaren't dating.
You sure this is the best test?
No. But you've kindof tied our hands.
Soon as this hits your intestines,
I'll look at it through an endoscope.
Stewart, I know you don't
want to talk about this, but...
people who get shotoften get ptsd.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
It's very treatablewith
drugs and therapy.
It's not ptsd.
My girlfriend was with mewhen
I got shot and she died.
I'm sorry.
But that's what I mean.
I lost someone myself.
I know it's traumatic.
No, what--what--what I'm
tryingto say is that...
I was like thisbefore the shooting.
Sie I was a kid.
Everything was hard for me.
I--I didn't go outthat
much. And--and when I did...
I had panic attacks.
Like physical pain.
No, it was, like, worse.
It was like I was dying.
Then I met angela.
She was the only reason
that I ever wantedto go out.
But then she died. And...
Blood test will be done soon.
I'm guessing that's a new technique.
Hey, you remember that idea that cameron had about
trying to torture the patient into admitting himself?
Pretty sureit was your idea.
You want me to slow down the test?
Everyone's got all
thesegreat ideas today.
So you're thinking patient won't leave because leaving
causes pain, so we gotta make staying more painful.
That actually makes sense.
You'll increase his pain, but
not enoughto make a difference.
He's on morphine.
He's on morphine now.
Pretty soon he'll beon less-phine.
'Cause when you restock, you'll actually
be givingcameron iv bags of saline.
And why do you thinkI'll be doing this?
Same reason you didthe surgery.
That was becauseit was an emergency.
No.
It was because your
marriageis falling apart.
When you confess adultery,
things tend to go bad.
When one part of your life does a titanic,
you make a life raft out of whatever's left,
which makes your jobmore significant,
which is why you didthe surgery,
why you pulled an all-nighter,
and why you'll do this.
She's having me sleepon the couch.
Just for a few nights.
I'm not doing thisto save my job.
I'm doing this to savehis life.
Right. That's what we'll telleveryone.
Have you considered that it's not my place
you really want to be walkinginto right now?
Ric ocasek would kill meif
I-- oh, you mean cuddy.
Yeah, she's a little nuts.
But she's beautiful,smart, funny,
and most important,she can stand you.
Yeah. I came here to
haveyou lecture me on cuddy,
not because there'sa killer mosquito
chasing me aroundmy apartment.
House,there is no mosquito.
This is all about cuddy.
Ah, she's bugging me.
Poetic.
Have you seen this bug?
Have you seen this bite?
No. What I've seen is a suppurating wound that you've
scratched and mutilated into a gangrenous state.
Delusional parasitosis.
I am not imagining things.
House, you'rea drug addict.
You're alwaysimagining things.
You got bitten the night you kissed her.
Your itching always gets
worsewhen you think about her.
You need to address this.
She's my boss.
No, you're not afraid of authority.
You're afraid she
actuallyis right for you.
You're afraidto take a chance
because it's too biga chance.
If it doesn't workwith her, then
maybe there'sno one out there.
I am not rationalizing.
I'm better off alone.
Also, you seen her assrecently?
You're not staying here.
- Oh, come on.
- No. You can go home.
Or you're goingto cuddy's,
gonna ring her doorbell,
and you're gonna ask herout on
a date like regular people do
at 3:00 in the morning?
- When do regular people
sleep? - Buh-bye.
Is he in enough pain to come in yet?
No.
Antibody tests back?
Inconclusive.
Then why are you here?
I missed you.
Endoscopy?
Inconclusive.
Well, then do it again.
I know it sucks, but I need
to test your stomach again.
it's really hurting.
I know. I'm sorry.
Try to get youon your back
and have you open your mouth.
I can't...
He's out. Anything?
No pulse. Start cpr.
Get the paddles. Get the
paddles! Who are you calling?
Pizza. You like anchovies?
I'm calling the lawyer.
Genuine emergency.
- He'll okay admission.
- He's dying.
Exactly.
Sorry to wake you.
Your introvert is having a heart attack.
If we don't restart his heart...
he can survive 15
minutes on oxygen and cpr.
We can get himto the hospital in five.
Lawyer says yes. Continue cpr.
2123 holden green. Patient with P. E. A.
- Clear.
- Wait!
I got a pulse.
Cancel the ambulance.
He's stable enoughto stay here.
his heart's back to sinus
rhythm, but it's bradycardic.
Taub's putting ina temporary pacemaker.
It'll keep his heartbeating for now.
hey, cameron, how would
you likeyour old job back?
I'm asking 'cause it'sthe
only way I can fire you.
Sorry.
In er, we like to actually resuscitate
dying people, not just let them flop around.
Could be lymphoma.
We'd have seen iton the abdomen.
It has to be a poison.
Organophosphates.
we checked the place over and over.
It's completely clean.
There are rose petals in the front entry.
Unless he's eating a
bouquet a day, he couldn't--
- how clean?
- Very.
He probably has a little ocd.
How often do you wash your tub?
Every couple days.
Bleach and ammonia?
Yeah.
You know how kids play
toy soldiers in the bath?
He likes to re-enact the battle of
ypres three times a week with real gas.
Ammonia and bleach makes chlorine gas.
Highly fat soluble.
He lost weight after the stomach pain.
Explains why his
symptoms kept getting worse.
Put him on parenteral
steroids and sodium bicarbonate.
even if you're right, that external
pacemaker's gonna fail eventually.
And I don't have the skillsto
put in a permanent one.
Well, maybe the poison
hasn'tcompletely shot his heart.
And you won't haveto feel
guilty for the rest of your life.
How am I gonna place the leads in the exact
spot on the right ventricle without fluoroscopy?
The force?
Taub put in the temporary one.
You can do that playing pin
the tail on the donkey.
Permanent pacemakers need precision.
So we can use the portable x-ray.
It's not real time.
Sonogram.
And what happens when I put him into v-tach
because the sonogram isn't precise enough?
He's dying.
Exactly why I don'twant
to be the one to kill him.
Thanks.
You knew I'd haveto say no.
But you came anyway.
You just wanted a
reasonto be angry at me.
- If there's something
wrongbetween us, then-- - forget it.
You know whywe spend nights at my house?
Because when we spend themat yours...
I could tellyou didn't want me there.
Why would I keepinviting you
over if I didn'twant you there?
You always kicked me outevery morning.
You never offered me a drawer.
You never cleared outyour closet for me.
I was just a visitor.
How long have you feltlike this?
From the start.
I know it's hard for youbecause
you lost your husband, but...
I can't keep chasing youforever.
I just tried your house. Where are you?
Clubbing. Good or bad?
Bad. Vitals are dropping.
The abdominal painkeeps getting worse.
Means we were too
latewith the treatment.
Tell the lawyerhe's off the clock.
We're done.
You're giving up?
Call taub.
Tell him to pick upsome morphine.
There's no needfor the
patient to be in pain.
He's on morphine.
No. He's on saline.
I figured you put himon saline
so I switched him backto morphine.
I love you.
When you reach
puberty,give me--
his abdominal pain.
That was on morphine?
Yes.
Is there something that causes abdominal
pain that doesn't respond to morphine?
I was right.
He is being poisoned.
What's this density on his hip?
Just bone.
Think less boney.
You think he's got lead poisoning?
Explains the constipation,
the nerves, seizes.
Hold him down.
You're not gonna feela thing...
except excruciating pain.
The mugger used hollow points.
They explodedand left fragments.
Your doctors missed a couple
hiding behind your hip bone.
It's no biggie.
Except years later, they started to dissolve,
and then, biggie, you started to dissolve.
I'll start him on chelation.
The agoraphobia,could it--
no.Lead wouldn't have started to
disintegrate till years after.
But it could have exacerbated the fear.
I don't need to change.
I know you think that.
But your lifecould be better.
You--you--you'dhave
choices.
He's lying.
About what?
About everything. About his life.
He doesn't even think he's
happy here. He's miserable.
- I've got everythingI need.
- Yeah?
Well, then why did taub find rose
petals in your entry hallway?
Struck me as a little weird.
Thought it might be medically relevant.
But it actually just told
me that you were pathetic.
The day you crashed in your entry way...
was your girlfriend'sbirthday.
You weren't there for the mail.
You were trying to golay
flowers on her grave.
Yeah, he's got ptsd.
Yeah, he's agoraphobic.
He's also a coward.
You want to change
your life, do something.
Don't believe your own rationalizations.
Don't lock yourself
up,pretend you're happy.
You were right. About my
husband. It affected me.
It still affects me.
If you're saying you'll
never be able to--
I cleaned out a drawer for you.
Like a big one.
* Im in love with a girl *
* Finest girl in the world *
* I didnt know I could feel this way *
* Think about her all the time *
* Always on my mind *
* I didnt know about love *
* All that a man should do is true *
* Im in love with a girl *
* Finest girl in the world *
* I didnt know this could happen to me *
www.tvsubtitles.net