I want to reassure you,
your child can have
a completely normal life.
How can a baby have
male and female DNA?
It's a condition called
genetic mosaicism.
The ambiguous genitalia
can be surgically repaired.
Repaired?
Made to look more...typical.
More typical?
But you haven't even told us
if the baby's a boy
or a girl.
That's...
that's a choice you
have to make.
Nice job, Jackson!
Whoo!
Take it.
He had the shot.
He lost his nerve.
Honey, it's okay.
He's doing great.
Three.
No fear that time.
Whoo!
Melanie.
Oh, my God.
Jackson!
Black heels or the boots?
You know I'm a fan
of those heels.
Boots it is.
For all we know,
House knows you're a fan
of those heels.
You think House
is gonna figure out
we faked our break-up
because of your shoes?
Go with the boots.
Gonna eat that?
Have at it.
Did you just ask
my permission
before you took my food?
Yes, we can.
Adolescent genetic mosaicism.
Collapsed during
a basketball game.
Presenting with persistent
pelvic pain.
Fun.
The parents haven't told
their son
that he could've been
their daughter.
They want assurance
that you won't either.
Less fun, but still.
That was easy.
Our new patient.
Part girl,
part boy.
All 13's dream date.
Severe pelvic pain
started during
a basketball game.
Could be dehydration.
ER gave him fluids
when he came in.
Still it feels chronic.
We've got a kid
who could mate with himself,
and we think he didn't have
enough to drink?
There are dozens
of intersex disorders.
Persistent pelvic pain
could mean
congenital adrenal hyperplasia,
PMDS--
Those conditions occur
in intersex kids
who are chromosomally
XX or XY.
Not XX and XY.
Parents recently started him
on testosterone.
Maybe there's some--
Vitamins wouldn't cause
pelvic pain.
There's a note in here.
We're supposed to refer
to his testosterone shots
as vitamins.
His parents aren't just liars.
they want us to be liars too.
I won't do it.
You guys will, though.
He's a kid.
Parents don't think
he's ready to deal with it.
My dad was the same way
about me
maybe having Huntington's.
Well, that was your experience.
It should surely apply
in this situation.
Pain could be caused
by a blind uterus
hidden in his abdomen.
He needs an MRI.
Right.
Boy with girl genes.
I'm sure you're the first doctor
brilliant enough
to check for a uterus.
He could have complications
from the surgeries
on his penis.
That can cause pelvic pain.
Way to multi-task.
Impress your boss
and humiliate your Ex.
MRI is a waste of time.
To continue the humiliation,
you'll put a camera
up his penis.
You're Dr. House,
aren't you?
What do you think's wrong
with our son?
These people were just coming
to tell you.
This is better.
Don't have to worry
about them losing their way.
We think that he has
a blind uterus.
He should have an MRI.
Did you send 'em a text?
Over the past 13 years,
we've educated ourselves.
Who needs med school
when you got Wi-Fi?
Let's schedule their son
for an MRI with contrast
right away.
Thank you.
- Thanks.
You said an MRI
was a waste of time.
So is arguing with them.
Contrast's in.
Jackson,
we're gonna get started,
so try to lie still.
How long do you think
the post-break-up awkwardness
is gonna last?
Foreman and I are both
professionals.
Stomach and liver are clear.
If by professional you mean
he's a T-1000 build
by cyberdyne systems.
I never understood what
you saw in him.
He's not really your type, huh?
Moving down through
the pelvic floor.
Here's my impression
of Foreman
on the happiest day
of his life.
Now the saddest day
We just broke up.
I'm not quite ready
to mock him yet.
House was a jerk
to split you two up.
But, bottom line,
he did you a favor.
Area around the intestinal tract
is clear.
No blind uterus.
I think there's something wrong
with House.
Who's he making miserable now?
Actually no one.
He okay'd an MRI
just because the parents
wanted to look
for a blind uterus.
There was no fighting,
no arguing.
He just went along.
It's a valid medical theory.
He doesn't think it is.
House decided to humor
these parents.
Maybe he had
a great cup of coffee.
Or a tremendous bowel movement.
Bottom line is your boss
is in a good mood.
Stop analyzing it
and just enjoy it.
We're gonna use this scope
to fill your bladder
with saline.
Then examine your urethra
for any narrow spots.
Why would there be
a narrow spot?
Sometimes it just happens.
Can my parents come in?
Sure.
I thought it'd be awkward
for you having them here.
I have this feeling
they've seen me naked before.
Now take a breath.
Just try to relax.
Mom.
It's okay, honey.
It's okay.
Hey, remember those sprints
they made you run in practice?
Those were so hard.
But you pulled through.
You can do this too.
I'm to the bladder.
Start the saline.
I'm gonna look around
and pull back on the scope.
Feels tight.
That pressure's normal.
Just try to hold on
for a few more minutes.
It's not down there.
It's my chest.
Can't breathe.
Can't bre--
can't breathe.
Is he okay?
Muffled heart sounds.
Jugular's distended.
Pericardial effusion.
We need ten gauge
on a syringe.
What's happening?
His heart is filling
with exudate.
If we don't drain it,
it'll stop beating.
We drained the fluid
from his pericardial space.
His heart rate is back
to normal.
Pelvis plus heart.
Doesn't fit with any
of the syndromes
associated with mosaicism.
Could be drugs, toxins,
an infection.
You're okay with this?
With what?
That we're considering
a diagnosis unrelated
to this kid being a shemale.
Assuming a coincidence
like that would usually
torture you
but you're completely unfazed.
Completely unfazed?
You think I'm totally lacking
in any fazing?
The idea that I'm anything less
than half-fazed
I actually find offensive.
It greatly fazes me.
He started testosterone--
Vitamins.
A few months ago.
That can cause autoimmune
diseases
like polyarteritis
and SLE
which can cause
pericardial effusion
and pelvic pain.
So it is related.
Now I'm unfazed.
Start him on corticosteroids
for the autoimmune.
Finasteride to block
the vitamins.
You slept with House.
He asked permission
before taking my bagel.
Took the case without a fight.
Honored the parents' request
for an MRI.
Yes, those were my terms
for sleeping with him.
He's in a good mood.
Sex with me would explain that.
But it doesn't explain
why I'm not curled up
in a ball weeping in shame.
I did not have sex with House.
If you two aren't keeping
something from me,
that means he's keeping
something from both of us.
That can't be good.
Or he's just in a good mood.
This is not a crisis.
Maybe you can get back
some of that money he owes you.
Hmm.
Testosterone blocker?
Does that mean if Jackson
has SLE
or whatever
that other thing was,
that he'd had to go off
the hormones?
Probably.
Then Jackson'll stop
developing.
He'll never go through puberty.
Maybe this isn't what's wrong
with him.
Maybe the testosterone
didn't cause it.
Yeah, but if it is,
then he'll never be a man.
Did we make the wrong choice?
You'll need to tell him
the testosterone blocker
is something else.
Or maybe this is
a good opportunity
to tell him the truth.
It might make it simpler.
For all of you.
You want us to tell
a sick adolescent boy
that he's really not
an adolescent boy?
That...doesn't
seem simpler to me.
No.
Just...
give him the meds.
So you have pain
in one arm and both your legs.
does it hurt right now?
No.
It's when I, like,
put pressure on them.
See...
it hurts when I do this.
Ow.
And this.
What about this?
Aah!
Ow!
Did you give House the moron
with the broken finger?
They've been in room two
about ten minutes.
Patient should've been screaming
for another doctor
seven minutes ago.
Thanks, Brah.
If I have this IV,
why do I need a shot too?
Just some extra medicine.
Just to be safe.
I hear you're quite
the basketball player.
What position?
Point guard.
Small forward.
How's your crossover dribble?
It's okay.
Not really that into basketball.
Gonna feel a little pinch,
okay?
So if you're not that into it,
why did you join the team?
My mom kind of made me do it.
My parents were the same way.
Always pushing me
to try new things.
It's more like what
she didn't want me to try.
I--I wanted to take dance.
She flipped out
and made me choose
between basketball and hockey.
What does your dad say?
He seemed okay with it.
Then he just caved in
to my mom.
Your palm is red.
What does that mean?
That we still don't know
what's wrong with you.
You were right.
He is in a good mood.
Bummer it didn't work out
with you and Thirteen.
It happens.
You guys seemed happy together.
It's probably for the best.
You know, the bisexual thing
and all.
It was never an issue.
No, it never is.
Until it is.
This is Thirteen.
Before you guys
got together,
she was hooking up
with a different girl
every night.
Long term, you really think
you could compete with that?
House, wake up.
We have to talk.
Stop pretending to be asleep.
We're not leaving.
House.
What's going on?
He's not breathing.
Can you get a pulse?
Barely.
Call a Code.
Get an ambu bag
from the nurse's station.
Heart still working means
synapses are still firing.
We just need to get
a message through.
Aah!
You stopped breathing.
What the hell is going on?
I think my penis
stopped breathing.
Do you know CPR?
Looks like your brain
is okay.
Pupils are equal, round,
and reactive.
I'm fine.
Other than the fact
that my nurple is now purple.
No wonder you broke up
with him.
I'm surprised yours
are still attached.
By the way,
I could see that from here.
I assume those are
our patient's lab results.
The patient can wait.
You could've died.
The only reason you'd ignore
a near-death experience
is you don't care
or you already know
why it happened.
It's called Vicodin.
I took too many.
Can I please
get some information
about our patient?
Patient's palms are red.
Lab tests confirmed liver
and kidney dysfunction.
I don't remember you taking
any Vicodin today.
I don't remember hiring
my mother.
What causes the enzymes
in little boy George's
existing heart problem
and pelvic pain?
You didn't take any yesterday
at breakfast either.
I don't remember having
breakfast with my mother.
Amyloidosis
with systemic involvement.
Protein levels are normal.
This kid's depressed.
If he's self-medicating
with drugs and alcohol,
that'd explain his symptoms.
Search the school.
Search the home.
Seriously?
Or are you just deflecting?
Both.
Where are you going?
Nowhere.
I'm staying right here.
So we can properly discuss this.
He's on heroin.
How can you--
Number one--
He's happy,
which means he's high.
Number two--
when he moved his bad leg,
he didn't use his hands
to support it.
Whatever he's taking,
it's stronger than Vicodin.
What are we gonna do?
You really think House
took too many Vicodin?
Guy pops 'em like candy.
I'm surprised it hasn't happened
before.
You miss sleeping with women?
Excuse me?
Simple question.
Yes.
It's a simple answer.
I'll...check under the bed.
I also miss sleeping
with other men.
And I'm sure you miss sleeping
with other women.
Monogamy is like saying
you're never gonna have
any other ice cream flavor
besides rocky road.
So you're saying
if you don't have pink bubblegum
for a while,
that one day you're gonna
chase down the ice cream truck?
No.
Rocky road is great.
It's a very delicious
and complicated flavor.
I also know that if I have
other flavors,
then rocky road is gonna be left
in the freezer
where anyone can just dip in.
Can we please drop
the metaphor?
Why is this coming up now?
Kutner said the silver lining
of our break-up
was I wouldn't be dumped
for a girl.
There's nothing in here either.
Seems like you're wrong
about this kid having drug
or alcohol--
When did he bring that up?
Earlier today.
Right before--
This morning Taub called you
a robot.
Huh.
Either it's a big coincidence
or...
they're jerking us around.
They know.
And if they know,
House knows.
This is bad.
No.
This is good.
House only has two ways
to handle us still going out.
He jerks us around
or he fires us.
He chose option A.
This is good.
But this is bad.
"I stand alone,
my soul and me,
beneath the mask
that others...see."
His chest is still rising.
He's just screwing with me
'cause Cuddy made me babysit.
"A pain that tears
and bites
"and will not bend.
Only when I sleep
will it end."
Downer.
You sure his chest is moving?
House.
If he's faking, you think
he's gonna come clean
'cause you said his name?
Back off.
Only Thirteen gets
to grab my nipples
this time.
You know, recreating the moment
when you made us
crap our pants isn't actually
all that funny.
That is sweet that
you're worried about House.
Unless the next stanza reads
"Hing to fry my brain
to death,
I smoked some primo
crystal meth,"
I'm not interested.
You can't deny that this kid
may be suicidal.
We're not here
to make him happy.
We're here to diagnose him.
It's an infection.
Swab of the kid's water bottle
turned up toxoplasmosis.
I'll start him on pyrimethamine.
I had no idea he felt
this way.
Is there a therapist here
that you can recommend?
It might help more
if you talked to him.
He's not ready.
If telling him the truth
would help him stop feeling
like this--
If I knew that it would make him
less confused,
I'd tell him right now.
But if she's wrong,
we'd only make things worse.
He obviously senses
he's different.
He's looking for answers.
Every teenager
feels different.
He's sick.
This isn't the time
to spring this on him.
Okay.
When you give Jackson
the antibiotics,
will you please restart
the testosterone?
Sure.
I get House wanting
to jerk me and Thirteen around,
but you guys?
Told you they were still
together.
How do you know?
Noticed you smell like
Thirteen's soap every morning.
You figured it out?
Yes, I'm a little slow.
Maybe someone should
let me know
when I should be insulted.
Then House doesn't know.
Probably does now
that you felt her up
during that last differential.
You noticed this
but House didn't?
Yes, I get it.
He's generally smarter than me.
Can we please move on?
He's not generally smarter
than you.
He's always smarter than you.
Unless...
Hello.
House is on heroin.
Well, that's certainly
an...interesting notion.
It's why his lungs stopped.
It's why he okay'd
the MRI.
It's why he missed...
things he wouldn't
ordinarily miss.
Um, we'll run some tests
and I'll let you know.
He's there, isn't he?
Well, that would certainly
explain
the inappropriate responses.
I--I gotta go.
Okay.
Sorry.
A consult.
When did you order these?
When you were in the bathroom.
I thought a celebration
was in order.
To cheating death.
You off bourbon?
We can get you something else.
I came here expecting
a burger.
Figured I'd have to endure
a little lecture
on moderation.
You never listen,
so why--
Instead, I get a drink.
Nice little serving
of respiratory depressant
on the day that my lungs
stopped working.
You seem fine now.
You don't believe
that I OD'd on Vicodin.
You figure I'm on something
stronger.
And because you can never,
ever assume anything
but the most screwed-up
scenarios,
as far as I'm concerned--
Funny how I'm usually right.
You think that I'm on heroin.
This is your version
of a tox screen.
Because if I am on heroin,
I can't drink that
without risking
another bout
of not breathing.
Well?
Good night.
Another shot?
I'm afraid so.
That looks like the vitamins
my parents give me.
Same red top.
These aren't vitamins.
What is it?
I can't tell you that.
You should ask your parents.
You idiot!
Okay, I admit it.
I have bulimia.
I look good though,
don't I?
Heroin.
Heroin!
House, of all the stupid--
I'm not on heroin.
I just caught you with
your fingers down your throat.
I'm on methadone.
Stupid product.
Heroin without the high.
Yeah, and twice the risk
of death.
But no risk of arrest.
You nearly died.
Today was a fluke.
I nodded off.
Right.
You're safe as long
as you
never sleep again.
Mistime your dose,
you die.
Couple of drinks,
Mix it with the wrong drugs,
you die.
You want to detox
from Vicodin?
Pick something that won't
kill you.
I'm not detoxing.
If you're looking
for something
to help with your pain--
Doesn't help my pain.
It eliminates it.
My leg doesn't hurt anymore.
She completely disregarded
our instructions.
He asked a question.
I was tired of lying.
I didn't tell him anything
about his genetic condition.
I want her removed
from our son's case.
I'm sorry for the position
Dr. Hadley put you in,
but I can't do that.
She's a valuable part
of Dr. House's
diagnostic team.
If he stays on the case,
so does she.
We have to deal with Jackson.
These questions
aren't gonna go away.
He's not ready for this.
Let's hope you're wrong.
I'm sorry. I'll stay away
from their son.
No, you won't.
In about 15 minutes,
you're the only person
that kid's gonna trust.
If he needs a hand to hold,
make sure yours
is available.
So what?
Am I a boy or a girl?
Some of your cells are male...
and some are female.
So basically I'm a freak.
No, no, buddy.
You're just a little different.
You've known this...
Since I was born.
And you never told me.
We didn't want you
to be confused.
So you lied to me.
Oh, please, sweetie,
we were just trying
to protect you.
Don't.
Just leave me alone.
Get out.
Let's go.
You still breathing in there?
'Cause if not,
I'm sending in janitorial.
I'm not breathing.
But it's strictly voluntary.
Should've seen the guy
who was in here before me.
I know about the methadone.
It's legal.
I have a prescription.
Whatever doctor you conned
into writing it
clearly had no idea
about your addiction issues.
Your lack of--
he knows I'm in pain.
What I put in my body
is my business.
You keep taking this,
you could die.
If you'd said that
if I keep doing this
you could die,
then it'd be your business.
I can't sit by and watch you
kill yourself.
As long as you're
in my hospital,
You can't do methadone.
I'll send someone
for my stuff.
That's it?
You're quitting?
You're choosing methadone
over this job?
I'm choosing lack of pain
over this job.
Eventually you have to talk
to your parents again.
No, I don't.
I have this one friend.
He's on my basketball team.
Will.
We hang out a lot.
I really like him.
Now I'm worried that I...
you know, like him.
Maybe I'm supposed to.
Because if I'm really a girl...
Hmm.
Do you feel like a girl?
I like dancing
more than basketball.
Is that what that means?
Jackson...
As hard as it is right now,
at least it's out
in the open.
You don't have to hide
behind a mask.
I found the poem you wrote
in your room.
No matter how bad things get,
killing yourself
is never the answer.
This was an English assignment.
We were supposed to write
a poem
in the style of Sylvia Plath.
You don't feel this way?
I'm sad sometimes.
I don't want to die.
At least, I didn't.
Are these antibiotics
supposed to make you nauseous?
Yeah, they can.
# lifting me up
like a garage door #
# I need to feel it when
the drug starts coming on #
# I know you, lord,
are a jealous lord #
# I know the tablet
is your competition #
# and I need-- # #
We're on our own.
Is he okay?
He's fine.
He's just not here.
Did he quit?
Did she suspend him?
She didn't say.
She just told me
I was in charge
until further notice.
So if we add bloody vomit
to our patient's list
of symptoms.
Surgeon reports the bleeding
was caused
by a gastric fistula
caused by necrotizing
pancreatitis.
She must've told you something.
Nothing that would help us
with this patient.
Heart, liver, kidneys,
and pancreas.
Obviously whatever
this kid's got
is something systemic.
Zollinger-Ellison?
Or systemic scleroderma.
Zollinger-Ellison fits better.
Why?
Can we at least call House?
We can.
I have.
He's not answering.
Put the patient
on proton pump inhibitors.
If he gets better,
it's Zollinger-Ellison.
If not, it's scleroderma.
Zollinger-Ellison
doesn't fit better.
You don't want it
to be scleroderma
Because that means
he's gonna die.
Patients die all the time.
Not the ones whose family
you've ruined.
I don't think that.
You do.
It's not your fault.
He was no more confused
than any other teenager.
Then I started a fire
and threw gas on it.
You were trying to help.
Hi, is House here?
He's getting dressed.
I'll be back around 10:00
tonight.
Go on in.
Okay.
Who was she?
I hired her to watch me sleep.
Make sure I don't stop
breathing.
Home nurses usually wear scrubs.
She's not a nurse.
You hired a hooker
to watch you sleep?
That just can't--
Surprisingly,
hookers are cheaper.
And they don't sue
for sexual harassment.
Which one?
You shaved.
The red one then.
You have two ties?
Meeting at St. Sebastian's
today.
Gonna try and talk 'em
into starting up
a diagnostics department.
Sounds great.
I just came by
to check up on you.
See how you were doing.
I'm fine.
I guess you are.
He hasn't responded
to the medication at all?
I'm afraid not.
So...
That means he's got
the other thing?
I'm so sorry.
We'll start him
on anti-inflammatories.
If we're lucky,
that will slow down
the progression.
My son has a death sentence
and I can't go in there
and be with him
because of you.
I'm sorry.
You find a homework assignment
and decide he's suicidal.
Make it your own
personal mission.
I let my feelings--
Oh, don't you dare apologize.
Like it could absolve you
of what you've done to me,
my family.
He was fine.
I understand why you're angry.
But this isn't where
you belong right now.
He won't let us
in the room.
He's a teenager.
You're his mother.
This is not the time
to start listening to him.
Go be with him.
Thank you.
I didn't do it for you.
We made a mistake.
No, we didn't.
The methadone's good for him.
The methadone
is gonna kill him.
He shaved.
He was wearing a tie.
He has a meeting
at St. Sebastian.
If he buys
a new pair of shoes,
should we let him smoke crack?
Cuddy, he's happy.
House doesn't do happy.
Pain or no pain.
Okay, maybe...
but he's our friend.
And this is his one chance
to not be miserable.
The heels.
Very nice.
No reason not to wear them
now that House is gone.
You okay?
Yeah.
Just tired.
Got some good news.
Patient's scleroderma
is responding
to the anti-inflammatory meds.
His AST level's dropped
a bit.
So he's dying slightly
less quickly than we thought.
That's great news.
I'm not okay.
Next time just say that.
What's his AST?
Uh...185, I think.
That's a pretty fast drop.
Are we sure it's from
the anti-inflammatories?
What else could it be from?
He's been off the antibiotics
for a while.
Proton pump inhibitor's--
He's back on testosterone.
Testosterone wouldn't help
his liver function.
But it could improve
his kidney function
which would also lower
his AST.
But not in kidneys damaged
by scleroderma.
Which means
it's not scleroderma.
I have an interview
in two hours.
Wow.
Hand over my letter
of recommendation.
Mm, sorry,
I haven't done it yet.
You have no right
to sabotage--
I was busy with this.
It's a list of requirements
for your methadone treatment.
Weekly drug tests.
Supervised doses
administered on a precise
schedule by me
or one of the nurses.
Seems weird
getting my meds here
when I'm working somewhere else.
Yes.
I'm offering you
your job back.
I want a raise.
No.
And a bigger office...
but in the same spot.
No.
We both know this is where
you belong.
Okay.
Welcome back.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You okay?
I have issues with authority.
- You?
W-we thought you were gone.
Cuddy missed me.
And what happened
to your cane?
She asked to borrow it
for some reason.
Patient dead or do I need
to do anything?
He's got scleroderma.
It's not scleroderma.
Wow.
Two days,
and you've already got
two separate theories.
You're back. Good.
We noticed a drop
in AST levels.
It's not from
the anti-inflammatory meds.
It's because his kidneys got
better from the testosterone.
Which rules out scleroderma.
When did you two come up
with this?
We ran into each other
in the lobby.
What did we miss?
When I say "we"
I mean "you,"
Since I wasn't here.
We've ruled out
Zollinger-Ellison.
That was a dumb idea.
Why?
Because it was wrong.
Also toxoplasmosis,
dehydration,
SLE, various intersex
disorders.
Oh, crap.
This kid like energy drinks?
I saw some empty bottles
in the team locker room.
But energy drinks
don't explain--
Nice work.
So...we're okay?
Why wouldn't we be?
Nice heels.
This is all
your parents' fault.
Excuse me?
Chug a lot of energy drinks
before, during,
and after practice?
Your son came in here
with simple dehydration.
That's why he collapsed
during the game.
The ER treated him for that.
It didn't help the pain.
That's where the energy drinks
came in.
They put a strain
on his kidneys
so he needed more time
to rebound
from the initial dehydration.
Then why isn't he better?
That's where your idiocy
came in.
Before we could give him
another glass of water,
you two insisted I do an MRI.
So I go down a blind alley
looking for a blind uterus.
And my team injects him
with contrast material.
If his kidneys
had been healthy,
they would've filtered out
the contrast
in a couple hours.
Since they weren't,
they went around and around.
Eventually getting absorbed
by his heart,
his liver,
and his pancreas,
getting in trouble
everywhere it went.
Your son was fine
when he got here.
It was your freaked-out
overprotectiveness
that nearly killed him.
Nearly?
He's young.
A few weeks of dialysis,
he should be fine.
You gave birth
to a freak of nature.
Doesn't mean it's a good idea
to treat him like one.
How you feeling?
A little bit better.
I saw you talking
to your parents earlier.
That's good.
My mom asked if I wanted
to take dance lessons.
That's great.
I'm actually worried
I might miss basketball.
Starting to get good.
There's no reason
you can't do both.
Starting tomorrow,
you'll come to my office
for your fix.
I'm done with the methadone.
I screwed up.
The kids' parents wanted
that MRI.
I knew he didn't need it.
I did it anyway.
That's what got him sick.
You just solved a case
that no one else could solve.
I created a case.
I played nice because
I was in a good mood
because I didn't hurt.
You don't need your pain
to be a good doctor.
I'm not interested in good.
You're afraid to be happy.
Why do you care
if I'm happy?
You're afraid of change.
The one thing you have
is your intellect.
You think if that's compromised,
you have nothing.
Just take it.
No.
Don't do this.
It's already done.
This is the only me you get.
www.tvsubtitles.net