Am I gonna have to give a speech?
- You're the publisher. Can't you do it?
- I can warm them up.
But you are gonna have to get over
this fear of public speaking
before the book tour.
Everybody.
Can I have your attention?
Thank you.
Tim has a few words to say.
There you go, Tim.
They're warmed up.
Well,
what do you say at a time like this?
Seriously, what do you say?
You could thank people for coming.
Thank you, Nick.
Actually, I'm always thanking Nick,
A man not only famous
for his ruthless editor's pen,
but his patient hand-holding
of crazy authors.
You'd think that after three novels,
I'd start to develop
a little confidence, but...
for a book like this,
we are happy to supply the confidence.
Best-seller.
That's not gonna happen.
What?
Come on.
Short stories don't make money.
Short stories weren't making
money back in 1908.
You'd'have to be illiterate
to think they'd do as well as a novel.
Okay, Nick, let's step away
from the champagne
before somebody gets hurt.
You slaved over this book
right next to me.
Why would Northrop even publish
if it's only going to tank.
Have you failed to notice
you're our star author?
Obviously, Elaine wouldn't want
to offend you.
Honey.
I... I'm sorry.
I don't... I don't know
why I said that.
He's joking.
Nick knows as well as anyone
what you have done is art.
Is folding paper into animal shapes,
you don't expect
to make a living off it.
- What is wrong with you?
- You think someone who goes
through 10 assistants a year and doesn't
return her own children's phone calls
would give a damn about the state
of the American short story?
Please, be quiet.
I think something's wrong.
That title was a mistake too.
People are gonna compare you
to Salinger,
and, boy, are you gonna come up
short on that one.
Honey!
Call 911.
Help! We need help!
House - Season 05 Episode 17
"The Social Contract" (v. 0.90)
Synchro: ShalimarFox, mpm, IceFreak
The HTeam's AnonymHouse
Cameron brought this up
from the E.R.
Doesn't look
like a friendship bracelet.
It's Phineas Gage.
The most famous case study
in medical history.
This patient got a railroad spike
drilled through his frontal lobe?
No. No trauma, but he does
have frontal lobe disinhibition.
Just like Gage.
Gage was a different person
after the spike.
Argumentative. Impulsive.
Whereas our guy became
a different person after chardonnay.
He was sober
when they brought him in.
There's also the nosebleed,
the collapse.
- MRI show anything?
- Nothing.
Good.
What fun would that be?
The tumor's not
in the cool neighborhood.
It's cool neighborhood adjacent.
A well-placed tumor in the nasal cavity
eroding into the brain
- could do the damage.
- Go stick a scope up Phineas's nose.
See what you find.
Daddy, I'm always gonna win if you keep
telling me what your cards are.
Well, then suppose
I tell you... while I tickle you.
Mr. Greenwald, I'm Dr. Taub.
This is Dr. Kutner.
We're here for another test.
Sorry about that.
You don't look sorry.
No offense.
- Although you do look kind of cheerful.
- It's a little creepy.
Should I want doctor who's
excited about how sick I am?
- I'm not...
- We're going to put this up your nose,
scan for any problems.
I can assure you that we are
completely unexcited about that.
Excuse me, sweetie.
She has an auditory
processing disability.
Marika-beleeka,
you have to get off the bed.
This might be
slightly uncomfortable.
Honey, do you mind if I step out?
I've to make sure the final arrangements
are in place for the breast cancer walk.
Yeah, you do that. I'll pretend
to be macho while a guy stuffs
three feet of plastic up my nose.
It's too bad it's not your nose.
Lots more room to maneuver.
I guess the walk
can wait ten minutes.
Or in a sensible world, even longer.
Just how does tying up traffic
for six hours stop breast cancer?
You know how it works.
People donate...
Why not spend six hours building
houses for Habitat for Humanity?
Or is it wrong to help
two groups of people at once?
I bet there are those who have
breast cancer and no home.
It's my job, Nick.
- You walked yourself last year.
- To be supportive.
And because I knew you wouldn't
have sex with me if I didn't.
I'm gonna make my call.
Make this go away.
God, that honker really is huge,
isn't it?
Wednesday night.
Low-Down-Blue-Meanie
versus the Incinerator.
I can't.
Let me rephrase.
Low-Down-Blue-Meanie.
I understand monster truck code.
Do you understand "can't"?
Not when it follows
"Low-Down-Blue-Meanie."
Is the world coming to an end
Tuesday night?
- Otherwise, Wednesday...
- All right,
it's not "can't."
It's "don't want to."
The fact is I just don't like
monster trucks.
- Yes, you do.
- No, I don't.
You've always liked monster trucks.
No, you've always liked them.
I've tolerated them.
Seriously, I can only watch
so many hyped-up dune buggies
crush so many motor homes
without feeling the urge
to go see "La Boheme".
And I hate opera too.
What are you hiding?
I'm not hiding it.
I'm saying it loud and proud.
Death to monster trucks.
No nasal cancer.
And no marriage either
if our patient keeps saying
everything that comes into his head
without regard for the consequences.
You always led me to believe
you were one of a kind.
Luckily, jerkiness is
a temporary condition for this guy.
No, it's not.
We may be able to fix
his impulse to say
his thoughts out loud, but he always
gonna be the guy who thinks them.
But he's also gonna be
the guy who doesn't say them.
If he spent his whole life constructing
this nice guy persona,
isn't that as much who
he really is as anything else?
You would argue that.
You're all persona.
I agree with Wilson.
This guy's a Harry Potter.
The sorting hat was going to put Harry
in Slytherin based on his nature.
He refused,
so he ended up in Gryffindor.
Through choice.
There's damage somewhere in his brain.
Find it.
Are you sure you understand?
No, I'm lying.
Except I can't.
You ask me questions.
While I talk,
you look at my brain activity to see
where it's screwed up.
Then you're gonna cut the
screwed up part out to test it.
It's depressing,
but it's not rocket science.
I think he understands.
I don't mean to be abrasive.
Especially since you're such
a pleasure to imagine naked.
- Again, sorry.
- It's okay.
Thank you for understanding.
I'd do you, though.
- Really, my apologies. This stuff...
- It's okay.
House paged.
I would do her in a minute with fudge
and a cherry on top.
Would someone please explain
to this woman?
- There's only so many apologies...
- He has frontal lobe disinhibition.
I've already embarrassed
myself with one doctor,
whom I am at this moment
imagining with you
in a king-sized bed
with a mirror on the ceiling.
I'm so...
so sorry.
But if I couldn't have
both of you together,
you definitely would be
my first choice.
Where's House?
It's like trying not
to think of an elephant.
You're not an elephant. Your breasts,
in fact, are all Homo Sapiens...
House isn't here.
He wouldn't have paged me
if he couldn't
watch and enjoy the...
Your tush is like the pistons
in a Ferrari.
You're welcome.
That was for my benefit.
- You're 40 years old...
- 38.
- The administrator of a hospital...
- Dean of Medicine.
People don't get personal with you.
Except for me, and you dismiss me
as a jerk who's jerking you around.
But that guy can only tell
the truth.
He prefers your body to that
of a smokin' young hottie.
So that was your way
of saying I look good today.
You didn't get
the slightest kick out of that?
Don't be ridiculous, House.
I hope you know
your pistons are second to none.
I'm okay. I'm not jealous
of Cuddy's pistons.
Starting baseline activation.
You sure?
You looked upset.
- What he was saying was obnoxious.
- You've never been called attractive?
- He didn't call me attractive.
- He cast me in his mental porno.
That's what attractive means.
"I'm attracted to you, sexually."
Attracted can also mean "I'm attracted
to the whole package. To who you are."
Slight elevation at transaxial 60.
It could.
It never does. It's what women
choose to hear, not what men say.
Actually, it's exactly what men say
if they have any brains.
We have enough for a baseline.
What can we ask him that's indiscreet,
but that he won't hate us
for knowing?
Nick, do you vote
the same way as your wife?
God, no.
Good. He's spiking at 30.
She believes I voted for Hillary Clinton
in the primary and Obama in the general.
You're thinking I'm secretly
a Republican, right?
Wrong.
I secretly don't vote.
Ever.
Wait, you're 46,
and you've never voted?
Your voice is no longer attractive to me
with that note of disapproval.
Although I'm sure that will pass.
Look at that.
There's a spot in the Cingulate
Gyrus that's not lighting up.
One vote makes a difference?
- Not mathematic...
- We've got what we need.
We can't biopsy that.
It's too close to the brainstem.
Could be neurosarcoidosis.
At least it's treatable.
We give him steroids,
if we're right, we should start seeing
his symptoms improve
within half a day.
What are you looking at?
I find your strong attachment
to a working democracy
to be extremely sexy.
Ooh, you smooth talker.
Do you think my nose is too big?
Relax, he also implied my
bedside manner was a little off.
You don't agree with that, right?
No.
No one's ever mentioned
your nose before?
- You're a plastic surgeon.
- They tell me it suits my face.
- It does.
- Maybe.
Maybe that's just
the social contract.
You tell me I look great,
I tell you you're a people person.
- How can you know the truth?
- You could ask for the truth.
What do you think of my nose?
Please tell me the truth.
It's fine. It's a nose.
Just proving a point.
Anyone sitting here?
Just my persona.
You know, it's amazing the
way people cling onto insults.
Or what they think are insults.
So that wasn't an insult?
I'm not suggesting
that, like our patient,
you hidding a dark sarcastic core.
Beneath a candy shell
of compulsive niceness.
I'm not always nice.
I'm not nice to you.
Because you know nice bores me.
Hence, still nice.
No, I'm suggesting
that you have no core.
You're what whoever you're with
needs you to be.
Okay, I guess
that could be insulting.
The interesting question is why.
Why do you think the world will end
in chaos and destruction
if you're not there to save it?
Because when my parents
put me in the rocket
and sent me here, they said,
"James, you will grow
to manhood under yellow sun."
Why'd you lie about monster trucks?
I didn't.
I checked your appointment book.
You got tomorrow night marked off, but
you didn't put down what you were doing.
You thought someone might look...
I'm playing racquetball
tomorrow night with Taub.
- Why would you hide that?
- Because the world revolves around you.
I devote time to anyone else,
you'd end up stalking me
and harassing them.
You say that
as though it wouldn't be fun.
And maybe I didn't want
to rub your nose
in the fact that we'd be doing
something you can no longer do.
Because I'm nice.
I thought you said the
steroids were gonna help him.
What... is it his heart?
EKG says heart's fine.
It's gotta be the kidneys.
I need to get him on dialysis.
He's on dialysis, and he's stable.
We know it's not systemic sclerosis.
Cyrano de Berkowitz.
Let it go.
Chronic lymphocytic leukemia
could explain brain and kidney problems.
The CBC showed
normal white blood cells.
So how long have you been
playing racquetball with Wilson?
Four, five times.
- Could be diabetes.
- Or a congenital metabolic disorder.
Congenital disorders generally
don't wait till you're 46 to manifest.
So he's a late bloomer.
His daughter has
a neurological condition.
First of all, Wilson played tennis
on his college team,
and you are a Jew.
You're not athletic.
Run to the end of the hall and back.
I'll time you.
Sandy Koufax is Jewish. Greatest
left-handed pitcher of all time.
Sandy Koufax is all you Jews
go on about.
Sandy Koufax and the holocaust.
Gets old.
There are dozens of congenital
conditions that fit our parameters.
We can't spend time gene testing
for all of 'em, especially
when we're only guessing
it's congenital.
Is a z-shot offensive or defensive?
It's both.
You suspected
that was a trick question.
But I could have said neither.
Diabetes makes more sense.
We can narrow the testing down
to 40 likely candidates.
- Test for peripheral nerve damage.
- He's got brain damage.
He's likely to have peripheral
nerve damage no matter what the cause.
That's why we should not
test him for it.
Test the daughter.
Kutner runs the nerve test.
Taub, you might be right
about the diabetes.
Take supper away from our patient
and run a glucose tolerance test.
Oh, and the nurses have been
working so hard.
You can do the blood draws yourself.
They have to be done
every couple hours.
You're punishing me
because you're jealous.
- I'm spending time with your friend.
- That would be petty.
I'm punishing you because you've joined
my best friend in lying to me.
Let me know when you're ready
to confess everything.
These can become either hot or cold.
As soon as it starts to feel
uncomfortable, I want you to tell me.
- There's something wrong with me?
- No, they're testing you to help Daddy.
Yes, what you're doing
is very important.
It's like the better you do,
the better we know your dad is.
I'll start with heat.
I know it's not his fault.
I know what he says is involuntary,
but it doesn't help.
Inside, he's still the same man.
That's the problem.
Apparently he's been thinking
this stuff all along.
Whoever that "same man" is, it's not
the person I thought I was married to.
You okay?
She should be feeling
something by now.
What does that mean?
Is she sick too?
You're burned. Why didn't you tell me
it hurt?
I wanted to help Daddy.
You said the better I do,
the better Daddy has to be.
Sorry.
- I'm starving.
- Only way we can do the test.
Good thing it's you
and not Dr. Hadley.
Could you keep her away from me?
I have a rich imaginative life.
I'd rather not share it.
We all have thoughts.
I know we all have sexual thoughts.
We have ignoble thoughts.
I just don't want those
to be who I am to people,
- especially not to my wife.
- I understand.
I don't think it would be fair
to define me by my passing thoughts.
My real choices are my actions.
And I've never done anything
to hurt her. I've never cheated.
- You're kidding me. You've cheated?
- What?
- Why would you say that?
- Because you look guilty as hell.
Are you serious?
- Of course you're serious.
- Yes, everyone knows.
God, they must think you're a creep.
They might not know.
They might be idiots.
I just say these things.
Why'd you page me here?
I need you to update me
on the patient's condition.
Seems to be dead.
Why'd you page me here?
I need you to update me
on the patient's condition
while hitting this against the wall.
- This is the only place we can do both.
- I finished the last blood draw.
I expect the people who work for me
to rise to a challenge.
Unless they don't expect
to work for me.
Last blood draw was at 6:00 A.M.
Sugar levels never rose
above 120 all night.
So the glucose was normal.
Means you were wrong about diabetes.
I still think it's the endocrine system.
Maybe I just got the wrong gland.
So you're going for thyroid
instead of pancreas?
Makes sense.
Fine.
I'm not playing racquetball
with Wilson.
I was never playing racquetball
I have never played racquetball
with Wilson.
I thought it would be helpful
if a department head owed me a favor.
But it's not worth this.
Not bad.
You put on a good show.
You studied up.
Wilson actually booked a court.
If you were really
a racquetball player,
you'd know that you were holding
a squash racket.
Tell Kutner to do
a thyroid re-uptake scan,
Then go grab a nap
in one of the on-call rooms.
We're taking you to do
a thyroid re-uptake scan.
- We think your...
- I'm not going anywhere
until you explain why my daughter
has a bandage on her hand.
You said you wanted
to run some test.
I'd known it would involve pain,
I'd have said, "hell, no."
It's a mild burn.
Since Marika has a neurological
disability like you,
- we needed to make sure...
- She has no disability.
Nick, you know about her problem
with auditory processing.
"Auditory processing"?
That's code for "I can't stand thinking
my daughter's not perfect."
The therapist said
Marika's test scores...
were indeterminate.
She doesn't have a disability.
She daydreams.
She gets below-average marks in school
because she's below average.
Every parent thinks their child
are above average.
Do you have any idea
what the word average means?
- Somebody has to be under it.
- Nick, shut up.
Honey...
I'm not saying you're stupid.
Your mother's not the sharpest
crayon in the box,
and she does great.
See, this is why I told
your mother to keep you at home.
Didn't want you here.
Marika, wait!
- Get her...
- You're burning up.
And your lungs are full of fluid.
I need 200 milligrams of furosemide
and two milligrams of morphine, stat.
- His temperature is 103.
- Infection.
- The steroids must have forced it.
- What kind It could be anything.
Staph Aureus,
tuberculosis, strongyloides...
Go back to Phineas, get a history.
We've got one.
He hasn't been out of the country.
- Get a detailed history.
- No one at home is sick.
No one at work is sick.
There's no sign of ticks or mosquitoes.
Get a more detailed history.
Ask him again.
And again until he remembers something.
Not you.
Kutner can do it.
You're gonna be busy.
I'm here to invite you to lunch.
Why?
I've been made.
House sent me back to you
as a double agent.
- Anything wrong?
- Eyes are a little red.
There's a shocker.
I haven't had a good night's sleep
since this thing started.
You should get some rest yourself.
That's a good idea.
This is going to take some time.
It'll be pretty exhaustive.
Are you afraid
of what you might say while I'm here?
Are you telling me there's something
worse than what I've already heard?
No, I don't know what I'm gonna say.
I don't know
how I'm gonna hurt you next.
I think we should be around each other
as little as possible right now.
This is pathetic.
I know.
Tell Marika I love her very much.
She understands that.
I don't think she does.
You're just saying that
to make me feel better.
Guy leads a boring life.
They stay home a lot.
No travel, no exotic pets,
no nearby standing water.
You sound pleased about something.
Can we get to that part?
His wife rescues dogs.
Among others, a big Rottweiler
who's taken over the house.
- Our patient hates it.
- Was the wife there to hear is?
Too bad. Keep going.
The dog marks his territory
all over the living room.
I asked what the odds were
that he would have put down
food or drink
where the dog could reach.
He said he put a glass on the floor
while he was fixing the television.
The dog was fixing the television?
- The patient's eyes red?
- I'm thinking Weil's.
Bacterial.
He lucked out.
Start him on doxycycline.
If he improves,
we'll know we were right.
I told Wilson you sent me
to get information.
And now you're telling me.
What does that make you,
a quadruple agent?
He let me print out his e-mails.
Excellent.
Information he wants us to have.
Did he let you print out
his deleted e-mails?
- Then go back there...
- As long as I was sitting there,
I thought I'd print 'em anyway.
Top one's the one you're looking for.
"Writing to confirm Wednesday
at 7:00 P.M."
It's outgoing
to jgonzalez@nymercy.net.
There's a Joan Gonzalez in oncology.
It's a consult.
Secret consult, 7:00 P.M.?
Joan is perky.
You're wrong. There was
a patient file attached.
- Where?
- It was password-protected.
Wilson doesn't password-protect
his patient files.
I'm the only one he'd expect
ever to look there,
and he knows there's only one
patient I'd want to check on.
You think Wilson's sick?
If Wilson had cancer,
there'd be no reason
for him to drive 3 hours
to Manhattan.
He could pull strings here
and get the best treatment.
Six articles by Gonzalez.
"Managing suicidal thoughts
in oncology patients,"
"Suicidal ideation
in children with leukemia."
I don't want to ask this,
but have you ever had reason
to think he might be depressed?
No.
Get out of here.
Your fever's down
and your lungs are clearing.
How long before
this brain thing goes away?
The infection's gone,
but the damage the infection did...
you'll have to live with.
You're telling me you can't fix this?
There's gotta be a way.
We'd need to remove the damaged area
in our Cingulate Gyrus,
- but it's too close to the brainstem.
- You can't risk it.
But I could shop around,
and maybe some better doctors
at a better hospital...
The brain stem controls
the body's involuntary systems.
The slightest mistake
could kill you.
Even if you survive, you may never
be able to breathe on your own again.
You may never...
- I get it.
I know this seems like a lot to deal
with right now.
But people have adapted to living
with all kinds of neurological deficits.
At least we can promise you
it won't get any worse.
Get the hell out of my room.
Your assistant said
that you were out of the hospital,
taking a walk.
Is there an emergency?
I don't know.
Is there?
You never take a walk
unless you've got something
- you need to think about.
- Maybe you just don't have
a good statistical sampling
of my walks.
The other thing you do
when you need to think
is you come to my office.
Apparently, this is something you can
only discuss with Gonzalez at NY Mercy.
Taub. Another graduate
of the House school of being a dick.
Private Dick.
I'd love to stay for the full
inquisition, but I need some hot coffee.
Of course you need hot coffee.
It's 45 degrees outside,
and you left your coat upstairs.
Why?
You're going to tell me
why I forgot my coat?
Once you get outside, the cold
would have reminded you.
You could have come back,
but you didn't.
You chose to be uncomfortable.
Why would someone choose that?
Because they hate themselves?
Has it ever occurred to you
that when I don't share something,
it might not be meant
as a challenge?
It might just mean
that I'd like there to be
one molecule of my life
that goes unexamined
by Gregory House.
Nick Greenwald.
I hear you're the guy in charge.
I'm the patient
with the disinhibition.
If you're here to say thanks,
you're welcome.
- Now go away.
- I'm not thankful. I'm pissed.
All the more reason to go away.
They're talking
about sending me home.
To what? A life where I'll continually
drive away anyone
who might for a second
care about me?
Those are the breaks.
You could operate.
You could die.
So I'm either better or dead?
I'm okay with that.
I've always been kind of a...
an impatient guy.
But I've worked hard
to keep my mouth shut.
I've made my wife happy.
I've made my little girl happy.
I want that back.
Otherwise, it's no life.
I want you to remove
a small problem.
I'm not a neurosurgeon.
But your boss is.
You could assist.
I'm sure you'd like
to add to your resume.
It's too near the brain stem.
- Nobody's gonna touch it.
- Your boss would.
He's an egomaniac. I know
'cause I keep seeing him at the club.
He just needs a little push.
I'm sure by now you've kissed
his ass sufficiently.
Would you like me to phrase it
as "you're politically gifted"?
I can do that.
You want me to help you?
Tell me why.
- Why what?
- Why you care.
The puzzle's solved.
The guy's alive.
The odds of coming out of this surgery
with that same status aren't that great.
My patient has
a quality of life issue.
He says awful things.
Hardly a medical condition.
When he leaves here,
he's going to lose his family.
He's gonna alienate
the people he works with.
And if he ever finds a friend
who's willing to put up
with his crap,
he'll be lucky.
Until he drives them away too.
I'll see what I can do.
You've apparently got
this whole coat thing backwards.
I may have overreacted.
You definitely overreacted.
- I knew you'd meet me halfway.
- It made me think.
You only snap on one subject:
losing people.
So I went back to the intel.
It's true there's only one doctor
named Gonzalez at New York Mercy,
but there's a Javier Gonzalez
who's a nurse in the psych ward.
And who could you lose
who'd end up there?
Maybe the reason I don't always open up
to you is because it's redundant.
Daniel wilson.
Once you got a name,
it's amazing how much stuff
you can learn on the phone.
I mean, if you're a doctor
and you lie freely.
They found your brother sleeping
in the lobby of an office building
in Manhattan.
Got aggressive
when they asked him to leave,
and the cops took him
to the Mercy psych ward.
There have been new anti-psychotics
developed since he ran away.
He's been on them for
a couple of days. And by tonight,
he should be in shape to talk to me.
But you're not sure if he wants to.
I'll be in New York in a few hours.
I guess I'll find out.
Why wouldn't you tell me this?
House, you and I...
We don't have
the normal social contract.
I don't expect you
to tell me the lies...
I am fully capable of lying to you.
I've lied plenty of times.
I mean, collaborative lies.
Giving someone a hand who maybe
needs to deceive themselves
just a little.
For two days I've been thinking about
how Danny's gonna react when he sees me.
If I said that to anybody else,
they'd say,
"don't worry.
It'll all be all right."
You wouldn't.
Because it might
all go horribly wrong.
Yeah.
Yeah, it might.
In which case,
you might want some company.
Your heart's beating.
First hurdle past.
Now we need know
if you can breathe for yourself.
Oh, thank god.
Now, do you know who you are?
Nick Greenwald.
Former S.O.B.
Thank you.
Now I can go back to my beautiful
life with my beautiful wife.
Maybe she'll stop whining
and cut me some slack
now that I've risked my life.
Doesn't make sense.
We removed the problem.
We removed the damage. Maybe
we were wrong about the problem.
I need to believe
we can get through this.
Temperature's 94.5.
Do you really think i'm stupid?
Honey, you're not stupid.
You'just...
Please don't do this.
- Could be the surgery.
- Do you respect me,
Nick, what do you think of
what I do for a living?
I think people who publicize
important things
are people who can't do
important things themselves.
Honey, stop.
- Don't.
- Do you regret marrying me?
- 94.2.
- Sometimes.
- Everybody wonders...
- Get me a heating blanket.
- Do you even love me?
- Yes.
I don't know why.
Wait.
Let me...
V-tach. Get me the paddles.
Clear.
Echo says his heart
is structurally fine.
But his temperature is still dropping.
He's headed for hypothermia.
I can't reach House.
It just goes to voicemail.
We were wrong about infection.
His temperature's going
up and down because something's
playing with his thermostat.
Which means the brain
damage is spreading.
What causes brain damage and nose bleed,
involves the lungs, heart and kidneys?
Cancer?
We could text him.
It's not cancer.
Normal psa, normal blood smear,
colonoscopy normal.
- Do a full body scan.
- House hates full body scans.
- House isn't here.
- House is right.
Everybody's got 3 or 4 meaningless
anomalies that'll come up on a scan.
Chasing each one will take time
we don't have.
Feel free to send him an im.
You told me
you saw your brother once.
After he disappeared.
13 years ago.
I used to go to Princeton
whenever I could.
I must have hit every
homeless shelter in town.
And then one day,
I'm just sitting at this deli,
having a sandwich,
I look out the window,
and there he is.
He was gone
by the time I got outside.
That's why you were so eager when
I told you there was a job at Princeton.
I thought it was just my charm.
That's the team.
Shouldn't you answer?
They already texted me to say
they're doing something stupid.
- There's a small abdominal aneurysm.
- Irrelevant.
- What else you got?
- Cyst in the pleura around the lungs.
Also irrelevant.
Couldn't cause any of the symptoms.
There's a density in the liver.
Could be vascular malformation.
If he's got multiple avms, screwed-up
blood flow would explain everything.
We can only spot
them with angiography.
We'll have to do targeted scans with
contrast and then embolize each one.
- Can we do that before he freezes?
- We'll find out.
The spell-correct on Kutner's phone
has got a hair trigger.
Either that, or the patient has
a cyclone in
the floral of his lungs.
You took a walk
in 45-degree weather,
and you left your coat behind.
Go ahead.
I think you were punishing yourself.
I think you wanted to feel what it would
be like be homeless a New Jersey winter.
That tells me guilt.
That tells me something happened.
The schizophrenia started
when he was a teenager.
When he was in college.
He was on meds,
but he'd still think a professor was
out to get him because he got a b,
or he'd fight with his roommates
because he never showered.
- Where were you?
- Med school.
He called me every day.
Talked for hours.
I didn't have hours.
Interesting.
Later for that.
Go on.
I was tired of being the guy
that everybody counted on,
so one night, Danny called...
One night, Danny called, crying,
upset about something.
I had to study for an exam.
So I...
I hung up...
Took my things.
Went to the library so I wouldn't
have to hear the phone ring.
I wonder how that turned out.
My mother called me the next day.
Danny had run away
and left his meds behind.
Which I knew meant
that he would never be able
to choose to come back,
because he'd be so detached
from reality.
So you made your one effort
to live a normal, selfish life
and the universe immediately
smacked you down.
And because we're wired to find
meaning in semi-random events,
you decided never
to be that careless again.
You don't think that's
a little facile?
Actually, I don't.
I think you did it consciously.
You developed your...
people-pleasing talents
the way an olympic athlete
develops his muscles.
Talk about an overreaction
to a single event.
It was a pretty big event.
Hanging up the phone?
That's what you're
blaming all this on.
That's the behavior you've been
trying to correct.
As though nothing else went wrong
in your brother'life.
Of course,
he overreacted too, but...
His glucose was normal.
We're not talking about
my brother anymore, are we?
It's House.
Adms don't explain his glucose.
Since this is significant moment
in my life and all...
Yeah.
- I think I'll just go in then.
- Explain that.
Right.
You'd given him steroids. His
glucose should have been elevated.
That wannabe cyst you found
in the whole body scan,
without the glucose,
it's an irrelevant cyst.
With the glucose,
it's a relevant fibroma.
He has doege-potter syndrome.
His fibroma is secreting
human growth hormone,
which acts like insulin,
lowering his glucose.
It doesn't explain the organ failure
or the brain damage.
This whole thing is an overreaction.
That one small fibroma.
It's benign, but his body's acting
like it's an invader.
His antibodies went
to war against it
and got carried away,
attack his other systems.
Take out the fibroma,
he'll be a happy hypocrite
again in no time.
Maybe I should call a cab.
Your wife's probably just late.
Yeah.
I'm...
sorry about...
You know...
The things I said.
I have a...
conspicuous nose.
It suits your face.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Traffic.
I have some good news.
I was gonna tell you,
and then you got sick.
It didn't seem like the best time.
I've been offered a better position.
I'd be coordinating cancer
awareness walks in three cities.
That's great.
Congratulations.
I know you've worked hard for this.
Thank you.
Is Marika okay?
I'm sure she's moved on.
Kids are so resilient.
You okay?
I'll be seeing Danny
again next week.
- I'd like you to meet him.
- Sure.
He sounds interesting.
Go on.
I thought seeing him again
would change everything.
It would be wonderful or terrible.
Instead...
We're just strangers.
It's kind of anticlimactic.
Which is better than terrible.
Go on.
Does it bother you...
that we have no social contract?
My whole life is one big compromise.
I tiptoe around everyone like
they're made of china.
I spend all my time analyzing: what
will the effect be if I say this?
Then there's you.
You're a reality junkie.
If I offered you a comforting lie,
you'd smack me over the head with it.
Let's not change that.
No, see, this...
If you were implementing
the social contract,
you'd say that,
but only because...
It makes me feel better...
It is kind of fun
watching you torture yourself.
Do you think things will
work out with my brother?
No.
But when it does go wrong,
it won't be your fault.
Thanks, House.
You do actually like monster trucks.
Absolutely.
The HTeam's AnonymHouse
www.tvsubtitles.net