You have a patient waiting.
See?
- I'm waiting for a follow-up.
- If you're talking about Mr. Casdin,
he has a "deceased"
sticker on his file,
as do all the other follow-ups
you have scheduled for today.
I had colds all winter.
Well, I've been in this room awhile,
but it's spring now, right?
I feel run-down
like maybe something big
is coming on.
Run-down.
Come on, give me something.
- Sore throat?
- No.
- Runny nose?
- No. I know it sounds weird,
I'm a nurse, but could you run
maybe a CBC or thyroid up.
Dr. Cuddy, I need a consult.
Until she stops seizing,
I may as well go back to my office
and get my diagnosis on.
She's urinating on herself.
She's having a seizure.
If she hadn't peed...
It's green.
Interesting.
House - Season 5 Episode 18
" Here Kitty"
Synchro: ShalimarFox, mpm
The HTeam's AnonymHouse
35-year-old woman.
Head of nursing at an old-age home.
Neurological symptoms and "P"?
Oh, green pee.
I get it.
Nice.
"Neuro" is also written in green.
Does that mean she has green
neurological symptoms as well?
From now on,
I'm gonna use two colors.
- Green indicates irony.
- Pseudomonas infection.
She'd have a fever.
Toxins?
Why are we taking this case?
Welcome, your lordship.
We were just preparing
your morning briefing.
Sorry I'm late.
And, yes, green pee does meet
the only diagnostic requirement
you care about, it's interesting.
But is it worth us taking this case?
"Us" aren't taking anything.
I'm taking.
You're accepting.
Okay, I accept.
She has adult-onset epilepsy,
and she really likes
those St. Patrick's day beers.
Go check out the house and the office
for toxins and infections.
Her neuro exam was normal.
No subsequent seizures.
It's not life-threatening.
It's not important.
Luckily neither are you.
You okay?
I'm fine.
You and House this morning,
the way you were arguing.
Airing disagreements
doesn't qualify as arguing.
Come on, man.
I'm just trying to help.
We're friends.
There are 400 Japanese teenagers
you were playing Halo with last night
you're better friends with.
Your avatar should ask
their avatars how they're doing.
I consider you a good friend
even if we don't hang
that much outside work.
- I wasn't arguing with him.
- You kinda were.
Fine, I was.
And you know what, I was right.
You got conned.
Methylthioninium chloride.
Notable side effect, green urine.
She's a nurse. She knows the dosage.
Knows how to fake a seizure.
She pees pea soup and gets
the warm attention of doctors
all week long.
She's a Munchausen,
and you're her mark.
So you're insight
is based on discovering
an anti-alzheimer's drug
at an old-age home.
No reason
it'd be sitting in her desk.
You ever tried to pee on yourself
in public? It's not easy.
Sorry, I rushed the jewish frat.
We peed in private.
For good reason.
I can spot a fake seizure.
Which means this was real.
Which means...
her problem is phenol.
Carbolic acid?
Yeah, maybe she
accidentally inhaled some
at a gout treatment facility
circa 1890.
It's still in some
antiseptic throat sprays.
She's been chugging it
all winter for her colds.
Phenol explains the seizure
and the urine.
She'd have to drink 5 bottles a day.
I'm sure you won't have trouble
discovering evidence of it
when you search her house.
Bye.
And you can start her on
charcoal hemoperfusion
for the phenol poisoning.
Seriously?
You were lying
about the throat spray.
That does make more sense.
So why are you wasting Taub's time?
I don't want him to know that
I'm wasting my time disproving
his fake seizure theory.
Zip.
Chris?
Chris Taub, right?
Neil Zane.
I was two years under you
at Collegiate High, remember?
Sure.
So you're some big doctor here now?
I'm a doctor.
You?
I was speaking at an Econ course
over at the University.
I tripped and banged my leg.
I have some time.
Come with me.
Hi.
Tests back?
Head CT was negative.
What about a thyroid up take
or abdominal ultrasound?
Sure.
How'bout I flash some lights
in front of your face first?
You want me to have another seizure?
We're gonna have to give up the room
unless we can confirm a problem.
Okay.
Damn it.
Oh, God.
Please forgive me.
I'm so sorry.
What are you worried about?
Maybe a night in jail for fraud.
I've to go tell one
of my employees he was right.
I'm not a Munchausen.
I'm gonna die unless you help me.
You'll have to come up
with something more original.
A cat predicted my death.
Cats make terrible doctors.
Oh, no, wait, that's women.
You're screwed.
How'd you slip?
I've had this dizziness
problem for a while now.
You get checked for labyrinthitis?
On antibiotics for a week.
No difference.
- Lie down a sec.
- I'm dizzy.
That's normal.
- So what are you teaching?
- Entrepreneurship.
I'm a CEO, Osttech Industries.
We make medical devices.
All right, you can sit up.
So did that tell you anything?
Did I...
Oh, my God.
The... you just cured me.
I figured you had
a tiny calcium deposit
in your inner ear;
I just shifted it around.
I've seen three doctors for this.
I'm buying you dinner.
- Forget it.
- Come on.
I'm also in investor in a club.
We'll make it a night out.
No, I'm married, boring.
I know some married
people who aren't boring.
A few years back, I was one of them.
Good luck.
If you're gonna kill me and rape me,
please do it in that order.
This is the cat, Debbie.
Have you heard of her?
Debbie.
- Sorry but without a last name...
- She was in the news.
We found her as a kitten.
She lives in the nursing home.
She only sleeps next to people
when they're about to die.
Ten patients in the last year.
And then yesterday she did it to me
while I was sitting on my couch.
Please, the whole staff,
the doctors even,
we all know this is real.
Can you come back later?
I have some business I'm conducting
with the Prince of Nigeria.
Just watch this video.
It'll prove I'm not lying.
Dr. House, I'm begging you.
Chest.
Quick!
Before she goes without
attention for eight seconds.
She's faking.
The cat told me.
Listen.
Soft breath sounds.
Means it's bronchospasm.
Can't fake that.
When Debbie climbs on a patient's bed
and goes to sleep,
we call the loved ones
and tell them to come in.
- You want to treat her?
- She's a nutjob.
Don't we all have quirks?
Aren't those eccentricities
what make us human?
It's like Debbie's here on earth
to bring people to the other side.
The doctors we spoke to
also agreed the cat...
Nutjobs get sick too.
So you think...
this cat story is nonsense.
And you admit she faked
her earlier symptoms.
But you still think
she's actually sick now?
Well, anything would sound ridiculous
If you said it in that voice.
Confirm she's faking
or I'm gonna have to kick her out.
- There's that voice again.
- I'll give you 24 hours.
Consecutive?
What are you doing?
No, Mr. Bond, I expect you to die.
- Bronchospasm, go.
- Bronchitis.
No cough, no fever.
- And Blofeld didn't smoke a cigar.
- He might have.
Dude had a lair.
Means he was rich.
Rich people enjoy a good stogie.
Sometimes send them as gifts.
Hey, Taub, did that sound
like I was awkwardly
trying to segue into making a point?
Yes.
Emphysema.
Lungs were clean on the CT.
Dogs can be trained
to predict diabetic comas,
epileptic seizures;
they can smell cancer.
It is possible there's
something in this cat.
It's more possible
that it was just a coincidence.
10 million nursing homes.
100 million pet cats.
One of them was bound
to pick a few winners.
Debbie was able to predict there was
something wrong before you were.
Is that a coincidence too?
Maybe the cat
didn't predict anything.
- Might have caused the deaths.
- We shoulda listened to Ted Nugent.
Yeah, it could be cat scratch fever
or visceral larva migrans.
Maybe he didn't kill everyone
at the nursing home,
but it may be killing Morgan.
The worms hop from the cat
to the cat lady's lungs.
- I could buy that.
- Those cigars were for me.
Hey, that reminds me,
why is some fancy CEO
sending you a box of Cuban cigars?
- Is it related to your money worries?
- What money worries?
Extrapolating from the fact that
he's been skipping his morning muffin,
I'd say that he lost almost all
his money on the market last year.
I'm on a diet.
I'm also extrapolating
from the online portfolio
you forgot to log off,
but it's mostly the muffins.
Scope her for worms in the lungs.
We could help out in there.
Yeah,
it takes at least four people
to look inside a crazy woman's lungs
for imaginary worms.
So you're in a good mood again.
You need another speech about
what a great friend I am?
I'm telling my wife
we don't need to downsize,
but maybe we do.
- You really lost all that money?
- I don't care about the money.
- I just feel bad for Rachel.
- She married a guy in one situation
and ended up with another;
that's hard on anyone.
Thanks.
Makes me feel much better
hearing my wife's a gold digger.
No, I just meant she married
this master of the universe,
successful surgeon,
and now he's basically,
you know, a flunky
for this mad scientist...
who saves lives, so that's good.
There are no worms in the lungs.
- What else could cause bronchospasm?
- Severe acid reflux.
- No esophagitis. It's not reflux.
- Why are you pushing a crash cart?
Because patients sometimes crash.
And they haven't yet invented
a crash tractor
for me to drive
wildly around the hallways.
Why are we in
the coma patients' room?
You actually think the cat
is going to predict someone's death?
No, I know the cat the not going
to predict anyone's death.
Then I will have
scientifically disproved...
You didn't keep
this patient despite the cat.
You kept this patient
because of the cat.
You're scared
there's something to it.
If I could prove the non-existence
of an omniscient God
who lovingly guides us
to the other side, I would.
Cat version's gonna have to do.
- Are you scared?
- Cats brains are always in alpha mode.
The scientific tests
that have seemed to confirm
physic phenomena,
that's where it takes place.
Please tell me that you were kidding
so I won't have to fire you.
I was kidding.
We still have a human patient, right?
Airborne allergens possible?
- Skin test was negative.
- Lungs may be more sensitive.
Or House just screwed up.
If you misinterpreted the breath sounds
as soft instead of loud,
it's laryngospasm instead
of bronchospasm,
which you can get from a simple panic
attack, which she was having.
- I also heard the lung sounds too.
- You saying I screwed up?
"Screwed up"
is maybe too harsh, but yes.
- Don't you want to check their charts?
- Of course not.
This is a double-blind.
I don't want to even
subconsciously signal
to Teddy which one's the sickest.
Her name's Debbie.
Are those welts on that guy's arm?
Were they here when we got here?
He has a severe cat allergy.
That never happened.
Look at Debbie.
Good news, mister...
Limpert,
when you don't die tonight
you will finally have done
something good for the world
as opposed to your life as a...
fireman.
Foreman's airborne allergen
theory makes the most sense.
Do a methacholine challenge
on catgirl to check it out.
I told you to get rid
of "death cat".
- Do you see a cat?
- I see a litter box.
This is a disability, Dr. Cuddy.
- Can't make it to the toilets on time.
- On the mice too?
Well, now you see the mice
actually prove that I don't have a cat.
Are these...
are these the genetically
modified lab mice from oncology?
Genetically modified for tastiness.
Get rid of the cat,
and get rid of your patient.
My team's doing
a methacholine challenge.
Your team just completed
a methacholine challenge,
which came up negative.
Who told you about the test?
I'll never say, but yes.
Her airways clamped down.
I heard it.
We kick her onto the street,
it could happen again.
I wish there was a lawsuit cat.
It could warn you.
I'm sorry,
but if you won't escort her out,
I'll have to get security to do it.
You're joining me
for a good-bye smoke.
I don't smoke.
Fine.
If you don't want the seventh graders
to think you're cool.
I went through your purse.
Horoscopes.
Good luck charms.
You went to a good college,
good nursing school.
So you weren't always
a superstitious idiot.
- I'm not a super...
- How'bout four years,
that sound right?
That's when you switched
from a family insurance plan
- to the one you're on now.
- I was married. I got divorced.
Two years before that,
you got chicken pox shots,
which you only get in adulthood
when you have a kid.
Or I should say when you had a kid
because no kid
has come to visit you.
Which all makes me think
something bad happened.
It was my stepson, Timothy.
What happened?
He was in school.
He was having his morning snack.
And he choked.
And the teacher saw it,
and they did everything
that they were supposed to.
He shouldn't have died.
You want to make it make sense.
What's wrong with that?
It's meaningless, is what's wrong.
What's wrong is that it doesn't do
a thing to bring your kid back
or put you and your ex
together again.
Rash on your neck.
Probably not enough for Cuddy.
I can't breathe.
Hey, doc.
Breath sound soft to you, doc?
Hooray!
You're officially sick.
Churg-Strauss fits best.
Here's the plan...
Taub, you change the litter box.
This is pathetic.
You're still punishing me for calling
you out on the green urine lady?
This is for ratting me out to Cuddy.
I'm not asking you to apologize,
just scoop some poop out of a box.
Just clean it.
- Let House do it.
- Yeah, that'll happen.
He won't just continue to let
our room smell like cat pee.
I'll clean it next time.
I'm outta here.
Now that you've delivered
that important lesson,
I'm gonna go test the patient.
What, you think your bag's
gonna die now?
Now you're punishing me
because you think I'm superstitious?
What do you care?
It's not so much
about me caring per se.
It's more about me wondering
why you're such a credulous idiot.
Thirteen, start the patient on steroids
for the Churg-Strauss.
Unless we have something
we need to argue about.
This is good stuff.
The best.
It's made from the distilled sweat of
recently laid-off hedge fund managers.
- Aren't you happy you came out tonight?
- Yeah.
I wasn't actually going to,
but not the greatest day at work.
I used to have an office like this.
- Used to?
- When I was a plastic surgeon.
But one day I took stock
of my life and...
screw it.
I had an affair with the daughter
of one of my partners.
They signed a non-disclosure.
I signed a non-compete.
And the funny thing is
I wound up telling my wife anyway.
You like your job?
Same as you.
Same as everyone.
It has its ups and downs.
You're lying to make me feel better.
Yeah, it's the best.
I'm in charge, you know?
I'm a kid with toys.
Speaking of which,
what do you think of the prototype?
It's amazing.
Gotta make it
a half-inch smaller though.
- You serious?
- I got small hands,
6.5 gloves, like women surgeons,
which are your fastest-growing market.
Meaning the girls would have to use
two hands to hit the switch.
Why do I bother paying
the idiots that work for me?
Put down that crap you're drinking,
because I am
breaking out the really good stuff.
What's wrong?
I went to the bathroom.
My urine...
- green again?
- It's brown.
I didn't do anything, honest.
"I'm just a girl who can't say no."
It is possible she's still faking.
She didn't fake
the for the bronchospasm.
You think she's faking
some stuff but not other stuff?
Maybe she's "unchausen".
I'm just saying the brown
urine doesn't make sense.
- What?
- Nothing.
We've ruled out every
possible cause for brown urine.
No blood in the urine.
Liver and kidneys fine.
- Brown could be fecal. A fistula...
- we checked.
How do we know the urine
is still brown?
Had to be.
Once you've gone brown...
if we've ruled out everything
that can make the urine brown,
what if it just looked brown?
If the green dye never left her system,
what plus green makes brown?
Purple.
Strep bovis infection
from colon cancer.
Paraneoplastic syndrome
would explain the bronchospasm.
We scoped her
when we checked for the fistula.
There's no tumor.
I wasn't scared
by the umbrella either.
What? Not everything's
about you, kutner.
I realize it's stupid.
I just... I don't know everything.
- I don't want to invite...
- Great,
'cause I thought your superstitiousness
had to do with your folks being killed.
But "you're stupid"
works just as well.
Why is there a ladder here?
Forgot that one.
Scopes don't work as well
as pillcams.
Give her one.
Find the tumor.
Come with me, tiny Taub.
Sorry I was late again.
I've got a long commute
from the poor house.
Knew it when I hired you.
You'd eventually Miss the money,
being the big shot
like your new CEO friend,
if that nightclub stamp on your hand
is any indication.
- Don't worry, I'm not quitting.
- I know.
Guy who signs a non-compete instead
of just telling his wife that he cheated
- doesn't have the guts to quit.
- Bad example. I did tell her.
From guilt, not from courage.
And bravely running to Cuddy
behind my back.
Arriving heroically
to work every day.
Cowards make lousy employees.
Maybe you're a coward,
maybe you're quitting.
Either way, I'm screwed.
You will note how
faster pussycat kill, kill
has snuggled up
by coma guy over there.
And more importantly,
she did yesterday as well.
And he's still breathing.
We done?
Thank you for showing me this.
But maybe she's just confused
in this new environment.
In 1844, a preacher
in upstate New York
added up some dates in the bible
and predicted Jesus' return.
His followers gave away
all their possessions
and showed up in a field.
Guess who didn't show.
So the preacher said
that he miscalculated,
and they went right back the next month
but with more followers.
Every time he was
irrefutably proved wrong,
it redoubled everyone's belief.
I know I sound just like them.
But I also know you're wrong.
Something terrible's
gonna happen to me.
You trying to prove
to her she's not dying?
That would be dumb,
as she might be dying.
This woman lost her kid.
Why are you attacking beliefs
that give her a little bit of comfort?
I don't care if her superstitions
make her feel better.
I just want her
to think more clearly.
Maybe that could make
her as happy as you are.
Where are we going?
Experimenting.
Stop it, Dr. Wilson.
It's just not cute anymore.
You already experimented
on the coma guy.
- Haven't you proved your point?
- Not to the patient.
And not to the millions
of idiots who drooled
over that news item
about the magic cat.
Why are you so obsessed with this?
Can't you just call her an idiot
and leave everyone alone?
Hey, look, kids, therapy cat.
You're a liar.
Therapy animals are dogs, not cats.
Aren't you feisty?
This one's special.
If she likes you,
interesting stuff happens.
Kids, playtime's over.
This is a good thing.
Because either you're starting to doubt
yourself which is healthy, or...
I don't believe in the legend
of good-bye kitty.
Or you're starting to give
a crap what other people think,
which is just another way of saying you
give a crap about other people.
I'd love to hear more of your theory,
but I don't give a crap.
Also the pillcam's back.
Polypoid.
- Raised edges.
- Raised edges are actually necessary,
since that's the opening
to the appendix.
How many times are we gonna watch this?
There's no tumor.
Oh, my God.
The death cat is attacking your legs.
You're gonna die.
Maybe it has something
to do with that little red dot
dancing around down there.
Oh, my God, the death laser
is attacking your legs.
- You're gonna die.
- We're wasting time looking for cancer.
She's still walking around.
She's still pretty healthy.
Maybe it's something minor.
Maybe we're not wasting time.
We wouldn't have seen a flat lesion.
Skin cancer could have
metastasized to the intestines.
Cool.
Check for melanomas.
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Come here.
Here, kitty.
- What?
- It's not cancer.
We found spider veins on her back.
They weren't there when she came in.
Spider veins means Cushing's.
Could cause
an abdominal disturbance,
- brown urine...
- But the bronchospasm?
Cushing's myopathy.
It's uncommon but...
wait a second.
You didn't wake me up to tell me
a symptom that's not killing her.
What else is going on?
I think she's dying.
I just told you it's Cushing's.
Treat...
I don't mean
because of the spider veins.
Mr. Limpert died.
- If that's my gym teacher...
- it's your coma patient.
He was stable for a year and a half,
and he just died.
The cat was right, House.
Here, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss.
Say "puss" one more time.
It's the 6th "puss" that really does it.
You're right.
Sulking will solve everything.
That cat sat on my lap,
and that cat knows something.
- You believe it now?
- Yesterday it was all a coincidence.
Yesterday it was
until I unintentionally
proved it wasn't.
Patient must have cushing's.
- We have to figure out whether it's...
- Cat's nose is powerful.
- It can smell liver or kidney failure.
- Exactly,
except if you'd glanced at the nursing
home files I had faxed this morning,
you'd know that most of the patients'
livers and kidneys were fine.
- What else?
- MRIS aren't telling if the cushing's
- in her adrenals or her brain.
- So check her A.C.T.H.
- A cat's vision is at the blue end...
- A.c.t.h. Is 11.7.
It's too close to tell.
We can't treat the wrong organ
'cause that won't solve anything.
She could have a cortisol storm,
could kill her.
Maybe as the senior fellow
you could have made sure
that my doors were closed, so that
I could be concentrating on the cat
instead of looking for the cat.
You all right?
Your nose.
What'd he say?
Sounds like he said,
"Do you like cranberry juice?"
Crap.
Cheaper than fake blood.
And more cran-tastic.
Don't ever leave my door
open like that again.
You're playing pranks,
and this woman could be dying.
So have Chase do a venous sampling
in her brain.
If he finds something, it's there.
If he finds nothing, it's the adrenals.
I'm not who I used to be.
I'm scared.
That's not a way to live.
I want to come work for you.
Jeez, Chris, you didn't think...
I didn't mean to imply
that I could hire you right now.
- You said you needed guys like me.
- I know,
but you don't have an MBA.
And I just hired
a chief medical officer.
Let me invest
in that laser scalpel start-up.
- I got money saved. Not a ton but...
- We put in a $2 million minimum
for the first round financing.
Look,
I guess I could take you on
at a smaller number.
But you have to understand,
it wouldn't be some quick payoff.
I know, I know it's not gonna change
my life overnight.
I just
need to start changing it.
Okay, then let's start.
What exactly are you hoping to find
inside your dead coma guy?
Catnip.
Chew toy.
I don't know.
That's why I'm looking.
Your patient had cardiac arrest
during the venous sampling.
We got her back,
but her heart's still tenuous.
- That tell us anything?
- She's weak, possibly dying.
So nothing.
What about the A.C.T.H. ?
Slightly elevated.
That confirms the Cushing's
is in the brain... go.
Are you sure that it's Cushing's?
You'd expect central body obesity.
- She's in good shape.
- If it had a normal presentation,
- there wouldn't be a cat involved.
- So it's the brain.
The next question is whether to remove
the pituitary right now...
That's not a question for me.
That's a question for the patient.
You'll present both sides
and let her decide.
All right.
I've gotta stop telling you my theories.
You always just try to prove me wrong.
You mean the theory about Cuddy's ass
getting bigger at the full moon?
I confirmed that one.
Photo's on my blog.
Normally, you'd be up in the patient
room hectoring her on what to do.
Instead you're up
in some irrelevant dead guy who may or
may not be connected to a magic cat
because you want to prove
to me that you don't care.
Case is over.
I'm exploring a scientific mystery.
I put up with your obsessions.
I even encourage them, for one reason...
they save lives.
I don't know what you're doing now.
Cushing's means you're overproducing
a hormone called cortisol.
The recommended course of action
is to suppress it with drugs.
And that will cure it?
Just treat it.
It could come back.
The only permanent solution
is to cut into your brain
and remove your pituitary gland,
but the surgery's dangerous.
Your heart stopped on the table
once already.
I want the surgery.
This thing is gonna kill me
if I don't kill it first.
Because of the cat?
Do you want to tell me
what an idiot I'm being?
I really believe that there are things
that science can't understand,
that there is a role
for faith and prayer,
but it's in the waiting room,
not the O.R.
There's a reason I got sick.
There's a reason for all the bad things
that have happened to me.
I don't know what that reason is,
but I know that if there isn't one,
if there's no greater
purpose in the world,
then it's not a world
I want to live in.
I'll schedule an operating room.
Early.
I'm not staying long.
I'm quitting.
You got a new job?
Well, then you're not quitting.
See you back here tomorrow.
You're not accepting my resignation?
Easier this way. It voids
the whole thing where you panic,
run back and grovel,
and I punish you and then take you back.
Bye.
Bring donuts.
Everyone loves those bear claws.
Here, puss, puss, puss, puss, puss.
Puss?
I've been waiting 15 minutes.
Where's Neil?
Neil doesn't work here anymore.
- He's the CEO.
- I'm sorry. I wish I could help you.
Sorry.
This is crazy.
I'm investing with his company.
He doesn't have a company.
He worked here,
but he was a receptionist, a temp.
Where is he?
He's in custody.
I really am not supposed
to say anything else.
I went to high school with him.
That's what everyone else
thought too.
I'm guessing you also
cured his ear problem.
Did you give him the money yet?
I was right.
And more satisfyingly,
you were wrong.
It was a coincidence.
The cat was not predicting deaths.
It was trying to keep warm.
Yes, dead people are renowned
for their warm glow.
They are if they're feverish,
like three of the patients were.
Or if they're wasting away,
like the other eight.
- Wasting doesn't...
- It does.
If it means someone sticks
a heating blanket on you.
Congrats. Because of your crazy
obsession with this cat,
you've solved
a completely trivial mystery.
Completely trivial?
My God.
It's clearly only partially trivial.
Debbie climbed on Morgan too,
which means she was overheated.
So what causes flushing and
mimics every cushing's symptom
except central body obesity?
Cancer.
A corticotropin-producing
carcinoid tumor of the intestine.
But your pillcam
didn't find anything.
Means it must be somewhere
the pillcam couldn't go.
The appendix.
Congratulations,
you probably saved her life.
You definitely saved
her needless surgery.
Yes, I did.
What's the O.R. Extension number?
Just curious.
Thank you.
I wouldn't come here for thanks.
That would be ungracious.
It's more about gloating.
You were about to cut out
a piece of your brain
just to chase
some crazy superstition.
- But I didn't.
- You "didn't" didn't do anything.
I stopped it.
And what made you do that?
Science, logic, reason.
Pick any three.
A cat chooses that exact moment
to sit on your computer.
Maybe that's science and logic
and reason or maybe it's something else.
You're an idiot.
I looked up the preacher
from New York state.
His followers never faded out.
They became
the seventh-day adventists,
a major religion.
That man changed
the course of history.
Because his followers
were as deluded as he was.
Maybe he just gave them
something to live for.
Feel better.
Cat pee on my chair?
- Blood on my face?
- Fake blood.
You pay for the dry cleaning.
Why are you still alive?
I'm not sure.
I guess he was impressed
you stood up to him.
And got a cat to pee on his chair.
A cat.
See you tomorrow.
The HTeam's AnonymHouse
www.tvsubtitles.net