Hey.
How long have i...?
forced trauma to the head...
since the accident,
he's had a continued...
why can't i get up?
No episodes of hyperten...
what's wrong with my legs?
Ekg's show normal...
hey!
Someone talk to me.
Dilation, no hypertrophy...
you don't
hear me talking to you?
Normal feeling pressure,
normal c.k. Troponin...
great heart for transplant.
My heart?!
Oh, god!
They don't know i'm in here.
Hey, genius.
I think it
violates certain ethical laws
to rip the organs out of
a guy who's still alive.
Possibly certain
law laws too.
Thank you.
Could you, um, get back
in your bed, please, mr. House?
It's actually doctor house.
This guy's a doctor?
There's also navy seal house.
But you're going to have
to save up for that one.
Really?
Well, that's interesting, but...
you're here because
you crashed your motorcycle,
not because i need a consult.
So, get back in bed.
I scraped my elbow, i just
need a truckload of vicodin.
Whereas, this guy...
he's brain dead.
No, i'm not!
So drop it.
See that?
Minimal brainwaves
don't mean he's alive.
I am alive!
I'm here!
No ekg response
to painful stimuli, hot or cold.
What you're seeing is random,
barely discernable.
I discerned it.
Listen to him, please.
No, that's just
the amplifier's
internal noise level.
It's on increased sensitivity.
No, it's not!
It's me.
Then why is
his eye following you?
Exactly.
Following motion's
an involuntary reflex.
No.
You're a doctor...
you should know these things.
No, no,
i'm not dead, i need help.
I'm here!
I also know
about locked-in syndrome...
that things
are either involuntary...
or voluntary.
Blink if you can hear me.
I hear you.
Oh, this is going to be fun.
Eye movement is deliberate.
Can you blink once
for "yes," twice for "no?"
I hope so.
The square root of nine?
He got that faster than you.
The brain is fully functional.
Lee...
where's molly?
You were in an accident.
Hit the brake,
hit the brake, hit the brake!
You've sustained a traumatic
injury to your brain stem
which has cut off
your brain's ability
to communicate with
the rest of your body.
Can you fix me?
Where's molly?
You still have movement
in your eyes.
So we can get you
to a rehab facility
where they can teach you
how to communicate.
No, i can't be stuck
like this.
Unless...
the crash didn't cause
the brain damage.
Maybe the brain damage
caused the crash.
Yeah, i couldn't stop.
Why couldn't i stop?
Look at his palms.
There's no scrapes.
He didn't even
try to protect himself.
So you had slowed reflexes...
or no reflexes.
You're not a doctor
in this hospital.
You are a patient.
Yeah, and you're the guy
who wants to cut out my organs,
and he's the guy who doesn't.
Stroke, cancer,
even a simple infection,
anything that insults
the central pons could do this.
Then that means
that i could be fixed.
You're giving him false hope.
He needs to accept
what's happened.
And work on making
the most of it.
Molly.
Hey.
Don't look
at me like that.
That's not
making me feel better.
I love you.
I don't know how god
is going to get us through this.
But he will.
Stop it.
I'm blushing.
What are you doing?
Just looking for some reading
material for the crapper.
These cts...
get back in your bed.
Come on.
The children
are in the waiting area,
can i bring them in?
No.
No, don't.
You don't want to see them?
I don't want
them having nightmares.
to scare them, molly.
You don't want them
to see you?
It's okay.
I understand.
You're going
to be better soon enough.
You really that sure?
Why are you so sure?
Baby, how'd you get so sure?
You okay?
Never better.
Here's your burger.
If you can't
bring mohammed to princeton,
bring princeton to mohammed.
That's my diagnostics posse.
Hot, dark, and darker.
Talk about
getting me better, please.
What are you doing
up in middletown?
Who cares?
Buying a gibson '57 goldtop.
It's the guitar
duane allman used to play.
Next to the trauma,
the mostly likely causes
of a sudden onset
of locked-in syndrome
are basilar artery stroke,
and brain hemorrhage.
Ct was clean.
Man, those fries look good.
Guy's an active bike rider,
his heart's fine.
A well-placed tumor
could explain it.
Jeez, is the last thing i ate
gonna be the last thing i ate?
It could evade the ct,
and still show up
on an mri with contrast.
It was a melted power bar.
She's the smart one.
I just keep dark and darker
to fill out the quota.
If we find it, treat it,
you could be fine.
I never thought i'd
be praying for a brain tumor,
but please, dear god.
If you're praying in there,
stop it right now.
We'll get his doctor
to order an mri.
His doctor's
busy teaching him how
to blink out "kill me"
in morse code.
Luckily, i found some forms
under the mattress.
Check it out, they have
those mri video goggles.
I heard these were awesome.
What do you see?
It's a beach.
Oh, look, there's taub...
drinking a margarita
and mocking us
for driving
all the way up here...
easy,
i can still feel in here.
Excuse dr. Kutner,
he gets a little excited
about new technology.
It can get loud in there,
and a little closed off.
These will put you
in a quiet place.
You can create a relaxing
scenario for yourself.
I hope they...
...work.
You're in my relaxing scenario?
I guess you like me.
Either that,
or you got sent here.
What? By god?
I'm not sure
if i believe in god.
You spend an awful
lot of time in church
for someone who doesn't.
I don't not believe either.
It's either one
or the other.
I go to church mainly
to keep my wife happy,
but...
i don't know,
i've never actually thought
that god could reach out
and affect my life.
But getting a brilliant doctor
in the bed next to me?
God is also the guy
who opened his car door
in front of you.
I think molly was right.
I think you were sent here
to make me get better.
I think so.
Hey!
Hey, dad.
Making a volcano.
You're making a volcano?
It looks like it.
What you doing, baby?
What time is it?
Hope you don't mind.
My new roommate snores.
And my new room
doesn't have you.
Your mri showed a lesion
in the central pons.
What is that?
What does that mean?
See it there?
No.
Mm, that's what they said.
But it's there.
Which means no way
head trauma did this.
It's cancer, causing
a paraneoplastic syndrome.
Unfortunately,
your current doctor thinks
its diffuse nature
means an infection.
And the bad news is,
the antivirals he's got you on
might kill you.
I'm not gonna die.
But the good news is
if they just almost kill you,
then dr. Idiot will realize
that his name
is not a coincidence
and he'll let me do
whatever i want.
Thank you.
See, the irony here is...
you're kind of fascinating.
So many questions.
But if you could answer
any of them,
you wouldn't be fascinating.
I get it, you're
a little nuts, aren't you?
Your wife is the one
getting you through this.
Your wife and me.
Although frankly,
the mri was a lot more useful
than four hours
of hand-holding.
I think.
If you had a wife,
you'd know why it matters.
You're a good guy.
Easy to talk to.
Wait, something's happening.
What's happening to me?
I need some help in here!
Your patient is seizing.
Why would he have a seizure?
Because he has cancer!
His brain stem
is compromised.
Why are you
still arguing with this guy?
You thought i was dead.
Welcome back.
And nicely played.
You almost died.
Exactly as we planned.
You knew this
was going to happen?
It usually happens when
you treat cancer
by pretending it's not cancer.
Right, doctor?
My turn?
It's cancer?
No, it isn't.
Yes!
A small tumor
in his brain stem,
causing paraneoplastic syndrome.
He needs plasmapheresis.
Can you give that to him?
No, i'm sorry, i completely
disagree with dr. House.
Please shut up.
I don't.
Which means i can treat him.
Let him. Let him.
Is that what you want?
Absolutely.
Would you send up
a couple of bellboys?
I got the transfefer papers.
Plasmapheresis is all set up.
Are you okay?
Fresh infusion of macho.
You like?
I can't move, and
she's worried about his boo-boo?
What were you
doing up there, anyway?
Antiquing.
I found you
a late victorian corset.
Come by later,
i'll tie you up.
Is heitting on her?
If she turns around,
she's into him too.
And there, yeah.
Sorry i didn't
show up in middletown.
I didn't get the message.
Probably because
there was no message.
I've decided
to accept your resignation.
Uh, i thought
we were past this.
I decided to stay.
No, you didn't.
You had it decided for you.
So now you're stuck here
with a boss
who knows that you want
to be somewhere else.
Which means you're no longer
motivated to impress me,
which means you're
no longer motivated
to come up
with good ideas.
Unless i'm wrong.
Save the cheerleader.
Save your world.
I got it from here.
I thought you already
solved this.
Are you thinking
you might be wrong?
What's going on?
Hey, just curious...
what were you driving up
to middletown for?
What do you care?
Why does he care?
Because i'm your friend.
I was buying a guitar.
Yeah, i heard that.
It used to belong
to a guitarist
who died
in a motorcycle accident.
It just reeks of
you screwing with people.
Your crash was ten miles
from the orange county
progressive pain clinic.
You live ten miles
from mary's dress shop.
And yet, that's not
even on my list of reasons
that i think you're
secretly a transvestite.
If you're going to another
state to get more narcotics...
he's on drugs?!
I went to visit
your ex-ex-ex-wife...
what?!
Who lives
in thompson ridge.
I let her know
about the extra money
you're making
on the lecture circuit.
So she'll be sure
to adjust your alimony.
You wouldn't do that.
Yeah.
I wouldn't do that.
Would you?
You guys are friends?
Shouldn't we be
entertaining our patient?
I performed euripides
with sock puppets.
You just missed it.
House said we should.
The mind is like a muscle.
If you don't exercise it,
it'll atrophy,
just like anything else.
Whoever's with him needs
to talk.
Keep his mind active, and
it'll show house you still care.
Not sure if i do.
Jeez, you're my doctor?
Then why don't you just quit?
I'm not sure
i want to do that, either.
Maybe you should figure it out
before house
figures it out for you.
Yeah, maybe you should have
your midlife crisis
after i'm better.
Kutner...
we'll be right back.
Wait.
Wait, what did you just see?
Do you drink?
He's a roofer.
Alcohol hardly
proves your theory.
Marchiafava bignami disease
fits.
Lft's are normal.
Speak english. Is it fixable?
What does that mean?
That hurts.
No tremors.
How much do you drink?
A six-pack a day?
I hate beer,
i don't even drink beer.
Maybe more or less.
Or maybe something else.
It may not be alcohol at all.
Street opiates
can also cause locked-in...
i don't get high.
So, either
we play 20,000 questions
with every street drug,
or instead of talking to him,
we talk to the lesion.
Talk to me.
We're going
to biopsy the brain stem?
For the record, that doesn't
count as your inspired idea.
It's sort of
where i was heading.
You're going
to cut into my head?
Why?
Stop treating me
like a piece of furniture!
I have a right
to know what's going on!
Where's that going?
Blood in your urine
clogged up your old catheter.
Peeing blood?
That must be what
the insecure doctor saw.
Every new clue gets us
closer to the answer.
Damnit.
The surgery
will get us more clues.
You have visitors.
No. Oh, molly.
Come in.
Daddy!
I told you not to bring them.
Well, they wanted
to see their father.
I can't even hug them.
They can handle it.
It's going to be all right.
You're not
so sure anymore, are you?
They must've told you
that it's dangerous.
That i could die.
And that's why
you brought them in here...
i got an a+ on my test.
To see me before i die.
I love you, daddy.
Daddy loves you too.
I want
to show you my drawings.
Kids just want a dad.
Even if he's just a lump.
Maybe you should go now.
Oh, no.
They can stay, please.
Let them stay.
Bye, daddy.
Sorry.
You were crying.
Damn.
We're going
to put you out,
just so we can
drill the hole.
Oh, that's
very thoughtful of you.
Then we'll wake you back up.
We'l'll need you to answer some
simple yes or no questions
while we're cutting, to make
sure we're not cutting...
it seems to be working.
Deep breaths.
In about ten seconds,
you'll feel lightheaded.
And by now...
you should be floating high
with lucy in the sky.
How come i'm not better?
God's not supposed
to work in trial and error.
God's mistakes
are well-documented.
If he'd done
everything right the first time,
there'd have been one plague
and zero great floods.
Those were
because of human mistakes.
You think your doctor has
an apartment on mount olympus?
God put me
with you for a reason.
I'm gonna be
all right still, right?
I don't know.
Lee. You with me now?
Easy questions.
You'll be done
before you know it.
Is this equation correct?
What,
so if you make a mistake,
i'm not going
to know that anymore?
Are these lines parallel?
Spatial relationships intact.
Take a look at this circle.
Is more than half of it shaded?
Of course.
Don't forget to blink.
Is more than
half of the circle shaded?
Sorry, yes.
Look at me, lee.
Again.
Is more than
half of this circle shaded?
Blink.
Come on, lee, blink.
Foreman, back out.
Why can't i blink?
Why aren't his eyes moving?
Two options:
my neurologist screwed up,
or else something the hospital
lawyer's going to have
to come up with
when you sue us.
Blinking and eye movements
are controlled
by a small cluster of nerves,
just millimeters
from the biopsy site.
But he's still in there,
right?
I mean,
he just can't communicate?
It's possible.
Also possible is that the
surgery caused so much swelling
in his brain stem,
that he's just gone.
He had one way to communicate,
and now that's gone.
Well played.
Brain biopsy revealed severe
damage to the myelin sheath.
Question is, why?
Epstein barr,
picorna viruses, malaria.
He runs a business,
meets a lot of people,
he could've
picked up rotavirus.
Did he report
having bloody diarrhea?
The wife's not sure,
says he doesn't complain.
Did you ask him?
We've prioritized.
He can only blink, a real
history would've taken weeks.
If he had epstein barr,
he'd have belly pains.
If he had picorna virus,
he'd have headaches.
Five other yes/no questions,
and maybe we'd know
what treatment to give.
And what treatment
would kill him.
Unless he's already dead.
Maybe there's another way.
Brain computer interface...
better known as bci.
The goal is to get
you to move that cursor
with your mind.
When you think "up,"
the computer
records the pattern.
Think "up" enough times,
it eventually
learns what you're thinking.
So...
start thinking "up."
You in there?
Are you trying?
I called
the ex-ex-ex-wife.
She was at a sweat lodge
in new mexico last week.
What were you
really doing in new york?
You know how you hate it
when i meddle in your lies?
I mean your life.
Why are you being
so evasive?
Unless you have
something to evade.
Interesting.
This has nothing to do with you,
your ex-wife, or my pain.
I was heading to the
down-state correctional facility
in fishkill.
One of your hookers
arrange a conjugal visit?
It's where foreman's brother
is being held.
This is going to mean
months of sleepless nights,
wondering if i could've
done something differently.
Maybe it's not
that i'm sick of house.
It's that i'm sick of
being scared out of my mind
to go to work every day.
Sorry.
Did that just...
was that you?
Are you really in there?
I knew you were in there.
I was scared.
Thank god.
I am scared.
Molly, i love you so much.
Have you had any bloody
diarrhea in the last two weeks?
Rotavirus out.
Any recent joint pain?
Epstein barr's out.
Have you traveled
out of the country lately?
What about
inside the country?
He was in st. Louis.
Good.
Could be missouri malaria.
Let's start treatment.
He was... he was there.
The machine must not be working.
Either that,
or he lied to you about it.
People do that sometimes.
For example, i just lied to him
about missouri malaria.
Did you go to st. Louis?
I should've told you.
Why didn't i just tell you?
Down.
When you weren't
in st. Louis for two days,
i assume you were getting
some strange for two days.
So does she.
You have to tell her i wasn't.
Amazing.
A man who only
has two blips at his disposal
can still lie.
I'm not lying.
If you were getting
some really strange strange,
you could've
contracted neurosyphilis.
Infection went to your brain,
froze you right up.
Good news is
it's treatable.
You'll be up and moving in
time to sign the divorce papers.
Why would i tell you the
truth about being in st. Louis,
and then not
tell you the truth about this?
He just admitted he wasn't in
st. Louis in front of his wife,
and you think he's lying
when she's not even in here?
I'm liking this one
more and more.
Don't fire him.
Were you out of the state?
I never left.
[beeping]
were you within 20 miles
of your house?
Yes.
Were you
within five miles?
Yes.
Within two miles?
Did you stay
at a hotel?
No.
You had to sleep somewhere.
Your car?
No.
A friend's house?
Yes.
That narrows it down,
depending on how popular
you are.
Tell the wife to stop crying,
get in here.
He says that when he was
supposed to be in st. Louis,
he was staying
at a friend's house.
Really.
Yes.
Let's assume that
you believe him for the moment.
Name your friends
within two miles.
Martin and kim's?
No.
Guess someone
who doesn't have a wife.
Dave?
Yes.
Got an address?
If this is where he got sick,
someone else here
should have symptoms.
Not if lee was the only one
coming down to the basement.
Furnace is rusty,
but no gas leaks.
Resumes
and cover letters here...
some are weeks old.
He's been spending time here
for a while.
Business wasn't going good.
I didn't want
you and the kids to worry.
I was trying
to protect you.
Molly...
i wish you could hear me.
I wish i could
make all of this better.
Looks like he temped
a few times.
As a janitor.
Factory out on route 10.
Factory foreman says they
make rechargeable batteries.
Mostly for cell phones.
Big step down from
running your own business,
to sweeping up.
Doing what i had to do.
Metal filings.
Judging by the color,
i'd say cadmium.
Which he'd aerosolize
with the broom,
then right into his lungs.
Heavy metal poisoning...
explains everything.
The chelation will scrub the
heavy metals out of your blood.
If we are right about the cause,
we should see some movement
in about a day or so.
Can't put
this thing on turbo?
I'm getting
a little anxious in here.
Somebody will
be here at all times
to, uh, irrigate your eyes,
keep you company.
Hopefully, it'll
help make the time go quicker.
My eyes
still feel really dry.
Thank you...
for thinking "up."
For helping me
find you in there.
Man, when you moved
that cursor...
bought my first girlfriend
a necklace.
It was silver.
It cost 180 bucks...
had to save for six months.
She hated it.
Really, seriously?
Did you tell this story
to someone who could walk away?
Never bought another
girlfriend jewelry again.
Until dr. Hadley.
You're dating her?
You might want to start
all your stories with that.
Same thing...
she didn't even wear it.
The diamond thing, she
was wearing it the other day.
If she doesn't like it,
she doesn't like it.
Apparently, i suck
at picking out jewelry,
but at least
have the guts to tell me.
Okay, getting boring again.
How long until we know
if this treatment is working?
You lied to me.
I wasn't having an affair.
So we needed money.
Who cares?
Last time business was slow,
you got migraines every day.
Why would you do that to me?
I'm sorry, i was...
i was stupid.
I was... don't go!
Don't!
Damn it, somebody...
put "i'm sorry"
on this stupid computer.
My eye is killing me.
I want to keep my job.
Great.
All you got to do
is come up with a good idea.
How about
we hook the guy's brain
into a computer,
so he can communicate?
That's a great idea.
For the guy who invented the
computer that can read minds.
Your idea was
to use his idea.
You didn't come up with it.
No one else came up with it.
If i didn't
re-establish communication,
we never would've found...
what's interesting
is why you're here now.
Not when i gave you
the ultimatum.
Was it something
the patient said?
I realized that
what we do here...terrifies me.
And...
overcoming that
is the only way i can matter.
Kutner found
the battery factory.
Kutner came up with the cadmium.
Maybe you don't matter.
I'm going to close your eyes
so you can get some sleep.
Hopefully, when you wake up,
we'll see some improvement.
Hope that includes
my eye feeling better.
Hand me
the flourescein stain.
What's that mean?
Epithelium looks torn.
These drops sting.
I'm going to close your
left eye to keep it protected.
I'm going to blink your eye
a few times
to distribute the dye.
Ulcerative keratitis.
Means it's
not cadmium poisoning.
Which means
you don't know what's wrong.
Again.
When's the last time
you changed that dressing?
Judging by the smell of it,
i'd say never.
He's locked-in,
his kidneys blew a fuse,
and now his eye is oozing puss.
I assume you went
over all of that with your team.
I also assume they
didn't have any brilliant ideas,
or you wouldn't
still be muttering to yourself.
This is going to hurt.
The way he's losing his myelin
makes an infection most likely.
Could be varicella...
road debris
has come to the surface.
I'm going
to have to scrub it out.
But the initial acyclovir
would've treated that.
Which pushes me
towards an autoimmune disease.
Like behcet's.
Here...this is going
to hurt even more.
Take two now, two later.
Of course,
if the varicella was resistant,
it wouldn't matter
what they did up in middletown.
Do an lp.
You've been
in the er too long.
When the patient
had head trauma,
white blood cells only indicate
that he had head trauma.
Or you could use the lp
for something useful.
If you find polys,
it's varicella.
Lymphs, behcet's.
Why did i fire you again?
You didn't. I quit.
You weren't visiting
foreman's brother, either.
Busy...
kutner's doing an lp,
so i have to focus.
I had prison security check
visitor logs, phone records.
You've never had any contact
with anyone at fishkill.
So, i ask again...
what were you
doing up in middletown?
You know
what's more interesting
than what i was doing?
The reason you are so obsessed
with what i was doing.
Stop deflecting, house.
Says the deflector.
The reason i was up there...
is the reason
you're scared i was up there.
I was checking out
your dirty, little secret.
How long have you
been sleeping with her?
How did you know?
Your only secrets are
the girls you find embarrassing.
And the only embarrassing girl
you've met recently
is the one at
your brother's cuckoo facility.
We've only been out
a few times.
She's a caregiver.
Like all of
your other failed exes.
And someone who
takes care of your brother.
Who was the last person
who took care of your brother?
You think this is oedipal?
Actually,
i was thinking masturbatory.
I guess your mom
took care of him first.
So, the safe course
is to gouge your eyes out.
Lp stands
for lumbar puncture.
We use this needle to
collect fluid from your spine.
That's a really big needle.
You're going to feel some
extreme pressure in your back.
I already feel pressure
in my front...
my chest hurts.
Something's wrong.
No, my chest!
I think i'm hav...
oh, god!
Call the code.
There is no god.
You don't know
what's wrong with me.
It doesn't seem that way.
So am i dead?
Not yet.
But you're about to be.
Okay.
Charging...clear.
Again...clear.
He's back.
No. No. Let me go.
He can't fix me.
I've been here for three days,
everything hurts.
It's okay, just...
just stop fighting.
She's got
to go on with her life.
The kids don't need this.
I can't do nothing for them...
i can't...
scratch this foot... wow,
that really, really itches.
So we put in
a temporary pacer.
Shut up, shut up.
He's trying to talk.
Is something bothering you?
If there's still tightness
in your chest, it's expected.
Is it your eye?
Why is he saying "no"
three times?
You only asked one question.
Maybe he's not saying "no,"
maybe he's saying "down."
Are you saying
that the pain is lower?
How low, your leg?
Your foot?
Left foot?
Check his... let me see now...
yeah, his right foot.
No bruises,
no rashes, no cuts.
Then there should be
no pain.
Is there
a tingling sensation?
Is it itching?
Itchy foot means
liver failure.
The liver's fine.
His enzymes have been normal
since we admitted him.
I didn't say "failing,"
i said "failure."
Just like you.
Liver's like a cruise ship
taking on water.
As it starts to sink,
it sends out an s.o.s.,
only instead of radio waves,
it uses enzymes.
The more enzymes in the blood,
the worse the liver is.
And once the ship has sunk,
there's no more s.o.s.
You think the liver's fine,
but it's already
at the bottom of the sea.
So dying liver released
toxins, damaged the nerves,
led to locked-in syndrome.
Now we just need to know
what's causing
the liver failure.
Liver, plus eye,
plus kidney...
most likely
sclerosing cholangitis.
Oh, god, if only
taub had said that,
it would've been a happy ending.
Do a biopsy to confirm.
I'm going
to numb up the area
where we'll go in
for the punch biopsy.
Where's the new bracelet?
She was wearing the bracelet?
You didn't notice
that i was wearing it?
Because you weren't.
He noticed,
and you didn't?
If you don't like it,
it's fine, it's not a big deal.
I like it,
that's the point.
I'd rather have it
at home in the jewelry box
than getting peed on at work.
You got the patient's urine
on that arm?
When i was
putting in the catheter.
Why?
You've got a rash.
The bracelet's real.
I figured.
So what if the rash
isn't just a rash?
What if it's an infection?
If there were
rats in that basement,
then the liver failure could
be caused by leptospirosis.
It transfers through urine.
Rat pee to him,
his pee to you.
The infection
would need an entry point.
Look for
any recent scratches, cuts.
Look.
Next to his fingernail.
The infection
destroyed your liver,
which released toxins that
caused the locked-in syndrome.
You were dying
of a paper cut.
I hope you're right
this time.
We found rats
in your buddy dave's basement.
Tested positive
for leptospirosis.
That means we're
on the right treatment.
So...
try moving a finger.
Your brain needs to get
used to doing its job again.
Try harder.
I'm sure you've lost hope.
I know we've told you
several times
that we knew what this was,
but this time we're right.
Concentrate.
Move one finger for me.
Welcome back.
I did it.
Rat pee.
Very nice idea.
Who came up with it?
I did.
Good.
You okay with him
claiming the credit?
It was his idea.
He saw the rash...
if he did, he'd have hung
a "mission accomplished" banner
in my outer office.
Don't toy with him.
If you're going to fire him...
the fact
that he stole your idea
means that he cares enough
to lie.
That's all i needed to know.
Rat pee.
That's a very nice idea.
House.
You left this in my office.
No, i didn't.
So either i have
a hole in my pocket...
oh, that's right
i remember now,
i stole it.
Because if you had gone up there
to check out my girlfriend,
you wouldn't have come back here
and lied to me about it.
You would've
thrown her right in my face.
You underestimate
the entertainment value
of your obsessions.
And then
there were all those calls
you weren't taking
in front of me.
So i dialed the number
of the calls you weren't taking.
You're seeing
a psychiatrist.
You had no right
to invade my privacy.
Is... is that...?
yeah.
It's irony.
Hey...
god sent you.
Suddenly,
you're not so fascinating.
You're spying
on your team.
Prioritize, wilson.
Is that what you really want
to torture me about right now?
I don't want
to torture you at all.
I think this is a great thing.
Not something you have to drive
an hour out of town
to shroud in mystery.
Whining on someone's couch.
That's an excellent use
of my time.
Maybe i'll discover that
my childhood wasn't perfect.
So your attitude about
therapy clearly hasn't changed.
And yet you went.
Which leads me to believe
that maybe something else
has changed.
Maybe you think you can change.
I credit cuddy with that.
Not much credit to take,
because i'm not going back.
Oh, house, please...
i assume you went because
you're tired of screwing up
every chance
you get at happiness.
New contact.
Delete contact.
Do not let the fact
that i found out about it...
don't beat yourself up.
I'm not going back
because it doesn't work.
You'll end up alone.
{le http://www.megaupload.com/ du dbut sera supprim pour laisser seulement la fin du lien}
www.tvsubtitles.net