You made your point.
Now how'bout letting us do our jobs?
Our point'll be made when your company
stops tearing down this mountain.
- Then who's gonna feed our kids? You?
- If you really cared about your kids,
you'd want them to have air
to breathe when they grow up.
- What'd you say, you son of a bitch?
- You guys aren't the problem.
You're being hurt more than anyone.
You breathe in that coal dust.
Coal is the dirtiest
energy on earth.
Gonna need some backup.
Not enough for you thugs
to assault the environment?
Doug, please, don't.
Susan? Susan! You okay?
She needs to get to a hospital.
She's dehydrated.
We have medics here.
- Let 'em give her fluids.
- She has no pulse.
Either unhook your arm,
or I'm gonna break it off.
Either way, this protest is over.
All right.
- What happened?
- You passed out.
It's okay.
Just stay hydrated.
You know we'll be back.
We'll be back!
Stop screwing around.
I'm not... screwing around.
I just can't...
Can't...
I can't stand up.
House - Season 05 Episode 21
"Saviors"
Synchro: ShalimarFox, mpm
The HTeam's AnonymHouse
- I need to push back our getaway.
- No, you don't.
Found you a board.
Perfect size to learn on.
I'm just postponing.
Olandt from philly general
wants me to get a patient
in to see House.
- So?
- I owe him a favor.
He's taken about a dozen
of my referrals over the last year.
I meant so that's five seconds
to hand House the file,
30 for him to question
your real motives,
a minute for witty comments
comparing the length of your legs
to Thirteen's...
plenty of time left over for the shore.
I need to make sure he doesn't toss
the file as soon as I'm out of sight.
Baby, can't repay the favor
on another case?
After last week, I could really
use a break from this place.
We both could.
Once I'm sure
he's really on the case,
then we're out of here.
And these legs and every
other part of me will be all yours.
He's seen three different
specialists.
Interesting.
Almost as interesting as you trying
to step into Kutner's shoes
just days after
he stepped out of them.
I am not shoe shopping.
I'm just trying to repay a favor
to his referring doctor.
What's the mystery?
The nut case spends all his free time
wreaking havoc at toxic waste dumps.
Tox screen's negative.
No neurological, muscular,
or cardiovascular abnormalities.
The guys cares about the environment?
That makes him a nut case?
He's a single guy in his 20s.
He cares about getting his hybrid waxed
by girls who care
about the environment.
See? Not a nut case.
He's probably faking
so he can sue the cops
- and get a six-figure settlement.
- If it was true,
why would he consent to be seen by
the best diagnostician in the country?
Now who's trying to get
her hybrid waxed?
We need to do
a vestibular caloric test.
See if the balance problem
starts above or below the neck.
And when I say "we," I mean "you."
You're the one with the favor
to repay, not them.
I'm going to be injecting ice water
in your ear canal.
If the resulting eye movements
are at all erratic,
then the balance problem
is in your inner ear.
Those in every room?
- I think so.
- Can you get rid of them?
Preferably from every room?
They use over 30 pesticides
to grow commercial flowers.
- The medical industry would be more...
- Concerned with medicine?
Let's fix your body, and you can
go back to fixing the earth.
- This is gonna get uncomfortable.
- I spent 14 hours chained to a tire.
- Most doctors would recommend...
- Our planet's headed for destruction.
Coastlines under water,
a million species extinct.
Feels like I'm tumbling
ad over heels.
That's normal... sometimes
this test causes vertigo.
And nausea.
Cameron just brought me a case.
Cameron is happy in the e.r.
There's no way she wants her nose
back on your grindstone.
Egg white omelet, no bacon,
whole wheat toast.
I say it's not my grindstone
she's after
and not her nose she wants on it.
She and Chase are practically
living together.
- What did you just order?
- An omelet.
Since when do you pass on the swine?
And wheat toast?
Might as well eat
a sheet of sandpaper.
Yes, but I don't like eating
the same thing two days in a row.
Your bro's nurse
not lovin' the love handles?
I'm just not in the mood for bacon.
And you're obviously trying to avoid
talking about Kutner,
which is odd, because you spent
a whole week obsessing about why...
He's no longer on my team.
I'm sorry he's no longer on my team.
Nothing else to talk about.
You're wearing the watch
he gave you for secret santa.
Five functions,
including a stopwatch
to time how long it takes you
to ask me if I'm okay.
You gonna order?
Not hungry.
It's just weird.
She's brought cases before,
but he's never made her
run the tests.
Maybe he's looking for someone
to mother him after what happened.
Only kind of mothering House wants
involves a bullwhip, leather diapers,
and a credit card.
Mommy's home.
Test made the patient lose his lunch,
but his calorics are normal,
his inner ear is fine,
and he still can't balance himself.
How many normal test
results do we need
to know the patient's
a granola-filled phony?
- He's not lying about his symptoms.
- And you know this because...
she changed her shoes.
If he was faking, he'd have vomited
on the other side of the bed.
Sparring with the police and chaining
yourself up for days can cause stress.
Stress screws with
the heart and arteries.
Carotid atherosclerosis
could cause a loss of balance.
Wouldn't show up on CT or MRI.
Could also be our only
warning before a massive stroke.
Do a holter and a carotid doppler.
See if his heart skips for more
than the spotted owl.
Although I didn't say "we."
If I had...
Sorry if this
is screwing up the test.
I've been hiccupping a lot
lately, but... not as bad as this.
How much is "a lot"
and how long is "lately"?
It's been on and off
for about a week.
Maybe a few hours a day.
Did you tell the doctors
in philly about it?
They didn't seem to think
it was any big deal.
So we're still leaving
tomorrow, aren't we?
I'm not sure.
The referring doctors didn't
realize that his hiccups were...
Hiccups?
With this duration and intensity,
mostly likely pathological,
and it could mean it's serious.
- Are you avoiding me?
- No.
So I shouldn't be at all concerned
that you're treating another
doctor's patient for hiccups
instead of going on a vacation
I spent a week planning.
There is a reason
I need to stay with this case
a while longer,
but I can't tell you what it is.
So... you admit you lied to me.
And now you're
asking me to trust you?
Yes.
No sign of heart
or arterial problems,
but he's been hiccupping
on and off for over a week.
Nice! I'm hooked.
You can get back to your shift
at the e.r.
Except, as far as the e.r. is concerned,
you're on vacation, right?
I postponed a trip because
I'm concerned about the patient.
Explains why you ditched Chase
and came to the differentials,
- not why you ran the tests.
- You told me to.
I'm not your boss, as you usually take
great pleasure in pointing out.
You don't still have
the hots for me, do you?
I care about the patient, and I care
about the people who work on your team.
They've been through a lot lately.
I just thought...
Was florence nightingale.
You're gonna nurse us back
to spiritual and mental oneness.
Would make sense if we were
having this conversation a week ago.
Think what you want...
that I'm here to get a job,
that I'm here to wrap you
in swaddling clothes.
The problem is, I think neither.
Because neither makes sense.
The only thing that does...
doesn't.
Pathological hiccups
plus inability to balance... go.
What she said.
Brain would connect the two.
It could, if cameron hadn't
already ct'd his head.
Empty as her boyfriend's calendar.
What does this have
to do with Chase?
- Nothing.
- Not sure yet.
Patient is on a jihad
against commercial flowers.
He's picketed several nurseries.
Organophosphate poisoning
- can cause both hiccups and...
- No g.i. problems, no hyper-salivation.
It's possible
it's not connected to a protest.
M.s. wouldn't show on the CT,
and his name's Swenson.
Scandinavians have an increased
susceptibility to m.s.
Better theory than he's faking it.
The clogs have it.
Do a lumbar puncture to confirm m.s.
I guess we'll just continue
to twiddle our thumbs.
God, I hope that's a euphemism.
How I'm supposed to do a lumbar puncture
on a patient with intractable hiccups?
I'm trying to figure out what
that could be a euphemism for.
You'll find a way.
You're not worried House is gonna be
pissed you're helping me do the test?
He said find a way, and you did.
- How do you think House is doing?
- That why you're here?
No, it isn't.
Even if house was messed up
by Kutner's suicide, it wouldn't matter.
He already thinks life
is nasty, brutish, and long.
And misery helps
his diagnostic skills.
All of which you know, so...
- why are you here?
- Which answer would you believe?
If you want Kutner's place,
it's fine by me.
I could use someone else with
the stones to stand up to House.
But you've gotta know it's gonna blow up
your relationship with Chase.
All I did was postpone
a three-day trip.
With Chase, to be with House.
- What are you doing?
- Ordering i.v. chlorpromazine.
This could still be neurological.
You could cloud his mental status.
You wanna get the needle
in his spine or you wanna talk?
You and House been talking
about filling Kutner's slot?
Yeah, we went straight
from the funeral to human resources.
You interested in getting
back on the team?
I'm interested in knowing
if Cameron's interested.
She's been running all the tests
for House's case.
Well, she hasn't said
anything to me.
But I guess, the referring doctor
might have asked her
to keep an eye on him.
Do you think Cameron's
in love with House?
That is a ridiculous question.
She's in love with you.
Are you in love with House?
That...
is an even more ridiculous question.
Two questions, zero answers.
Think I can extrapolate from there.
Sorry, I'm just
the zone delivery guy.
I'm, Doug Swenson's wife.
His history said the environmental
kamikaze was single.
He... he probably didn't
want me to worry.
He told me he was in jail with
some of the other protters.
Yeah, no worries there.
He's... in jail a lot.
Not so often in the hospital.
I searched his email, and I found
the referral to you yesterday.
You must really love your husband.
And travel by rickshaw.
It only took you
18 hours to get here.
Who eats kale?
It's so bland,
it doesn't even taste like kale.
I had to find somebody to take care
of our four-year-old son.
- Doug's all right, isn't he?
- I have no idea.
I know he's an idiot.
And now I've learned that he's a liar.
So we're making a...
- who told you that I was in here?
- The doctor in the office next to yours
said that you might be here.
I got it figured out.
- That mean we don't need to do the lp?
- I was talking to her.
- You're not even supposed to be here.
- You want us to stop or not?
What?
I don't care what you do with him.
You're not doing a favor
for a doctor in philly.
You're doing a favor for
an oncologist in north Jersey.
I'm spying on you for Wilson?
Spying, preemptive grief counseling.
Wilson sees you ten times
more than I do,
he's a better liar, and he wouldn't have
to cancel a vacation to do it.
Good points.
Also doesn't explain the diet.
What does any of this
have to do with my husband?
Nothing.
Meet mrs. Environmental nutbag.
- Or did you keep your maiden name?
- He's married?
Yep, got a kid too.
Double threat.
Eco-freak and deadbeat dad.
- Sorry... parentally challenged.
- No, his neck.
It's torticollis.
Reaction to the chlorpromazine.
It's not just a spasm.
It's swollen.
Crunchy.
It's definitely not m.s.
Crunching sounds were caused by
an air leak between his lungs.
Lead in his mediastinum could've
been caused by prolonged hiccups.
- More likely, it was the neck spasm.
- Maybe It was there all along.
We just didn't notice it till
the other symptoms made it worse.
What causes loss of balance,
pathological hiccups,
and a hole in his gloria steinem?
He was protesting
a lumber mill last fall.
- Sarcoid's been linked to pine forests.
- No, his a.c.e. Levels were normal.
Progressive systemic sclerosis?
Guy practically lives
at industrial waste sites.
If a solvent got absorbed through his
lungs, caused an autoimmune firestorm.
Start him on iv methyl-prednisolone
for systemic sclerosis.
- Do a full work-up to confirm.
- By myself?
Without yourself.
Grab a bat.
Grab some pine.
Time to bring in the first string.
Why?
You obviously want to be here.
I can't figure out why.
I wanna see where you go
when you can't be here.
You know what vacation means, right?
You're here because of House,
Chase, or overtime issues.
He's very concerned.
- Chase, not... House.
- If it's all right with you,
I'd rather communicate with Chase
by communicating with Chase.
Are you in love with House?
You... are not concerned about me.
You're marking your territory.
You shouldn't
be involved with House.
Neither should I.
Neither should anyone.
You and Chase are good together.
Just don't screw it up.
- When are you gonna stop this?
- How can you ask me to stop?
You're in a hospital.
You have a son.
The steroids ought to get him
breathing normally again.
But autoimmune diseases are serious.
It might not be a bad idea
to take some time at home, rest up.
I can't just quit.
Do you hate us that much?
I love you.
And I love our son.
But why should he matter more
than everyone else's?
- He does.
- Why??
Because he's biologically
connected to me?
There's no rational reason.
He's our son!
And he's gonna need
to drink clean water.
And breathe clean air.
I'm doing this for him too.
Come on in, House.
Because who else is it
going to be at 10:30 at night?
And no, thanks.
I already ate.
Didn't ask you to dinner.
But you were going to.
And when I explained
that I'd eaten hours ago,
you were going to move on
to your real entree,
rifling through my kitchen.
Inviting me to search your kitchen.
Means you know that I'd find nothing,
or you know that I'd find something,
you're hoping that I'm going to assume
the former and I won't bother to look.
Or it means it's late, I'm tired,
I know you're here to advance
some paranoid theory
based on a single egg white omelet,
and I'd like to get it over with
- so we can both go to sleep.
- Your single-omelet theory
conveniently overlooks the grassy knoll
you had for lunch today:
vegetable and grain gag-athon.
The warren commission found no evidence
of a second lunch,
possibly because it was stolen
from the doctor's lounge.
You're not getting any fatter.
Your medical records were clean.
- You checked my...
- You're alone tonight,
so it's Kutner.
How could Kutner
have any conceivable...
Your patients live,
your patients die.
You float above it all
like a medical colossus.
- But a fellow doctor dies...
- That's brilliant.
Kutner was a wake-up call
that if I didn't eat healthier,
I might kill myself.
Mortality is mortality.
And... ice cream...
is ice cream.
Full fat content.
Quadruple fat content.
Stuff you haven't eaten just
proves you haven't eaten it.
You were hoping for evidence
of stuff I have eaten?
First door on the right.
Excruciating pain in his left leg!
Acute onset about ten minutes ago.
What are you doing to him?
I assume they were checking
for vascular pulsations.
Either it's negative,
or he's a big wuss.
It's not a tumor or an aneurism!
Metabolic bone disease?
Bone density's normal!
But the bone covering might not be!
If it's osteomyelitis, an infection
- eating away at his periosteum...
- That explains the pain.
Odds are it's a subclinical infection
that we made it worse with the steroids.
Start him on IV antibiotics.
X-ray his legs
to confirm osteomyelitis.
Cameron's done
a full set of lower-body x-rays.
The infection obviously flared.
Do 'em again.
Even if I had changed my diet,
what possible reason could
I have for hiding it from you?
Ankle, tibia, fibula...
all look normal.
No inflammation, no signs of osteo.
Hang in there.
We're almost done.
You and your wife...
you talk about stuff?
Sex.
- No. Anything else?
- Money.
I'm gonna go way out on a limb here.
Foreman not a chatty Cathy?
Normally, it doesn't matter.
But last week it did.
You wanna date men,
good chance talking won't be...
his femur's fractured.
That's impossible.
It's the hardest bone in the body.
And he broke it lying in bed.
How can you have a broken femur
without so much as a bruise?
Whatever broke it
had to do it from within.
Osteogenesis imperfecta?
Brittle bones
wouldn't cause hiccups,
plus, we'd have seen abnormal
coloring in the sclerae.
Which leaves cancer.
Since when does bone cancer
cause hiccups?
Which means it's not bone cancer.
Or it's not cancer.
House is right.
It'd be hard to find a guy
outside Chernobyl
who'd been exposed
to more carcinogens.
Pesticide plants,
nuclear waste sites.
Tell Chase to repair the break.
You two prep him for chemo.
You wanna blast him with chemo
for a cancer
- we don't even know he has?
- Nope
I wanna blast him with chemo
for a cancer that explains the symptoms.
Intramedullary nail.
Hold on.
That your House imitation?
Some late-breaking epiphany?
I just need you to get a bone biopsy
before you insert the pin.
- For a broken leg?
- House is prepping him for chemo.
Thought it might be worth checking
before pumping him full of poison.
- Does Cameron agree with House?
- Cameron isn't on the case anymore.
Still enjoying your day off, I see.
- Why are you prepping him for chemo?
- The more interesting question is
why do you care?
- You're not even sure that it's...
- Why do you care from here?
You can monitor the patient from home.
What's the difference between the two?
You're not at my home?
- This has nothing to do with...
- Any other differences?
Less medical equipment,
more training bras,
and more vegemite sandwiches.
Actually, technically,
right now, Chase is here.
That's because you ignored
that I called him.
And it's irrelevant to my point,
which is...
you and Chase are over.
You are wrong.
You decided that his single drawer
of clothes is one drawer too many.
But you don't have
the guts to tell him,
so... you're emotionally
walking away...
instead of actually walking away.
Which is stupid, because only one
of those is good for your heart.
He's gonna ask me to marry him.
I... was looking
for some thick socks.
Found the ring.
And you want to say no?
So I circle right back
to his single drawer of clothes...
I don't want to say anything.
I don't want him to ask.
Not now.
Couldn't hurt...
we're all a little freaked out.
We go home, we just
wanna hug someone.
We just wanna know everything's
gonna be okay.
I don't want him to propose
just 'cause he's scared.
She's got a headache, fever.
She's completely exhausted.
Tell him about your chest, honey.
Her breasts are really tender.
You guys have a hot tub?
- She must go to the gym a lot.
- Not in years.
Then maybe, when you
travel on business,
you zip on down
to that complimentary hotel spa...
- Sorry, did you just say yes?
- What the hell's wrong with her?
- Got a minute?
- He doesn't.
- What's wrong with her?
- Sorry.
I'm sure she's got a medical crisis,
and I need more time to figure out
some leading questions
for your wife.
- What's going on with Cameron?
- She doesn't want back on my team
and she doesn't want to jump me.
What?
You ask a question,
I rule out two possibilities,
and you're satisfied?
That means you don't want an answer.
You just wanted to know there
wasn't a particular answer.
Either you were worried
that she wanted back,
or you were worried
that she wanted back on me.
This isn't a medical crisis, is it?
Could be.
A lot of STDs hang in the balance.
I give up.
Vinegar compresses four times a day.
Any chance I could just
leave it at that?
Pseudomomas folliculitis.
It's a skin infection
from crowded and contaminated
hot tubs,
which you obviously use,
but not with your husband.
Tried to help a sister out.
The nuclei were all normal sized.
Bone cells were well differentiated.
No dysplasia means no cancer.
That's good, isn't it?
We hope so.
Although it also means we still have
no idea what caused the break.
How does it feel?
It hurts.
- Is it supposed to look like that?
- No, but it's probably
residual bleeding from the surgery.
We should be able to...
I need two units of FFP, right away!
My God!
What's happening?
He's bleeding out.
- Means it's gotta be cancer.
- It's gotta be, except it's not.
- The biopsy was negative.
- Biopsies can be wrong. Symptoms can't.
All signs point to cancer, but you can't
blast a cancer you can't find.
Sure you can.
Prep him for total body irradiation.
You do realize that's insane.
Not unless you think the cancer's
cleverly hiding outside his body.
Steroids weakened his immune system.
That much radiation will kill him
before it kills the cancer.
And if he doesn't have cancer,
we could cause one,
or destroy his system altogether.
He could die from an infection.
You'd rather do nothing,
just let him die on his own?
I'd rather make his cancer worse.
Give him insulin-like growth factor,
make any tumor or malignancy grow.
- Grows big enough, we can find it.
- That's pouring gasoline on a fire.
At least total body irradiation's
an actual treatment.
His idea is better.
Pour away.
I lost my mojo.
Have you retraced your steps?
Does your cleaning lady
check your pockets before...
I was clueless about Kutner.
I was wrong about Cameron.
Taub came up with an idea that I should
have seen long before he did.
No one saw anything coming
with Kutner.
You hardly ever see Cameron anymore.
And you hired Taub to come up with ideas
that you wouldn't have come up with.
And I have no idea
why you're eating carrots.
Good.
I'm losing my mind.
All you got to say is "good"?
House, a guy you worked with
for two years,
who you mentored and, yes,
possibly even cared about,
just blew his brains out.
You can't find the reason,
can't find the meaning in it,
because sometimes there isn't any.
Sometimes...
this is all there is.
You should be losing it.
You'd be crazy not to be
off your game.
But your mojo
is right where you left it.
Just... keep playing with it.
I gotta go.
Help yourself.
I know this is a tough process.
At the first sign of any tumors
or masses, we can...
start saying prayers?
It's gonna be OK.
Once we can...
No, it's not gonna be okay.
You're growing his cancer.
This isn't the doctors' fault.
I've exposed myself
to a lot of bad stuff.
I knew the risks.
I want my life to mean something.
If that means I'm destined to...
He's in v-tach and no pulse!
Grab the paddles!
Charging.
Clear!
Clear.
I've been looking for you.
And... I've been thinking about you.
Just hadn't reached
the looking stage yet.
Which is the problem.
You asked for a day.
I gave you two.
You told me you had a secret
you couldn't share.
I respected that.
Now I don't know what's worse...
blowing off our vacation
to hang around House
or continuing to blow it off
when he won't hang around you.
If you think I'm
bit interested in House...
I don't know what
I'm supposed to think.
I know this looks bad, and...
I don't care how it looks.
I care what it is.
And you're not telling me
what it is.
I'm trying to trust you, but...
just...
I need a little more time.
This...
has nothing to do with House.
Yeah, well, it has nothing
to do with me, either.
Not anymore.
Let me know when I can come
pick up my things.
Nothing on the echo.
We drew a troponin level.
No signs of myocardial ischemia.
All the tests were normal.
Loss of balance.
Pathological hiccups.
Air leak between the lungs.
Broken femur, now tachycardia.
Go!
Come on, give me something.
Give me a bad idea.
Maybe I could turn it
into a good one.
Fine.
Open him up, put in a defibrillator.
That's permanent and risky.
We don't even know what,
if anything is wrong with his heart.
Redo all the tests.
In the meantime, open him up,
put in a defibrillator...
so he can live long enough
for you to finish the tests.
Balance organs, nerves,
lungs, bones, heart.
Things you use to make bratwurst.
There's no sign of infection.
It's not a metabolic
or autoimmune disease.
It's definitely not cancer.
- I think.
- Definitely not cancer.
Aren't you gonna pick?
I'm thinking.
Is there a ticking clock?
You already put your money in.
- You never do that until you decide.
- That's very observant of you.
Too bad you distracted me.
Now I'm...
thinking I might change my mind.
There's nothing healthy
in that machine.
No, there's not.
Gummi bears.
You hate gummi bears.
People can change.
More importantly, I hate them.
Fine...
then I won't offer you any.
You manipulative bitch.
You're not suddenly eating
healthy because you want to.
You're eating healthy because
you know I don't want to.
I've been mooching food
for ten years.
Now, either it suddenly started
bothering you this week
- or you're...
- screwing with you.
It needed to be done.
After Amber died, I withdrew,
tried to change everything,
hoping I'd sort it out,
find some deeper truth.
It was a mistake.
I should have gone back
to normal, to here and now,
because that's all we can
ever really count on.
Things need to get
back to normal in your life,
and what could be more normal
than me screwing with you...
and you figuring it out?
You manipulative bitch.
We need to put in
a cardioverter-defibrillator.
It'll keep your heart beating
while we keep looking.
What does that mean?
It means, even if we
figure this out,
you'll have to stop protesting
anywhere not near a hospital.
Got a few questions.
We're about to start doing...
A hopefully pointless
medical procedure.
Your life and my mojo
hang in the balance.
Pesticides are evil.
Which means that commercial
flowers are dowsed in evil.
But plant life
is nature's answer to evil.
So you have a garden?
No, we live in an apartment.
- A window box, then?
- No.
- Potted plants?
- Nothing, the commercial growers...
Yeah, they're evil. Got it.
House, I really don't think
we have the time for this.
Your marriage sucks.
Thank you.
All marriages suck.
Your marriage sucks.
I love her.
He loves a tree in Oregon
more than he loves you.
But he can't have sex with it.
Unless it's that slutty oak
outside Portland.
You wanna get to your point?
She's had enough.
She's gonna leave.
Or maybe she's just not
putting out, whatever.
You gotta make it right, right away.
You gotta compromise that
precious flower principle.
Never.
Once.
Three weeks ago.
Our anniversary.
I missed the dinner
to be at that rally.
You planned it for months.
You were mad.
Really mad.
I bought you flowers.
I brought them home.
And you were gone.
So was your suitcase.
I tossed them and bought you
the earrings.
Roses?
You have sporotrichosis.
It's an infection
from the thorn of the rose
which, by any other name,
is still a cheap marital aid.
- The flowers are what gave me...
- Lesion on your eighth cranial nerve
knocks out your balance.
Another on your phrenic nerve
gives you serial hiccups.
We then spread it to your bones
and heart with steroids
and insulin-like growth factor.
Please tell us
that this is good news.
It's good news for him.
It's good news
for future generations.
It's crappy news for you.
He's gonna be fine.
He'll never doubt himself again.
There you go.
Damn, I was hoping I would
interrupt something.
Your favor's repaid.
Patient's cured.
He's already packing for another
Earth day extravaganza next week.
He almost died.
He can't take a few days?
People only change after trauma
if they wanted to change
before the trauma.
Or if they've watched too many
afterschool specials.
- You talking about Chase?
- I'm talking about you.
You lost husband number one.
No surprise that the death
of a colleague
would make you question another
long-term lease.
You teaching commitment classes?
I thought you were too busy...
I'm sure that was going to be
hysterical. I give you the cliff notes.
Don't try to dump him
by dumping cases on me.
I told you I never
wanted to dump Chase.
Absolutely.
You want him to dump you.
It's totally different.
Much less guilt.
Either way, you're out
of reasons to avoid him.
Kutner was a pretty dumb one
to begin with.
I should never have
postponed our vacation.
I should never have planned it.
I found the ring in your sock.
I didn't want you to propose
out of some sort of...
knee-jerk reaction
to what happened to Kutner.
Guess you don't have
to worry about that anymore.
I'm not, I...
I don't care what happens.
I just...
want it to happen.
Are you proposing to me?
I'm...
proposing that...
you propose to me.
After I broke up with you?
After you ruined
my planned proposal,
- you expect me to...
- I'm not expecting.
I'm hoping.
Solved another case.
Busted Wilson.
Looks like you're not
losing it after all.
The HTeam's AnonymHouse
www.tvsubtitles.net