- It's way too fast.
- It felt good.
- If we could clear
the stage quickly, please.
- Maury, it's too fast.
- It's exactly the same.
- Then slow it down.
- Everything
all right, Jeremy?
- Sure.
Ready whenever you are.
- From the allegro, please.
- What's his problem?
- His back's not 100%.
- He can't talk
to the conductor like that.
- No, he can't.
She could.
- You okay with the lift?
- I'll be fine unless
you mess up the timing.
- My timing is perfect.
- It was last night.
- Moment of truth.
- Aah.
- Damn it.
- Penelope, are you all right?
- She--she can't breathe!
Call a doctor!
- Are you gonna ignore me
all day again?
I help you.
- You tried to kill Chase.
- Doing what you wanted,
that's all, boss.
- I exist.
- No, you don't.
I acknowledge
my subconscious exists.
Now go away.
Saying it is one thing.
Living it is another.
You're not rational...
not completely.
- Put the phone
on the receiver,
send the hookers home,
and get dressed.
We've got a case.
- I'm taking a personal day.
- 21-year-old star
at the New York Ballet
collapsed on stage.
- I love ballet.
But as someone
may have mentioned,
I'm taking a personal day.
- Cuddy said get your ass in
or you're fired.
- She's not gonna fire me.
- She's not gonna fire you...
if you don't go to work?
- Okay.
- How long do you figure
till I just disappear?
- Hold on.
- No tumors or punctures
in the lungs,
no bruising,
no sign of trauma, no STDs.
- And supplemental oxygen's
only gotten
her saturation level to 60.
Lungs keep collapsing
despite a chest tube.
- E.R. ruled out the obvious.
White count and temp
were normal, so no pneumonia.
- Coffee's burnt.
Thirteen's wearing
cherry-flavored lip gloss.
Foreman's staring at you.
Any of that helpful?
- House?
- STD?
- We just said the tests were
negative. You think we should--
- No.
- She's a dancer.
What about dehydration?
- What about
a pulmonary contusion?
C.T. showed no inflammation
on the lungs.
- What about dehydration?
- B.U.N. and Creatinine
are elevated but within range.
- Hey, I'm just the irrational
part of your brain,
but elevated means high, right?
Dehydration
could hide an infection.
- Dehydration
Go treat her
for the obvious--
I.V. fluids and antibiotics
for the pneumonia.
- We're like Magic and Kareem.
- Mr. Pietramala,
you have kidney cancer.
- Wow.
Is that a bad one?
I mean, they're all bad, but--
- The door was closed
for a reason.
- Well, now it's open
We need to talk.
- H-he just told me
I have kidney cancer.
- Then you'll obviously need
a moment to process.
- House.
- I'm hallucinating.
- I'm...
I'll be right back.
- I need you to sit in
on my differentials,
double-check everything I do.
- You can't treat
patients if--
- It's got to be sleep apnea.
I get a good night's sleep,
and I still feel exhausted.
Lack of delta sleep
can lead to hallucinations.
- Do you have
any other neurological symptoms?
- I don't think so.
- Aphasia?
- No.
- Memory loss?
- Irritability?
- Yeah, that one!
- Don't deflect.
He cares about you.
You care about him.
- You shouldn't be practicing.
At least--
- Tell him--
- Enough!
Don't give me the look.
I told you I was hallucinating.
- Who were you talking to?
- Someone
who's not actually here.
Beyond that seems irrelevant.
- Your mind made a choice.
It means something.
- You know
he's just gonna keep asking.
- Kutner.
- Good choice.
He feels bad.
- You gonna help me or not?
- Yeah.
- I could eat from this place
seven days a week.
- We practically do.
- You can order
tomorrow night.
Do you want some wine?
- No, thanks.
I have my husband's sperm.
- Your dead husband's?
- We froze it
when he got diagnosed.
- And you kept it?
All this time?
- I used to think
if I didn't find anyone, then--
- You found someone.
- I know,
But...
- What if it goes wrong?
What if I turn out to be
a-a radical anarchist
with a secret family
and that I-I age backwards?
- Nobody plans
on getting divorced.
I didn't plan
on my husband dying.
But he did.
- So you--you're saying
you want a prenup...
in liquid form.
- What if it's not
sleep apnea?
Trauma from
your motorcycle accident?
Vicodin abuse?
You need to be admitted.
- I know you're wrong
about sleep apnea,
which means you know
you're wrong about sleep apnea.
You're scared.
Tell him you're scared.
- I can't sleep with you here.
- Did it work?
- Do you see someone
standing beside me?
- No.
- Then, no.
- So what's next on your list
of things it's not?
- Patient's not responding
to the antibiotics.
Still can't breathe.
- So run a test
to confirm it's pneumonia.
- We can't do a bronc
because her lungs
are still collapsed.
- Transtracheal aspiration.
- That's basically
waterboarding.
- It is pretty radical.
- It's a great idea.
- Regular radical,
me radical,
or me out of my mind radical?
- Somewhere
between regular and you.
- So what's the problem?
- Everything okay?
- No.
Our patient can't breathe.
Either do the test
or come up with a better one.
So we're down to infection,
trauma, M.S., schizophrenia,
or pills.
- Schizophrenia
usually manifests younger.
- That's why
it's further down the list.
I can confirm an infection
with a simple blood test.
- An infection
can be treated...
cured.
Means you still got a job.
Means you still got a life.
It doesn't make it
a better idea, just a nicer one.
This the rational you talking?
- Can't do this on my own.
- When we inject the water,
it's gonna feel
like you're drowning.
But it'll be over
in a few seconds.
- Then it'll be better?
- A little.
- Hold her shoulders down
a little.
Ready?
- You're doing great.
Here comes the liquid.
- Taub.
- I slipped.
Oh, no.
- What?
- Her skin came off.
- Her skin is sloughing off
faster than we can replace it
with the artificial skin.
- Could be autoimmune.
- A.N.A. was negative.
- Focus on the lungs.
- You want us
to ignore the fact
that she's lost 80%
of her skin?
- We know
it's not lung cancer.
Could be a liver tumor,
eats through to the lungs.
Get an ultrasound of her liver.
If you find masses,
get a biopsy.
- We can't just ignore
the skin.
It's obviously
the most significant
and dangerous symptom
right now.
- I don't think
it is a symptom.
I think we caused it.
- By doing what?
- I prescribed antibiotics.
- Toxic epidermal necrolysis--
that's a one-in-a-million
reaction.
- Yeah, well,
maybe this is the one.
Get swabs
of her old skin to confirm.
Where the hell were you?
- I do have a practice.
- Ballerina
has toxic epidermal necrolysis.
- Are you sure?
- About to be.
- You didn't do anything wrong.
You prescribed antibiotics.
Any other doctor would've done
the exact same thing.
- Any other doctor?
Words can hurt, you know.
I have no reason
to feel guilty.
It doesn't make any sense...
unless there's something wrong
in the limbic area of my brain.
- Guilt as a symptom?
- It's consistent with M.S.
And since the blood tests
were negative,
I have to apologize.
If I feel better,
then you're right.
I was feeling an emotion.
If I feel nothing...
it means
my limbic brain is shot.
- I'm Dr. House.
Anyone explain
to you your status?
They found a mass
in my liver--cancer.
- They said they think
they can treat it
and that the skin
is starting to take.
- I'll be able to dance again.
- She's half dead,
and she's wondering
if she'll ever plie again?
Healthy priorities.
Let the mocking begin.
I'm sorry.
I...
treated you for an infection
before confirming
that you had one.
That's why you lost your skin.
I know you're in pain.
I know that I caused it.
I'm sorry.
- Very nice.
- Thank you?
- Nothing.
- Maybe you didn't mean it.
- I meant it.
- Did you do a liver biopsy
to confirm--
- Couldn't. The artificial skin
was too thin.
She'd bleed out.
Why were you talking
to the patient?
- I think skinless women
are hot.
Do a transjugular liver biopsy.
If she bleeds,
at least it stays in her veins.
- Did you just check
with Wilson again?
- No.
I felt nothing.
It's M.S.
- Apologies aren't supposed
to make you feel better.
They're supposed to make
the other person feel better.
- In order
to make you feel better.
- Fine. You want to do
an L.P. to confirm,
or is guilt enough
to start filling prescriptions?
- Last mass about a centimeter
to your right.
Problem?
- Short burst of flutter.
We're almost done.
- Entering
the right hepatic vein.
Cameron kept
her dead husband's sperm.
- She doesn't like yours?
- She likes his better.
Or at least she...
wants to hang on to it
in case mine is...
unfaithful or something.
- Wow.
- Advancing two centimeters.
- You got to let her do it.
If you don't,
you'll be stuck
with her forever.
- I want to be stuck
- She married a dying guy.
She has issues.
You...
cannot leave her...
ever, for any reason,
'cause then you're not just
the guy who left her,
you're the guy
who killed her kids.
That's not a good rhythm.
Get out.
- Narrow complex tachycardia--
she's gonna crash.
- The biopsy was negative for cancer
but the procedure
sent her heart into a-fib.
- We don't know
it was the biopsy
that caused the heart problem.
Maybe the heart
caused the lungs to collapse.
- Why is Wilson here?
- You were looking for cancer.
Thought it'd be helpful if--
- We didn't find cancer.
- Yes, which you reported
to me five seconds ago.
Thought I'd let him finish
his hors d'oeuvre
before getting the bouncer
to take care of him.
- Until we can regulate
the heart,
we can't get
any meaningful pictures.
So we can't tell--
- Metoprolol
can correct irregular heart--
- Tried it.
Didn't work.
Is Cuddy making him oversee--
- No.
- Heart's too irregular
for MRI.
Other scans would--
- Then you're making him
oversee your choices.
You don't trust yourself.
Why?
- Wilson, get out.
- Are you sure?
- Do I need your approval
to throw you out?
- You happy now?
- There's only one time her
heart's gonna be perfectly still
for our pictures,
and that's when she's dead.
- If it's not M.S.,
severe mental illness
and vicodin
are all that's left.
Mental illness means...
you can no longer
practice medicine.
Vicodin means detox,
which means pain
for the rest of your life,
which means you can no longer
practice medicine.
- Are you saying
we should kill her?
- No.
- If we stopped her heart,
we could get our pictures
and then restart it.
- What if we can't restart it?
- Then she stays dead.
- We restart hearts
all the time.
- It'll take four minutes
for us to MRI
her entire heart.
- And we only have
three minutes
until there's brain damage.
You sure about this?
- Yeah.
We're gonna stop her heart
so I can MRI it.
I think it was her idea.
Pneumonia was her idea, and it
almost killed the patient.
- Her?
- Oops.
- Kutner was secretly a woman.
That's why he killed himself.
It's Amber.
- Your subconscious
picked my dead girlfriend?
- Yeah.
The irrational part of my brain
works like the rational part
of yours.
How about that?
- It...raises questions.
- It answers questions.
- Who cares?
I've got competing ideas.
They can't both be right.
- Everybody gets competing
ideas. Everybody has doubts.
- So is it regular radical,
me radical,
or me out of my mind radical?
- It's on the upper end
of you radical.
Do you have any alternative?
- Nothing that anyone
in my head has come up with.
- Then you're
as safe as you can be.
- Great.
You get the L.P. results back?
Yeah.
It's a big shock.
You don't have M.S.
But while I had
your blood sample,
I checked vicodin levels--
way too high.
- I need the pills.
- Not an argument.
He knows that's not an argument.
- It could still be
schizophrenia.
- House...
if you're on anti-psych meds,
you're not gonna
be able to practice.
- I know.
- You'd prefer
electroshock therapy to rehab?
- I'd prefer something
that could actually work.
- You're rationalizing.
- No kidding.
- I know that you're afraid
of the pain, but electroshock--
- Don't give me
the cancer voice,
that overly earnest tone.
- Heart attack, stroke,
seizure, death, or worse.
- Worse?
Double death?
- You live, but you damage
the only thing you care about--
your rational mind.
I'll make some calls.
- I'll actually be dead?
- Just your heart,
just for a little while.
- Hopefully.
- I had an idea.
- Stop having ideas.
- Insulin shock.
- Yes.
That's marginally
less dangerous than E.C.T.
puts you in a coma.
Could cause--
- Could work.
- If you had psychosis,
which you don't.
- I've had no diarrhea,
no sweating, no vomiting,
none of the symptoms
of vicodin overdose.
- Yeah, except
the "I see dead people" thing.
- I've been popping pills
for years.
I've only been seeing things
for days.
Something changed.
- Vicodin addiction
is still more likely.
- So we're no longer dealing
in absolutes.
- House, I'll be up
in five minutes.
Then we can talk
about how you'd rather be
in a coma than in rehab.
- Actually, if you could be
up here in two,
that'd be really helpful.
- Why?
- 'Cause I'm about
to put myself
into insulin shock.
- Left atrium is fine.
- Left coronary artery
also fine.
We're almost at three minutes.
- Keep going.
- Chordae tendineae clear.
- Right atrium is fine.
- I got to start her back up.
- We have some time.
- We're over.
- Right coronary artery
is fine.
- The three-minute threshold
is a guideline.
- She might have less.
We have to stop.
- What's that by the aorta?
- I don't see anything.
- I'm restarting her heart.
- That's a shadow.
Two centimeters--
- You're only scared
because you know
this is gonna work.
- We're over three minutes.
- I need glucose in here!
You could've died.
- It worked.
Where are my pants?
- Are you sure?
- She's been everywhere
I've been for days.
She's not here, ergo...
- This was not
the next rational step.
- Now who's being biased?
You wanted me to detox
as much as I wanted--
I forgot how to do my zipper.
- Any other
neurological deficits?
- You don't seem to annoy me
as much as usual.
Not sure that's a deficit.
and...
I'm all better.
- Is she really gone?
- Absolutely.
I can feel myself repressing
all kinds of icky things.
I check out, don't I?
Damn.
- He didn't see anything.
He saw an artifact
on the monitor.
- It was a shadow
on her heart.
- She'd already been
technically dead
for three minutes.
I thought keeping her alive
took precedence
over prolonging the photo op.
- Any brain damage?
- No, all tests indicat--
- Obviously you had more time.
Best of luck.
- I assume we can't kill her
again and take more pictures.
- Uh, you'll want to check
with Wilson?
- Good one.
- It's something, a lesion.
- Tumor, scar tissue.
- Could be an abscess,
infection.
Explains why it's invisible
in the blood.
It's doing its damage
behind closed doors,
sealed off.
- See, the problem
with speculation
is you make a spec out of "u"
and some guy named "lation,"
which really
doesn't affect me at all.
- We have to guess.
It's all we've got.
We can't do a biopsy.
Last time we went
into her heart,
she had a major cardiac event.
- Which just leaves...
- What are you looking for?
- I don't know yet.
- The picture doesn't change.
She lies there in pain.
He sits there worried.
- Nothing changes.
I just had an epiphany...
all by myself.
Popped into my head
out of nothing.
- Care to share?
- He's too devoted.
- Too devoted?
You think he feels guilty?
- Right, I'm being cynical.
People can care because they
care, not because they cheated,
theoretically true.
But gonorrhea fits better.
- No. No STDs.
We tested her.
- You tested her blood.
- That is the test.
- That's not
where her problem is.
Gonorrhea disseminated
to her heart,
got walled off in an abscess.
It'd be invisible.
- And...
would look like a shadow.
- No need to test her again,
but we can check
Prince Charming.
Once you confirm,
cut the abscess
out of her heart.
- Here are your onion rings,
extra well-done.
- Thank you, Molly.
And another beer
when you get a chance.
I'm celebrating.
- Alone?
- Thank goodness.
Don't tell me.
I was right.
- Yep.
Boyfriend has gonorrhea.
- And everyone's a winner.
- He's not too happy about it.
He insists he's never cheated
and must've gotten it from her.
- Don't think so.
- Timing would fit.
He's got no symptoms,
and she's dying.
- Lying would fit too.
- He's not hanging out
in her room anymore.
What does it matter?
You were right.
We're prepping her for surgery.
- I saw guilt in him.
If he's not actually guilty...
then I wasn't right.
I was lucky.
- House,
you made a brilliant deduction
about her heart.
- And if I was just lucky...
- # enjoy #
# yourself #
# it's later than you think #
# enjoy #
# yourself #
# while you're still
in the pink #
# the years #
# go by #
# as quickly as a wink #
# enjoy yourself #
- Wilson...
come get me.
# it's later than you think #
- I know a nice facility
outside Philly.
I went to undergrad
with one of the directors.
- Thanks.
How many shirts do I need?
- They said three.
They have laundry.
- Like living with mom again--
delightful.
- It's probably Foreman.
- He's unavailable.
- Tell her the infection's
made her septic.
We can't remove the abscess
until we get her B.P. up.
And it's not responding
to fluids. It's not--
He's off the case.
- Patient okay?
- Yeah.
- He's lying.
- Why don't I feel scared?
- I'd say you're unaware
of what you're feeling
at this moment.
- I feel like crap.
My life is falling apart,
but I don't feel scared...
not of the rehab anyway.
- We've always been able
to find a way to cheat.
- It won't work.
- You want it
to work this time.
- Do we?
- House...
it's your only option.
- What do I do
if my only option won't work?
- You don't give up.
- Hmm.
It's either that
or electroshock every six hours.
Good night, Wilson.
- What if we put her
on a heart-lung machine?
- She's septic.
We don't need
a heart-lung machine.
We need a "blood vessel
holder together" machine.
- We could try
high-dose dopamine.
It's a vasoconstrictor.
It'll close the blood vessels
so she won't bleed out.
- Her heart can't take
that much dopamine.
It'll explode.
- And if we don't use
the dopamine,
it'll implode.
- Is House really done?
- It sounded that way.
- Dopamine it is.
- It's late, and I'm tired.
Can we get to the talking part
of this conversation?
I quit.
- Great.
My nanny
is off the clock at 7:30,
so...
your week off,
bigger desk...
tighter nurses uniforms,
or whatever other stupid thing
you're about to demand
is gonna have to wait until--
- You can go suckle
the little bastard child
who makes you feel good
about yourself.
- Screw you.
- Don't do this.
- I'm hallucinating.
- From the vicodin?
- Ruled out everything else.
- We can, uh...
admit you through the E.R.
under a pseudonym.
No one has to...
- I'll cheat...
Scam,
find some way to keep using.
- These people
know what they're doing.
- These people don't know me.
You do.
- She's not your keeper.
She has no responsibility
for you.
- I need you.
- Let me call my babysitter.
- Blood pressure's 90 over 60.
- We know.
- I'm just saying.
It's still 90 over 60.
It's holding.
- Abscess is intact.
Doesn't look like any of the
surrounding tissue is affected.
She's gonna be fine.
- Doctor.
- We've got a problem.
- Lie down.
I'll get you some tea.
Yeah...
then I'll be better.
- Do you really think
she hasn't searched this place
for your secret stash?
- I already did this room...
and the bathroom
and your bedroom.
Where should I look,
in the kitchen?
Coffee cup in--
in the top shelf.
- That was a test.
I already did the kitchen.
- Nicely played--
She'll think you've come clean,
given her everything.
There's more.
- Don't!
You're hurting already.
It'll only get worse.
- House, you should tell me
where it is now,
because you won't have the will
to tell me in two hours.
My shoes in the closet.
- It's like I don't even know
who you are anymore.
Aah!
- It's okay.
Shh.
Hold my hand.
- Am I okay?
- We were able to
successfully remove the abscess
from your heart.
But the dopamine
caused the blood vessels
in your hands and feet
to clamp shut.
We need to amputate,
or the gangrene will spread.
You'll die.
My feet?
- And your hands.
I'm sorry.
- No.
I'm a dancer.
- The tissue can't be saved.
- No.
- We know what House would do.
- House would have never woken
her up to ask for consent.
If you can't live with the
answer, don't ask the question.
- You're saying we should
accept her decision?
- Bold idea, I know.
- Maybe we can get
the boyfriend
to convince her to do it.
- Yeah, boyfriends
get everything they want.
- Forget it.
The boyfriend doesn't want
to talk to her anymore.
- Where are you going?
- Home. The case is over.
- No, it's not.
Not until we come up
with something that might work.
It's a shame
that she might die
because House has some
personal crap to work through.
- Technically, if she dies,
it's because House has some
personal crap to work through,
and we weren't smart enough
to get the answer without him.
False alarm.
- Drink this.
- That's your advice--
drink this?
It's Ginger.
It'll ease the nausea.
- You know
what would calm the nausea?
Vicodin...
marijuana...
a coma.
- Oh, don't pretend
you didn't see it.
I saw it,
which means you saw it.
Send her away.
- Too bitter.
I already had enough bitter.
- I'll add some Honey.
- You're pathetic.
If you want the pill,
just send her home.
But you can't,
because that would be
admitting defeat to her.
Now, this is interesting.
If you take the pill,
you don't deserve her.
If you secretly
take the pill,
you don't deserve anyone.
- No!
- Aah!
No!
- This isn't gonna work.
- It might work.
That's all we're going for.
Vasodilators can--
- Big jump from reopening
to reanimating.
I'm out of the ulnar.
I'm not seeing any clearing.
This won't work.
- This probably won't work.
- Radial artery's
really tight.
- Don't go too fast.
If it clots,
she loses the hand.
- If it clots, she's dead.
- I can't believe it.
- What?
- It might be working.
- Can you stop?
The breathing.
- Air goes in,
air goes out.
- Then use your nose.
- You're supposed to feel
like crap.
You're doing great.
- And after?
- You come back to work.
- What if I can't?
- Opioid dependency can make
you think you have more pain
than you really have.
You're gonna be okay.
- You're telling me what I want
to hear with no evidence.
- I'm telling you
what I believe to be the truth.
- With no evidence.
- You're hardly
the most unbiased observer.
- Neither are you.
I'm your hospital's
biggest asset.
- Is that
why you think I'm here?
- It's why you're here.
It's why you're lying
to me about--
- I haven't lied to you
in 20 years.
- Sure you have.
Which means
that you just said that
because you want to tell me
what you lied to me about
20 years ago.
You're an ass.
- Am I wrong?
- I wasn't
in your endocrinology class.
- You sat next to me.
I cheated off you on--
- I audited
your endocrinology class.
- Why would you--
- Because I thought
you were an interesting lunatic
even then.
- I'm not here
protecting hospital property.
- We're alone.
- We've been alone all night.
- No, I mean Amber.
She's gone.
- Where's Jeremy?
- He left.
You okay?
- The surgery worked.
- Congratulations.
- # you've had a hard time #
- I can't do it.
- # living with a hard heart #
- You have doubts.
- You don't?
- # you hardly feel #
- No.
- # a thing #
# and you don't know where #
- Well, that's...
# to start #
naive.
I-I want to spend
the rest of my life with you.
I love you.
That's how I feel right now,
but...
I don't...
know.
- I'll wait until you do.
- # it won't be long, long #
- I ca--I can't know.
No--no one knows.
- I do.
- # it's coming
after you all day #
# surrounding #
- I'll see you in later?
I have some papers
to push for you.
- # when you look
at me that way #
# I don't know
the thing to say #
- Thank you.
- You want to kiss me,
don't you?
- I always want
to kiss you.
- # come on,
come on and try #
# ooh ooh ooh ooh #
# come on,
come on and sail away #
# sail away sail away
sail away #
Subtitles by LeapinLar
www.tvsubtitles.net