Help!
Help me!
Dry heaves are gone, so am I.
I'll check with the doctor.
I'm here voluntarily,
just got to check with me.
I'm sorry.
Dr. Nolan left specific instructions.
She's not sick. She's scared.
So tell her to tell...
And he's black.
I thought you'd be a little more
sensitive on the slavery issue.
- Can't keep me.
- You look a lot better.
I am a lot better... No painkillers,
no hallucinations.
Leg hurts, but it's manageable.
Great job.
Gonna miss you. Want to start
missing you as soon as possible.
Legally, you're free to go
whenever you want. I suggest you stay.
I'll take it under advisement.
If the hallucinations
were from your vicodin,
why didn't you just check yourself
into a rehab facility?
I was deluded into thinking
I might be crazy.
But you had been abusing vicodin
for years.
Never had delusions,
never had trouble sleeping,
never had any problems,
other than narcissism
and antisocial behavior,
until two colleagues died.
Your father died.
Your issues run deeper than vicodin.
That's not gonna cheer me up, is it?
You need to be transferred
to our long-term ward,
started on medication,
talk therapy...
Yeah, I get it.
Just one thing
I'm getting hung up on.
I can leave whenever I want.
How about I start with that?
You can't go back
to practicing medicine.
I don't want to practice medicine.
I want to be an astronaut.
Well, if you want
your state astronaut's license,
you're gonna need my recommendation.
Is that a popular, new treatment...
Blackmail?
You need to get better.
Welcome to ward six.
So brass tacks...
What do I have to do,
and how long do I have to be here?
Depends on you.
Process is pretty basic.
If you follow the schedule,
agree to take meds,
participate in group
and individual therapy,
- we can work on goals.
- I set a goal.
- Excellent. What is it?
- My goal is to get your boss
to write the letter
that I want him to write.
Now let's talk process.
I can smile through
gritted teeth and play nice,
but there are serious risks of violence
involved in that choice,
so I'm going with turning
this ward upside down,
making you and your boss' job and life
so unmanageable
that he'll write whatever
he has to write to get rid of me.
He's all set.
Thanks.
I've never been
in the end unit before.
Yo, I don't need an escort.
Get off me.
Who are you?
You believe these guys?
Lecturing me on manic depression,
like I couldn't write a book or two.
I stop taking my meds,
because I want to stop taking my meds,
because nothing is wrong with me.
No reason to keep
dragging me back here.
When I'm on them,
everything slows down.
That's when the problem is.
Nice to see you. My roommate last time
couldn't stand me.
- Really?
- Juan Alvarez. J.A.'s my stage name.
But Alvie's what everybody
around here calls me,
like the Woody Allen character
in Annie Hall,
but the Puerto Rican version
and not as neurotic.
So what do I call you?
You're actually waiting
for an answer this time.
Call me House.
He's a brick
Wait up.
I've already got
the whole place wired,
so I'll give you the rundown.
Yo, everybody!
This is my new roommate,
House, y'all.
- Main thing you got to know...
- Is this the line?
Hey, Gabby,
meet my new roommate, House.
- You can call him "Heezy."
- No, you can't.
Don't worry.
She won't call you anything.
She hasn't talked in, like,
ten years or something.
Good you came here.
You need to know the lay of the land.
I need to request a new room.
You're funny. You're also gonna
come here to get your meds.
- I'm not on any meds.
- You either? Good for you.
Tell me my mind works too fast.
Probably tell Usain Bolt
he runs too fast.
Excuse me.
I know you're busy ignoring me,
but my minibar is empty.
You think bolt could do the long jump?
That sport needs to evolve.
Had the same world record for,
like, 20 years.
I think if one guy
launched himself headfirst
and right before he hits the ground
does a front flip instead,
get three extra feet out of that, easy.
Go be that man.
My head!
You're not getting any haldol.
Sorry.
That's Hal.
His real name is Connor,
- but we call him Hal...
- I got it.
We can't play that.
They keep it locked up.
I wish we could, but at the same time,
imagine how annoying that could be.
Crazy people playing on it all the time.
We'd never get any peace.
I want to introduce you
to everybody.
Do you think he's serious?
He's a doctor.
He knows that acting out
will only reinforce our diagnosis.
Or it'll work.
You think this is something
we should be concerned about?
A patient makes a threat,
you should always be concerned.
There are two new additions
to our ward.
You all know Alvie.
Thank you. Hold your applause.
It's great to be back here in Mayfield,
not just for the food,
not just for the ladies...
well, okay,
maybe just for the ladies.
And you should also welcome Greg
to the floor.
Don't worry about the name.
I'm just passing through.
Don't want to break any hearts.
Can we go outside now?
Not now, Jay.
So he's claustrophobic, right?
You're claustrophobic?
Can I get a pen
to write this stuff down?
Where are you going?
- Where's he going?
- It's okay.
Paranoid... check.
Dr. Beasley...
I am having an issue with the food.
- What's the problem?
- I swear I'm eating less and less,
and I just keep getting
bigger and bigger.
- A crayon? Anybody?
- We'll talk about it another time.
I understand you all
had art therapy yesterday.
Maybe we can hang some
of the new pieces on the wall.
Cut your wrists, huh?
- Greg, there are certain topics...
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Is suicide taboo?
Gosh, if I've broken a rule
on my first day,
I will kill myself.
Group's over.
That flew by.
You realize you're not
the first uncooperative patient
on this floor?
Really? Is there a club?
Come with me to the clubhouse.
That didn't take long.
I'm that good.
Come on.
Come on, Alvie!
Let's see some action!
You got nothing!
- Me, me.
- Pass, pass!
Good.
Come on, guys!
Ready to play nice?
Would you believe me if I said yes?
Then, yes.
You do know I'm trying to help you.
I also know you're trying
to be sweet, caring, and effective.
You're just not.
You want out.
Just talk.
Be honest.
Try to work with people.
Try to deal with people.
- He's on my team!
- Shut up. Nobody likes you.
Am I crowding you?
Can't see the sun?
No, everything is closing in.
He's the claustrophobic one, right?
'Cause I'm doing this from memory.
- You have to dribble.
- Why?
The CIA satellites aren't watching me.
They're watching you,
'cause you're wearing green.
That one was just too easy.
Seriously, anorexia?
What, are you supposed to be a girl?
And in answer to your implicit question,
yes, those pants
do make you look fat.
How upset were you
when you woke up in the E.R.
and you were still alive
and a failure?
2-0, good guys!
You're right. It is rewarding
when you reach out.
You can't go up there.
It's yard time right now.
Put it on my tab.
I think you'll find
music therapy's more effective
if the patients are inside
to hear it.
Where'd you get the key?
They gave it to me.
So if she ever talks,
are we gonna get a German accent?
She's my husband's sister.
So let him come play the piano.
He doesn't know how to play.
Nice.
You're a little heavy
on the right foot, though.
See her head?
It bobs to the music.
It's the only real reaction
I'm getting from her.
It feels like we're talking.
You're not talking.
Her head is bobbing to her pulse.
Are you a new doctor on the ward?
Technically, yes.
Can I lead this time?
Leave the lid unlocked
when you're done.
Can you close the door?
You're letting all the cool air out.
If you keep up
this scorched-earth policy,
you're gonna end up
living in this room.
Are you ready to try another strategy,
or do you want me to leave you in here?
21. 2-1, that's game.
Hey, House is back.
I'll get the ball.
I need some meat.
I got no one left to play.
- I'll play you.
- Girl. Come on, House.
You can serve.
I've had some time
to think about the approach
I've been taking.
I know I'm unhappy here, and I...
I've been taking it out
on you guys...
unfairly.
It was...
misdirected anger.
'cause when you think about it,
the real jerks here...
Are the doctors.
See how they give you
a ping-pong table,
but no paddles, no net?
It's like they're mocking you.
Preach!
The game is called table tennis,
not table volleyball.
Greg, you know where this
is gonna end.
Who ever saw
a tennis court without a net?
Little run-down park across
from my apartment growing up...
Three courts, no nets.
No one ever used it.
No one's gonna try to hang
themselves with a ping-pong net.
- No!
- Ridiculous.
You treat us like little kids.
Little kids are allowed
to play ping-pong,
- and they can play the piano.
- Yeah, worse than little kids.
All right, why don't we just go
and sit down
and discuss it?
No, I want to discuss it right here.
Guys.
Guys!
House is right.
I think everyone here
can handle these.
Seriously?
Is that your strategy... Give everybody
what they want except me?
You're a natural leader.
You could do something
useful down here, for them,
definitely for you.
Or we could keep fighting...
If you think you can break me,
if you think I'm not every bit
as stubborn as you.
Came to fight the man
and he had the master plan
But it started to unravel
Nolan smashed him with his gavel
- Like blah!
- Shut up.
So you gonna keep trying
to make them miserable?
New plan?
What is it?
I don't know yet.
His mind is burning
The wheels are turning
The butter is churning
You think Nolan can keep
House from strolling?
It's easier to come up
with a new plan in silence.
Right. Cool.
Can I hump?
I'd like you all to welcome
another new addition to our ward...
Steve.
Freedom master.
Steve Elkerton is just a cover.
It's like Clark Kent
or Bruce Wayne or Peter Parker.
Cool.
We got more jesuses than superheroes.
I try to blend in
in the outside world,
but I figure in here,
everybody gets it.
We're living in the ward of justice.
Can you explain a little more
about what you think everybody gets?
There's good and evil in the world.
And some people are... special,
and they're chosen to help keep
evil forces at bay.
You don't think
you can stop bullets, do you?
I move out of their way.
Can you read minds?
It's group time, Greg.
Why isn't she talking?
She needs help.
She needs somebody to save her.
That's what we're all trying to do.
Let's take five minutes.
Everybody get to know Steve.
I can fly.
I know you're scheming,
working on your next elaborate
plan to get out of here.
Why don't you put the plan
on hold for a few days?
See what happens.
Just let me do my job.
If you prefer private to group,
we can do that,
maybe try some SSRIs.
If you think nothing's working,
you can always go
back to your schemes.
God, if only you'd said that
two minutes ago,
before I came up with my new scheme.
Now I'm committed.
Get it?
Shaq up in my area
I'm a better baller
and a better rapper
And I'm good at basketball too
Do you have third-floor privileges?
Ever since I shared in group
about my uncle fondling me.
Is that true?
And now I can use the
third-floor vending machines.
You eat sour cream and onion chips?
The whole point is the dipping.
Sure, we save time by not adding
the mix and sour cream,
- but you're missing out on...
- Break into Nolan's office.
- Commando style.
- I want you to focus.
- You want me to mess him up?
- Go into Nolan's office.
Look at his calendar. I need the name
of the woman he met with at 11:00 today.
No problem. And I'll get you
some chips. If they have them,
I'll get you some dip, but I've never
seen dip in the vending machine.
Get me chips and dip.
- What else?
- I get it, I get it. Plan "B".
"B" is for blackmail.
I got you covered.
Commando style.
Let me go!
I just wanted a little snack.
That ain't right!
Yo, I didn't know
the machine was moved!
I want some ritz bits!
I might be pregnant!
I get these cravings!
You get the name?
Nolan's schedule book has a big "x"
marking out the whole middle of the day.
Then we can assume the girl
he's with is called "nooner".
Nooner, nooner
Nolan's gonna spoon her
- He's gonna "fork" her.
- And then he's gonna knife her
I didn't check the phone
or anything else.
That's okay.
I got her license plate.
I call my friend. He gets the name.
I get the letter
that gets me out of here.
You got phone privileges?
I'm on level minus four.
I'm still writing with a crayon.
You? You got to be at level five.
That's like the top
of the space needle.
Hal's the only one
that's up that high.
Hal's at level five?
They give him a point
every time he clears his plate.
I've been eating his potatoes.
- Will he sell you some minutes?
- I pay two cigarettes for the potatoes.
Phone's worth a lot more.
Can you cheek a pill?
That's too bad for you.
You sure you're good with this?
Got to be done.
So how do we start?
I think we just start.
Make it good. Make it real.
Just do it already.
Code gray!
Give me five milligrams of haldol!
Help! Get him off me!
Give it to him!
Dude, that was awesome.
Think Hal will mind if they're wet?
No, it's your other friend
at the asylum.
How's it going?
Hallucinations are gone,
so is the vicodin.
How's the leg?
How's the pain?
They got me on some nonnarcotic.
I'm dealing.
I need you to run a license plate.
Was there a hit-and-run
on your floor?
House, just do
what you're supposed to do.
Listen to the doctors,
and I'll be able to visit soon.
Track down the owner of this car,
and I'll be able to visit you
in your office tomorrow.
My doctor is too smart,
too old, and too well-dressed
to only be running one ward.
He screwed up something in his life,
and I think he's doing it again.
I need her name so I can
blackmail the blackmailer.
He called me.
Why?
He wanted to know about you.
He wanted to warn me
that you'd be calling for something.
And he told me if I wanted
to help you get better,
I had to let him do his job.
Now I'm calling you to
tell you that if he calls you...
I'm so sorry.
I wish I could help you.
You can.
It turns out...
You're my only friend.
House ain't a newbie,
now he living on this floor
And I hate you.
I'm gonna cooperate.
That's not much of a plan.
That's actually their plan.
No, I'm pretty sure their plan is for me
to actually swallow the pills,
to actually cooperate.
I'm so proud of my little roomie.
I only taught him
everything he knows.
One, two, three.
Stomp, you start the betting.
Highest card wins.
That's probably a fold.
Richter.
Two cigarettes.
He's not confident, Alvie.
Crush him,
in the form of a rhyme if you want.
No regrets, raise ten cigarettes
That's a lot of nerve
for someone with a two on their head.
You're messing with me.
You can't raise ten.
I only have five.
- Throw in your phone card.
- I'm not gonna throw in it.
Can I play?
- Come here.
- Why?
I wanna see if you've got what it takes.
Give me your best poker face.
Too rich for my blood.
You can take my seat.
Med time!
How are you feeling today?
Better than yesterday,
not as good as tomorrow.
I've been humming to her.
She sways.
It might be significant.
Are you ignoring me, or are you letting
my charm wash over you?
Kind of tough to play and chat.
A couple of weeks ago, you told me
playing to her
was a complete waste of time.
You're right. Your playing
does get worse when you talk.
I assume she loved music.
She played
for the Philadelphia philharmonic...
Cello.
If she responded to the piano, she might
respond even better to the cello.
I play a little.
Maybe I'll bring one in tuesday.
Thank you.
Different desk, different doctor.
You've been on meds for a while now.
I'll be checking in with you
to see if we need to adjust your dose.
Any dry mouth, trouble sleeping?
Can I go now?
There's a manic out there
with a fresh carton of cigarettes,
and he's a terrible bluffer.
It's nice to see that you
and Alvie are friends again.
- Tell me about your fight.
- He hit me. I hit him back.
Repeat until pulpy.
Alvie told me
you instigated the thing.
That tends to be
the way fights work...
Different interpretations
of the same circumstances.
Very understanding attitude.
- There's that tone again.
- You're smart.
How come every time you compliment me,
it sounds like an accusation?
You're not having any side effects
from your meds, which is unusual.
- It's not that unusual.
- The fight isn't adding up.
Why don't you stop pretending
that you haven't reached a conclusion?
You don't trust me.
Actually, it's more fundamental
than that. You don't like me.
- I didn't say that.
- You think I'm not taking my meds.
Are you?
So what do you want me to do?
Want me to take a urine test?
Will that earn your trust?
Actually, yeah.
Have at it.
A little dignity, please.
You know the rules.
I have to watch.
But you don't have
to have courtside seats.
Can I at least use a stall?
For he himself has said it
And it's greatly to his credit
That he is an Englishman
He is...
an Englishman
Get it while it's hot.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
Freedom Master,
think you could help me out?
You need help?
Of course...
- That's what I do.
- Great.
Could you move the piano?
500 pounds.
That's not too much, is it?
Is there something
trapped underneath or...?
No. I just want to move it
away from the window.
- My powers aren't for frivolous...
- Just one lift.
- Why are you doing that?
- House, it's none of your business.
I'm curious.
As a doctor, what are you doing?
Either he is Freedom Master,
and he shouldn't be here,
or else he's suffering
from a serious and dangerous delusion
that he needs to deal with.
So...
Legit medical reasons.
You're not trying to break him
because he's a little different.
He's not different.
He's delusional.
- Can you help me out?
- What is she looking at?
You're not a superhero, Steven.
- You're a regular person.
- I can save her.
We're all just regular people.
- It's what we do.
- They stole her voice box.
They have it in there.
That's what she's staring at.
Your wife is dead.
- Good can defeat evil.
- Not every time.
Evil people killed a lot
of good people that day.
You couldn't save her.
No one could.
It's in there.
Her voice is in there.
Code gray.
Her voice is in...
Don't do it.
I'm not doing anything.
You're thinking.
Things go from thinking to doing
way too fast in this place.
Keep thinking, you're gonna
wind up with no mo in your mojo.
- I'm thinking of hitting you again.
- You hate Medina. You hate all of them.
You want to hurt them. Keep pretending.
Step away from the hate.
What's the difference
between pretending to cooperate
and cooperating?
Pretending is pretending.
It's not real.
You don't mean it.
I sat and watched while he did
something stupid and pointless.
- I cooperated.
- Soon, you won't have to watch,
because you're going home.
You'll be getting your job back.
Everybody inside!
Closing ceremonies.
Everyone attends.
One of you is going home.
It's been a great week.
A number of you
have made tremendous strides.
But today we're here to congratulate
Susan.
We're proud of her!
We wish her well, and we hope...
to never see her again!
- Where's Freedom Master?
- He isn't able to take part.
Get out there.
They said everybody has to get out.
Talk!
Say something!
- Leave him alone.
- Did you drug him?
Of course I didn't drug him.
He's in flat affect.
He's practically catatonic.
Hey, we got cake.
- He's fine.
- Double chocolate.
Don't tell me that he's fine!
You did this!
He was functioning.
- He was happy.
- He was delusional.
He's way better off now.
Let's talk.
Thinking sucks.
I'm not allowed to get angry?
They screwed him up.
And for the record...
I am two privilege levels above Susan,
and I got the same depression-scale.
Every patient is different.
It's not about scores
- and levels and...
- Happiness is happiness.
Test is test.
Coping is coping.
- And you think you're...
- Absolutely!
I need to address
some deeper issues,
which I can do
on an outpatient basis.
3 hours a week?
That's my opening offer.
If you want to counter, I'll fold.
"No" is not an argument.
- Are you trying to frustrate me?
- No.
"No" again?
I can cope!
I'm coping.
In fact...
I'm coping better than you think.
I've not been taking my meds,
not one.
And, I still scored a "high functioning"
on your depression test.
So your proof of your well-being
is that you lied?
Manipulated.
My proof is
that I can fool the test and you,
which means I am high functioning.
I am sane, rational, capable.
I should not be here.
These are your pills from today?
I'm not gonna take it.
I'll just cheek it again.
Lick it.
- You want me to lick your hand?
- I washed.
It's sugar.
Your test results
were improving too regularly
and too quickly.
I was concerned that you weren't
taking your pills, that it was an act,
so I switched you to a placebo...
to see if your...
Improvements would continue.
Your psych tests told me nothing,
but your urine tests
told me you were faking.
You need to stop
fighting the system.
You need to let me do my job.
So...
What's the next plan?
There is no new plan.
I'm out of plans.
So what do we do?
We stop talking.
I see you've got some cello
in your trunk.
And, no, that's not a euphemism.
Are you spying on me?
I'm living
in a psychiatric hospital.
Staring out of the window
is what we do.
I assume you'll need help
carrying it up.
I still got grounds privileges.
And who's going to carry you
when you're carrying the cello?
Yes, cast aside
the useless cripple...
How very German of you.
Seriously, the thing
weighs a ton with that case.
- I think i'll need a dolly.
- Or we could ask Clark Kent
to pitch in.
- The dolly's probably easier.
- The dolly...
already feels good about itself.
He was a happy-go-lucky superhero
until they told him
he has no powers.
We let him help out,
he feels good about himself.
Might be less depressed.
Why do you put your life on hold
to visit your sister-in-law
five times a week?
Am I somehow a bad person
for showing compassion?
You're not even a bad person
for lying about why you're doing it.
That is impressive.
That is a superhuman feat.
Why don't you take a rest
before flying that thing up to the ward?
He's still depressed.
Give me your keys.
You gonna dangle them in front
of him to entertain him?
I'm gonna make him feel
like he's flying.
I'll drive him around the grounds,
top down,
wind in his hair.
Seriously...
you're gonna say no to that?
Why are you so nice to me?
I think you have a good heart.
Would you still be nice to me
if I told you that I lied?
I'm not just driving
around the grounds.
I'm kidnapping him
and stealing your car.
You sure?
I was starting to feel
a little heat between us.
Thought we had kind
of a "Bonnie and Clyde" thing.
Bonnie and clyde get shot to pieces.
See you.
You can do this.
If you hold my hand,
I can do it too.
Don't let go!
Going up!
Freedom Master's back!
Keep it down, freedom master.
You're scaring the good citizens.
- It was the coolest moment of my life.
- It was fun.
You can repay me
by telling Nolan he's an idiot.
Smell that fresh air
and the warmth of your yellow sun.
We do enjoy it.
Careful of the traffic.
Don't go damaging any fenders.
Come on, get down.
There's no cry for help.
There's no cat in a tree.
Thank you, Greg.
He's lucky to be alive.
He's got a lacerated spleen,
rotational pelvic fracture,
compound break
of the femur and humerus.
Everything in your life has been
about finding the truth.
But suddenly, with this guy,
you decide to reinforce
a sick man's delusions.
You just wanted to take
a swing at me.
You don't care about getting out.
You don't care about him.
You don't even care about the truth.
You don't care about anything.
I'm transferring you
to Winslow psychiatric.
You'll have better luck pulling
the wool over their eyes. I'm done.
Don't.
I need help.
So how is this supposed to work?
You sit. I sit.
We talk.
- About what?
- About whatever you want.
- You want me to whine about my mother?
- You want to whine about your mother?
I can tell you about the time
I was five and my goldfish died.
If that's where you'd like to start.
I've had a billion things happen to me.
How can I know which ones are relevant?
- As far as I'm concerned, they're all.
- Well, we better get moving,
'cause this session
could take 50 years.
Yes, you are the sum
of everything that's happened to you.
And, yes, some events
are more relevant than others.
But the only way
we can figure out which ones are
is to talk.
So tell me,
what's on your mind?
What do you want?
I want to get better...
whatever the hell that means.
- I'm sick of being miserable.
- So you'd like to be happy?
Again with the reflecting...
Yes, I'd like to be happy.
Being happy is an excellent goal.
Not many patients can crystallize
what they're hoping
to get out of this.
- Well, bully for me.
- So now all we have to do
is figure out how to get you
from here...
to happy.
SSRIS?
That's your genius technique?
I don't think we should ignore
any tools that can help.
I know you don't have
a problem taking drugs.
For my leg, for pain.
Think of this
as being for psychic pain.
I don't want to change who I am.
Miserable?
Do you think that by taking meds
you'll lose your edge,
stop making the unique connections
that make you a successful doctor?
If Van Gogh was your patient,
he'd be satisfied painting houses
instead of The Starry night.
Van gogh would still be making inspired
paintings of the night sky,
just maybe not
from the room of his asylum.
- You don't know that.
- I know
both his ears would be intact.
And I know his life...
would be better.
I know this doesn't come
naturally to you.
But you want my help,
which means you need to trust me.
Delicious.
Why are you here?
I'm waiting for my communion wafer.
You're cheeking it, right?
Nope.
Tell me you're cheeking it.
I swallowed it.
We don't take meds.
You don't take meds, Alvie.
I decided to get sane.
You're scamming again.
You can tell me.
I'm not scamming, Alvie.
They broke you.
They didn't break me.
I am broken.
Now stop worshipping me and go and worry
about your own loser life.
I hate you.
- Prom?
- Got an assignment for you.
Role-playing?
I'm not sure how pretending
to be a businessman
with a foot fetish is gonna help,
but I'm game.
Have you connected
with any of the other patients?
You've been here 4 weeks.
Tell me about your relationships
with the other patients.
Diane...
is convinced
that silent girl hates her.
Richter's not as paranoid as you think.
He just likes that you think that.
And my roommate hates me.
Only one of the things indicated
how somebody else feels about you.
So...
I'm sure that they've done
some form of rudimentary analysis on me,
concluded that I'm a jerk.
You know, there is a way
for them to find out things about you
without deductive reasoning.
I have had relationships.
You've screwed up relationships,
every one of them...
Almost like that was the goal.
I want you
to trust...
people.
Try.
Get dressed.
Just open up?
Just open up.
Trust.
Strangers?
We'll start with strangers,
then work our way up.
If it helps, I find "hello"
to be an excellent icebreaker.
It's like "hello," only shorter.
I'm glad we were able
to save that time.
Judging by the fancy suit,
I'd say you were a donor.
The nervous demeanor
says maybe you've had issues,
probably is why this place
has personal meaning.
But this is supposed to be about me.
I take advantage of my friends.
Friend, really...
I've only got one.
It can be tough.
- I'm not gay.
- Oh, neither am i.
Actually, I am.
See that guy over there?
He's my lover.
He's also my psychiatrist, which some
would argue is a little inappropriate,
but they just don't know
what love is.
Am I right?
You're not gay.
No, but I have to tell
intimate secrets to people.
Maybe they should be true.
Hadn't thought of that.
To be on the safe side,
I should do both,
starting with the fun ones.
Come on, let's get me better.
I'm a philanderer.
Philanderer doesn't mean
that I give a lot to charity.
- It means...
- I know what it means.
You were asking me
if there were any nuts
in the hors d'oeuvres.
What?
Honey.
What did my husband just say to you?
I...
was asking him if there were nuts...
in the hors d'oeuvres.
- Then where is your EpiPen?
- My what?
No one with an allergy would
walk around without an EpiPen.
- Give me your purse.
- Stop!
- Come...
- No.
What really happened
is...
I thought he was cute.
I hit on him.
We're going.
You having fun?
I did connect with one guy.
But then my propensity
for screwing things up overtook me.
Then my desire to have fun
overcame my propensity.
You didn't screw it up.
The assignment wasn't to get you
to trust with a piece of your soul.
The assignment was to teach you
that you can trust.
Did any of these people rat you out
as the obnoxious womanizer
or the porn producer
that they think you are?
Why do you think
that people would treat you
worse if they knew the truth?
Good night, doctor.
Are you in trouble?
Apparently not.
So what's next?
You want to be my pimp?
Why don't we just talk?
How come you weren't pissed
at me for stealing your car?
It was a nice thing to do.
I'm not sure about the German-English
translation of nice.
The stealing was nice or...
ruining Freedom Master's life?
What you did was misguided
and irresponsible,
but it was also nice.
You gave him a moment
of pure happiness.
You asked me why I come here
so often to visit Annie.
She was my best friend.
Then she started pulling away...
from everybody.
The doctors don't know why.
I think
I married her brother because...
he was the only other one
who was going through the same thing.
But he stopped visiting
after a couple of years.
I just...
couldn't stop.
I miss her.
I should go.
Good night.
So what happened?
- You're talking to me now.
- No.
Was it fun?
She kissed me.
Don't read into the phrasing.
We kissed each other.
And how do you feel?
How do I feel?
It was a kiss.
Kisses are good things.
That was a loaded "okay."
Not at all.
Why would you assume that?
'Cause you're being judgmental.
If I had said that I'd had a delicious
Chilean sea bass for dinner,
would you say,
"And how do you feel?"
If the sea bass was married,
I might.
See, you're being judgmental.
Isn't that against your code
or something?
I'm simply stating the obvious.
It's complicated,
not just because she's married
and not just because
you're institutionalized.
I know you spent the last 12 hours
trying to figure out
what that kiss means.
Who's that woman you were with
in the parking lot?
When you deflect,
it's more effective
when you're not that transparent.
Obviously you have no problem
with the infidelity.
You're trying to rationalize that,
"if it's okay for your doctor,
it's okay."
But for the record,
- I am not having an affair.
- Then who is she?
Why are you working so hard
to figure out the details of my life?
I might not have to work so hard
if there were personal items in here.
You got one number on speed dial.
It says "Dad".
Come on, how old are you?
- Why are you so afraid?
- I want to talk about you.
I want to know whogives me advice.
I'm not giving you advice.
I'm asking questions.
I think that kiss meant a lot.
I think that scares you.
I think there are
no personal items in here
because you have no personal life.
How do you think
you and Lydia will end?
You are a lonely man.
You've screwed up every
opportunity you've had.
What's the ending to the story?
I don't know.
Visiting time!
Why did you kiss me?
How many reasons are there?
I like you.
It felt like a nice way
of showing you that.
Open it all the way.
Keep it open.
How'd it go with Lydia?
I found out
you can only be happy so long
before the catatonic guy
with two broken limbs
rolls off the elevator,
philosophically speaking.
Why do you value your failures
more than your successes?
My mother caught me masturbating...
to pictures of her mother.
Can we get past
these cute deflections?
Successes only last
until someone screws them up.
Failures are forever.
So you accept that fact.
You accept that
there's nothing you can do.
Okay, I accept the fact
that there's nothing I can do.
Now, what can I do?
You acknowledge failure,
and you move past it.
You apologize.
Powerful things these apologies.
Get someone to jump off a building.
You say two words,
and you move on with your life.
Hardly seems fair.
Is that the issue?
You caused him pain.
If the world is just,
you have to suffer equally?
You're not god, House.
You're just another...
screwed-up human being
who needs to move on.
Apologize to him.
Let yourself feel better.
Then you can learn
to let yourself...
keep feeling better.
Dr. House, everything okay?
Time for group.
Group time, everybody!
I have a surprise.
2 weeks from today,
we're going to have
the mayfield talent show.
Talent show?
Who's in it?
I'd really love it if everybody here
could participate.
- Then who's gonna watch?
- The staff will come,
friends and family.
- You gonna tape this?
- No, it's just for us.
If it's just for us,
I vote we don't do it.
Think of it as a fun way
to work on...
on our therapeutic issues.
Avie, maybe you could sing
one of your songs.
I don't sing. I rap.
You can write something just for us.
I don't write.
I just do, freestyle style.
I think you're gonna want
to be prepared.
- Make something special.
- Always special.
How about you, Diane?
Is there something you'd like to do?
I don't have any talents.
Sure you do.
You all do.
Steve, don't you think that Diane
has hidden talent
that we'd like to see come out?
You really think he's gonna answer?
- Eventually.
- Why?
Because things pass.
Things change.
It doesn't mean they get better.
You got to make things better.
You can't just keep talking
and hope for the best.
Diane, maybe you and I can work together
and figure something out.
I can save him.
"They stole her voice box",
that's what he said.
That's what she was staring at.
- That's why he's staring.
- Dr. House, please.
- 'Cause there's a music box in there.
- Orderly.
Just give it to me.
I can...
I am not having a psychotic break.
I promise you this will work.
It's the blue box there
on the top shelf.
This is what you wanted.
This is what you needed...
a voice.
You thought you could cure
silent girl with this.
So by your own rationale,
it should cure you.
There's nothing wrong with you.
You're healing.
All the parts work.
Just speak.
Come on, speak!
Say something!
I think maybe everyone
should take a break now.
You're trying to fix
instead of moving on.
I brought dvorak...
four hands.
What?
I need to know what this is.
It's sheet music.
I told you.
It's just...
two people having fun.
There's two possible outcomes.
It ends.
Someone gets hurt.
Or it doesn't end.
So the end sucks.
It doesn't mean
the beginning has to.
Everything ends.
Life ends.
It doesn't mean
that we can't enjoy it.
I can't...
I can't do this.
All I know is,
I was happy five minutes ago,
and now I'm not.
How's that better?
Good-bye, Lydia.
I'm really worried about e. c. t.
Apprehension's normal.
- Has anyone else had it?
- They shocked me, man.
Thanks.
That's very reassuring.
- I don't know if I should do it.
- Just do the treatment or shut up.
- Greg, there's a process.
- Yes, a process.
Wouldn't want to disrupt
the process with results.
Heezy had a rough night last night.
Guess he decided to go back to being
an ass instead of a hypocrite.
Let's move on.
Alvie, are you making
any progress writing your rap?
But really, no. I just don't want
to write my songs down.
It takes all the spontaneity
out of it. It's not...
of the moment.
If you write things down...
When the time comes, my rhyme comes,
when my spotlight shines...
Yeah, you're a genius.
Rhymes with "penius."
Sorry to interrupt, dr. Beasley.
Dr. Nolan asked me to give you this.
- Is this a day pass?
- He'd like to see you.
Thanks for coming.
I was hoping you could,
take a look at my dad's chart.
A consult?
What happened? You went through
every sane doctor in town?
I thought you wouldn't mind
getting off the ward.
Cleaning lady found him
on the kitchen floor.
Doctors here don't think
that he'll recover,
that I should pull the plug.
I want a second opinion, so I...
I thought I'd be a fool
not to call you.
Lacunar infarct,
converted to hemorrhagic stroke.
It squashed his brain.
They didn't miss anything.
- That's what I thought.
- That's what you knew.
His brain
has been replaced by blood.
It's over.
And that's obvious to any doctor
who looks at that scan, even a shrink.
You want someone to tell you
that what you need to do is OK,
to give you permission, absolution.
Not now, House.
You have no friends, no family.
At some point,
you made a mistake.
You lost everything.
And now I'm the closest thing
you got to a friend.
Just shut up.
I don't need you here...
to play this game.
I'm sorry I pushed you away.
It's what I do when I'm afraid.
Again, german-english
translation may be a little off.
I'm not... I'm not crying
because of you.
I'm crying because I'm pathetic.
I brought her cello,
in case she magically wakes up
for the show.
Then I take the apology back.
We're all pathetic.
It's makes everything interesting.
I'm sick of life being interesting.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the one, the only,
Juan Alvarez!
What's up? Ward six
is jumping off, y'all!
Give it up for DJ Richter
on the ones and twos.
DJ Richter, spin that!
Welcome to Mayfield
where the day feels long
we act strong, but there's
got to be something wrong
see, we got hidden talents
you don't see hidden secrets
if we could show you those
If we could show you those
Then we wouldn't have no regrets
Wanna know my secrets?
Sit back and let me explain it
My pops split, mama got sick
Clich, ain't it?
Now I'm a manic hispanic
I'm trying to make it work
But the doctors think I'm lazy
My roommate is a jerk
Dr. House is in the house, y'all
Give it up for Dr. House
to the stage, y'all
Paging Dr. House to the stage,
y'all
Are you there, Dr. House?
It's on
Bring it on
He's coming to the stage, y'all
It's Dr. House on the remix
Dr. House on the remix
They say to take your pills
They say don't be a creep
But how can I get better
If I can't get no sleep?
You gotta think before you act
In order to progress
If you don't make connections
Then your whole life is a mess
Yeah, so tell me, doctor,
what I really got to know
How do I get better?
Just do a talent show
Well, I guess I'm just a mess, yes
Preach it to me, brother
A life of restlessness
But at least we have each other
We got each other, we got each other
Like two brothers from another mother
Duck and run for cover, ward six
How are you doing?
You hanging in there?
Usually, I open with that.
Thanks for staying.
So...
What do you want to talk about?
Things are actually...
Actually good.
You don't want to complain
in front of the guy who lost his father?
I'm not that cured.
I still got stuff to do, but...
I'm good.
I'm sorry.
I was trying to prove a point.
I was trying to be right.
I ended up putting you
in a dangerous situation,
and I was not equipped to handle it.
You got hurt, and...
it's my fault.
And I'm sorry.
Med time.
I'll try those pink ones today.
You?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Got a surprise.
Today, we're here to congratulate.
Annie!
We're proud of her!
We wish her well, and we hope to...
Never see her again!
If you go silent for over a decade,
you don't just get to slide
right back into society.
She's going to a rehab facility first,
in Arizona.
Her family's moving there.
Sorry, House.
I just found out myself.
I want an overnight pass.
- I can help you.
- I've earned it.
- Yes, but...
- Isn't extending trust
part of the whole
"getting me better" thing?
If you insist on a pass, I'll give it
to you. But I know where you're going,
and I know you haven't
thought it through.
We need to sit down,
talk about this.
Please, give me the pass.
Hi.
Hello.
Who are you?
I'm...
Ben, go inside, okay?
You didn't say anything.
And now Annie's leaving,
and I hear you're going to Arizona.
My husband travels to Phoenix a lot.
His corporate headquarters are there.
We've been wanting to move for years,
but we've been tethered here.
And now, we're not.
I don't want you to go.
I don't want to go.
But I can't break up my family.
I can't leave my children.
I just don't want it to change.
I'm sorry
that I didn't come to say goodbye.
I thought it ended kind of perfect.
I have to go.
Not the most exciting use
of the overnight pass I've ever seen.
She left.
And...
I'm lost.
I'm gonna write your letter...
to the medical board,
so that they give your license back.
You can't just console me
by giving me a lollipop
when I skin my knee.
Two things happened.
You got hurt,
that means you connected to someone else
strongly enough to miss them.
And more important,
you recognized the pain
and came to talk to me,
instead of hiding from it
in a Vicodin bottle.
The fact that you're hurting
and you came here,
that you're taking your meds
and we're talking right now...
Come inside and get some sleep.
Tomorrow,
you can start saying your goodbyes.
Today,
we're here to congratulate Greg.
We're proud of him.
We wish him well, and we hope...
To never see him again!
House!
Back off.
People already think we're gay.
What do you need, Alvie?
My meds.
I want to get better.
www.tvsubtitles.net