I guess everybody else
is dead...
Which means
we're totally outnumbered.
We got to make up
for that in pure firepower.
You want to raid
the feeding area, don't you?
Two boxes of grenades
in there.
It's our only chance
at getting out.
Uh, Vince, that place
is a death trap.
Lucky for you,
I've got the mega-Blaster.
Lee, you go right.
Roy, straight down the middle.
I'll cover you both.
1, 2, 3!
Where's that cover fire?
Mega-Blaster, dude.
Mega-Blaster!
Aah!
What the hell?
Got it!
Vince, where are you?
Ah, I can't get them
off of me!
Vince, you d-Bag,
where are you?
Damn it. Damn it.
Damn it, Vince.
Ah.
That blood look
funny to you?
Still working on it.
The code's a little janky.
Hey, boss, you just like
watching us
Get our asses shredded?
Yeah, not that
you're not hilarious,
But we hit the shelves
in three months.
Vince?
Vince, what's wrong?
My hands.
They're on fire.
Your ncv test was normal.
Rules out carpal tunnel.
No evidence of trauma.
Your blood work looks normal.
Then what is it?
I don't know.
I'll arrange to have you
transferred to a neurologist.
A neurologist?
Don't you have some famous
diagnostics guy?
What's he doing?
I quit.
You can't quit.
I think you're confusing me
with jake gyllenhaal.
House, are you okay? Yeah,
and I want to stay that way.
Talked it over
with my therapist.
I need to change
my environment, my habits.
But he cleared you
To get your license back.
Which will help immensely
with my new job in research.
I've sent out
some resumes.
Research means no patients,
less pressure.
Well, you just got out.
Have you had enough time
to think this through?
I'm sorry.
I know this will affect
both of you...
And Thirteen...
And the one with the nose.
I just can't risk
coming back here.
Okay.
That was surprising.
I want to run the department.
You consider waiting
until House clears the lobby
Before you start angling
for his job?
He's not dead or sentimental
and somebody needs to do it.
Not necessarily.
Departments of diagnostic
medicine don't exist.
The only reason we have one
is because of House.
You reassigned us,
Kept us on payroll
for three months.
You might as well
give me a chance.
You're a great doctor.
I want you to stay on
in neuro.
But House was a genius.
House was an egotistical,
pill-Popping lawsuit magnet...
And a genius.
And I worked with him longer
than anybody else.
I can do this.
You get one shot.
What's House gonna do?
No idea,
but he's gone.
So how about we focus
on the medicine?
What?
You're the boss.
It's kind of sexy.
Here I thought
it was just the pants.
Uh, diabetic neuropathy?
Hba1c looks fine.
Could be hypothyroidism.
No fatigue
or weight gain.
What about complex
regional pain syndrome?
That's a good idea.
Let's run with it.
Look at that.
No House,
the job still gets done.
And yet something's
missing.
I'm short.
He's black.
You're gay-Ish.
That's it.
Treat for crps.
Prep the patient
for spinal stimulation.
I don't buy it.
Crps isn't that well
understood, but...
I think
it's mercury poisoning.
I eat a ton of sushi.
And you're currently getting
mixed reviews
In speed-The-Plow
on broadway.
Google it.
It's pretty hard
to consume enough fish
To give yourself
mercury poisoning,
And it doesn't usually present
solely with pain.
But it can.
Check out
the atlantic medical journal.
This guy came in
with burning pain
Caused by, uh,
"erythromelalgia"
Caused by mercury poisoning.
Who needs actual doctors
when you got the internet?
No offense,
but doctors make mistakes.
Medical errors
are up 30% this year.
You should check the rate
of patient error.
There's a ton
of information out there.
Why wouldn't I educate myself,
be my own advocate?
Crps came up
in my search too.
But I've never had
any skin discoloration,
And my pain is sporadic
and not constant.
It's got to be worth
one lousy blood test.
You know how House feels
about people touching his ball.
No. Chase refuses
to tell me.
Right.
My husband's gay. Witty.
I hear you're taking over
for House.
You're gonna be great.
Congratulations.
Not permanent.
Yet. Taub and Thirteen
cool with it?
He's older than you.
She's seen you naked.
Not like we haven't
been working together
For two years now.
Working with is different
than working for.
You saw House.
How was he?
He was...
Good.
He was honest,
took responsibility.
It was kind of weird.
Uh, is Thirteen around?
I need her to sign off
on her e. R. Transfer.
She and Taub are doing
a spinal stimulation.
No, they're not.
I just dropped a patient
In the cath suite,
and your guys were not in there.
You know,
usually spinal stimulation
Is done with the patient
in the room.
He asked us to test his blood
for mercury.
It's unlikely,
but not impossible.
It's also not what we agreed
on. Testing doesn't hurt.
It only takes 20 minutes.
I figured it didn't matter.
I'm thinking
I should decide
when it matters.
When you're done
Marking your territory...
Test results.
Surprise, surprise.
Marcus webly was wrong.
I'll handle this.
You expected
not to have mixed feelings?
I know it's the right call.
Just don't know what to do
with my time.
And my leg...
Pain's flared up
Since I left mayfield.
Ibuprofen's barely putting
a dent in it.
You need a hobby.
Right.
Doctors the world over
treat chronic pain
With collections
of hummel figurines.
No, I didn't say
you need a lame hobby.
You need something
to keep you engaged,
Connected
to other people.
You already made me
get a roommate.
Wilson's got one bedroom.
I don't think we can get
any more connected
Without unzipping.
Okay.
So what does Wilson
like to do?
Vince, I'm dr. Foreman,
head of diagnostics.
So you must be
the genius' replacement.
I prefer to think of myself
as genius 2.0.
Your blood tests ruled out
mercury poisoning.
What was my mercury level?
2.8.
That means for every deciliter
of... I know what it means.
I also know
it's above normal.
I want mercury chelation.
Your level
isn't elevated enough
To produce your symptoms.
You can't know that
until we de-elevate it
And see if my pain improves.
It's a judgment call.
Based on ten years
of medical training?
I think you have crps.
I want to try
spinal stimulation.
So, basically, you want
to shove a needle in my spine
Based on a glorified hunch.
I'll stick
with the chelation.
If you don't want to get better,
I think we're done.
What do you mean "done"?
You're not interested
in my medical opinion.
I'll move on
to my next patient.
You'll move on to a doctor
willing to run
All the unnecessary tests
and procedures you want.
Or you can stick around
and be cured.
Makes no difference to me.
I'm glad you changed your mind.
Don't know about that.
Dr. Foreman basically
strong-Armed me,
Which is impressive.
Stimulating at 100 hertz.
Guess you found him
A little more persuasive
than two of us...
Probably the pants.
He reminds me of me.
Is it supposed to hurt?
Not if we're in correctly.
Is it your hands?
Your back?
No, my chest.
Can't breathe.
Heart rate's 140,
climbing.
You need to hold still.
What did you do?
Deep breaths.
His lungs
are filling with fluid.
Analysis of the fluid
from Vince's lungs
Shows the lung problem
is really a heart problem.
He's got a thickened
left ventricle.
When his heart sped up
during the procedure,
It jacked up the pressure
in his lungs,
Causing pulmonary edema.
Good thing I talked the patient
into spinal stimulation.
It did lead us
to discovering a new symptom
And proved he was wrong
about mercury poisoning.
We lucked into that discovery,
and we were wrong about crps.
Ventricular thickening
plus neuropathy
Could equal lyme disease.
Not without joint pain.
When is his new game
coming out?
Couple months.
He's probably working
nonstop.
Might be using more than coffee
to power through.
Cocaine use
explains the symptoms.
So we search his office
for drugs.
No.
We're gonna ask him.
In a lot of ways,
cooking is like music.
Different elements combine
to make a symphony.
Difference is
that beethoven's 5th
Isn't gonna be poop
tomorrow.
What was my one condition
for allowing you
To tag along?
Try not to be a jerk.
I'm trying.
I'm just failing.
Roll your meatballs
and keep an open mind.
How hard are you trying not
to make a ball joke right now?
They're smoking.
Your balls.
Oh!
Ow. No, no.
They're browning
way too fast.
Blue is the color
you got to watch out for.
Enough.
My god, they're...
They're still raw inside.
By the time
they're cooked through,
The outside
will be burned.
I think there's
a medicated powder for that.
Although vinegar could work.
My o-chem prof talked
about how, theoretically,
You shouldn't trust the results
of a hemoglobin a1c test
On a chronically acidotic
patient.
The acid in the blood
slows the reaction
Between the hemoglobin protein
and blood sugar.
Browning meat is the same
chemical process,
Which means, it should also
be slowed by acid.
That actually
makes sense.
You might've...
saved my balls.
That's the spirit.
Obviously, the procedure
didn't go as planned.
The heart problem
was unforeseeable,
But I still feel
responsible.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
How long you guys
been doing it?
I think it's best
if we kept things professional.
Tough to do now that I've seen
you rock a leopard-print bikini.
Congrats, by the way.
Up top.
You hacked
my profile page?
Your treatment nearly gave me
a heart attack.
Figured I'd check
if you had the credentials
To go with the cojones.
One search led to another.
Is there a shot of just her?
I'm thinking screen saver.
We need to know
if you've been using cocaine.
Nope. Dude, you just block
everybody,
Or do you really only have
three friends?
We need you
to be straight with us.
We need to be able
to trust you.
I cleaned up my act
12 years ago...
After my
college roommate o. D.'D.
Okay.
Search his office.
You think he was lying?
No. But I'm not sure.
It was worth asking.
If he'd have said yes,
it would've saved us a trip.
But he didn't.
You have to forget
about him.
The patient?
House.
First, you try acting like him.
That doesn't work.
So then you try
the opposite.
Now you're mad because you have
to use his move.
I feel like
tom brady's backup.
Tom brady's backup
now makes $10 million.
Stop comparing.
You can do this
by being you.
We should still check out
his office,
Talk to his coworkers.
I'll get Taub.
And...
Thanks.
Oh, and dinner tonight
at 7:00.
Can we make it 8:00?
Already made a reservation
for 7:00.
Hi.
I'm making gnocchi.
Oh, I didn't mean
to intrude.
I just... Cecile's in my cooking class.
She doesn't speak english.
If you bake the potatoes
Instead of boiling them,
it's less moisture,
Fewer gluten bonds,
lighter gnocchi.
You seem good.
Feeling better.
House, I need to talk to you
about your leaving the hospital.
I do love
a good groveling,
But my decision is final.
That's fine
As long
as I'm not the reason for it.
I know that sounds
completely narcissistic, but...
Yeah.
But it's not.
We flirted.
We kissed.
I fondled.
I hallucinated
a night with you
And yelled it
from a hospital balcony.
You're not a narcissist.
So what am I?
Not the reason I'm leaving.
House...
I'm gonna miss you.
Lady, either kiss him
or leave.
We got work to do.
You just couldn't keep
your trap shut.
Make the damn gnocchi.
Bye.
I guess you're not in a hurry
to get back to the office.
And you are?
I'm not trying to avoid
my boyfriend.
I'm a lizard.
Not an idiot.
You've been in a crappy mood
since we got in the car.
And you're completely okay
with being ordered around
By someone who 24 hours ago
was basically your equal?
Unlike you, I didn't expect
anything different.
The work part,
I can get used to.
He didn't ask me
to go to dinner.
He told me we were going.
He's never
done that before.
So even the score.
Go home tonight,
Put on some heels,
and break him like a pony.
You'll feel much better.
What?
Wow, that's one
Big-Ass bird.
Wow.
It's kind of amazing.
The way the wings move,
it's so real.
Get them off me!
I know what's wrong
with the patient.
I'm going to call
Foreman.
Little help.
Your partner said
You studied birds
to improve the game animation.
Did you touch them?
Can't dissect
without touching.
It's the best way
to understand the anatomy.
It's also a good way
to contract an infection
Called psittacosis.
We spoke to dr. Foreman.
He wants to start you
on antibiotics.
Does that infection
cause problems in the...
Joystick area?
I'm kind of stuck
in play mode.
Yes, we get it.
She's very, very pretty.
It's not her.
I mean, it was...
When she was here with her
boyfriend three hours ago.
You've had an erection
for three hours?
At first,
it was just embarrassing,
But now it's really starting
to hurt.
Will the antibiotics help?
I'm afraid not.
This isn't psittacosis.
His erection persisted
even with medication.
We had to put in a surgical
shunt just to drain the blood.
You missed dinner.
And a shunt doesn't require
both of you.
I'm dedicated.
So the holy trinity:
Heart, hands, hose.
Could be Guillain-Barre.
Not with normal
nerve conduction.
Thrombocytosis.
His platelet count
isn't that high.
Brain tumor
makes more sense.
I'm sorry.
I just realized...
Joint pain and joint pain.
Honest, I wasn't laughing
because of the obvious tension
Between the two of you.
Erection points
to a circulatory problem.
I'm with Foreman.
It is possible
for a brain tumor to cause...
We're going
with thrombocytosis.
Okay.
You're mad I didn't ask you
to dinner?
How long
have we been dating?
It felt like an order.
Your tone of voice was...
My tone?
I'm under a little pressure
right now.
How about giving me
a break?
Look, this is tough
for both of us,
Except I haven't just gotten
a promotion.
So now you're jealous.
No. I'm just saying
don't complain
About the burdens of command
to your employees.
I was complaining
to my girlfriend.
Who are those guys?
I have no idea.
Meet the competition.
Steve Paulson.
Neurology, st. Mark's.
Nice to meet you.
You called another doctor?
Lots of other doctors.
Posted my symptoms
on the internet.
You guys are 0 for 2.
I thought I'd look
for some backup.
I can cure all your symptoms
with my papaya toxin cleanse.
Month's supply, $395.
Okay, that guy's an idiot.
That doesn't mean they all are.
Neither one of you have
privileges at this hospital.
Please leave...
Now.
Uh, dr. Foreman,
sorry for the intrusion,
But, um, I noticed
you haven't done a head MRI yet.
'Cause he doesn't
need one.
I'm pretty sure
he's got a brain tumor.
We considered that
And concluded thrombocytosis
is more likely.
I'm starting him
on hydroxyurea.
His platelets don't seem
anywhere near high enough.
If you took an image,
I'm sure you'll...
There are no signs
of increased ICP.
I'm not delaying treatment.
Looks like we need
a tiebreaker.
Dr. Hadley,
what do you think?
I think both theories
have merit.
So brain tumor,
Otherwise you'd back
your boss/boyfriend.
I want an MRI.
Fine.
I'll set it up.
Great. You're up.
I need a taster.
Ragout with pork sausage,
Beef thigh, no cream.
It's a little early.
Did you even go to bed
last night?
Bed is for sissies,
Unless you're having sex,
in which case...
No, bed is still
for sissies.
Doesn't this seem
a little bit obsessive?
Should've been here
when I was butchering the ox.
What do you expect?
I'm an addict.
I turn everything up
to eleven.
Yeah. I thought you were trying
to tone that down.
No. I was trying to find
something I could set at eleven
Without blowing out
my eardrums.
Star anise
with caramelized onions.
The sulfur compounds
bring out the meat flavor.
I couldn't sleep
because of my leg.
It was either make ragout
Or go out on the street
looking to score.
Good choice.
So, so good.
He asked me a question.
I answered.
You told me
to make my own decisions.
I do, and you stab me
in the back.
I didn't even say
what I really thought.
I hedged, and I don't like
that I hedged.
If I have
a legitimate opinion...
Express it
in private.
In public, the team opinion
is your opinion.
Except the team opinion
That's my job.
And what's mine,
To lie when I'm asked
a direct question?
You would've done it
for House.
Maybe you just don't want me
to succeed.
Maybe you just want
to kick me again
For not asking you
to dinner.
At least when House
was being an unbelievable jerk,
I could talk
to my boyfriend about it.
I may be a jerk,
But you're wrong.
Mri is clean.
That rules out thrombocytosis.
You're early.
For what?
I knew you'd show up here
complaining about Foreman.
Thought you'd hold out
for another week at least.
I showed up to ask
if you've seen thrombocytosis
With a platelet count
under...
I went crazy,
not stupid.
I leave,
Foreman embraces
his inner mugabe.
What's that?
Embryonali...
Unhatched chicken egg.
I'm gonna suck out
some of the yolk
And replace it with ragout.
By the way, you can tell
the other lepers
That their absence
has been noted.
Cameron didn't come by?
Daddy's little co-Dependent
is all grown up.
Making room
for daddy's hot bisexual
With boyfriend problems.
It's not a problem.
It's, um...
Okay.
It's a problem.
I mean, I get it.
The patient's a nightmare.
He posted his case online.
It... You know Foreman.
You know the situation.
How can I get him
to tone it down?
Stop being a coward
for one thing.
He's the one who's afraid
of failure.
At a job that no one before me
has ever done.
His fears are justified.
You're just afraid
of giving him control over you,
Which might work at home.
It makes it almost impossible
for him to do his job.
Pass me
those crackers.
You're saying
this is all my fault?
I'm saying...
That you would be happier
If you learned
when it's okay to give in.
What?
You just suggested
that I give in
So that I can be happy.
What did they do to you
in there?
Taste this.
Mmm. Good.
This might be the best thing
I've ever eaten.
And, yes, I'm including
what you're thinking of now.
You are an amazing cook!
I know.
And yet, my leg hurts.
Fire her.
I'm not gonna fire her.
Then stop being
such a wuss.
I'm not being a wuss.
Challenging you
is part of her job.
But when she does it,
you take it personally.
So you're saying
this is my fault?
I was trying to bury it
a little, but, yeah.
You got to eliminate
either the challenge
Or the reaction.
Or we could stick
with my original plan.
We get drunk and talk
about how girls are lame.
Yeah.
This problem will go away
on its own.
It's 8:00
in the morning.
Coffee ice cream.
No frittata?
No bombolini?
Started thinking
about what you said,
About me obsessing.
Started obsessing
about obsessing.
Decided to take a day off.
You were enjoying cooking.
How like a man to think that
I enjoy slaving over a hot stove all day
While you're off
banging secretaries.
You said it was keeping
your mind off the pain.
That was before I discovered
the biggest loser marathon
On cable.
I like to pretend
they can see me eating.
And your leg?
It's fine.
My leg's killing me.
Cooking helped for a while.
I guess I got bored.
My leg
started hurting again.
Then I got worried,
and that made the pain worse.
What are you worried about?
That nothing's gonna help.
That I end up
in the very dark place.
I'm fine...
Just not happy.
I didn't let you out
because you were happy.
I let you out,
because I believe
You had the skills
to cope with that.
You tried one thing.
It didn't work.
So move on.
Write. Play chess.
- What if nothing works?
What if nothing
gives me more
Than a few days before my brain
starts looking for the next fix,
Before my leg feels like
someone's shoving nails into it?
What do I do then?
If nothing in the world
can hold your interest,
Uh, we'll deal with that
when we get to it.
But you have to trust me,
and you have to be patient.
I brought you a doughnut.
The florist was closed.
I'll get a vase
and put it in water.
You know
I'm sorry, right?
I'm sorry too.
Do you think, um...
We could start over?
That's a fantastic idea.
We're gonna be late.
Your boss won't mind.
No way.
His lymph nodes blew up.
He's been treated
for thrombocytosis,
But there's been
no change.
I was wrong.
God, you are a genius.
I'm adding this to my list
of symptoms.
That didn't work
last time.
Because I didn't think big enough.
Now I offer $25000 reward.
Steroids reduced
his facial swelling.
Swollen lymph nodes
rule out thrombocytosis.
How did so many people
get my personal email?
The internet
is a magical place.
Lymph enlargement
makes me think polyarteritis...
You were saying?
No point in treating the symptom
and not the disease.
Your stunt generated
quite a few responses.
Let's take a look.
I'm way ahead of you.
Paraneoplastic syndrome
secondary to spinal tumor.
No. No hypercalcemia.
No muscle spasms
or incontinence.
You are possessed
by the biblical demon "legion. "
No, no jumping off a cliff
in a herd of pigs.
Otherwise it did fit.
Graves' disease.
No. Thyroid levels
are normal.
You want us to spend
the next few days shooting down
Every theory in the world,
or can we do our jobs
And come up
with one that works?
I want you to test me
for amyloidosis.
That your professional
opinion?
It's the wisdom of crowds.
Studies show the collective
decision of a group
Can be more accurate
than any individual's decision.
I went through my emails.
Amyloidosis got the most votes.
If you had amyloidosis,
There'd be speckling
on your cardiac ultrasound.
In 100% of cases?
Fine.
I'll make you a deal.
We'll do a kidney biopsy
to test for amyloidosis.
When it comes back negative,
You pull your case off of the internet
and retract the reward.
It's either that,
or I don't test you at all.
Deal.
If you wanted a quickie,
you should've called ahead.
I'm a mess.
Came home for lunch.
You have lunch with Cuddy
on tuesdays.
She was busy.
And you are checking up
on me.
You know,
you can talk to me.
Is that my laundry?
You were running out of socks
for me to borrow.
You got plenty
of underwear, though.
I'm fine.
You said that
this morning.
And consistency
proves what?
Really. I'm good.
I'll put these in your room.
* you always hurt *
* the one you love *
Biopsy showed deposits
in the renal endothelium
Consistent with amyloidosis.
The internet was right.
Start him
on dexamethasone.
Already done.
This may not be
the best time for this...
But I quit.
I got an offer to join
a friend's surgical practice.
Um, you don't generally get an offer
unless you're looking for one.
I put out some feelers when I found
out House wasn't coming back.
I lobbied to keep
the department open
So you could keep
your job.
Yes. That was incredibly
altruistic of you.
It's nothing personal.
Actually, I think
you're doing pretty well.
But I came here to work
with House.
He's a jerk.
We'll be fine
without him.
Do you know how many resumes
we get every day
Without even asking?
Might be a few less
after Cuddy shuts us down.
The case got solved
under your watch.
Does it really matter
how it happened?
It matters.
What if I'm just not ready
for this job?
Okay, you're sad.
I could tell you the story
about me and my roommate
At Sarah Lawrence.
Okay.
Her name was lindsey,
And she was a cheerleader
from iowa.
I broke my toilet
this morning.
I'll get my tools.
I blocked the intake valve
So I could collect
some of House's urine.
Cuddy,
he was barely limping.
What did the lab say?
The urine was clean
for vicodin.
It did, however,
Contain strange
epithelial cells.
Further analysis showed they were
from a labrador retriever.
Damn.
He's using.
No. No.
Vince. Vince.
Vince, relax.
It's dr. Foreman.
Kill it!
No! No!
I don't have my blaster!
He's hallucinating 'cause he's burning up.
Amyloidosis wouldn't do this.
The antipyretics didn't work.
Hopefully the cold tub
will get his temp down.
Maybe we should see
if anyone's sent in other ideas.
Maybe the reward money
attract...
No. I'm not letting
anyone else jerk us around.
The masses were wrong
about amyloidosis.
They don't know
about the fever.
I'm going with light-Chain
deposition disorder.
You okay with that?
Yes.
We think you have a disease
called LCDD.
It causes protein
to build up in your organs.
You think?
We can't definitely confirm
the diagnosis.
And our only chance
of beating this
Would be to start you
on high-Dose chemotherapy.
But I do have to warn you
That in your condition,
it might kill you.
Do you want me to get you
some more information?
You're my doctor.
I trust you.
No, you don't.
You're scared, and you don't
want to make this decision.
My career is riding
on this case...
Nowhere near as important
As your life.
But I think the best shot
for both of us
Is to treat for LCDD.
Okay.
All right, let's get you
out of this tub
And into chemo.
We know you're back
on vicodin.
No. The only thing you know
is that I'm a genius
Who got a dog
to pee in your toilet.
You don't know how I did it
or, more interestingly,
Where I peed.
House, you've spent the last
three months...
Et tu, Butte?
You got no reason
to be here.
He's the one
I was jerking around.
Why is your leg better?
Ow. It hurts.
Please go away now.
If you really think
I'm using,
How about asking me
before taking a wrench
To your plumbing?
House, you're an addict.
You can't be surprised
if we can't take you
At your word.
Fine. Let's get you
some proof.
Hide your eyes, ladies.
House.
You too.
My godson
made me that mug.
If the lab says
that this is retriever too,
Please let me know
right away.
It'd explain
my overwhelming desire
To wipe my butt
on your carpet.
Thank you for dragging me
into this.
Stop the chemo.
He's got fabry's disease.
He was in the tub
for an hour.
His fingers should have pruned,
but they didn't.
Already stopped chemo
and confirmed fabry's.
I'm glad you both agree,
But could somebody
loop me in here?
We assumed the deposits
in your kidneys were proteins,
But they were fats.
Fabry's makes them build up
In your organs,
choke your nerves,
Keep your fingers
from pruning in water.
It's chronic
but manageable.
How'd you figure it out?
lodine mumps.
His lymph nodes swelled up
after the head c. T.
We thought it was a new symptom,
but it wasn't.
It was a reaction
to the contrast.
lodine mumps takes lymph nodes
off the table.
Remove that symptom...
And that just came to you?
I looked through
the online responses again.
Someone posted it
this morning.
Heard Cuddy made it official.
Department's yours.
Congrats.
I'm sorry.
I went behind your back.
On a scale of 1 to 10,
how mad are you?
A 7.
And that's stupid.
You did the right thing.
It's my fault you thought
you had to go behind my back.
I should've stood up
to you.
But you didn't 'cause
you didn't want to fight again.
It's our first case.
It'll take time to adjust.
What if by the time we get adjusted,
we don't like each other anymore?
That's not gonna happen.
You sure?
'Cause ever since I took this job,
we've been making each other miserable.
I really don't think
this is gonna work.
You're breaking up
with me?
No.
The other night when I thought
I was done, you were there.
I need you.
I don't want
to lose you.
Why are you...?
You're firing me.
I'm sorry.
I slipped.
You took vicodin?
$25,000.
I solved
my old team's case.
I was about
to take the pills.
I went online.
I found people posting
medical problems,
And...
My leg stopped hurting.
Oh.
Oh?
I'm supposed
to be changing my life.
This is not a change.
Well, maybe I was wrong.
Says the guy making sand castles
in my brain.
We need to keep you
from using.
Taking your job away,
the medical puzzles,
Nearly drove you
back to it.
Maybe diagnostic medicine
Is the key
to keeping you clean.
So you're okay with me
going online, solving cases?
No. You can't sit all day
in a room by yourself.
Isolation
fosters depression.
The hospital is part
of my old life.
If I go back,
I might become...
Who I was before,
pills and all.
That's a possibility.
But could be...
The only thing worse for you
than going back to diagnostic medicine
Is not going back.
Guess we're gonna find out.
Sync by K!r!lleXXI after honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net