[Metric's Stadium Love]
(Madison)
sure, let's give up now.
It's no big deal.
it's just Pharmacide.
Just their tour
kickoff.
I mean, who cares
if we miss
The most insane party
in the world?
Come on, Phoeb.
victory or death.
Or possibly cake.
Look, I'm sorry.
Sorry, your caffeine fix
is on its way.
Will you hold on?
We're the DJ's assistants.
[girls shouting]
Hold on.
No, I said we both work
for him.
you mean her.
the DJ's a she-jay.
It's okay, Dave.
She's my "plus one."
Make that "plus two."
(Jordan)
you weren't worried,
were you?
Yes.
and there will be punishment
Unless you tell us
everything.
You've been here all night?
After the party, we went up
to the presidential suite
with the band.
(Phoebe)
It was ginormous.
like, ten rooms.
We had a few drinks
and some weed
and played "drummer God"
on this giant plasma tv.
Which she rocked,
by the way.
I think I hate you
right now.
Colt took me up to the roof,
But by then the gate
to the pool was locked.
So no one was up there.
So we just climbed over
and jumped down and, um...
Went skinny dipping.
Did you do it?
No.
He was so sweet.
Later, he played his guitar,
and he wrote a song for me.
All: ohh.
(Kaitlin)
Oh, my God!
Jord, what happened
to your foot?
(Avery)
Maybe you twisted your ankle
when you jumped.
(Kaitlin)
Or it could be
your allergies.
My aunt was allergic
to some cold medication,
and her hands swelled up
like the marshmallow man's.
Jord, are you okay?
Jordan!
[Massive Attack's Teardrop]
Foreman expects me
to read an x-ray
on this itty-bitty screen.
He should have emailed me
a larger phone.
Why are you packing?
We're leaving this afternoon
for the conference
on pharmacology
and public policy.
We?
We discussed this.
It's been on your calendar
for weeks.
So has Ramadan.
Think of it as a vacation.
Nice, healthy
Adirondack air.
Or not.
I don't care.
you're coming with.
You should come with me.
State pillow fighting
championships.
Dollar beers,
wet t-shirts.
In the words of the philosopher
Eddie Money,
I've got two tickets
to paradise.
House, when you moved in
I promised your therapist
I'd be here for you.
I can't be here if I'm there.
Unless you're there too.
So it's not a discussion.
fine.
I'll let Foreman know that
the 16-year-old patient
with severe edema
can wait.
Relax.
I've got no idea
what's wrong with her.
So odds are, not fatal.
still not going!
She's got rhabdo.
Who wants to come to the
pillow fighting championships?
Rutgers has got
a great team this year.
I'm so glad their anchor
didn't turn pro.
a 16-year-old girl
suddenly has
The joints of an 80-year-old.
You think we can discuss this
for a second?
It's rhabdo.
The patient gave you the answer.
she fell down and went boom.
We have to leave in an hour,
so should we eenie-meenie?
The fall would explain
the lower leg damage,
but not the swollen hands.
Hard landing caused
crushed muscles.
crushed muscles released toxins
into the blood stream.
Toxins caused swelling
in the hands and legs.
Just another way of saying
It's rhabdo.
59 minutes.
She's a credit card kid.
Her parents are architects.
They're working on a project
in Shanghai.
Could you be sitting
any further away from Chase
and still be
in the same room?
It doesn't have to be rhabdo.
The swelling could also be
caused by deep vein thrombosis.
She has allergies.
could be anaphylaxis
or some heart condition
that we don't--
It can't really be
any of those things
Since it's rhabdo.
I know it's rhabdo.
Foreman knows it's rhabdo.
Deep in his heart,
even Chase knows it's rhabdo.
Isn't it annoying when
everybody in the room knows
something you don't?
I'll test for everything.
He's an ass.
Contrast is ready.
She already thinks
I'm cheating on her.
maybe this is House's way
of telling you to talk to her.
Sure.
How was your day, honey?
By the way, I killed someone.
If I tell her,
that's dumping a burden
on her forever.
Okay.
[sighs]
No sign of obstructions
or clots.
Tell me what you came here
for, House.
I've got a legitimate
medical reason.
You must be so proud.
I've forgotten it.
I guess it's no big deal,
since I was only using it
as an excuse
to come check out
Patty and Selma.
I feel bad.
I haven't named your testicles.
Word on the street is
you set a new personal best
for low-cut.
I don't know why you chose
to give them the names
of somebody's aunts.
It's a compliment.
they're always smokin'.
Oh, I remember.
I need you to authorize the
medical discharge of a minor.
That's why I'm holding this
in my hand.
I haven't finished
testing yet, but it's rh--
Your outbox is
three times normal size.
It's not a metaphor.
There's a lot to be done
before the weekend.
You could take
the papers home with you.
Unless you're not gonna
be home.
Unless you were,
for example,
going to a medical conference.
I'm driving up with Wilson.
me too.
You aren't on
the registration list.
I love that you checked.
But Wilson said--
That I have a case?
yeah.
You're authorizing
the discharge right now.
That was a metaphor.
Busy right now.
Is he dying?
Yeah.
In the next ten minutes?
Unfortunately, no.
He's in a lot of pain.
I've thought about it.
you're right.
I should go
to the conference.
You found out
Cuddy's going.
Oh, God, no.
She'll ruin everything.
We leave in two hours.
[whispering]
Please...morphine.
(Wilson)
I'm right here.
I'm right here, Joseph.
Two days away.
You think I should pack ball-y?
You can't leave.
You lit a fuse.
You need to watch
the bomb go off.
The bomb was gonna
go off on its own
if you kept quiet.
So now you either have to
come up with a convincing lie,
or tell her the truth.
Your choice.
Ck levels point
to rhabdo.
Of course.
Except for the part where
imaging shows no sign
of muscle crush.
Hi.
I'm your doctor.
This is Lars Ulrich,
[Metallica's Fuel playing]
the greatest metal drummer
of all-time.
You know the song?
Good.
Drumstick.
Another drumstick.
I want you to rock out
to the music
the way you did last night.
Go on.
This is a classic
medical test.
Hippocrates used it.
Let's go.
Come on,
you've gotta keep time!
Cross over on the high hat.
Let's head bang!
House, what are you doing?
The chart said
her potassium's low.
Rhabdo elevates the potassium.
And monkey drums.
Ergo...
The levels must've been
really low
last night.
Which causes...
I can't move them.
[music stops]
Temporary muscle paralysis.
Given this rate
of muscle fatigue,
there's no way
she could've climbed stairs
and then a fence to the pool.
Low potassium means
no jump,
means no trauma.
tests mean "yes rhabdo."
Ergo, something else caused
both the rhabdo
and the low potassium.
This time start by getting
an accurate history.
Be careful.
Our patient's a big fat liar.
What did you really do
last night?
(Cameron)
We need to find the cause
of your low potassium.
You could have
a kidney disorder,
leukemia, adenoma.
We need to know about
any drugs or alcohol.
anything that might have
threatened your health.
Come on, Jord.
Okay, we didn't spend the night
with the band.
You can't tell
our friends.
have you heard of
Stiletto:
Warrior Queen of Space?
It's a comic book right?
Thank you.
yeah.
Yes, and a freaking amazing
new sci-fi series.
and they're filming
the motion picture now.
It's a prequel.
The other girls
wouldn't get it.
only Phoebe understands
my passion.
Only Phoebe understands
the bushido of the heel.
[girls chuckle]
So what actually happened
last night?
(Jordan)
We were with our friends
trying to get into
the Pharmacide tour party
at the Adams.
And then I found out that
Jeffrey Keener's gonna be there.
I follow his tweets.
It's tragic that I have
to explain this.
he's the creator of Stiletto
issue number one.
And the tv show.
He's a God.
So did you guys
go up to him?
God, no.
We keep a ten-foot rule.
It's not stalking
if you don't go up
to the person
and bother them.
So we just
followed him around.
Discreetly.
He ditched
after half an hour
and went down
to the hotel restaurant
for a late dinner.
And you went with him?
Discreetly.
(Jordan)
We played it so cool.
(Phoebe)
For two hours,
we lived his life.
We did everything he did.
Ate the exact same meal
he ate.
Cool.
The rest of their story
checks out.
The hotel manager says
mom and dad were charged
for food and a room,
three pay-per-view episodes
of Stiletto.
Are you trying
to kill yourself?
It's from the same batch
the girls ate.
They ate what he ate.
And what a hundred
other healthy people ate.
Dig in.
Lunch is on the Adams.
What if food is
the answer?
Not this food. Any food.
Jordan says
she ate all of this.
She's 16,
all about body image,
and she obviously worries
about fitting in.
Bulimia would account
for her symptoms.
we should do a barium swallow
for mallory weiss tears,
Start her on
nutritional supplements,
get a psych consult.
Why are you reading
my program guide?
It's not like you plan on
attending
any of the presentations.
I like to know
how much boredom I'm missing.
"Patient perceptions
of complications
in end-stage chemotherapy."
You didn't tell me
you were giving a paper.
And that was wrong?
Last time you presented
a paper,
you gave me an advance copy
and asked for feedback.
And you're wondering why
I wouldn't want to repeat
that experience?
Oh, look!
an '80s party.
Just when you think
you left Flock of Seagulls
behind
in your rearview mirror,
suddenly it's up ahead
like an undead hitchhiker.
Cuddy's going.
Did you pack my leg warmers?
If you want her...
ask her out.
My God, man!
She's not some floozy
in a bar.
She's the floozy
I work for.
There's gotta be
no radical steps here.
Gotta be subtle.
We happened to attend
the same party.
The chat happens
to turn personal.
Like the frog
in gradually boiling water.
Exactly.
She'll be red and delicious
before she knows it.
[chuckling]
What?
What could possibly go wrong?
Chase went to the gym
five times this week.
Okay.
(Cameron) One of those times
I followed him.
What?
And yes, I know how humiliating
that admission is.
Where'd he go?
The gym, that time.
But I know that something's--
I'm stopping you
right there.
This is a conversation
you should be having
with Chase, not me.
I've tried having
this conversation with Chase.
No sign of tears.
It's not bulimia.
Is he having an affair?
No.
Why should I believe you?
You shouldn't.
you should believe him.
(man)
Baby...
Sweetie...
how are you?
Jordan!
Normal sinus rhythm.
Heart rate's fine.
BP's dropping.
(Derek)
What's happening to her?
(Foreman)
No pulse.
Oh, my God!
You said her heart rate
was fine.
(Chase) cardiac tamponade.
Drain the fluid now.
[monitor alarm beeping]
(Derek)
What is going on?
(Cameron)
She's bleeding around her heart.
Blood constricted
her heart muscle.
She's on antiarrhythmics,
but we don't know how long
we can keep her stable.
(Foreman) seemed to be
triggered by stress.
Her parents had just--
Did her blood pressure drop
during the barium swallow?
Dropped to 50 systolic
in three minutes.
Rules out chronic conditions.
Acute conditions limit us
to toxins, infections.
Could be anything.
A gas leak,
arsenic in the wallpaper,
fungus in the shower.
I'll get samples from her room
and the restaurant.
(House) Talk to our
little gossip girl.
You need to know exactly
where she's been
and what she's done
in the last 24 hours.
Oh, I think--
[stammering]
Welcome to the convention,
Dr. Perlmutter.
It's my 25th
consecutive year.
Perlmutter loves the '80s.
Do you need me to leave too?
You might remember stuff
she doesn't.
We didn't do anything
we haven't told you about.
We hung out at Jordan's
all day.
And then we called a limo
to go into the city.
We stopped at
Bruce Springsteen's House.
Jord...
don't joke around, okay?
You're really sick.
just tell him the truth.
Bruce let me play
the first electric guitar
he ever owned.
My God,
why are you lying?
How can you not believe me?
Turn to your right.
Mr. Keener, I really
appreciate you coming.
Oh, it's not that much
of a hike.
My room's only
six floors up.
Last night, do you remember
two girls, about 16?
That table right there.
they made an impression.
Well, they were hard to miss
With the giggling
and the staring.
I'm sure that happens
to you a lot.
I'm sure that happens to you
a lot more.
(Foreman)
She can't control it.
A bleed in her brain is
affecting her thalamus,
causing her to lie.
We need to know everything.
You two were never
apart?
Except for when she went
to go get ice.
But that couldn't have taken
very long.
You don't know?
It was in the middle
of the night.
I woke up when she came back
into the room.
And she told you
she went to get ice?
[Men Without Hats'
Safety Dance]
♪ we can dance if we want to ♪
♪ we can leave your friends
behind ♪
♪ 'cause your friends
don't dance ♪
♪ and if they don't dance ♪
♪ well, they're no friends
of mine ♪
♪ say, we can act
if we want to ♪
♪ if we don't, nobody will ♪
♪ and you can act
real rude... ♪
(Cuddy)
House...
1980s.
You sure?
they weren't specific.
How much did it cost you
to rent that?
It was in Wilson's bag.
Dr. Perlmutter,
I read your article
on neural degeneration.
Wait, you didn't really
take that seriously, did you?
I just wrote that
for the money.
Well, hey there, Jane Fonda.
would you care to dancercize?
Sorry, we were just about
to hit the floor.
Thank you.
Your leg?
I'm okay.
As long as you don't
expect rhythm.
[Cyndi Lauper's
Time After Time]
You remember the last time
we danced?
Med school, the week we met.
No.
I saw you
in endocrinology.
Tracked you down
to the hoedown.
I meant, we met
before that.
In the bookstore.
Ah.
My third day of school,
I hand my syllabus to the guy
behind the counter.
He barely looks at me.
Just skims the sheet
and tells me
I'm overly ambitious,
I have a chip on my shoulder,
and I know how to party.
[chuckles]
I'd forgotten you knew
how to party.
I said, "you're
making that up."
And you said, "your class
schedule is overloaded.
"but none of your classes
are before 11:00,
"and no one takes
Professor Lamb's course
unless they have something
to prove."
Because Professor Siegal
covered the same ground
and was the easier grader.
I tracked you down.
Endocrinology...
the party.
And one thing led
to another.
And then it didn't.
I was gonna call you.
No...don't do that.
There was no expectations.
I was just as into it--
I was gonna come see you.
Figure out where things
would go from there.
That was the morning
I got the call from the Dean
and I was expelled
from my first med school,
and there didn't seem
any point.
I should go to my room
and review papers
for the infectious disease
panel.
♪ after my picture fades ♪
♪ and darkness has turned
to gray ♪
♪ watching through windows...♪
Hello?
Yeah.
Thanks for telling me.
7:00 in the morning.
Somebody better be dead.
My patient,
Joseph Schultz.
Oh.
Under the circumstances,
that's the best thing
that could have happened, right?
Yeah.
I just wish I had been there.
Didn't hear you
come in last night.
Yes, and it was almost 9:30.
Things didn't go
as you planned?
We've moved on
to a new phase.
I tell Cuddy that I've always
been interested in her,
and she walks out
of the room.
Well, either she just
wasn't ready for that,
or maybe she was
just surprised
and didn't know how
to react.
What are you doing?
Interesting reflex
of guilt just now.
Your patient's been dying
for six weeks.
You couldn't have predicted
he'd go this weekend.
Or could you?
[typing]
"Euthanasia:
let's tell the truth.
We all do it."
That's a great
opening line.
Are you insane?
I didn't want your notes
before,
and I don't want 'em now.
Well, she didn't
get ice.
She got out in the lobby.
she could have gone anywhere.
Let's start with
for how long.
(Chase)
Fast forward.
[audio racing]
Stop.
Rewind.
Back.
Wherever she went,
she was only gone
for, like, five minutes.
(Chase)
She's holding something.
(Cameron) It's Keener's journal.
He must have left it
in the restaurant that night.
She went back, claimed
it belonged to her.
She was looking for an excuse
to knock on his door.
(Wilson)
I know what you're gonna say.
I'm not insane.
Doctors are rarely
indicted.
Whoa...
I was just thinking
of your career.
But yeah, if you're
one of the doctors
occasionally indicted,
I guess it could
affect that.
Someone needs to say
what life is really like now
for people who are dying.
What doctors have to go through,
the decisions we have to make.
Alone.
Without guidance.
Someone should say that...
in an unsigned letter
to the Times.
I'd be telling the truth.
I'd be saying
what we're all thinking.
Who cares?
The oncology department
is subsidized by drug companies.
They don't want it run
by a murderer.
We're all murderers.
We just don't have
the guts to admit--
And once again, who cares?
You won't be hirable
anywhere.
If there's one thing
I've learned from you,
it's that I should do
what I think is right
and not worry
about the consequences.
Yeah, it's worked out great
for me.
Um, I don't mean
to be rude,
but I'm expecting
a notes call from L.A.
can we make this quick?
Did Jordan come to your room
the other night?
Let me put it another way.
We know Jordan came
to your room the other night.
Look, I've tried
to be helpful.
i don't know why
you want to pretend
I'm lying to you.
But this is getting
too weird for me.
We need to search your room.
You don't,
because she was
never here.
Allison, calm down.
You would cover your ass at
the expense of someone's life?
We know she brought up
your journal.
That was helpful.
He'd be crazy
to risk his marriage
for a one-night stand
with a teenager.
Sensible people only
risk their marriage
for something
more serious?
I'm not having an affair.
We're talking about Keener.
Fine.
He doesn't care
about his marriage.
What about his career?
Statutory rape would
ruin it.
It's admitting statutory rape
that could ruin it.
Which is why we'll never
hear the truth out of him.
Rufies OD explains
all her symptoms.
We should start treating her
with flumazenil.
Isn't the MRSA panel
going on?
We got kicked out.
She started crying.
Yeah, well, discussions
of urinary catheterization
will do that to me too.
The babysitter had
an emergency.
Oh...how did you like
'80s night?
House talked with you?
I was being subtle
about it.
You left suddenly.
I know House can be
a little much sometimes...
no, he was sweet.
I just know better
than to rely on that.
He's trying.
Yeah.
I know.
I'm a mother now.
I need a guy I can count on
every single day.
That's never been House.
(Foreman) It's not rufies.
She's bleeding
behind her kidneys.
We're transfusing another
two units packed red cells,
But she keeps
springing leaks.
It looks like a toxic reaction.
Keener must have
given her something.
The guy's a comic book writer,
not a drug dealer.
There's a lot that wouldn't
show up
in a standard tox screen.
But he's never gonna
tell us the truth.
Not gonna get the truth
out of her either.
We will if we drug her.
Amobarbital would suppress
her thalamus.
(Chase) She's on antiarrhythmics.
Amobarbital could stop
her heart.
She's already dying.
You're angry at me.
You're taking it out
on this guy 'cause you think
He's lying to you too.
And you're gonna kill
our patient in the process.
We need to know the truth.
We should call House.
Yeah.
He'll recommend we take
the cautious approach.
[whistling]
[door shuts]
Pretzel?
Those are gonna show up
on my credit card
at seven bucks a bag.
There's an all-you-can-eat
buffet downstairs.
Studies show that $10 wine
tastes better
if you're told that
it costs $90.
I'm sure the same thing
must be true of grape soda.
Have one.
We can toast your
pending unemployment.
Yes, you can sit here
running up my hotel bill,
or you can go get the woman
of your dreams.
I didn't know Angela Merkel
was attending the conference.
I just spoke with Cuddy.
She doesn't think
you're reliable.
And you will remain
friend-zoned
until that changes.
I can't convince her
That I've changed my entire
personality in a weekend.
Yeah, but you could make
the first step.
What does she need?
Today, a babysitter.
What are you thinking about?
Fjords.
You see?
Seriously.
I know this is out
of your comfort zone,
But don't scheme.
Don't--
Just do the deed--
You tell me that
I've gotta show her
I've changed,
and yet you act like
you don't believe I can.
If I can't convince
my best friend...
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean--
I didn't mean...
You drugged me.
She's better off
without you.
Words can hurt, you know.
I thought truth serum was
only stuff they gave people
in lame spy movies.
(Cameron)
We know you're scared.
But we know you want
to tell the truth.
We're gonna help you
do that.
(Cameron) What happened between you
and Jeffrey Keener
the night you went up
to his room?
(Jordan) I couldn't believe
he even talked to me.
I told him how much
his work means to me.
I figured I must sound
like a moron.
But he was nice about it.
He said I was special.
Heart rate's increasing.
140's acceptable.
Let her talk.
Did he give you anything?
a drink, pills?
(Jordan) He said it was ecstasy.
But it didn't look like ecstasy,
and it didn't really
make me feel
how ecstasy usually does.
(Cameron)
How did it make you feel?
It just made me
really tired.
What did it look like?
a capsule? Tablet?
It was a tablet. Round.
Could be lithium.
(Jordan) He just started touching me.
At first it seemed nice.
But then...
I didn't want to insult him.
That's enough.
I'm so sorry.
I love you guys so much,
and I just--
I feel like I've let you down.
I'm gonna kill him.
I'm gonna kill
that son of a bitch.
Before you do that,
look here.
(Foreman) Increased periorbital
blood flow throughout.
It means everything she's
been saying has been a lie.
Everything?
S-so you still don't know
what's wrong with her?
Sorry.
Oh, I thought you were
room service.
Something going on
with your patient?
It's quiet in there.
Is Rachel asleep?
I thought maybe you could use
a babysitter.
Actually, I've got her
in day care downstairs.
Oh.
Great.
Maybe later.
[Rachel laughs]
[Rachel cooing]
Hey, House.
Hey, Lucas.
This is awkward.
A bit.
That awkwardness would
probably go away if I left.
Huh?
It's Foreman.
I'm trying to update House,
but his phone's off.
House!
He's not here.
Patient's losing blood faster
than we can transfuse.
Cameron did an online search
and found out
Keener travels with his dog--
we're treating for rickettsia.
Any idea where he is?
Oh, no!
I was supposed to be giving
a paper five minutes ago.
Okay...okay...
Dr. Wilson has asked me
to tender his apologies
for his absence.
You'll be hearing
my paper instead.
Unfortunately,
there wasn't time
to correct
the program schedule.
"Euthanasia:
"let's tell the truth.
"we all do it.
"we just don't talk about it.
"we play the game.
"we use other words
or we don't use
any words at all."
Hmm. Nice phrasing.
Hello?
Uh...I don't know
what department I want.
Uh, I need...pants.
Patient S,
a 55-year-old man.
"End-stage lung cancer.
"His pain was beyond
the point
"where we could even pretend
to treat it.
"I showed him how to use
the morphine pump.
"I told him too much morphine
would kill him,
"but not to worry.
"The machine only gives out
so much.
"to override it you need
to enter a special code.
"I went to the door
"and told the nurse,
'the code is 328.'
"I said it loudly.
"When he first came
to my office,
"i told him I would be with him
every step of the way.
"But I left him alone
at the end.
"i broke that promise
to cover my ass,
I failed--"
I was wrong when I wrote that.
I've never given any less
than my best.
I am incapable of turning away
from a responsibility.
My friends take advantage
of that fact far too often.
I know that I gave that man
everything I could.
and I know that
he knew that too.
"This is a burden no one
should have to carry alone.
And this is a decision
no one should make alone."
Because frankly,
I don't trust all of you.
Doctor.
(all)
Doctor? Doctor?
question...
Excuse me, Doctor.
Not many people would
have your courage.
Thank you,
Dr. Perlmutter.
Hey.
Before I start shouting,
Foreman says they're
looking at rickettsia.
Thanks for the message.
Continue.
What the hell?
You think that little
shout-out is gonna
make me forget that
you drugged me,
hid my pants,
stole my speech?
You wanted the paper
out there, it's out there.
And your job is safe.
That was my paper.
You don't ask what I want,
you ignore my wishes,
you drug me.
I'm waiting for you to name
something new
to our relationship.
You've got no good reason
to be angry with me.
Oh, really?
I should be thanking you?
If this was about getting
the story out there, then yeah.
Of course, if this is actually
about something else...
Maybe you feeling impotent
because patients keep dying
and you think you need to make
some grand, stupid gesture--
You need to be a hero--
Well, then, yeah, sorry.
I did screw it up.
You stepped
over the line.
This was not
your decision.
My God, there are 10,000
oncologists in this country.
Every one of them
loses patients.
But only you would feel
guilty enough...
Of course,
we can't even argue
on my schedule.
It's House.
(House)
Take down the bags.
It's too soon to tell
if the meds are gonna--
It's not the meds.
It's the blood
that's killing her.
What's everybody doing?
you're stunned, right?
I mean, blood?
(mother) She's had internal bleeding.
She needs the blood to--
(House)
Is that the mom?
I've got a good comeback
if it's the mom.
Yes, I'm her mother.
Sure, she needs blood,
if you want to kill her.
Then you'd have nobody left
to neglect--great plan.
Your daughter has
vibrio vulnificus,
courtesy of a few scrumptious
oysters on the half shell.
I didn't eat any oysters.
(House) Thus proving that she did.
boy, that's neat.
100 other people ate
those oysters.
I ate--
Is that the dad?
I've got a good comeback--
It's Chase.
Oh, I thought the dad might've
been Australian too.
There was nothing wrong
with the oysters.
All oysters have vibrio.
But almost no one has
hemochromatosis.
It'd give here a unique
susceptibility to vibrio,
cause the swollen joints.
but it got attributed
to bulimia,
so she got supplements.
With iron.
(House) Which overcooked the liver,
which caused bleeding.
More blood, more iron,
more bleeding, more blood.
Is she going to be okay?
Only if we give her
high-dose ceftazidime
for the vibrio and chelate
for the hemochromatosis.
Now, Cameron,
Pick up the phone
and give me a dramatic exit.
So...how'd you two
crazy kids hook up?
I suspected someone in
accounting was skimming money,
and I wanted to
investigate quietly.
And since you introduced me
to the only detective I know...
And one thing leads
to another.
Why keep it a secret?
You protecting me
in my fragile state?
you think I was
an unhinged looney
who was about
to go off the rails
at a badly timed bit of news?
I just don't advertise
my personal life.
I needed help
with the baby.
Lucas drove up.
Yeah. She was worried.
A little worried.
As a friend.
I had to hide
in our room
and be the dirty
little secret.
Kinda sucked.
I told her
it wasn't necessary.
So you had some hallucination
about having sex with her.
I don't think we need
to talk--
I mean, I imagine having sex
with women all the time.
No big deal.
Though I guess if they knew
what I imagine,
it could get awkward.
And I guess
it's different because
in the fantasy,
she was your savior.
But I mean,
that was months ago, right?
All the work that you had to do
to get straight--
You've been institutionalized.
You've had way bigger stuff
to deal with.
I should shut up.
[sighs]
Can I buy you a ginger ale?
A ginger ale would be good.
With lemon.
Infection's clearing up nicely.
You should be out of here
in a few days.
Oh, that is wonderful.
[cell phone rings]
Jack, how are you?
Sweetie, your father
and I think
we should reward ourselves
with a little time off.
(father) That meeting's gonna have
to wait a couple of weeks.
We're staying here.
(mother) You should think about
where you'd like to go.
Honey, they're saying
the specs are wrong
for the whole foundation.
Can you at least
come talk to 'em?
Let me see.
You okay?
Yeah.
No.
(mother) Soil engineering report
was fine.
I'm used to it.
(mother) Who are you talking to?
So...about what happened
that night.
(Jordan)
I never even got up
the courage
To knock on his door.
(mother) Well, you'll have to send me
their numbers.
(Cuddy) Yea!
[laughing]
[baby giggling]
(Cuddy) What is that?
(Lucas) Are you driving?
He looks like a guy
who'd be there every day.
Minibar is restocked.
I say we grab some pretzels
for the road--
When you do what I did,
it's not enough
to tell yourself
you did nothing wrong.
You need to hear it
from someone else.
If not God or society,
a friend.
Otherwise you go crazy.
What you said to me
up there...
Thank you.
You're a good friend.
Cuddy should know that.
Yeah, you should let her know
that I drugged you
So you wouldn't confess
to murder.
Let's get out of here.
(Wilson) Someone could have
recognized you.
First U.S. conference
I've attended in 15 years.
Perlmutter?
Toronto, all weekend.
Airtight alibi.
I'm sorry.
I don't know why I always
suspect the worst.
If you say you're not
having an affair,
you're not having
an affair.
Oh, God, you are.
I'm not.
Okay. Sorry.
Again.
If you don't want
to tell...okay.
But I could help.
Whatever this is,
it's eating away at you.
We could get past it together.
I love you
no matter what.
We lose patients sometimes.
One of those patients...
Dibala...
We didn't ac--
We didn't actually
lose him.
I killed him.
www.tvsubtitles.net