How the...
Most people...
go for the...
hardwood or carpeting.
I think guitars and garbage
work just as well.
Got the urge to play last night.
Had to go back to my apartment.
Thought I'd save on future trips.
It's very eco-friendly of you.
How about keeping down
on the noise pollution?
6:33. You should be flossing by now.
I'm not going to work today.
I'm going hunting.
After I sleep in.
Is it that time of year again?
- He's a self-important jerk.
- He's my friend.
He's a self-important jerk.
Seems to be what I'm attracted to.
Guy calls you Jim.
Doesn't even know your name.
Jim is short for James.
Now go away,
Lim.
Nice shot.
I nailed that tree.
Maple syrup for dinner.
We should have got a guide.
Doesn't count as new adventure
if you have someone holding your hand.
On the other hand,
we are holding weapons
and have no idea what we're doing.
Fun.
We need to sneak up on them.
I read that the native Americans
say turkeys know what you're thinking.
So I should stop thinking
about German porn.
That'll lure them closer.
We're terrible at this.
At least it's cold
and my new boots leak.
It's almost time anyway.
Did you bring the bag?
May 30, 2004.
10:07 a.m.
Dr. Wilson informed me
that if treatment didn't go well,
my leukemia would give me
only six more months to live.
November 30, 2004.
Six months later, I didn't die.
As long as I am alive,
I will find new and exciting ways
to thank you
for giving me another year.
Now move very,
very far away from there
so that I can be sure
and thank you again next year.
Thanks, Jim.
All right, let's see
how many more turkeys we can miss.
This will work.
- What the hell?
- God.
Sorry. I don't know what happened.
I can't move my arm.
Am I having a stroke?
I don't know.
.:: La Fabrique ::.
R[H]ésus AB+ Team
ShalimarFox
mpm
Arrow
Benj
Good news. Head CT doesn't show
any signs of a stroke.
So he's gonna be okay?
I cannot believe
how much you've grown up in five years.
She's...
She's not family.
Ashley, my girlfriend.
New life, new adventures.
- Ashley, meet Jim.
- It's good to meet you.
So this arm thing,
does that mean his leukemia's back?
I checked blood counts
and blood cell morphologies.
- Everything is normal.
- So these blood tests,
it means it's not cancer for sure.
- He said I'm fine.
- So what it is?
Hopefully something innocuous.
There's a doctor I can speak to
who's great...
Who's great at diagnosing...
What?
Sorry, that cold sore,
how long have you had that?
Two weeks. I'm sorry.
I got the call.
- I didn't have time to cover it up.
- What is it?
That cold sore is caused by a virus.
Assuming you kiss,
the virus could transfer,
infect your spine,
and cause the paralysis.
A disease
called transverse myelitis.
- And is that good news or bad news?
- It's great news.
I'll get you a room
and start you on acyclovir.
I just had a House moment.
Diagnosed transverse myelitis
from a cold sore.
How cool is that?
Patients really eat that crap up.
It's why I'm loved.
- What am I doing here?
- Ultrasound is clear.
He's definitely not pregnant.
No gall stones.
Could be diverticulitis.
- Have you eaten any seeds?
- I'm joining you, Antonio Aguilar.
We'll play in God's Mariachi band.
Draw some blood.
The self-important jerk
does not have transverse myelitis.
He's got cancer.
How do you...
Maybe I paid the redhead down
in records a few bucks
to cc me on all your cases.
Patients die, you might get sad again.
Make a speech would end your career.
Frankly, I'm stalking you for you.
- How long does a blood draw take?
- Almost finished.
When you're finished
almost finishing it, test it.
Mi estomago's ripped open
by the hand of God.
- He spilled my blood.
- Confusion. Delirium.
Why rule out
the hand of God so fast?
Your guy's low white count
and right arm paralysis
equals a recurrence
of his leukemia.
Simple math.
Did you look past
the first page of the file?
No AML cells anywhere.
I did the blood smears myself.
It's still cancer.
You know how I know?
He's got an oncologist for a doctor.
And your magical leukemia detector
is more powerful
than a flow cytometer?
I look for zebras
because other doctors
rule out all the horses.
In this case,
you are those other doctors.
You haven't earned a zebra.
- 100 bucks.
- Are you serious?
Friends don't diagnose
friends with cancer.
I get it.
Your problem is you're not objective.
Your caring is clouding your diagnosis.
Just cut that out
and you could be a pretty decent doctor.
Just give me the lactic acid level.
27.
The fact
that you can't speak English
is not an excuse for you not being
humiliated by what I'm about to say.
It's also not an excuse for you
not telling us
that you were a tennis pro.
If you had,
- we wouldn't have wasted our time.
- Fine.
100 bucks.
Is Tucker settling in?
Already got
his first dose of acyclovir.
And don't worry,
I ordered his girlfriend the kiddy meal.
Next patient on deck.
Del Clinton, day six of chemo.
You just missed the grandkids.
That's all right.
Last time they were here,
they painted my tie.
You're almost ready to go home.
You feeling okay?
I feel like I felt
after the last four rounds.
In oncology,
familiar pain means all is well.
So that's good, right?
I heard Jesse and Zeke
were by earlier.
Sorry, Del, I gotta run.
How are they doing?
They're fine.
No game-winning hits?
No aced report cards?
- No school plays?
- I guess not.
I thought you had to go.
- Are you depressed?
- I have cancer.
You've had cancer for a long time.
It's never stopped you from bragging
about the grandkids.
I guess I'm feeling
a little more down than usual.
Can you give me something?
I don't want you to get alarmed,
but sometimes depression can be a sign
that something else is going on.
I'm just gonna order extra tests.
- What's going on?
- It's his foot now.
- It's nothing.
- It's not nothing.
I just started getting
a little tingling feeling in my foot.
- Is that bad?
- It's gonna be okay.
It might mean his foot fell asleep.
It might mean nothing.
Could you give us a few minutes?
- Why can't you tell me?
- Because you're making him nervous.
Give us a few minutes, okay, hon?
It's not the disease
you thought it was?
The medicine I gave you
is not working.
I might have to hit it harder.
I'm gonna add ribavirin
to your treatment.
Are you sure
that this isn't a recurrence?
- So the brave face is just for Ashley.
- She's young, she's terrified.
- She's not really equipped.
- Don't worry.
Once you've had cancer,
recurrence is your biggest fear.
I get it.
I've looked every which way there is.
That's not what's happening here.
Can you call my daughter
and ask her to come down?
You can't do it?
She hasn't exactly been talking to me
since I got together with Ashley.
I'd really like her to be here.
Of course.
Exactly how serious does it have to be
to justify you coming to see your dad?
No. I'm sorry.
I'd rather you regretted coming
than regretted not coming.
Thanks, Emily.
How's Tucker?
He's made a mess of his personal life.
But physically, he's gonna be fine.
- Transverse myelitis.
- What does House think?
What is this?
Is House my overseer now?
No, it's just not always a good idea
for doctors to treat
their friends, that's all.
House has got 100 bucks on cancer.
So unless you want in
on the action...
Is Bonnie still a realtor?
As far as I know.
Do you mind if I call her?
I'm looking for a new place.
I'm moving in with Lucas.
It wasn't the tennis.
You're moving in with Lucas?
You're Bonnie's friend.
You know how to reach her.
And yet instead of calling her,
you come and seek my permission.
You want my blessing,
and implicitly, House's blessing.
I don't need House's blessing.
Good.
So when will he be able
to move his arm again?
Should be soon.
Started smoking again?
Is it bad that he's coughing?
Hi, Dad.
Melissa, hey.
I didn't know you were coming.
I was at Mom's house
when Dr. Wilson called.
I can go if it's gonna be weird.
No, no, stay. It's fine.
- How are you?
- Is he okay?
He's okay.
I'm not a big fan
of this coughing though.
You must be Ashley.
Are you okay?
Do you think this cold sore thing
could've caused this?
No. Whatever's causing this
is affecting more than his nerves.
I need a crash cart in here!
Don't you guys have
a dying Mexican crooner to attend to?
He isn't dying anymore.
Found out he was on a popcorn diet.
Eating ten bags
of microwave popcorn a day.
Huffing the fumes scared his lungs.
That's...
very strange.
Where's House?
Performing his ritual "hiding from Cuddy
to avoid getting a new case" dance.
It's sort of a jazz-fusion
type of thing.
He's probably eating in the morgue.
I can page him.
Actually... maybe it would be better
if I talked to you alone.
House and I have a bet
about one of my patients.
You guys mind making him
100 bucks poorer?
43-year-old male
in remission from leukemia
presents with left arm paralysis
and trouble breathing.
- I assume House's money is on cancer.
- Thanks. That's very helpful.
- Subdural hematoma would explain...
- CT ruled it out.
I thought it was TM
I started antivirals, but he got worse.
Bacterial infection?
Bacteria'd move much faster.
He'd be dead already.
Could be fungal.
It would explain
his breathing problem,
but not his "unable to move
his arm" problem.
Actually,
if aspergillus fungus balls
took root in his lungs
and spread to his spine,
it would explain both.
The treatment involves riddling
the infected area
with BB-sized pellets
of antifungal meds.
I assume
you don't just load up the 12-gauge
and pepper me with birdshot.
No. We have a slightly
more humane delivery system.
But we do have to open you up.
It is surgery.
And like any operation,
there are risks.
What do you think, honey?
I don't know.
Is surgery really such a good idea?
He just seems so sick.
I just...
you should do
whatever you think is best.
Is this the only way
to go after this thing?
Because of the rapid progression,
we don't have time to test or try IVS.
And he's strong enough.
Definitely.
- I want you there during the surgery.
- Of course.
You gotta do it.
Good.
Dr. Chase will be in here soon
to get you set for the O.R.
Page Dr. Chase to Tucker's room
for a surgery consult.
- And can you get me...
- Mr. Koplovitz wants to talk to you.
- Everything all right?
- He wanted to talk to his doctor,
not his doctor's assistant.
- And House is looking for you.
- What did you tell him?
That you were in the clinic.
I figure that gives you about 10 min.
Here.
Mr. Koplovitz's chart. Go.
Hello, Saul.
- I heard you were looking for me.
- I'm very tired.
But I can't sleep.
Today's your lucky day.
I happen to be a sleep specialist.
Thanks, Doc.
- Can a guy get a little privacy?
- Nice hiding spot.
Actually, it's perfect.
It allows me to hide from Cuddy
and find you.
What did she want?
She was checking up on Tucker
thanks to you.
That's it?
Like what?
Something about you?
Something you could interpret
as being about you?
An anagram maybe?
Play hide and seek somewhere else.
- My patient...
- No problem.
Give me the 100 bucks you owe me
and I'm gone.
Tucker doesn't have cancer.
He doesn't have a ball of fungus
in his lungs either.
Next time you want to use my team,
at least leave a tip.
I'm late for surgery.
Your assistant said you'd be in here.
I talked to Bonnie.
Let's take this outside.
Mr. Koplovitz just got to sleep.
Sorry. She found us
this fantastic loft.
- Outside.
- It's not a loft, it's more urban.
Not that I'm urban, but I used to.
Two bedrooms.
Got wonderful views.
It's a really great place.
Procedure should take about an hour.
I'll be observing the entire time.
Maybe it'd be better
if you stayed with Ashley.
She's more scared than I am.
Well, she's...
At her age...
she's not supposed to be dealing
with issues of life and death.
Wasn't what I was planning
when I went after her.
Why did you leave Melissa?
We got married young.
We...
I'm not sure.
There's nothing to talk about.
Why are you doing surgery
when I need you finding me a new case?
You don't want a new case.
Oh, right.
Guess I'm here for Wilson.
Obviously you didn't tell me
that Cuddy was moving in with Lucas
'cause you were protecting me.
Which is odd since I told you
that I'm fine with their relationship.
So obviously,
you question one of those assumptions
or you have an issue with logic.
Yes, you're fine with them dating.
But moving in together
is a whole other level
of commitment.
This is the 21st century.
I realize that the logical course
of any adult relationship
could one day lead to fornication.
Although,
the fact
that she wants to buy a loft
could mean that their relationship
is not as serious as I thought.
For God's sake, House,
don't do this to yourself.
It's a loft.
It has no deeper meaning
than open-space living arrangement.
If you bought into her diatribe
about rediscovering
her lost city girl roots.
And two bedrooms.
It just reeks of commitment issues.
Yeah. Or she has a baby.
This is classic
mid-life Cuddy crisis.
This is her version
of a two-seat convertible.
Clearly you're fine with it.
Wilson, he's got global lung damage.
Means it's not fungal.
It's PCP pneumonia.
Obviously something
is knocking out his immune system.
Three options.
HIV. Acquired SCID.
Or my personal favorite, cancer.
I'm sure you'll test for all three.
62-year-old African-American man
with lymphoma now in remission.
I did a CT and found a small lesion
on the upper lobe of his left lung.
If he's in remission,
why did you bother scanning him?
During a routine follow-up,
I realized the patient was depressed.
That's quite a call.
The treatment indicate...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize you were
in the middle of something.
It's a conference room
with glass walls.
You thought I'd be alone?
Your patient has cancer.
Not that guy.
He probably also has cancer.
And he's probably also your buddy.
Thought you'd want to know.
'Cause you owe me 100 bucks.
You have acute
lymphoblastic leukemia.
A.L.L.
So it is a recurrence.
It's different.
It's a second leukemia.
Probably caused by the chemotherapy
we gave him five years ago.
That's why you didn't see it.
Maybe they can rename it
ironic leukemia.
This is not the end.
Tests show that the cancer
is limited to your brain.
- That's good news.
- How can cancer in his head be good?
The blood brain barrier separates
the blood in your head
from the blood in your body.
Keeps the cancer bottled up.
We can go for a cure.
So give me the numbers.
90% chance of cure.
Really?
What if we're in the 10%?
Steady decline.
But six months of a good quality life.
Does he have to go through
another bone marrow transplant?
Chemotherapy.
We can go at this with drugs alone.
When do we get started?
We begin by surgically planting a shunt
so the drugs go directly into the brain.
I booked the O.R.
You're the only one who can make cancer
sound like good news.
We get it out of your head
and you walk out
paralysis gone and cancer-free.
We also need you to sign
a health care proxy.
If something goes wrong
someone needs
to make decisions for you.
What are the chances
of that happening?
Very remote.
I think maybe Melissa
should be my proxy.
What?
No.
Coming through.
House got a new case.
Revised O.R. schedule.
Sorry, Wilson, had to bump you.
- It's not like your guy's bleeding out.
- Your guy's not bleeding out.
The nurse who books the O.R.
thinks he is.
- Your case is no more urgent than mine.
- Yeah, but you're way more patient.
It's okay.
You can talk about the paperwork
in the prep area.
You trust her more than me.
About this, yes.
You've been through the good stuff,
but she's been to hell and back with me.
She gives me the best shot
of getting through this.
- You still love her.
- Don't be silly.
I love you.
Please...
don't make this
into more than it is.
- Anything?
- No.
- Can you feel this?
How about here?
Where is everybody?
Melissa and Emily went downstairs
to get some breakfast.
- Ashley?
- She had work to do.
I thought she was off today.
She didn't really have work to do.
She was pissed
so she pretended to have work to do.
I let her pretend.
Move your fingers.
- The chemo's not working.
- Does that mean it's not cancer?
No. It means the chemo
from your first round of treatment
has made the leukemia resistant.
So I'm in the 10%
that don't get cured.
Maybe not.
We just removed a screw
from a guy's lung.
And the weird thing is
he didn't get better.
- Any idea what that means?
- It means you're not listening to me.
No. It means I'm ignoring you
to make a point. There is a difference.
The problem is,
I have no idea what point you're making.
That your idea is implicitly
not worth responding to.
Doubling your patient's chemo dose
is stupid.
Damn. Now it's explicit.
It could swamp out the resistance
of the cancer cells.
The fact it theoretically should work
doesn't make it any less stupid.
Of course it does.
- It's exactly what you would do.
- I'm me. You're you.
And a table is a table.
And chemo is poison.
And double chemo is double poison.
I can handle it
when things go wrong.
You can't.
And things could go very,
very wrong.
I can handle it.
Sounds pretty dangerous.
It is.
What do you think, Mel?
I think you should call Ashley.
You're my family.
I'm sorry I forgot that.
I think that you should try
whatever could keep you
with us longer.
- Look.
- I can move them.
What is it, Jim?
I'm gonna need to run some tests.
Intraepidermal superficial bullae.
- Could be Pemphigus.
- Or it could be from the fire.
Either way, he's dead.
We can't stop the oozing.
Don't care.
I'm here because it's 1:15
and Wilson started testing at 12:45.
- Which means...
- The cancer's gone.
But over half his hepatocytes
are dead.
In only 24 hours?
He needs a new liver.
Look on the bright side.
You can publish the results
of this case study.
No one will ever
double the dose again.
The double dose of chemo
got rid of your cancer.
But it also trashed your liver.
If I don't find you a new liver,
you've only got about 24 hours left.
So what do we do now?
Your father's been moved
to the top of the transplant list.
- But all we really can do is wait.
- That's it? We wait?
- Tell me something that I can do.
- I'm sorry, Mel.
You and Emily don't match
Tuck's blood type.
And neither does Ashley.
So a live liver donation is out.
The best thing to do
is just what you've been doing.
Be together.
Hope he already told you
that you're gonna die.
It's gonna make what I'm about to say
a lot more relevant.
I know it's raining
out there in the hallway, but...
I was just in the ER testing my patient
for autonomic dysfunction.
It's the only department with a shower
big enough for the whole team,
plus the cardiac monitors, plus me.
Anyway, relevant part,
we're just wheeling the guy out,
trauma came in.
- Motorcycle versus semi.
- How bad?
Bad for the motorcycle.
Good for your liver.
- Blood type's match.
- Why wasn't I paged?
Because there's a problem.
No organ donor card.
Dead guy's sister is next of kin.
She's refusing to allow the donation.
- Where is she?
- 20 minutes away.
How do you get the call
that your brother's dead
and then run out the door?
"That reminds me,
I had dry cleaning to pick up."
Did Cuddy buy the place?
Not yet.
- You okay?
- Just making conversation.
- Yours was getting boring.
- What are you planning?
- I'm not planning anything.
- And I don't believe you.
How are you gonna punish her
for dating Lucas?
Now this conversation
is getting boring.
Are you really OK?
I am not okay.
Not even close.
See, that's very adult of you.
No, it isn't.
It's just me accepting the fact that
there's nothing I can do and moving on.
Which is, I think,
the definition of adulthood.
If it is,
being a kid is a lot more fun.
Showtime.
I didn't speak to him for years.
But when my parents died,
at their funeral,
we made peace.
Our parents must've blessed it.
And I'm sure they would want him
to do good
with his last act in this world.
They wanted us to be friends.
Our relationship wasn't strong,
but it was growing.
If I allow you to defile his body,
it will destroy that bond.
The itai will be harmed.
It will save my patient's life.
What if I told you...
that he wasn't dead?
Are you saying my brother
is still alive?
You're being an idiot.
I don't have time to talk you
out of your religion
so I'm stuck with giving you
a technicality
that will let you justify
doing the right thing.
What if his last living act
was to donate a part of his liver?
Not the whole thing,
just one small piece.
Then I'm not defiling a dead body.
The last generous act
of a living person.
It's too late.
The liver started to degrade.
It's no longer viable
for transplant.
Well played.
Religion killed another person.
It's not fair, Jim.
You just helped me
get my family back together.
I'm not ready.
I would've had six more months with them
if you hadn't given me that extra chemo.
Now I have less than one day.
I'm sorry.
We knew the risks.
I don't want to lose them again.
I can't lose them again.
There's nothing more we can do.
Five years ago,
when I needed a transfusion,
you used your own blood.
We have the same type.
Which means you can give me
a part of your liver.
- I'm your doctor.
- You're my friend.
Should I die
because you're also my doctor?
- Of course not.
- Then. You're fired.
Now you're just my friend.
Now you can do what's right.
Tucker, it's...
I can't.
Late night with the Pigeon sisters?
Every now and again,
I'd like to come home
without getting interrogated.
Someone's cranky.
And late.
Where were you?
Just getting a drink.
Why are all my frozen dinners
thawing on the counter?
I needed room
for my margarita jell-o shots.
I use test tubes as bottles
so they'll be shaped like my cane.
Why'd you go out drinking alone
when you got such great company here?
Tucker wants me to donate
a lobe of my liver to him.
And you were out drinking.
So you're actually considering this?
Yeah. I was out marinating
my liver in alcohol
to get it ready for the transplant.
Your mouth says no,
but your pathetic attempt
at a deflection
has guilt written all over it.
It's my fault.
It is my fault!
- I gave him too much chemo.
- You cured his cancer.
- Killed him in the process.
- Quibbles.
He's had a predictable complication.
Surprise. Bad things
happen to people who are sick.
Doesn't make you responsible.
No... not legally.
Ethically.
- Ethically!
- A table is a table.
Don't be a doormat.
Boy, you are...
you willfully ruined my food
and have taken over my living room
because you already think I'm a doormat!
You know what...
you're wrong.
You... clean up your stuff
and get out.
You're wrong.
How's Tucker?
Still not dancing.
But scans came in on Del Clinton.
- It's good news.
- Thanks.
Let me know as soon as Tucker
takes a turn for the worse.
I want to be there.
See that small spot
at the top of the lung?
That was then.
This is now.
Spot's gone.
That tiny little spot?
It's not too impressive, is it?
That little dot could've killed me?
Fortunately, we caught it early.
It's gonna be okay.
That's amazing.
You got all this off me
not talking about my grandkids.
Thanks, Bonnie.
Just gonna have to sit tight
for a while.
I put an offer on the loft.
Seller turned me down.
I offered exactly what a similar
unit sold for three months ago.
I want to donate a lobe
of my liver to Tucker.
- That's insane.
- I'm donating a small portion of...
You have hundreds of patients.
And until I run out
of excess organs,
why shouldn't I do everything
I can to help them?
Because you're a doctor,
not a donor.
Why did you make me
the head of oncology?
Not because you have
the most organs.
You're thoughtful, caring.
Caring.
By your own criteria
a strength and not a weakness.
This is coming out of guilt.
This is coming out of friendship.
I have a friend who's about to die.
And I have the opportunity
to save his life.
Call me a doormat,
get it all out of your system...
but I'm doing it.
Why?
He's my friend.
I'm your friend.
All the pain pills I've taken.
- What if I need your liver?
- Right.
How selfish of me not to have
considered your possible future needs.
They're all dying.
They're all your friends.
I'm not here for an argument.
No. Right.
That's room 12A.
So why are you here?
Wanna make sure
that I called the moving van?
The operation is in two hours,
and I'd like you
to be there with me.
Why?
Because if you die, I'm alone.
How you feeling?
Can't complain considering
if it weren't for you, I'd be dead...
twice.
You?
I feel good.
Sending out your laundry?
Going to rehab.
Some place up in Katonah.
Up by your new house,
not near your old house.
Easier on Ashley.
I see.
I was thrilled to get
the family back together
and Melissa's great in a crisis,
but the person you want
when you're dying
isn't the same as the person
you want when you're living.
Actually, it's James.
You ready to admit
that he's a self-important jerk?
I still feel good about what I did.
You don't feel angry?
I'm a little disappointed.
Disappointment is anger for wimps.
You don't have to be so gentle
about everything.
It's okay to get angry
once in a while.
You can't change a table.
Actually, you can.
Just need a coat of paint
and the guts to use it.
Bonnie told me what Cuddy bid.
You're gonna outbid her?
We do need a bigger refrigerator.
She hurt my friend.
She should be punished.
You got mad.
I'm proud of you.
Cuddy won't share that sentiment.
How are you gonna explain it to her?
I'm changing our address
to a p.o. box.
She'll find out eventually.
A problem delayed...
is a problem denied.
I'll take it.
Baby steps.
www.sous-titres.eu
www.tvsubtitles.net