♪ ♪
[growls]
[exhales and growls]
Good explosion!
Drive it!
Drive it! Drive it!
[growls]
You watching 77?
I'm watching everybody.
You don't need
to watch everybody.
You need to watch 77.
You his agent?
Just an objective mom.
His explosion
is impressive.
It's not just burst.
He can pull too.
You know, the only reason
he went to a double "a" school,
He was a bit
of a late bloomer.
He's a big man now.
You should be his agent.
Nice pancake, 7-7!
You're moving up
those draft boards!
Thank you, sir!
On one, on one.
Ready?
(all)
break!
♪ ♪
(quarterback)
blue 90. Hike!
♪ ♪
[grunts]
good job!
Second level, nice!
Off our quarterback!
[players shouting]
[grunts]
[players shouting,
whistle blows]
(coach)
play's over!
The play is over!
♪ ♪
Save the aggression
for between the whistles!
Daryl.
All right,
back to work!
[grunts]
Daryl.
[grunting]
Daryl, stop!
(player)
what are you doing?
[massive attack's teardrop]
House 6x12
Moving the Chains
-- Sync by addic7ed.B3 --
-- for addicted.com --
[house humming]
♪ ♪
What are you doing?
Canoeing.
But I seem
to be taking on water.
This is not okay.
Use your own bathroom.
No canoe in my bathroom.
My leg hurts.
Soaking it makes it feel better.
You were the one
who had to have this condo.
Maybe next time
you should consider amenities,
Like two full baths,
instead of just the joy
Of outbidding cuddy.
The guy who signs the loan
gets to pick the bedrooms.
Stay out of mine.
Well, you owe me 35 bucks
for the grab rail I installed.
[daryl grunting on computer]
oh.
[door opens]
Hit the kill screen.
Boss is here.
It's not porn.
It's our new patient.
Bummer.
22-year-old male--
6'7", 310 pounds.
Clearly has
brain involvement.
The guy has no recollection
of this entire incident.
Football player.
Those the ones that get hit
in the head a lot, right?
E.R. Ct'd him--
no concussion, no stroke,
No cortical degeneration.
And he had
a full psyche evaluation.
He's not crazy.
So it's roid rage.
I don't think they grow them
that big naturally.
E.R. Also tested for steroids.
He's clean.
Only proving that our guy
got his hands on the good stuff.
The negative test at least means
steroids is less likely.
We should discuss
other possibilities.
Why?
He injects his sore ankles
With lidocaine every game.
You think he's above
injecting steroids?
(foreman)
repeated head trauma
could damage
The base of the brain,
leading to a pituitary adenoma,
Which leaks gnrh.
Pituitary damage wouldn't be
visible on a ct scan.
Could cause the excess hormones
that could cause the rage
And would elude
the e.R. Steroid test.
Fine.
Bilateral venous sampling
to find the elevated gnrh.
Mri to find
The pituitary damage.
Unless, of course,
there is no pituitary damage,
In which case, our guy got
his hands on the good stuff.
Foreman.
Let the peasants
handle the peasantry.
Your brother needs to get
picked up this afternoon...
From prison.
Your older brother,
in case your confusion is--
How do you know
about that?
He left a message.
Said he couldn't get you
on your cell or at home.
I get it.
You're busy.
You'll pick him up the next time
he comes out of prison.
Is that all?
You're officially unbusy.
Family is family.
Take the rest of the day.
Go see your brother.
I have work to do.
Do you feel any pain
that's deep and persistent,
Not just muscles
or joints?
Everything hurts all the time.
That's football.
It might not be
just football.
We're gonna test for damage
to your pituitary.
If there is,
it could create excess hormones,
Which could be causing
your pain.
It would also explain
your rage attack.
And if my pituitary
is damaged,
How long would it take
to treat?
I don't want to get
ahead of ourselves
And start promising
deadlines.
(glenda)
I-I'm sorry, doctor,
But he's playing
in front of pro scouts,
Coaches, and gms
this Saturday.
This is the job interview
for the rest of his life.
If we do find
something wrong,
We can go in through the nose
and repair the damage--
Nothing too invasive.
You'll need a couple days
of recovery,
And then we can have you back
by game time.
Thank you, doctor.
There's nothing wrong
with your eyes.
Well, then
your gizmo's broken.
I'm seeing spots.
Or you enlisted,
You got the cool haircut
and the awesome pants,
Then you realized
that your plane ticket
To the middle east
was coach,
And you decided to rethink
your promise.
No.
I've already been there--
three deployments.
Now they want me
to go again.
But my wife's pregnant.
So our homeland
should be unsafe
Because your private
was unsafe.
Look, my wife and I
planned this perfect.
My enlistment was supposed
to be over last week,
So we got pregnant
six months ago.
Now they tell me
I'm getting stop-lossed--
Army speak for they don't care
about the fact
That I've already finished
my contract.
I don't care about the fact
that they don't care.
Hey, come on.
I waited an extra hour
just to make sure I got you.
Why?
I saw you limping
out there.
Vietnam?
Viet--
How old
do you think I am?
I don't know, vietnam age?
Well, back in my day,
The real dodgers had the stones
to run up to canada
Or shoot themselves
in the foot.
They didn't come
to free clinics
Whining
for doctors' notes.
Go hug your wife.
Tell her to get a babysitter.
You'll be back in time
to video
The kid's first steps.
I don't need
to see the scan.
I can tell from your little
puppy-dog eyes
That his pituitary's fine.
Are you gonna say it,
or should I?
You were right
about the steroids.
You're a genius.
Next time with feeling.
Put the cheater
on a somatostatin analog
To clear it out
of his system.
Send him back
to his football game.
I've never done steroids.
Well, somehow your gnrh
got elevated.
This will help get it
back down.
Mom, I swear.
Who's gonna draft you,
daryl?
You're stupid enough
to try that stuff,
Especially the week
you know you're getting tested.
You guys must've mixed up
your labs
Or got somebody else's blood,
because I never--
[machine beeping rapidly]
Okay, what is that?
Tachycardia.
Lay back down, daryl.
[labored breathing]
Why's my heart beating
like this?
It's not steroids.
I need some adenosine!
And get that crash cart
over here!
Oh.
House, next time--
Marcus.
Oh, right.
You two know each other.
What are you doing here?
Uh, interviewing.
Oh!
Who are we kidding?
Interview's over.
You got the job.
What job?
My new assistant.
Part of his parole--
he needs a job.
Just trying to do
my part.
You were wrong
about the steroids.
Patient had
a paroxysmal tachycardia.
We cardioverted him
back to sinus rhythm.
We're gonna get an ekg
and a sestamibi scan.
Marcus...
Let's talk outside.
Family is family.
Hey.
Good to see you too.
Did you have
a hard stretch?
No, not bad.
I hardly got raped at all.
You can't work here.
Well, your boss says
I can.
I'm not playing.
Lighten up.
Man, this could be fun.
I get to see your world.
You get me access
to the pharmacy.
I am playing.
Come on, man.
You look good.
I'd already know that
if you came to visit
Every once in a while,
but whatever, I get it.
It--it's cool.
You don't want to see me.
You don't want
to pick me up.
It's all justified.
I'll just have to win you
back over.
Let me explain something.
This man who's offering
you the job--
He's not a philanthropist.
He seems more helpful
than you.
He doesn't want
to help you.
He only wants to use you
to screw with me.
You know how you can screw
with him?
Act like your brother getting
a job doesn't screw with you.
Trust me, it'll be better
for both of us
If you go back in there
and tell him
You can't take the job.
I'm not a person
who has the luxury
Of turning down jobs.
Well, figure something out...
'cause you cannot work here.
Mm.
Oh!
[possum hisses]
Ho-wah!
House!
[possum hisses]
Okay.
Oh! Oh!
(taub)
we spent all night,
used all the fancy machines.
Patient's heart
looks fine.
(house)
well, if it was fine,
It wouldn't go aflutter
Just 'cause you walked
into the room.
Light whip,
two extra shots.
Thank you, sir.
Judging by the look
on your face,
I assume you're upset
That big bro didn't take
your advice
And skip town.
You told him
about our conversation?
He bought me breakfast.
(house)
it was fun.
Put lunch in the books,
just you and me.
Our patient
could have a pfo.
Well, naturally, you jump
right to a urinary issue.
Pfo's not urinary.
It's a heart issue.
It is? Oh.
Well, naturally,
you think
It's not a urinary issue,
'cause you're so embarrassed
about your own
Past urinary issues,
You don't dare broach
the subject.
Oh, come on.
You spending the night
over at bobby samson's.
[sighs]
I did not wet the bed.
I spilled a drink.
We're not buying it, eric.
We never bought it.
Why aryou telling him
these things?
What's the big deal?
It was 25 years ago.
Oxygenated
and deoxygenated blood mix,
The rough flow causes a clot,
explains the heart and head.
(marcus)
like that power forward
from loyola marymount,
When he, um...
Hank gathers?
That's not what happened to him.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
let your brother speak.
What happened
to hank gathers?
(marcus)
conference tournament--
Alley-oop dunk,
jams it home.
Then he runs up the court
and splat.
He dropped dead
of a heart thing
Right there on the court.
I remember that.
On autopsy,
they found he had
A hypertrophic
cardiomyopathy.
(house)
rage and tachycardia
Are warning signs.
Seriously?
Because my brother
remembers a basketball game?
Hey, I don't care
where an idea comes from,
As long as it makes sense
and embarrasses someone.
[door opens]
Are you out of your mind?
As a former
psychiatric patient,
I take offense
at that terminology.
All I did was ban you
from my tub.
Whatever happened
to proportional response?
to coherent conversation?
That...Thing...
Broke tiles,
gashed the walls,
And pooped everywhere.
Expect a bill for repairs...
And payback.
What was that?
I have no idea.
Everybody else thinks
Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy
makes sense?
Good. Stick the patient
on a treadmill.
Stress his heart
until it stops.
You want to induce
cardiac arrest?
Only real treatment
is for the patient
Never to stress
his heart again,
Which means we have
to tell him to retire
At the ripe old age
of 21.
Stopping his heart
speaks louder than words.
Go.
Maybe it's a good thing.
He gave your brother a job,
responsibility.
I'm not arguing
that he shouldn't have a job.
I just don't want him
having one here.
I understand that house
did this to annoy you.
But why is he succeeding?
[sighs] you know
what my brother did
The last time
he got out of prison?
He stole money
from my parents to buy drugs.
He robbed a liquor store.
Then he moved on
to jacking luxury cars--
Last time.
Every time.
I've known my brother
for over 30 years.
You haven't even known
him a day.
I'm sorry.
The exterminator
charged $250
To get the opossum
out of there,
And the contractor
estimates
$1,500 to fix the bathroom.
And why are you
jerking foreman around?
Because it's fun.
Maybe you should give
those bills to the guy
Who left his own
bathroom window open.
Your motives always run deeper
than simple fun.
I want to learn more
About one of my employees
so that I can manipulate him
And destroy him
if and when I choose.
Information is power.
Not buying it.
Okay.
Why don't you tell me
my real evil plan?
I don't think
there is an evil plan.
You regret not having
a relationship
With your own family,
And you don't want to see
foreman go down that same path.
I think...
You're actually
being nice.
Oh, shut up.
You can't accuse me
of an opossum attack
And underhanded kindness
in the same visit.
Then I'll come back.
[door opens]
(chase)
treadmill test was a bust.
The guy's
in unbelievable shape.
We couldn't get his heart rate
above 150.
Your boss is secretly
a very nice man.
I know.
If we can't re-create
the cardiac event,
We can't prove
Hypertrophic
cardiomyopathy.
Either we find
a bigger treadmill...
Or...
Did I miss the memo
about you being released?
I'm feeling fine.
I can't keep laying here
in this bed missing practices.
All excellent points.
Give me your arm.
What's in the shot?
It's a vasodilator.
Since we can't exercise your
son's heart on the treadmill,
I'm gonna have to do it
chemically.
What's wrong?
You're turning white.
What does that mean?
It means
he doesn't need football
To get a good job anymore.
Raynaud's phenomenon--
Vasospasms cut off
the blood supply
To his fingers.
Could be early onset
rheumatoid arthritis.
Rheumatoid factor
is negative.
(thirteen)
arterial plaque
throwing clots
Would explain the fingers,
head, heart.
You really think a guy
with stenosis
Could've aced
that treadmill test?
You're kidding me.
You got him a desk?
And a nameplate.
Man's got to have a place
he can call his own.
(chase)
what about
takayasu's arteritis?
Lymphoma's a better fit.
We should remove his spleen.
Bold move to skip
straight to surgery.
His big game's coming up.
We don't have time
to biopsy,
Wait for the pathology report,
and resect.
(chase)
right.
We should remove his spleen
without confirmation
So he won't miss
the big game.
Hang an ethanol drip.
That won't treat
For either lymphoma
or takayasu's.
If it's lymphoma,
the ethanol will make him itchy,
And foreman can remove
his spleen.
If it's takayasu's,
he'll lose his radial pulse,
And chase can start him
on steroids.
Marcus!
What are you doing here?
My new assignment
is to shadow you
In enemy territory
And document your every word
to the patient.
Just don't say
anything stupid.
You're not an idiot.
Don't do this.
Come on, man.
I'm a new person now--
no more drugs, no more lying.
And if I can't get
my own family
To give me an opportunity
to prove that,
Then what's the point?
Mom and dad
gave you a chance
And a second
And a third.
I'm not about
to give you a 54th.
Why isn't your minion
fetching your lunch?
He's busy spying
on his little brother.
[chuckles]
What?
That's very demeaning.
You obviously have a theory
As to why demeaning
is not demeaning.
You're escalating
To prove I was wrong
about you being nice,
Which you would only do
if I was right.
Do you even listen
to yourself?
23-year-old just came
into the e.R.,
Asked for you.
What's her cup size?
I don't think
his cup size
Is relevant
to his condition.
He accidentally shot himself
in the foot.
Oh!
Seriously?
I give you a choice
between moving to canada
And shooting yourself
in the foot,
And you chose the bullet?
I didn't want
to be a fugitive.
You think this is gonna
get you discharged?
We'll patch it up
and send you right back.
Don't patch it up.
Look...
You got screwed over
by your own government,
And that sucks.
But all you're gonna get
out of this
Is a five-day vacation
and a band-aid.
When I signed up,
I was just a guy.
Now I'm about to be a dad.
I go back over,
There's a chance my kid grows up
without a father.
You got a girl pregnant.
You're still just a guy.
How much longer
we have to wait?
We have to keep going
Until you start
feeling something.
Might help
if, uh, you told me
What I'm supposed
to feel.
If I do that, that's all
you'll be thinking about.
Then you'll be telling me
that's what you're feeling--
Power of suggestion.
The other black dude
who was in here earlier,
He your brother?
What gave it away?
The way you looked at him.
I have two older brothers,
And we always want to kill
each other.
[chuckles]
Oh. Mm.
Something wrong?
Not really.
It just feels itchy.
Is that
what you're waiting for?
Means lymphoma's most likely,
but that's actually good news.
How could that be good news?
Because it's treatable.
We can remove your spleen
tonight laparoscopically.
Will I be able to run
by Saturday?
We can get to the radiation
in the off-season.
[chuckles]
Hey, ma.
Wake up, ma.
Wake up.
I'm itchy.
Means I can play.
Ahh.
[humming]
♪ ♪
[sighs]
Oh.
[sighs] what are you doing
in the dark?
Lying in wait.
Jeez. What happened
to your face?
Right...
Play innocent.
Like you weren't looking
for revenge for the prank
That I didn't pull.
It's karmic justice,
but I didn't do it.
Of course you realize,
this means war.
Isolating
the gastroepiploic artery.
Nearly there.
Foreman, come and take
a look at this.
Liver's inflamed.
So the itching wasn't caused
by his spleen.
It's not lymphoma.
What happened
to your face?
Wilson annexed
the sudetenland.
(foreman)
no abnormal "t" cells
or "b" cells.
It's definitely
not lymphoma.
Liver biopsy only revealed
Nonspecific
inflammation.
Kind of like the time
you took
Your mom's
birth control pills
On a dare
And ended up
with swollen nipples.
That never happened.
Right, and your nickname
All the way up through
high school wasn't erica.
It wasn't.
Okay, I may have made
that one up,
With the understanding
that my brother
Still had a sense of humor
And would figure out
to play along.
Polymyositis would explain
The head, liver, heart,
Even the white fingers.
It would also be accompanied
By a significant decrease
in muscle power.
Marcus!
Chance to redeem yourself.
Does our patient
look strong to you?
Sorry, eric.
Big brother disagrees
with your diagnosis.
Felty syndrome?
You said the liver was inflamed,
not the spleen.
Can you believe they let
this guy perform surgery?
What are you doing?
Requesting permission
To share my idea
without being belittled
In front
of your new assistant.
Permission denied.
Continue.
[sighs] our patient
has cartilage damage
In both ankles.
He gets lidocaine shots
before every game
To mask the pain.
Team doctor uses the same needle
twice by accident,
Viral hepatitis.
You think
he's an idiot,arcus?
I don't think
he's an idiot.
Okay.
Go test his blood.
Come on.
We have a lunch scheduled.
So you jerked me around.
Your allegiance lies
with your brother.
I get it. Admirable.
Here's the problem.
I hired you
to tell me the truth.
If you don't do that,
you no longer have a job.
I don't know what secret
you're looking to uncover,
But my brother
is a decent guy.
He was arrested
for grand theft auto.
You're gonna be
disappointed.
Try me.
He tell you
I was with him?
Was it your idea?
We did everything
together.
I don't know
whose idea it was.
I was 16.
He was only 14.
Little punk couldn't even see
over the steering wheel.
He's quicker
with a flathead screwdriver
Than most people
with a key.
[footsteps approaching]
Sorry to interrupt
my character assassination
With boring medical stuff,
But when we drew
the patient's blood,
It clotted right there
in the vacutainer.
So the problem
is not in his blood,
It's the blood itself.
He's been working out
in the cold doing two-a-days.
It's got to be
cryoglobulinemia.
I usually love breaking
bad news.
But in this case...
Start the patient
on warfarin.
I'm so sorry about that.
You were saying...
We drove for about ten minutes
before we got caught,
And that was it.
When our mom came down
to the station,
She didn't say a word
the whole ride home.
She came up to the driveway,
turned off the car.
We're sitting in there
in silence.
Then without turning around,
she said,
"I'll pray for you."
And she got
out of the car.
Wow.
You got off easy.
Easy for you,
easy for me,
Not easy for eric.
His life mission
became to never disappoint
Our mother like that again,
Because he is a good guy.
I thought he would tell
that story at the eulogy.
But I heard
he didn't give one.
Your--
Your mother's dead?
If he didn't tell you,
I'm sure he had a reason.
Look, you can mock him
all you want
About peeing in the bed,
But...
Please...
Don't bring up our mother.
Your blood contains
an abnormally high volume
Of certain proteins
called cryoglobulins.
They become thick
when it gets cold outside.
It's like a car
trying to run
After the oil's turned
to sludge.
We think that's what's been
causing all your problems.
So I just need
a quick oil change
And I'm good to go.
This oil change
isn't so quick.
We have to put you
on blood thinners
And other medications.
The process will take
two to three weeks.
But after that,
You should be able to play
without a problem.
After that, it's not
gonna matter.
(glenda)
doctor, if daryl
Doesn't play in front
of the scouts
On Saturday,
he won't get drafted.
Can't you wait
until after the game?
If we wait
and let him play,
There's a good chance
he dies
Right on the field.
I had an epiphany.
Usually that precedes you
walking away with purpose, so...
Flathead screwdriver.
And then I say...?
It's not a game.
It's proof that you didn't rig
the grab rail
And make me fall.
I already have proof
of that--
The fact
that I didn't do it.
I can't go on that.
But I can go on the fact
That I had to borrow
a flathead screwdriver from nora
To install the thing, 'cause
we only had a phillips-head.
And then, of course,
I returned it late that night
In a completely
successful effort
To see her braless...
Whoa. Wait. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Which means that you didn't
have the tool to sabotage
The grab rail.
Braless under, like,
a sweater
Or, like, a--like, a--
Now I also have proof
That I'm not responsible
for the opossum,
Because I'm absolving you
Of responsibility
instead of escalating,
Which you know
is not my nature.
So someone is breaking
into our place
Just to screw with us?
The opossum...
Was meant for me.
(wilson)
I'm so tired.
It was exciting
till about 2:00 a.M.
Now it's just torture.
(house)
did you even go to college?
This is the escalation,
isn't it?
Keeping me up all night,
nothing happens,
Then you keep me up all night
again tomorrow.
This is your retaliation.
You see,
that's just illogical,
'cause I'm staying up too.
Maybe you napped all day.
I gave you empirical proof
that I did not prank you.
No.
No, you did not.
You created empirical proof
that I didn't prank you,
Selling me on the notion
that you didn't prank me.
Maybe you self-pranked.
I don't master-prank.
Is that cut on your cheek
even real?
See, this is exactly
what our nemesis wants--
Divide and conquer.
Can't you see that?
Okay.
I'm going to bed.
(house)
I'm telling you,
if you sleep now,
You're gonna wake up
next to severed horse heads.
Or worse,
the rest of it.
[fire alarm beeps,
sprinklers turn on]
(wilson)
oh!
House!
The flat screen!
Ah. Ah.
You would never sacrifice
the flat screen.
Oh, this guy is good.
[sighs]
is there a reason for this?
[ball bouncing]
(house)
[french accent]
there is a reason
For everything,
mes amis.
I am troubled to report
that we have
A criminal
in our midst.
Guilty of what
exactly?
Last night, the fire sprinklers
flooded our apartment.
And before that,
I found an opossum
in my bathtub.
You each had motive.
You each had opportunity.
This is the emergency
you paged me about?
[clears throat]
Not so fast,
Mademoiselle cuddy.
No one leaves here
Until they can account
for their whereabouts
The evening last.
Bye.
[normal voice]
okay, no one
Who is employed by me
leaves here
Until they account for their
whereabouts the evening last.
What about you,
professor chase?
Why would I?
Because
you hold me responsible
For breaking up
your marriage.
I was here all night
with thirteen,
Monitoring our patient's
I.V. Blood thinners.
Can either of you
prove that?
The patient's alive
and improving.
Is that proof enough?
For now. What about you,
colonel taub?
I was out to dinner
with my wife.
Really?
Your wife.
Yes, really.
Good enough.
'cause I had you pegged
all along.
You certainly had all the motive
in the world.
First of all,
I'm not interested.
Second, I don't even know
where you guys live.
Yesterday I confirmed
that you are a liar.
What are you
talking about?
Well, at least a liar
By omission.
House!
Don't.
Get this, class.
Foreman's mom died.
He ever tell any of you?
(wilson)
house,
I think you're getting
off topic here.
(thirteen)
is he serious?
Did your mom pass away?
About three months ago.
I'm so sorry.
Why didn't you tell
anybody?
(house)
and to top it off,
You refused to say anything nice
about her at the funeral.
I didn't talk because it isn't
anyone's business.
Stop.
You don't have to explain
yourself to this guy.
You want to hit me,
don't you?
Marcus, don't.
I quit.
You should stop him.
He needs this job.
Our patient needs
a fresh I.V.
I don't need
two or three weeks.
See?
Got my color back.
That means
you're getting better.
But it doesn't mean--
it means I am better.
My coach had
the team doctor come by.
He cleared me to play.
Did your team doctor realize
you're on blood thinners?
I'm off them now.
You're still sick.
You're not ready to go off
your meds.
Daryl, listen to him.
It is not worth the risk.
I'll come back
on Sunday, mom.
You guys can give me
all the meds I need then.
The treatment doesn't work
that way.
Please go with him.
[grunts,
exhales sharply]
Antibiotics
aren't working.
We're gonna switch you
to different ones,
But you're gonna lose
your toe.
[laughing]
Outstanding, soldier.
(house)
as a geveral rule,
Before you celebrate,
do a little research.
The army's medical
evaluation board
Is perfectly fine
With nine-toed infantrymen,
As long as they can walk
and run.
So I lost a toe
for nothing?
Afraid so.
Unless you want me to keep you
on the old antibiotics,
Let the infection spread,
And we could amputate
more than just a toe.
Why are you risking
your life for this?
Your mom
doesn't want you to.
My mom sacrificed
everything for me.
Her telling me
not to come here
Is just another example
of that.
I do good out there,
I could take care of her
For the rest of her life.
Who am I if I don't
sacrifice for her?
That's family.
[distant whistle blowing]
You okay?
Everything's blurry.
I can't see.
Take me back
to the hospital.
The blindness means
we were wrong about his--
(foreman)
actually, I'm responsible
for that.
Spiked his water bottle
with nitrates,
Dropped his blood pressure,
Robbed oxygen-rich blood
from his brain,
Making him blind.
Figured a temporarily
blind patient
Is better
than a permanently dead one.
Vision was already coming back
by the time I dropped him off
At the hospital.
Well played.
If only we could combine
your medical chicanery
With your brother's ability
to fetch me mochas,
You'd be
the perfect foreman.
Where are you?
I'm busy.
(taub)
great. So we don't have
a new symptom.
Means we should just stick him
back on his blood thinners,
And he should be okay to leave
in a couple weeks.
Actually, we do have
a new symptom.
Any of you take a look
at his readmittance chart?
Between the time he checked in
and the time he rechecked in,
Our patient lost
a single pound.
Patient like that would
usually shed over ten pounds.
(taub)
the obvious answer
Would be steroids,
But since we've already
ruled them out...
(chase)
so he's not injecting.
But he could be getting them
naturally--
Paraneoplastic syndrome.
The body
produces antibodies,
Which battle cancer,
Which could also act
like growth hormone.
We've eliminated lymphoma.
What other cancers mimic
growth hormone?
Lung, pancreatic,
renal, breast--
It was a rhetorical question.
I don't really care.
Go test him for all of them.
[knock at door]
[door opens]
What are you
doing here?
You need a job.
Maybe I can talk
to house,
See if I can get
your job back.
Soon as he knows you're okay
with me being there,
He won't want me back.
Maybe I can help you
figure out something else.
I promise...
I won't let you down.
Don't do that.
Let's just...
See how it goes.
So, uh,
do they mandate you
To stay here
at the halfway house?
Or can you come stay
with family?
It's foreman.
Well, it should stop
now that marcus left.
That's the whole point.
[people gasp]
Oh, I'm sorry.
Was my leg sticking out?
I'm so distracted lately,
trying to think
Of something funnier
than fire sprinklers
Going off in the middle
of the night.
Any ideas?
Whoa, easy there, tiger.
I know where you live.
You know how I know?
'cause my girlfriend and I--
We tried to buy
that very same condo.
Why don't you leave me
out of this?
Wilson was the one
who bought the place.
And you're living there.
You...
Deserve to suffer
equally.
Actually, I suffered more
now that you just tripped me.
Hey, hey, I-I-I'm--
His suffering
will equal out,
'cause he actually
feels remorse.
Why would you out
yourself?
You can't even imagine
the retribution.
Oh, there won't be any.
I am ceasing
all offensive operations.
I have both made my point
and established my superiority.
And if you even get
to the planning stages
Of retaliation,
I will tell cuddy
that she lost her dream place
To you two.
See, she's under
this odd impression
That you guys
are her friends.
There's no cancer.
We scanned him
head to toe.
We checked blood smears
for leukemia.
We even ultrasounded his chest
looking for breast cancer.
Maybe I was wrong
about the weight loss.
(taub)
you weren't wrong--
we found blood
In his catheter bag.
His kidneys are failing.
(thirteen)
so it has to be cancer.
Paraneoplastic syndrome
is the only thing
That can link kidney,
Heart, and liver--
even the rage.
(foreman)
why can't we find it?
We've looked everywhere
inside this guy.
What if it's not inside?
You know why you're black?
'cause god loves me
more than he loves you?
Hmm. What I was going for
was melanin.
You got lots of it.
It makes your skin dark,
Protects you from the sun's
harmful u.V. Rays.
What are you doing?
Unfortunately,
it also prevents
Even those with advanced
medical degrees
From considering melanoma
as a diagnosis.
Other hand.
On the rare occasion
that black people
Do get skin cancer,
They usually get it
on the white parts--
Palms and soles
of the feet.
But your hands and feet
are so smashed up from football,
My team are likely
to have written off
Any skin blemish
as a bruise.
But now that I know
that melanoma
Is the only thing
that fits...
Come take a look
at this, mom.
There's the thorn
in the panther's paw--
Paraneoplastic syndrome.
Your body forms antibodies
To fight the tumor.
Those tiny little proteins
Travel through your blood
and wreak havoc.
We remove the cancerous mole,
Everything should be fine.
I'll tell dr. Chase
to schedule the surgery.
Why bother?
I missed my shot.
What kind of life
am I gonna lead now?
Did you study
really, really hard?
Then the same crappy life
That the rest of the guys
you'll be graduating with
Are gonna lead...
Minus the student loans.
Hey.
You ready?
Almost.
And...Done.
I heard house and wilson
are getting pranked by someone.
You wouldn't know anything
about that, would you?
No.
Why should I believe you?
You said I had
a trusting face.
I still don't understand
Why you wouldn't let me
retaliate, though.
They stole your dream.
Well, that's overstating it.
It's just a condo.
It's not because you feel guilty
about hurting house
Or guilty
for being with me?
We'll buy another one.
I just don't see the need
to make a war out of it.
Well, I think
you're rationalizing,
Which a less confident man
than myself might take as a sign
That you're
second-guessing.
Okay, you know what?
Forget that last part.
I heard foreman
and his brother
Are trying
to work things out.
That's nice for them.
It's nice of you.
You didn't provoke marcus
to quit
So the pranks would stop.
You were becoming
the common enemy
They could bond over.
You are the diabolical,
Yet benevolent puppet master.
I provoked marcus to quit
Because he was no longer
useful to me.
I hired him
to get information.
I got information.
Uh-huh.
And how are we gonna
get back
At lucas?
We're not.
I win.
-- Sync by addic7ed.B3 --
-- for addicted.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net