[alarm buzzes]
[alarm stops]
[break up the concrete
by the pretenders]
♪ there was a red brick road
where I grew up on ♪
♪ and a pretty stone wall
around a fragrant lawn ♪
♪ fish in the pond
that sparkled in the dawn ♪
♪ but it ain't no more ♪
♪ it's all gone gone gone ♪
♪ whoa ♪
♪ ram it cram it grand slam it ♪
♪ break up the concrete ♪
♪ prod it sod it
metal-rod it ♪
♪ break up the concrete ♪
[baby cries over walkie-talkie]
♪ deg-deg-deg-deg ♪
♪ dega-dega-dega-dega ♪
♪ ♪
♪ and the depot over there
right next to the tracks ♪
♪ that the slaves put down while
breaking their backs ♪
♪ whoa ♪
♪ ram it cram it grand slam it ♪
♪ break up the concrete ♪
♪ prod it sod it metal rod it ♪
♪ thwack it crack it
lineback it ♪
♪ break up the concrete ♪
♪ shake it bake it
earthquake it ♪
♪ break up the concrete ♪
♪ deg-deg-deg-deg ♪
♪ dega-dega-dega-dega ♪
♪ ♪
♪ break up the concrete ♪
(lucas)
hey.
Slow down, sister.
Actually,
I need to speed up.
Rachel woke up early
with a fever
And she's been terrorizing
me all morning.
I'm already late.
Sorry, stakeout went longer
than I thought.
Have you ever been to a rave?
Good-bye.
You're already late
and rachel's sick.
Neither of which can
be solved by you leaving
Right this second.
The entire hospital
is depending
On a proposal
I've yet to finish
And need to present
at 8:30.
It's 7:30.
It's 7:37.
I'll have you on the road
in ten minutes.
Come on, you don't want to go
into your meeting all tight
And stressed out,
do you?
[break up the concrete
by the pretenders resumes]
♪ ♪
[cell phone rings]
That's yours.
It's house.
Ignore it.
It says "emergency page."
I said ignore it.
Sweet.
♪ break up the concrete ♪
♪ deg-deg-deg-deg ♪
♪ dega-dega-dega-dega ♪
[both panting]
I'm sorry.
It's hard
to pace yourself
When you've been thinking about
it for ten hours straight.
That's great.
Now I'm late,
Stressed out,
and frustrated.
Sorry.
If you give me a minute,
I can--
It'll wait.
[sighs]
You can do it.
Do what?
(the pretenders)
♪ break up the concrete ♪
I thought you were coming
in at 7:30.
Rachel woke up
with a fever
And then I...Just couldn't
get here any sooner.
There's a problem
in the pharmacy.
(house)
hey, boss lady!
You don't answer
emergency pages anymore?
Tell them all I'll
be by as soon as I can
And tell him I assumed it was
either about the wolf again
Or the procedure I refused
to approve yesterday.
Turned out it wasn't
a resistant staph,
But I still say that
if it had been,
Infecting him
with malaria--
Seriously, house,
I don't have time for this.
You're lying.
I have a meeting in 20 minutes.
Not talking
about your meeting.
I'm talking
about the phone call.
I didn't ask what you
were talking about,
Because I don't care.
I was with your boy toy
on a stakeout last night.
You were with lucas?
He needed someone
who could diagnose
A soft tissue injury
from across the street.
Apparently he doesn't
know any good doctors.
Or the ones he does know
actually have lives
Outside of work.
Things got a little slow,
So we made some wagers.
One being whether I could
get you to stop
The miscegenation
with an emergency page.
What made you think we'd--
He said you guys do it
every morning.
Everybody lies.
Remember?
So you weren't actually--
Good-bye, house.
I'm gonna need
a definitive answer
Before any money
changes hands.
[door opens]
sorry to interrupt,
But the grc called
about the budgets,
The pharmacy
is still waiting,
And your 8:30
just arrived on campus.
He should be here
in ten minutes.
Figured this would
be the one day he comes early.
Can you proofread
this for me?
When are you gonna find
your own assistant?
Not today.
Thank you.
I'll be back in five.
Dr. Cuddy.
I know we're usually fine
with two c.S. Reps,
But I want a few extra hands
today just in case.
And have I.T.
Recheck the network.
I don't want to hear later
that the new lines
Can only dial out
or the computer crashed.
What's going on?
Hopefully nothing.
Just make sure you're ready
if people start calling.
You wanted to see me?
Hey, dr. Cuddy.
Yeah, uh, I wanted
to let you know
There's a problem
with one of the orders
That came in last night.
Which is?
They sent double
the amount of meds we ordered.
Did you call and ask why?
Yeah.
They insist
it's not a mistake.
So fax them
the original p.O.
Yeah, that's what
I was planning on doing,
But, um...
I can't find it.
Actually, I can't find
any of them.
Oscar, I don't have time to
straighten out your paperwork.
Where's stan?
He doesn't get in till 9:00
And it's actually
not my paperwork.
It's gail's paperwork,
and she's out sick today.
So put it on her desk
and let her
Figure it out when she
comes back.
All right, but it's
not my problem if--
Oscar, not today,
okay?
Was it the whole shipment
or just one med?
It's just one.
Vicodin?
No, 25 milligram
ephedrine tablets.
What?
Call gail.
Tell her I want to see her
in my office asap.
But she's sick.
This place is full
of sick people.
Just get her in here.
Dr. Cuddy, your 8:30
is waiting in your office.
Now.
[cell phone rings]
Oh, I got to make
a quick trip upstairs.
Can you get the guy
in my office a cup of coffee?
I'll be right back.
I've gotten you
coffee before.
What's wrong?
(hourani)
it's freezing in here.
I can hardly feel my fingers.
Please tell me you didn't
send a 911 page
To tell me
the heater's broken.
It's not broken.
House bribed the physical plant
to turn on the ac
So I'd hurry up.
So hurry up.
This man's abdomen
is wide open.
His core temp
is down to 95.
Fine.
I will deal with it.
You better or
I'm gonna file--
I don't care what he told you.
Turn it back up now.
Thought you had
an important meeting.
You're an idiot.
What are you gonna do
the next time
One of your patients
needs a liver transplant?
Go talk to wilson about
something completely unrelated
And see what happens.
Mystery infection guy
is now covered in boils
And has an abscess big enough
to put your fist in.
He needs to get into
an o.R. Tout suite.
Hourani will
be done soon.
Good.
I'll have some
hot chocolate waiting.
[elevator bell dings
and cell phone rings]
Marina, hey.
How's she doing?
She vomited?
Give her some more ibuprofen and
put her in the bath for a bit.
And call me in a half an hour
if it doesn't go down.
[cell phone rings]
sorry, marina.
I have another call.
Just call me
in a half an hour either way.
Hey.
What's up?
Tell him I'm halfway there.
He's the one who insisted
on the early meeting.
I--
all right, I'm coming.
Morning, eli.
Sorry about the wait.
Oh, it's all right.
I hear you got a sick kid.
Yeah, I know what that's like.
Or I should say my wife does.
So you guys ready
to give some ground
So we can make this deal?
Why would we do that?
We've been going at this
for eight months.
Soon as you decide
to get reasonable.
I'm the one
that's unreasonable?
You've taken weeks to respond to
every proposal I've presented.
Atlanticnet insurance
is the largest healthcare
Provider in new jersey, and
you're not the only hospital
Whose contracts are up.
So is your team ready
to come back to the table?
Yeah.
We're not going to.
This is our final offer.
We're willing to go
with a capitated structure,
But we need at least
12% increase
In reimbursements
across the board.
Well, the good news is I can
give you a quick response.
Not a chance.
But as always,
nice talking to you.
Say hi to your sister
for me.
If you don't
accept the offer,
We're gonna terminate
the contract.
Gonna be hard
to keep this place open
If all your patients
have to pay cash.
Princeton plainsboro
is the smallest hospital
In our entire network.
We're also the best.
Doesn't matter.
We are responsible
for covering 13 million people.
We don't have enough cash
To buy them
all maseratis.
I know what you paid bergen,
Newark beth israel,
robert wood johnson--
'cause they have leverage.
You can be expensive
or small,
But you can't be both.
I've engaged jones/curtin
to handle the p.R.,
And I'm prepared to make
the announcement
At 3:00 p.M. Today.
First lesson every good
poker player learns
Is don't get emotional.
You don't have the cards.
And the sooner
you realize that,
The sooner a reasonable
contract will get signed.
You have until 3:00 p.M.
To change your mind.
I always did
like your style.
Gonna be sad
to see you go.
They're waiting for you
in the conference room.
Thanks.
Uh, take this up
to the call center
And tell claudia to give one
to each c.S. Rep
And to start going over
the answers to each question.
Okay.
And under no circumstances
is any of this info
To go outside that room.
The scripts are numbered
and I want a list
Of every person
she gives one to.
Got it.
Anything else?
No.
If you really wanted
to make a deal,
You should have ditched
the push-up
And gone with a demi.
Nothing makes a guy wanna
close like high beams.
What have you heard?
Your meeting with the weasel
lasted less than five minutes,
Which means you either agreed
to a completely sensible
30-day extension
or one of you
Issued a completely
ridiculous ultimatum.
Oh, goody.
You or him?
Me.
Way to go, boss.
You just said
it was ridiculous.
Ridiculous to make.
Fun to watch.
As long as it's not
just a bluff.
Please tell me
it's not a bluff.
It is not a bluff,
and it is not ridiculous.
Just because we're
not some huge--
Mr. Pluta started
hallucinating
Before we could
put him under.
His b.P. Is plummeting.
He has an elevated
heart rate.
Looks like congestive
heart failure.
Interesting.
I don't care how
interesting it is.
You are not infecting him
with malaria.
Since when is malaria
a cure for heart failure?
It's not.
It's not congestive
heart failure.
It's gotta be...
Just got off the phone
with hourani.
I'm sorry, dave. I don't
really have time right now--
Think I had time to listen
to him go for 20 minutes
About the damn temperature
in the o.R.?
I took care of it.
It's not an "it."
It's a "him" you need
to take care of.
You got the entire staff
catering
To house's every whim,
and I can't get approval
To hire a replacement
for the surgeon
He stole from
my department?
A doctor I only took on
in the first place
Because of pressure
from you.
So you didn't want chase,
But now you're pissed
you can't have him?
You want to convene
a search committee
And start looking
for a new chief of surgery?
No, dave.
Then you better stop
spending all your time
Putting out his fires
and start doing your damn job.
Ahem.
There a problem
with dr. Thomas?
No, just refereeing
a dispute about the o.R.
So we don't yet have
a contract with atlanticnet.
We gave you an extra week
And you assured us
you'd have a deal by today.
We could have a deal,
just not the deal we deserve.
So what do you want,
approval for an extension?
We've been at this
for eight months.
An extension isn't
gonna change anything.
So what's your plan?
I presented a final offer.
I told them that we would agree
to a capitated structure
If they increase
reimbursements by 12%.
A final offer?
What does that mean?
If they don't accept
it by 3:00,
We're gonna terminate.
Are you out of your mind?
If we don't accept
atlanticnet insurance,
We'll lose 80%
of our patients.
We'd be lucky
to last three months.
We're not asking for anything
they can't afford.
Their last offer
was a 4% increase
And you're demanding 12.
They're paying even more
at some places.
Units that have lower ratings
than ours.
In a perfect world,
that would definitely matter.
Sanford, they're all
about growth.
And they know they
don't get new customers
By marketing themselves
as the biggest.
They do it by claiming
they're the best,
And they can't do that
if their patients
Can't come to us.
What was morgan's reaction
when you told him?
He didn't give in,
but he will.
I told him I'd make
the announcement at 3:00.
He'll call back
before then.
They need us.
No, we need them.
We need each other.
The negotiation
is your responsibility,
So we can't stop you
if this is what you want to do.
But just so we're clear,
If we don't have a contract
with atlanticnet,
You're not gonna have
a contract with us.
Guess who didn't show up
for clinic duty?
Oh, don't tell me.
The guy with all the boils
needs a liver transplant.
No, his doctor needs a nap.
You want me to try
to find him?
You really need him?
I need someone.
[sighs]
I have cancer.
Why do you think
you have cancer?
I don't think I have cancer.
I know I have cancer.
I had surgery to remove
a malignant polyp
In my colon
six months ago,
And now it's spread
to my liver and lymph nodes.
So you're under the care
of an oncologist?
Yeah, but he won't give me
the prescription I need.
Do you need more painkillers?
No.
I need breast milk.
Human breast milk?
Yes.
It has cancer-fighting
qualities.
Well, in newborns,
it's been shown
To reduce future risk.
No, in adults
with cancer too.
I've read studies.
Hmm.
Look...
I even know a place
where I can buy it.
I just need a prescription
so I can
Get reimbursed
by my insurance company.
They said they'd reimburse
the cost of breast milk
As a cancer treatment?
They reimburse prescriptions,
So if you write me
a prescription,
Then they have no choice
but to pay.
Well, actually,
they have a choice.
What are you, some type of shill
for the insurance company?
No.
Look, I've been paying
premiums for 30 years,
And I've never been sick
a day in my life
Till this happened.
Now I can't work.
I got no money.
And you want to help them
screw me over?
I'm not screwing you over.
Well, then give me the script.
It won't help you.
Will it hurt me?
No, but--
Okay, so it won't harm me
and it won't harm you,
But it's this
insurance company--
This is not about insurance.
Then give me
the damn script.
I'm sick.
I need help.
I need something.
I'm sorry.
Bitch.
[sighs]
Anyone call?
Yeah.
The e.R.
They said the vascular
who's on call
Doesn't have privileges.
Then why is he on call?
Dowd's at a conference
and got him to fill in.
Be nice if he got somebody
who can actually work here.
Call ereshefsky.
Ereshefsky?
She's not gonna do it.
She owes me a favor.
She's still not gonna do it.
All right.
Oh, and there's a guy
in your office.
I think he's a lawyer.
Why is he in my office?
Said he didn't want to sit
around a bunch of sick people.
I tried to stop him.
Hi.
I'm dr. Lisa cuddy.
Ronald westbrook.
I appreciate your taking
the time to meet with me.
Hard to avoid since
you're already in my office.
Sorry about that,
I just got over
A wicked cold
that didn't want to--
How can I help you?
I represent martin acevedo.
He's filed a suit
against pph
And dr. Robert chase
for performing surgery
Without consent.
Yes, I saw that.
I also saw
the consent forms.
They were all signed.
Yes, but my client
was assured
That the procedure would just
be a few minor sutures.
Wait.
Your client accidentally
cut his thumb off
With a table saw,
right?
Yes.
And dr. Chase reattached it?
You're saying he didn't
want it reattached?
No, he most certainly
did not.
His insurance only covered 60%
of inpatient expenses,
So he would only agree
to the cheapest option.
So what did you tell him?
I said I'd sew up the skin
over the exposed bone.
Then I put him under,
got his thumb
From the paramedics,
and reattached it.
What's he gonna do?
Tell the judge
that I harmed him
By reattaching
a vital digit?
Both he and the
insurance company are suing
To get out of paying
the bill.
It's over $80,000.
It was his thumb.
I couldn't just let him
toss it in the trash
To save a few bucks.
[sighs]
The pharm tech
who called in sick is here.
She's waiting
in your office.
He barely even looks
at me anymore.
We haven't had sex
in months.
You don't need pills
to lose weight.
There are healthier ways,
legal ways.
You don't understand
how hard it is.
Ever since our second child,
no matter what I do.
I just wanted to lose
ten more pounds
And then I was gonna stop.
I'm sorry.
Forging pharmaceutical orders,
stealing--
Don't fire me, dr. Cuddy.
Please.
I'm begging you.
If sam finds out,
he'll divorce me for sure,
And my kids--
I will never do it again,
I swear.
Just give me
a second chance.
I won't report the theft
to the dea...
But I have to fire you.
[sobbing]
Just take a few minutes
to compose yourself,
Then go down to hr and they'll
give you your last check.
I've been a perfect employee
for seven years.
I know, but this
is too big.
I'm sorry.
[sighs]
How's it going?
Got three hours to save this
place from bankruptcy,
I just fired one
of my best employees,
And the woman taking care
of my sick child
Isn't returning my calls.
Rachel's gonna be fine,
I'm sure whoever he or she
is deserved it,
And we're not going bankrupt.
Are we?
Don't worry.
The board will fire me before
they allow that to happen.
They'd never fire you.
I just told
atlanticnet insurance
I'd terminate unless
they gave us a 12% bump.
They might fire you.
Marina,
hey, it's me.
I haven't heard back
from you.
Can you call me
as soon as you can?
Thank you.
You try lucas?
He's either sleeping
or avoiding me.
You in a fight?
Not yet,
but we're gonna be.
What do you think
I should do about atlanticnet?
You're asking a guy
who paid
Full sticker price
for his last car.
You ask house?
He's a master manipulator
who always gets what he wants.
This situation is
out of control enough already.
House is the last person
I want to get involved.
Get out of my chair.
And the answer is no.
You ever noticed how
many porn sites
Have "mom"
in the domain name?
Hot moms, hungry moms,
mature moms.
That ought to make you
feel pretty good.
What do you want?
Looks like boils,
altered mental status,
And heart failure was called
by renal cell carcinoma.
I need your signature to start
treating it with malaria.
Don't worry.
I'm giving him chemo too.
What is your sudden
obsession with malaria?
Just trying to play my part
cutting costs.
Malaria is the simplest,
cheapest method
Of delivering hypothermia.
Right.
The only money you care about--
You bet someone
you could use malaria
As a diagnostic tool?
That doesn't sound like me.
Forget it.
Okay, let me see
if I've got this straight.
A bet that puts one patient
at minor risk is juvenile?
And irresponsible
and dangerous.
But going all-in
against atlanticnet--
Is not a bet.
That is a carefully considered
negotiating position.
I'm gonna put this
in your inbox.
I just hope
it doesn't get lost
Underneath all the other stuff
you're carefully considering.
Can you take a look
at these per diem schedules?
Let me know
if you see any conflicts.
Got it.
Oh, and ereshefsky
actually did come in.
You catch her leaving a sponge
in a guy or something?
Wasn't a medical mistake.
What was it?
Can't tell you now.
She came in.
Hey, dan!
Have you audited
the ephedrine orders yet?
Why?
You told me she confessed.
Stan.
All right, yeah.
I'll take care of it.
Today.
You know he's cussing you out
in there now.
I don't care
as long as he does it.
What a bitch.
What are you doing here?
Sounded like you were going
to be too busy for lunch,
So my specialty,
spinach lasagna.
Sure you didn't come looking
for more people
You could brag
about our sex life to?
Okay.
Sorry.
From now on,
I got nothing but bad things
To say about our sex life.
Or nothing to say.
And what's going on
with marina?
She hasn't called me back.
She was gonna call.
I told her I'd let you know
everything was okay.
So her fever broke?
What exactly does that mean,
"when a fever breaks"?
Lucas, I'm very busy.
Does she have a fever
or not?
That was gonna
be your lunch?
And you didn't have
breakfast either.
No, she doesn't
have a fever,
And the rash was just, like,
a little diaper rash.
What rash?
She has a rash?
Little one.
Lisa, don't worry.
I'm telling you.
[cell phone rings]
Oh, god.
I must have grabbed marina's
cell by mistake.
And I turned the ringer off
on the home phone
So I could sleep.
What are you doing to me?
I take it
your deal's not done.
Not yet.
How about I take
a quick look
Into the guy who's in charge
of the negotiations?
Or better yet,
the ceo.
If I get some dirt,
you can use it as leverage.
There's no time.
How do you even
find these guys?
Thanks.
You should have seen
the guy's face.
I thought he was gonna have
a damn coronary
Right there in the tee box.
Excuse me.
You're keith tannenbaum,
Ceo of atlanticnet insurance,
right?
That's me.
How can I help you?
Well, actually,
I think we can help each other.
I am dr. Lisa cuddy,
Dean of medicine
at princeton plainsboro.
Oh, yeah.
Well, how are you?
Well, I'm a little unhappy.
You're aware
that our contract
With your company
is up this week?
Yes, and we have
a negotiating team
That's working
all that out.
Princeton plainsboro
has the highest-rated e.R.
In the state,
the most advanced icu,
And the most innovative
diagnostic medicine department
In the entire country.
Good to know.
Now if you don't mind,
I'd like to--
While atlanticnet insurance
has a marketing budget
That's more
than our pediatric icus
And transplant units
combined.
Your pga sponsorship could pay
for our walk-in clinic,
And the money you
spend to fuel
Your two private jets could fund
our air ambulance service
For the next three years.
Your point being?
Your growth may be good
for your bottom line,
But ours allows us
to save lives.
And I would rather not
have to announce to the press
How selective
your company appears to be
When it comes
to cutting costs.
[scoffs]
Well, morgan was right.
You are one tough gal.
You can portray me
as a rich bastard
In the press all you want,
Just as long
as I stay rich.
Stan is looking for you.
I'm busy.
He said it's urgent.
I don't understand
how it's even possible.
I've checked it twice.
How much?
Ten cases.
Ten cases?
Going back three years.
What the hell have
you been doing, stan?
You're supposed
to be managing this place.
All the paperwork I signed
was correct.
She must have altered
the orders afterwards.
Didn't you ever cross-check
it with the bills that came in?
I delegated it.
To whom?
To gail.
Look, she seemed perfectly
trustworthy.
How was I supposed to know?
By doing your job.
I'm sorry.
Have you notified the dea?
The dea?
Jeez, stan.
Hello!
You don't steal $50,000
worth of pills
Because you want
to lose weight.
She's supplying
a meth lab.
Just get her back
in here.
All right.
Now.
Oh, you ever want a job,
trust me.
He'll double whatever
you're making here.
Take it he liked
my proposal.
Enough to tell me to get
my ass back over here today.
Here.
He's willing to go to 8%.
Eight?
We were at four.
Your board's gonna think
you walk on water.
I want 12.
You're not gonna get 12.
There's just no way.
8% barely covers
our cost inflation.
But capitated structure
should allow you
To hold down inflation.
And shifts all your risk
onto us,
Which is why
we deserve 12.
Lisa, come on.
The guy who mows my lawn makes
more than my kid's teacher.
Hell, the two guys
whose lunch you interrupted
Could get fired, and their
severance would be more
Than most of their employees
make in a lifetime.
It doesn't have anything
to do with what you deserve.
This is it.
Take it or leave it.
[sighs]
What are you doing?
Hey.
Know any good
transplant surgeons?
Turns out his kidneys aren't
the only thing failing.
And I know what
you're thinking.
But malaria wouldn't destroy
his liver that fast,
Especially since
we never infected him.
I thought you said--
Apparently foreman
now thinks that he has
The authority
to overrule my orders
Just because the fda
wouldn't approve.
Don't worry.
I'll deal with him.
If you could just
talk to hourani--
What would you do?
If you paged me
during sex?
About the contract
with atlanticnet.
I got them to come up to 8%,
but we should get at least 12.
It's all numbers.
Do the math
and nothing else.
It's not about my pride.
It's about the principle.
They're trying to screw us
over because we're small.
That's what they're
supposed to do.
They should be pressuring other
hospitals to be more like us,
Not trying to make us
more like them.
It's stupid.
Putting your job on the line
in an effort
To stamp out stupidity isn't?
You would.
Probably.
But then I also wanted
to try to cure cancer
By infecting a guy with malaria
to win a $50 bet.
You really want to be
like me?
As you know,
for the past eight months,
We've been trying
to renegotiate our contract
With atlanticnet insurance.
It's been a difficult process,
But I wanted
to let you all know
Before we made
the formal announcement
That as of 5:00 p.M.
Today,
Our contract with atlanticnet
will be terminated.
We've doubled
the number of
Customer service
representatives
In our call center.
Current patients
will still be allowed
To remain in our care
for 30 days,
But starting tomorrow,
we will no longer
Be accepting patients with
atlanticnet health insurance.
[overlapping dialogue]
(man)
why weren't we told
about this sooner?
Come on, marina.
Pick up the phone.
I'm busy.
We found a liver match.
All right.
Get him prepped.
I'll straighten things out
with hourani.
Hourani's not the problem.
House is.
Now he wants chase
to do the surgery.
To prove to hourani
he doesn't need him?
To prove to thomas
that chase
Was his department's
best surgeon.
And what does chase
want to do?
Chase wants to do the surgery.
And you don't want him
to do it because?
I don't care who does it.
So what's the problem?
In order to get our patient
into the o.R.,
We have to get him
on the surgery schedule.
In order to do that,
we need someone to put him there
Who neither house
nor thomas can overrule.
[sighs]
What?
Would you rather
I go back on vicodin?
She's not massaging
your leg.
She will...Eventually.
Why am I the only person
here who cares
What happens
to this hospital?
Get off your ass and get your
department under control.
At least for
the next few days.
Gonna take longer than
a few days for a company
The size of atlanticnet
to start feeling
The squeeze
of your p.R. Campaign.
If they ever do.
And you know this how?
From all the time
you've spent researching them
And their other contracts?
The way they handle
their press relations?
I know
they have a nascar team.
Despite what you may have
learned at hebrew school
Or from jimmy cliff,
Sometimes the bigger
they are,
The harder
they kick your ass.
I'm not
trying to be greedy.
But he's
also not interested
In being forced into
a medical bankruptcy.
Mr. Acevedo, I am sorry you're
having financial difficulties.
But because of us,
you still have a thumb.
I assume that's something
a carpenter might need.
And I assume you didn't
ask for this meeting
So you could lecture
my client.
You have insurance.
But by filing this suit,
You've caused us to get paid
nothing by them either.
That's not our problem.
Actually it is,
Since he's responsible
For any expense
we're not reimbursed.
But if you drop this suit
And make it clear
that dr. Chase was acting
In your best interest
when he reattached your thumb,
Then we'll be able
to resubmit the claim.
And you'll cover his
deductible,
Attorney's fees, and 50 grand
for pain and suffering?
Actually,
I was thinking more like
We'd cover
half his deductible,
Which means
you'd only owe $16,000.
You mean you
want him to pay you?
Yes.
Do you have any idea
how much it costs?
How many years it takes to
train someone in microsurgery?
We gave you back your life.
You can still work.
You can button your own shirt,
hold a fork.
Martin, let's go.
I'm sorry.
I know I should pay.
But I just can't.
I still cannot work.
I'm already underwater
on my house.
And I have
two kids with braces.
You think you'd be in
better shape without a thumb?
Right now...
Financially? Yeah.
I would be.
Well, so would we.
But when you came in,
we didn't think about that,
We just took care of you.
Made sure we did
whatever you needed to get well.
Yeah, right,
all you doctors care about
Is healing.
[phone ringing]
That's why there's
all those bmws and porsches
In the parking lot.
Damn it.
Come on,
we're out of here.
We'll see you in court.
You're right,
you will.
You still have
a thumb because of us.
And like everyone else
in this world,
We don't work for free.
We earn this money.
And if we have to take
your house to get it,
We will.
[chatter]
What's going on?
I think
they're fighting.
Out of my way, now.
Out of my way.
[struggling noises]
What the hell is going on?
I told them
to use their words.
[loud whistle]
[heavy panting]
That pharm tech
is back.
She's in your office.
You, there.
You, over there.
I don't wanna hear a word
out of either one of you
Until I get back.
You lied.
So?
What're you gonna do
about it?
Well, for one...
Notify the dea.
Good.
I'm sure they'll be
very interested to hear
How doctor house forced me
to help him steal the meds
And the administrator
who he's having sex with
Has been helping him
cover it up.
You really think you
can lie your way out of this?
Yeah, I do.
Anything else
you wanna know...Bitch?
The hospital board's chairman
wants to speak to you.
Tell him I'm busy.
I did, but he--
Tell him I quit.
[tapping on glass]
[sighs]
You owe lucas the money.
We were having sex
when you called.
The breast milk guy
finally found a doctor
To give him what he wanted.
If it works,
it's way better than malaria.
It was worth a shot.
I...
I thought they
were the ones bluffing.
No way they'd
let us terminate.
They're
not gonna fire you.
And you're not gonna quit.
Why not?
Because you're an idiot.
This place needs you.
And that matters to you.
[sighs]
What do you think
of that pharm tech?
Gail.
She's a sociopath.
You knew
she was stealing meds?
No.
But have you seen
the way she opens the mail?
Why didn't you ever tell me?
Figured it might
come in handy one day.
[chuckles]
Gail, I like you.
I always have.
And I know you
must've gotten sucked up
Into a situation
you weren't able to control.
Really, is that what happened
with you and house?
I'm not gonna back down
Just because
you threaten to smear me.
Now, if you agree
to tell the truth,
There are things
I can do to help.
Think about
your husband, your kids.
I know you're a good person
deep down inside.
You can't completely hide
Everything about yourself
in seven years.
You're an idiot.
I started stealing from here
six months after you hired me.
You still don't even know
the half of it,
And you never will.
You wouldn't have
even found out about this
If I hadn't gotten sick.
And you aren't as tough
as you think you are.
There's no way you'd
let this job get taken away.
And if I go down...
You're going down.
[sighs]
Hey...
Can you tell stan
to give this to
The dea agent
when he comes by.
A flower?
Yeah, lucas gave it to me.
I thought he might
come in handy one day.
[gail on recording]
I started stealing from here
Six months
after you hired me.
Nice.
Least I came
out on top once today.
Where you going?
To hand the board
my resignation.
Hopefully whoever
they hire to replace me
Can still get the 8%.
[cell phone ringing]
Marina!
I've been trying to get
in touch with you all day.
All right, I understand.
Just how is rachel?
And the rash?
Great.
I'll be home early--oh!
Aw!
[sighs]
perfect.
You bitch.
I didn't think
you'd actually do it.
I told you I would.
Call the dogs off.
You got your 12.
Congratulations.
Yes!
Whoo!
[shine on by eric bibb]
♪ ♪
[phone ringing]
(lucas)
you gonna get that?
www.tvsubtitles.net