Who is it?
It's Tom.
Tom, your husband?
What's he doing here?
Uh, what's going on?
I'm sorry, I know I'm
not supposed to be here,
but Evelyn's school
contract's due tomorrow.
I knew I was forgetting something.
Let me, uh, find a pen.
Hey. Hey.
Not quite sure what Emily post
recommends in this situation,
but I'm Tom.
Damien. Hey.
Sorry to intrude.
I just--I wasn't quite sure
when she'd be coming home.
No problem.
Thank you so much for catching this.
Yeah.
Well, I'll get out of your way,
it was good to meet you,
and I'll see you later,
hon.
Bye.
So...
Seems like a nice guy.
Ooh.
Jules, you okay?
No, my stomach.
Here. Lie down.
Ow!
Try to--
get Tom.
Ow! Tom!
♪ House 6x18 ♪
Open and Shut
original air date on April 26, 2010
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.Com --
♪  ♪
You know what would be perfect?
Hmm? French toast tower.
You still go to Mickey's?
What's your cholesterol?
It's my one vice. I'm keeping it.
As much as I would love
to clog my arteries,
I have a 10:00 ct and I
still have to race home,
get changed.
Maybe you could keep
some clothes here.
Maybe I could.
He's just trying to
get into your skirts.
And I don't mean metaphorically.
Well, he's got the legs for it.
So I will see you tonight?
Yeah.
Bye, House.
Have a nice day.
"Have a nice day."
How civilized.
I said I'd stay t of it.
What?
Nothing.
Clearly something.
Nope.
House, on a list of your attributes,
there's nothing that
even rhymes with "coy."
Okay, I may have seen
something in the fridge.
Like the end of your relationship.
She put the milk in the
door and not on the shelf.
It's not a big deal.
You hate that she did that,
but you didn't say anything.
You're trying to get us to fight.
No, I'm trying to help.
If you got an issue, let her know.
I should have known
that you weren't done
sabotaging this.
Fine. Stew in your irritation.
And sure, last time
it bubbled over
into resentment and rage,
leading ultimately
to a painful divorce
that neither of you ever
really recovered from,
but I'm sure this
time it'll be great.
Interesting case.
35-year-old woman with
fever and abdominal pain.
E.R. ruled out all
the usual suspects.
Stop before you
interest me to death.
And she's in an open marriage.
That's not interesting.
It's just weird.
Know what's weirder?
That other humans are
monogamous in the first place.
No other species on the planet
mates for life
and if you're gonna bring up swans,
they cheat like everybody else.
They just have better
pr than rabbits.
Animals also eat their young
and kill their rivals.
That make it weird
that most of us don't?
Says the guy whose
opposable thumbs have been
all over how many women
who aren't his wife?
A functional open marriage
is like a Unicorn.
It's a mythical creature
that doesn't exist.
Someone always ends up unhappy.
Our patient's unhappy becau
se she's suffering
from an intestinal blockage.
Boring.
Then we have to find a
reason to rule it out.
What about herpes colitis?
She picks up the infection
from one of her partners.
It takes root in her colon.
Std panel was clean.
Chances are, this couple was
unhappy in the first place.
This is their attempt
to save something
that never--
go on.
Herpes might not
register
if she was exposed in
the last six weeks.
But it would show up
on a barium enema.
Wait.
You're gonna do it?
Gotta see if our
patient's a Unicorn
or just a slutty horse.
Think how much fun
Taub could be having.
Barium coats the inner
lining of your colon.
Lets us get a good look
at it on the X-ray.
I can get somebody
else to pick up Evelyn.
I feel like i'm abandoning you.
I'm on painkillers.
I'd rather this not
be what you think of
every time you look at my butt.
Okay, roll onto your side.
It's fill 'er up time.
So is Evelyn his new squeeze?
She's our daughter.
Must be interesting
growing up in a production of Oh!
Calcutta!
She's six.
She knows as much
about our sex life
as any other kid her age.
You can explain that
she's the reason
the two of you stayed married.
You've been in the
room five minutes.
You got us all figured out.
Of course, you left out
the part
where we love each other
and we want to grow old together.
But you just don't want
to be young together.
Look, when you think about it,
tons of couples do what we do.
It's just that with most of them,
one spouse doesn't know about it.
We decided things work better
when people tell
each other the truth.
Tank's full.
I'll page the radiology elves.
I'm not saying I hate it.
Just doesn't go with your eyes.
You hate it.
Little bit.
Any more heartless critiques
of my general appearance?
Nope. All done.
So is she as bendy as she looks?
Maya and I are just friends.
No, you and I are friends
and you don't have coffee
with me three times a week.
She's an interesting person.
She grew up in Ohio.
She has three brothers.
Fascinating.
Last week, that Cambodian lab tech
was telling us how he
survived the Killing Fields
and you left to go get a donut.
So we flirt. It's fun.
It's dangerous.
That woman would totally do you.
You think?
Nothing is gonna happen.
All I'm saying is if you
want to be on a diet,
you might want to stop hanging
out by the dessert cart.
X-ray was clean.
She doesn't have herpes colitis
or abdominal pain.
It stopped hurting
during the X-ray,
which means it was just an
intestinal blockage that passed.
We should discharge her.
Absolutely.
There's no need to find
any underlying cause
'cause these things
never happen twice.
Take her digestive
system for a test drive.
Give her a radio-opaque milkshake.
X-ray every 15 minutes to see
if it makes any unscheduled
stops on the way through.
We'll be here all night.
No, Taub will be here all night.
Talk to the Unicorn
and then tell me you don't believe.
I did an abdominal
ct on a kid today
and found a six-inch bezoar
made entirely of gum.
I mean, who gives a three-year-old
an endless supply of g--
you okay?
Yeah.
I mean, there was hair in it
and maybe a piece of paper.
So... how long you been married?
One of the few drawbacks
of having an open marriage.
Nobody ever asks me about
current events or the weather.
Yankees look good this season.
Seven years.
And, uh, how long have you-
you know?
After three years, we realized
that traditional marriage
was making us both miserable.
Most people get
divorced at that point.
Yeah, we didn't want
to get divorced.
We still loved each other.
We just realized that
expecting one person
to fulfill all of your needs
forever is unrealistic.
There are happy monogamous
couples out there.
Sure.
One or two have the perfect marriage.
Everybody else has figured out
how to settle for less.
I don't want to settle and end
up resenting my husband.
I'd rather g the 10%
he doesn't give me
somewhere else so that i c
an really appreciate him
for the 90% he does.
I think something's wrong.
With your stomach?
My heart is racing.
Try and take deep breaths.
I'm going to try to
slow your heart down.
Is this because of the blockage?
No. It's not working.
Need a crash cart in here!
I need a list of all your
sexual partners
from the last six months.
Why?
Your wife had an arrhythmia.
The progression of symptoms
from bowel to heart
makes a parasitic
infection most likely.
Since Julia hasn't been
out of the country--
the only place that
I've been recently
is a business trip to Nebraska.
But either of you
could have picked up
a bug from one of your partners.
It's kind of... complicated.
How many partners are
we talking about?
Ballpark.
None.
None?
We have a great sex life.
I don't need anyone else.
So why not just tell her that
and close this whole thing up?
You married?
I--I was.
Did you ever agree to go see
a chick flick with your wife
or pretend to enjoy
classical music?
Stravinsky never groped my wife
in a Midtown hotel room.
She needs this.
I don't.
But I don't want her
to feel bad about that.
He's lying.
Guy's got a license to drill.
Why would he lie about not using it?
That's not the lie.
The lie is that he gives a
crap about how his wife feels.
If they're both screwing around,
that's one thing.
But if she has a piece on
the side and he doesn't,
the only way he'd be okay with that
is if he's betraying
her in some other way
that, in his mind, makes them even.
My Unicorn isn't a Unicorn.
It's a donkey with a
plunger stuck to its face.
Right.
Even the guy who's not cheating
is doing it for underhanded reasons.
No, no, no. He's not being cynical.
He's assuming the husband
is doing something
to even the score,
which means he thinks
there is a score,
which means,
cheating swans aside,
House believes in monogamy.
He's being romantic.
What I believe is that men
are genetically
engineered to be jealous.
Doesn't matter if i thi
nk there's a score.
I guarantee you he does.
Any of the wife's partners pan out?
She's been with two
people other than Tom
in the last six months.
Neither of them have been
outside the tri-state area.
So we're back to the husband.
You just said you believed--
he's doing something
behind her back.
What better cover than a
business trip to Nebraska?
Like that's really a place.
Let's find his travel records
and get back to work.
You seem pretty mellow
about this couple's deal.
Thought you'd be first in
line to shake a finger.
They're still married. I'm not.
Not that I could ever do it.
I was jealous of House and
Cameron never touched him.
Not counting the
emotional fondling.
When my mom was dying,
my dad had an affair.
He told you this?
I'd seen them get out of his car.
Two years after mom died,
they got married.
That must have sucked.
At the time, yeah.
But looking back... It makes sense.
My mom never knew about it
and he needed someone to
make him feel less alone.
He took care of my mom
day in and day out for 2
1/2 years before she died.
He was devoted to her.
Loving someone else
didn't change that.
So loving two people
at once is fine
as long as one of them is dying?
Whoever's taking care of me
when I get sick, I hope they've got
someone else to take care of them.
Tom was telling the truth.
He really did go to Nebraska.
Plane ticket and restaurant seats.
Forget Nebraska.
Maybe they just bought their
parasites at the mall.
You know, we should really
throw away that loofah.
They're imported.
Sometimes they're not sterilized.
We think our patient got
amoebiasis from hers.
Is she gonna be okay?
We're treating now.
She should be fine.
It's actually kind of bizarre.
She and her husband
have an open marriage.
They sleep with other people?
Well, she does.
Her husband's totally fine with it.
I mean, it's crazy, right?
And you're bringing
this up because?
I thought it was interesting.
More interesting than
your other cases, I guess.
I mean, you talk about
your colleagues,
you rant about House.
You don't usually
mention your patients.
Is open marriage
something you want?
No.
I mean...
I know you'd never...
All this time and energy
you spent convincing me
you weren't cheating...
And there's somebody else.
I'm not-- some more
water sir?
Okay.
There's a woman at work.
People say she's attracted to me,
but nothing's happened.
Nothing's going to happen.
I'm not having an affair.
But you want to.
No, honey.
I'm trying to be honest.
I don't want to make
the same mistakes.
Be honest then.
Are you attracted to her?
Look... she's attractive.
There's an attraction.
Aren't there men who
make you feel that way?
Of course there are,
but it never occurs to me
to act on it because-
because I'm married...
To you.
And that's enough for me.
Aren't I enough for you?
Of course you are.
Our patient's lost all
movement in her legs.
There are other doctors, Chris.
We're talking.
I'm sorry.
The woman's paralyzed.
I'll get a cab.
Tests show no spinal cord injury,
no cerebral lesions, no hemorrhage.
Finally got a stool sample.
The loofah's innocent.
No sign of amoebas
or any other parasites.
So paralysis, arrhythmia,
and intermittent abdominal pain.
And he nicked himself shaving.
Sorry. That was Taub.
But it was easier to solve.
Means he used the crappy
razor in his locker,
which means he slept here.
Thanks to you.
I brought up open
marriage with Rachel.
It was a disaster.
On the medical front,
we've knocked out sex
and foreign travel.
Could be an electrolyte imbalance.
So the only time you're not
interested in my marriage
is after you bw it up?
You're the moron who
took marital advice
from Tila Tequila.
You pushed me into this.
Figured it would either
blow up your marriage
or make it more honest.
Either way, you win.
What about sex?
I'm talking about the patient.
Is that cool with everybody?
We've ruled out sex.
We ruled out sex with other people.
Tom said he and Julia
have been doing it
three or four times a week and she
's got boys on the side.
Increased libido can be a symptom
of adrenocortical carcinoma,
which also explains
her other symptoms.
A woman who likes sex must be sick?
Just because everybody
in this room
wishes that all women
were horny all the time
doesn't make it so.
Get an mri of her adrenal glands.
Hi.
Okay if I take the sports page?
Sure.
Would you mind using a coaster?
Oh.
Sure.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Also, it'd be great
if you'd replace
the toilet paper when
you finish a roll.
And when you load the dishwasher,
you can't put a big,
flat bowl on the bottom.
It traps the water so nothing
on the top gets clean.
And please don't throw banana
peels in the bedroom trash.
I haven't done any of those things.
You're probably not even aware of--
I hate bananas.
Oh, my God. It was House.
I'm sorry.
He's been trying
to get us to fight.
Why would he think that
stuff would make us fight?
Because of the milk.
You put it in the door.
The body of the refrigerator
is the coldest part.
The temperature in
the door fluctuates,
which decreases shelf life.
Wow.
When did you get all ocd?
I just want clean dishes
and unspoiled milk
so we can all stay healthy.
Oh, it's about health.
What about the coaster?
Does that replenish
my B-12 or something?
Can we just drop it?
Sure.
You have this list of annoyances
the entire time we were married?
Get better, mommy.
I love you, rabbit.
Julia, you have a guest.
Hi.
This isn't a good time.
Dr. Hadley, did you say
there was a video
game in the playroom?
Maybe you can teach me
how to play one of them.
See you in radiology.
Get out of my wife's room.
Your relationship with her sta
ys out of our space.
I was worried about her.
Tom's right. You should go.
So it's fine if we have sex,
but if I drop by to
see if you're okay--
this is our family.
Sorry.
I spent two years of residency
wearing shirts that
were a size too small.
How hard is it to ask me not
to put them in the dryer?
And I only did your laundry
because you were never home.
I didn't ask you to.
Of course you didn't.
You just got annoyed whenever
you didn't have clean underwear.
I never said I was annoyed.
That's the point.
You didn't say anything.
So I'm getting a lecture
on communication
from someone who had
her lawyer inform me
our marriage was over.
Asking for an open marriage.
You got stones.
Conversation sort
of got away from me.
It was a train wreck.
I think it's good
you brought it up.
I read a study that found
men who have multiple copies
of a certain vasopressin receptor
are twice as likely
to be unfaithful.
Maybe you're just
one of those guys.
So my cheating is
biologically predetermined?
Fantastic.
Multiply times five.
We need a better
look at the medulla.
I thought you'd be relieved.
This gets you off the hook.
It's just genetics.
I'm 5'6" and have a
receding hairline.
I hate genetics.
Medulla's clean.
I don't see you wearing
lifts or hair plugs.
That's because being short and bald
doesn't hurt anybody.
The only thing hurtful
about your other
genetic predisposition is
that you keep denying it.
It's not good for you or Rachel.
There's nothing there.
It's not adrenal cancer.
And maybe you're right about me.
But I'm not gonna stop trying.
Rachel's worth it.
Look up there.
The lung.
What is that?
You served me with divorce papers
in the middle of a medical
conference in New Orleans.
I threw a bottle into
an antique mirror.
Oh, you exhibited an emotion?
I wish I'd known you were capable.
I loved you.
I thought I was gonna
be following you
to Baltimore, remember?
I called about apartments.
I set up interviews.
How could you think that we
still had a real marriage?
We hadn't had a
conversation in months.
Maybe because I was working
two jobs to support us.
No! No!
It's because when you were home,
it was like talking
to a block of ice.
You were obviously
so pissed off at me.
I was killing myself
so that you could take
that non-paying internship.
That you said that I should take.
I was trying to be supportive!
Why do I have to be the bad guy?
Expressing yourself does
not make you the bad guy.
Okay, then. You were
being a selfish bitch.
VQ scan confirmed the spot
on Julia's lung was a clot.
Think there's a chance
the husband's a plushie?
If he has a secret,
I highly doubt it's more
relevant than the clot.
Clotting disorder would
explain everything.
Question is, which one?
Do you read any of your
departmental memos?
Only the ones labeled, "n-s-f-w."
Accounting notified
you two days ago
about your patient's insurance.
Sorry, that's "n-n-s-f-w."
Here. He doesn't have any.
Try not to bankrupt them.
Oh, I'm long past the
number of procedures
that'll bankrupt them.
Julia's got insurance.
I saw the policy
number on the form.
But the policy lapsed
due to non-payment.
I already made three
calls about this.
You should have been aware of that.
No, there's just a mistake.
Of course we have health insurance.
We're actually a little
behind on the premiums.
But I pulled money
out of my retirementccount to cover it.
They said that we'll be fine in--
Why the retirement account?
We'll just give you
a few minutes to--
and by "we," she means "she."
I lost all of our savings.
Sounds like a secret to me.
I started her on heparin to prevent
further clots, but we still
don't know what's going on.
Of course the husband's
secret was money.
If it's not sex, it's always money.
Unless it's sex for money.
How did he lose it anyway?
It's not medically relevant.
You're not gonna care.
Wilson's been teaching
me how to care. Try me.
He builds wind turbines
and leases them out to
local power companies.
You're right. I don't care.
Clotting disorder: Dic.
Factor five leiden,
antiphospholipid syndrome.
Vitamin k deficiency also fits.
Causes thrombophilia and is
consistent with abdominal pain.
Congratulations, House.
Sam ended it.
What happened?
Go test our patient's blood.
But it can wait five minutes.
For everything we discussed.
I'm sorry.
Well, at least you're
actually taking responsibility
for once in your life.
Sorry that she left.
It's not my fault.
I didn't even want
to get involved.
You dragged it out of me.
What about the
dishwasher and the banana
and the toi--
she left because of the banana.
I just wanted you to
stand up for yourself.
Tell her what you want.
If doing that causes
her to walk out
for the second time,
well, your relationship
wasn't gonna last anyway.
Or you could have stayed out of it.
I could have kept my mouth shut,
been annoyed sometimes,
but I'd be happy,
because I'd still be with her.
Now all I have is cold milk.
As long as you're free,
you want to grab some dinner?
Did Tom go home for the night?
For starters.
I told him to leave.
I don't want him here.
Money is a complicated subject.
Yeah, it's not the money.
I mean, the-
the money's bad, but...
When we first opened our marriage,
I got involved with a guy
who lied about being single.
Then one day, his wife calls me.
She's crying and screaming
and totally out of control.
And I felt...
superior.
I thought I don't ever have to
worry about feeling this way
because Tom and I are
honest with each other.
Well, here I am.
Hi.
Sorry I didn't make
it home last night.
I needed to run some tests.
You know what the worst part was?
When y had your affair...
Wasn't the sex.
It was the lies.
Realizing that the
narrative of my life
was totally wrong.
You weren't stuck in surgery.
You weren't out of town.
I don't want to go
through that again.
I told you nothing's--
Thursday nights.
You have to be home by midnight.
You don't bring her here.
You don't talk to h
er about me
and I don't want to meet
her ever in any context.
Are you giving me permission
to sleep with other women?
It's what you want, isn't it?
I want you.
You want more than me.
You want that thrill.
But I love you.
And I really believe
that you love me...
And we have a good life together.
And at this point,
either I walk away
or I try to accept
who you really are.
Tomorrow's Thursday.
Yes, it is.
All our tests came back negative.
It's not a clotting disorder.
Which means we need to
come up with a better idea.
So what causes problems in
the stomach, heart, nerves?
Oh, my God.
You know what it is?
Taub's wife gave the green
light for an open marriage.
He's wearing cologne,
but not the stink of shame.
You got a date.
I am going out with Maya tonight
with Rachel's blessing.
Mazel Tov?
Maybe the problem isn't her blood.
Maybe it's the vessels
carrying the blood.
No sign of schistocytes
or hemolysis.
So you're actually going
to sleep with another woman
then go home to your wife?
Thank God someone's
keeping us focused on
what's really important.
Taub was gonna do
all of that anyway.
Pulmonary arterial hypertension.
Imaging showed normal diameter
in her pulmonary artery.
Here's a thought--
Taub's wife is now
totally on the market.
Mind hitting me with her digits?
She would love that,
but duty calls.
What's the matter?
My stomach.
Same pain as before?
Yeah, but worse.
Get the portable
ultrasound in here.
We need to get a look at her belly.
Help me!
Pain, pain went away,
came back another day.
Question is, what brought it back?
Physical exam was unrevealing.
Ultrasound was clean.
So afterwards, are you gonna shower
at your girlfriend's or at home?
Patient. Abdominal pain.
Yeah, he's right.
Let's get this wrapped
up before 6:00.
Taub turns back into a
faithful Pumpkin at midnight.
Patient was out with her
boy toy before she came in.
Maybe the pain was triggered
by sexual excitement.
Because lying alone
in a hospital bed
contemplating bankruptcy-- hot.
My point was that
arousal is a function
of the parasympathetic
nervous system.
If that's where the problem is,
the pain could be triggered by crying,
which seems--
pns. Also controls digestion,
which she's been doing without
screaming her head off
since she's been here.
What if what matters isn't
when the pain started,
but when it stopped?
It was during an X-ray.
You think that cured her?
No, but House prepped her for
the X-ray with a barium enema.
Well, that wouldn't
treat anything except--
go.
You're in pain because
part of your intestine
folded in on itself.
It's called an intussusception.
It's cutting off blood flow.
We need to fix it before your
bowel gets necrotic and dies.
Once you do that,
will I get better?
When this happens in adults,
it's usually a sign
of abdominal cancer.
We'll fix the overlap,
and then search your
intestine for tumors.
Foam?
I have a bad feeling about this.
A friend can't spontaneously buy
an overpriced itali
an espresso machine
for another friend?
What did you do?
Nothing. That's the beauty.
I genuinely tried to help Wilson.
I told him to stand up for himself,
which you know is
legitimate advice.
And his relationship blew up.
Is he okay?
Ah, he'll be fine.
Point is, I realized something.
I do nice things,
nice things happen to me.
Karma works.
So you're paying it forward?
If this should somehow
lead to Lucas dying
or oral sex,
so be it.
Namaste.
Think I should wear a tie tonight?
This isn't weird at all.
I mean, where's
Rachel eating tonight?
Home.
What if she's going out too?
She is allowed to, right?
Of course. It's only fair.
But I don't think she will.
Your wife only eats dinner at home?
If she did go out,
that would be tough,
but I think i can handle it.
Don't do it unless you're sure.
I know I'd rather be
jealous than a liar.
Got something here.
Kelly clamp and scalpel.
Biopsy showed
non-specific inflammation,
which suggests ibd,
only it doesn't explain
the cardiac problems.
Or her declining kidney function.
We ran panels during surgery.
Actually, ibd does make sense,
'cause it could trigger
ankylosing spondylitis,
which would explain the
heart and the kidneys.
Start her on sulfasalazine
and tnf-inhibitors.
Oh, and Taub,
I'm not gonna see you before
you head off for gomorrah.
Just remember,
if you get disoriented...
Breathe through your nose
and look for the horizon.
I can't.
I really thought I could do this.
Logically, it makes perfect sense.
But...
all afternoon,
all I kept thinking about
was the two of you,
together,
and you touching her.
Nothing's happened.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
'Cause I really wanted it--
no.
I've been an idiot,
and I don't need anything else.
I just need you.
You mean that?
I do.
I love you, Rachel.
I love you too.
Let's go home.
Is that okay?
There are other doctors.
The treatment's not working.
Her left kidney failed last night.
The other one's right behind it.
It's not ankylosing spondylitis.
Kidney biopsy showed she
had iga nephropathy,
which could be caused by
or associated with any
of these conditions.
We've gone from too
few ideas to too many,
and our patient's
running out of time.
Why the lack of afterglow?
Physio girl not as
freaky as you'd hoped?
I went home with my wife.
After all that,
you chickened out.
I can't hurt Rachel like that.
Sickle cell anemia would
have shown on blood tests.
No flattened intestinal villi
rules out celiac.
Seriously?
Our patient's dying,
and we can't move past my sex life?
Seriously,
you'd think it'd kill her
if we spend 15 seconds mocking you?
Time's up.
Normal liver enzymes
rules out hep b and cirrhosis.
Alport and anti-gbm antibody
are both untreatable,
so if she has them
we can't help her.
And it can't be
henoch-schonlein purpura.
No inciting respiratory infection
and no rash.
I don't care what it's not.
I want to know what it could be.
Well, everything left on the list.
The list was not created equal.
Neither was man, by the way.
Hemochromatosis is a possibility.
Excess iron builds up,
causes problems throughout the body.
Weil's syndrome also affects
multiple organ systems,
and it wouldn't have been
treated
by the antibiotic the E.
R. gave her.
Sarcoidosis makes sense too.
Good.
Treat for those three.
I think you should call Tom.
Am I gonna die?
I don't know.
If he walked in here right now,
I'd look in his face and all
I would think is "liar."
Don't you think
that's kind of unfair?
You say honesty's all-important,
but you conveniently igno
re the truth
that some truths hurt people.
Tom lied to protect you.
He was covering his ass.
I'm not talking about the money.
Tom hasn't slept with anyone else
in over a year.
He told you that?
So my entire marriage is a sham?
No.
Your husband, who only wants you,
lied so that you could be happy.
That seems pretty real to me.
Yeah?
Hey.
Listen, I'm sorry.
Me too. I shouldn't have said--
no, you were right.
I was selfish back then.
I'm trying to change.
And I don't know if
it's House or what,
but... you're different too.
I'm trying.
I always thought that I
was keeping the peace,
but I was just resenting you
and giving you a reason to leave.
I wish we had this
fight ten years ago.
Is it okay if we don't
give House the credit?
Oh, I recommend it.
"O" for three.
Her kidney function
is still declining.
We're gonna need to start dialysis.
Glad the husband's back.
After missing so
many little deaths,
he should be here for the big one.
Top six, anyone?
Polyarteritis nodosa?
We'd have seen some
improvement on prednisone.
Guy's wife's dying,
and he stops to buy flowers.
They're from his garden.
Mercury poisoning fits.
Those are lilacs.
My mom used to grow lilacs.
My dad made her get rid of them,
'cause there were too many bees.
We ruled out hsp
'cause there was no inciting
respiratory infection.
But in rare cases, it can also
be triggered by a bee sting.
We also ruled it out
because there's no rash.
Maybe we just didn't see it.
Have you been stung
by a bee recently?
Uh, about a month ago.
What's going on?
I think your wife has
henoch-schonlein purpura.
Systemic vasculitis
can cause
lesions and inflammations
throughout the body.
It's pretty awful,
which explains why it was
named after a German.
Actually two germans.
Lesions can pop up in the heart,
sometimes in the kidneys,
but always on the skin.
Means you'd have a rash somewhere.
I don't.
Not that you know of.
Okay, I'm gonna have
to check your holes.
I'll start with the mouth.
If there's nothing there,
then things might
have to get kinky.
Say aah.
Aah.
I was kinda hoping for kinky.
Is that good or bad?
We'll treat her
with high-dose ivig
and cyclophosphamide.
You should be fine.
I'm gonna be okay.
I love you.
That is adorable.
Other than you still wanting
to have sex with other dudes,
and him bankrupting your family,
I think you kids are
pretty much home free.
Mm-hmm?
And...
You two made up?
No.
You can thank me later.
I'm all-in.
All right.
Fold.
♪ ♪
♪ met you yesterday ♪
♪ out in the place where ♪
♪ here in the corner of your eye ♪
♪ Now you hold a heart ♪
♪ that was not mine to give ♪
♪ for I cannot feel alive ♪
♪ ♪
♪ the way that you are ♪
♪ the way that you want me ♪
you need a hand?
♪ The way that I am ♪
thanks.
♪ When I'm with you ♪
♪ the way that I feel ♪
sorry about canceling
the other night.
Me too.
♪ The way that I am ♪
♪ with you ♪
♪ the way that I feel ♪
♪ ♪
♪ the way that you want me ♪
you wanna go somewhere?
♪ ♪
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.Com --
www.tvsubtitles.net