A crane collapsed
in downtown Trenton.
Don't care.
That's my great-grandfather.
No, it's just a book he wrote.
Open it up.
Seriously, you're giving
this to us?
It's a big step you're taking.
I wanted to congratulate you.
I understand that's
the adult thing to do.
How did you know?
I've known for a while.
The fact that you
decided to cohabitate
is not exactly a spoiler.
Unless my intel is wrong.
Trouble in paradise?
We have to get to Trenton.
♪ House 6x21 ♪ Help
Me Original air date on May 17, 2010
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.Com --
Can you hear me?
Hmm?
That sound like a yes?
Sir, we have to get you to the O.R.
You have a bad wound,
but we're gonna pack it
and transport you
as fast as we can.
Skull fracture.
Glasgow coma score of 11.
She's immediate.
Move on.
This guy's dead.
His wounds aren't so--
forget the wound. Look at his toes.
Atherosclerotic emboli.
He'll never survive the surgery.
Maybe his shoes were too tight.
It's not the shoes.
Skin shows smoker's facies.
He's not gonna make
it till morning.
He'll just take up
an ambulance ride,
surgeon's time, and an icu bed.
He's expectant. Leave him.
I only nodded off for a second.
I lost control of the load.
I'm so sorry.
Don't worry. We're gonna
get you outta here.
I'm sorry.
He's secure.
Ready? Three, two, one.
That's it.
Crane operator.
Made it through amazingly well.
Lucid and responsive.
Stable fracture, right humerus.
Haven't gotten to
his lower half yet.
Tell me when something hurts.
I fell asleep.
Killed all those people.
Something other than
your conscience.
Is that a pill in your pocket,
or are you just happy to have
a tiny pill-shaped penis?
Caffeine pills.
You fell asleep taking these?
I drank two cups of coffee too.
Is that normal for you?
No, I hate coffee.
I'm working on no sleep.
My daughter has the flu.
This much caffeine
for a coffee virgin.
There's no way he fell asleep.
He passed out.
Which means a neurological
disorder
caused the crash, not fatigue.
Hey.
We're taking the crane
operator back to Princeton.
They said he was barely hurt-
-he can wait.
Steal an ambulance.
And call the team.
Tell 'em we got a case.
House. No! I need you here.
And he needs me there.
And he moans louder than you do.
There were over 100
people in that building.
Only 76 have been accounted for.
Foreman and your team can handle
the crane operator for now.
Having fun down there?
Lots!
Every time Cuddy
leans over a patient,
it's another opportunity
for a down blouse nip slip.
What's going on
between her and Lucas?
Besides them moving in together?
That's not enough for you?
I gave her the
housewarming gift earlier.
And she paused for a split second,
like she was hiding something.
It's probably her moral
revulsion
at housewarming gifts.
Or maybe she didn't
want to accept a gift
for something she wasn't gonna do.
You actually think they're not
moving in together?
What was that? You okay?
Yep. Vending machine collapsed.
She still using your
ex-wife as a realtor?
As far as I know.
Well, know a little farther,
will you?
Look into it.
Hey!
There's somebody down here!
If you can hear me,
tap three times, or call out.
Is anyone there?
I'm not getting anything.
I heard something-
-there's gotta be a void down there.
There's a million voids down there.
It was the parking garage.
But equipment hasn't
picked up any movement.
Dogs haven't picked up any scent.
There's smashed cars down there.
The gasoline throw off their scent?
Look, we gotta get
back to work, okay?
We'll get to this area soon.
Excuse me.
Anybody hear me?
Hey!
Aah! Oh...
Help me.
What's your name?
Please...my husband's gift.
I was supposed to pick
it up at the framers.
It's on Elm.
Well, you should
have told me earlier.
I could have picked
it up on the way.
What's your name?
It's a picture from
our Tortola trip.
For his birthday.
I'm not asking your name
because I wanna become friends.
I'm trying to gauge
your mental state.
Hanna.
Okay, that's a start.
What day of the week is it?
Tuesday.
Better still.
What happened?
You know that giant
construction crane next door?
It's kind of on top
of you right now.
Okay, I'm gonna try
to pull you out.
Ow! My leg!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Okay, okay.
Whew...
I'm gonna need to get help.
No, stay! Someone else will come.
No one knows I'm down here.
Please! Stay with me.
Don't leave me in the dark.
I'll be right back.
No! Don't leave me in the dark!
Please stay!
He's still in the E.R., House.
We haven't had time to
start a differential.
Perfect! Let's start right now.
Put me on speaker.
What causes syncope?
Your guy's stable.
The two dozen other patients--
don't need to be diagnosed.
They just need to be bandaged.
What causes syncope?
Vasovagal reaction...
Meningioma. Sick sinus syndrome.
Or you're wrong, and he just fell asleep.
How's he gonna sleep
with 50 cups of coffee
going through his veins?
Were you never a medical resident?
I hear ten, eleven, and twelve.
Where's Thirteen? She's not here.
And the answer to your
next question is no.
I don't know where she is.
Do you have the answer to
my question after that?
Space-occupying lesion in his brain
is most likely.
Mri will prove I'm right.
Or it'll just prove
he suffered head
trauma from the crash.
Which we'd wanna find anyway.
Two birds with one scan. Do it.
Having trouble finding
a vein for Hanna's iv.
She getting weaker?
Paler? No, no. She's stable.
That means her blood
loss in minimal.
Buys us some time.
Get the iv into her tibia.
It's almost hollow,
feeds into the venous system.
Which they obviously don't
teach you in emt school.
This side's still
leaning pretty bad.
Gotta shore up this beam.
Told ya I'd be back.
...On my side.
Heard you might be thirsty.
Ah...
I assume that bodes
well for the rescue?
Structural beam.
High compression concrete.
I can't break it up.
You can't get me outta here?
Naw. Just means we gotta
move on
to a different piece of equipment.
I got airbags comin' in
that'll lift 70 tons.
What's your name?
You testing my mental state?
I'm gonna be stuck down here
for a while.
I'd like somebody to talk to.
Look, the guy who
just left is the one
who's gonna be holding
your hand through all this.
You talk to him.
Little pinch.
Aah! Oh! Ow!
Oh... Okay. Big pinch.
I gotta call my husband.
Can I use your phone?
Uh, no bars down here.
L'chaim.
Where are you going? Don't worry.
Fire marshal bill
will be back soon.
So I hope I didn't weird
you out
giving you that gift.
Can we talk about this later?
Of course.
Is now later?
Maybe things aren't going
so well with Lucas.
If so, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to
step into anything.
There's no problems.
We're doing just great.
Thank you.
So why the weirdness?
Can you help?
When I opened it,
I didn't think it was
a housewarming gift.
I thought it was an
engagement present.
It just happened last night.
No wonder you wanna
hide this from me...
Since I'm such a delicate flower.
I didn't know what to say.
And I've been slightly distracted.
That might make sense,
'cept you're not wearing the ring.
So...You are hiding it,
which begs the question--
House...It's in my office drawer
because I knew I was coming here.
It's not weird.
There's no mystery.
I'm just getting married.
'Scuse me.
How much longer?
Uh, less than a minute.
Are you in any pain?
Nothing now. Just a
little claustrophobic.
Shouldn't you be taking care
of those other people,
the ones that I hurt?
Everything checks out okay.
My nose is bleeding.
It's expected, given the
trauma you've sustained.
That's not expected.
The way things fell,
this support beam
is now holding up a
giant pile of rubble.
We can't lift it without
jeopardizing everyone down here.
So it's time to discuss amputation.
No.
Please listen to me.
We've been down here
almost two hours.
By the time they clear away the rubble-
-
we are not cutting off her leg.
You don't have to rush through this
to make his job easier.
You kidding me?
We leave the leg pinned,
we're risking crush syndrome.
What's that?
Your leg isn't getting
enough circulation.
The longer it's pinned
the more the muscle dies.
So what does that mean,
like a limp?
Dying muscles release poisons.
We free your leg,
the poisons rush back into your system.
It could stop your heart.
So could cheeseburgers.
Let's get your lazy friends
to start moving that pile.
She's got two more hours
before crush syndrome
could possibly set in.
We're digging up there by hand.
I can't guarantee I can
get 10 tons of debris
pulled off in two hours.
Well, you need to try.
It's my leg.
It's not just crush syndrome you
gotta worry about, okay?
There's gas leaks. There's fire.
We can never rule out
secondary collapses,
no matter how much we shore
this thing up.
You think chopping
off someone's limb
inside a pile of
dirty rocks is safe?
Sepsis, fat embolism, a hemorrhage.
Those risks are nothing
compared to the risk
of this thing coming down again.
Captain, he's a jerk.
But it's what the patient wants.
Can we please
just give it a couple more hours?
Yeah.
I gotta get up to triage.
Thank you, doctor.
House.
You don't need to thank me.
Just makes sense.
Just promise me you won't
let them cut off my leg.
I promise.
Does that make you feel better?
For some reason, it does.
Your phone is working down here.
Switched carriers.
Better rollover minutes.
Talk.
Mri was clean, but afterwards,
he started bleeding out
of his eyes and nose.
So there was something
wrong before the collapse.
Unless it's just conjunctive
coagulopathy from the trauma.
Yeah, yeah, yeah--you don't
think he was sick before.
We get it! You're wrong.
Brain infection?
Sorry I'm late.
Where were you? Physical therapy.
I left my phone in my locker.
The infection causes neurological symptoms,
goes systemic, and D.I.
C. xauses the bleed.
Good theory.
Except for the part
that there's no fever.
Get an X-ray venogram.
See if you can find a
reason for your existence.
Also look for venous sinus thrombosis.
Would have seen it on the mri.
Not if you were too
busy not looking for it.
We should X-ray for a
facial fracture first.
This could all be simple trauma.
Just do what I tell you.
Be back in ten minutes.
You're leaving?
There's a dozen people
here who can save you.
I'm apparently the only one
who can save this other guy.
W-wait!
Don't go.
Hanna's freaking out.
She's having a panic attack.
She can't breathe.
She's gonna rip out all her ivs.
So calm her down.
She wants you.
I'm flattered. Give her oxygen.
They won't let o2 down there.
Fear of explosion.
You have to go back.
She needs you, House.
You only came back
because I freaked out.
Right?
Oh, no.
I just realized how...
Big and scary the world is
and how cozy and safe
this little place is.
Thank you.
I'm sorry I needed you.
Here. Call your husband.
Charlie?
I'm here in...
They called you?
They're helping me.
Are you coming?
I don't know how this could happen.
It's your birthday.
I'm so sorry.
See? This is why I
lied about the phone.
Your bp is spiking,
so you're bleeding faster
from your leg wound.
I'm gonna have less
time to save it.
Hang up.
Okay. Okay, they're
telling me I have to go.
That was stupid of me.
It was nice.
I don't see that
as a contradiction.
He was already on his way.
He was in Baltimore,
and they all saw it on the news.
How many people were hurt?
What did I tell you about not
raising your blood pressure?
Can I ask what's
wrong with your leg?
Crane fell on it.
Small world.
You could have just said no.
I'll remember that for
my next human contact.
Would you pray with me?
No.
I'm not in the habit
of encouraging
my patients' superstitions.
How is that a habit?
You plan on getting trapped
under a building again?
I don't believe in God.
I don't either.
Please?
I always thought...
If I did the right thing,
if I treated people right,
then good things
would happen to me.
You think that's how it works?
I didn't use to.
Then recently I tried...
Now I don't know.
Good news.
Advancing catheter
through interior jugular vein.
You told House you were at therapy.
Did you transcribe
the entire meeting?
Entering the cavernous sinus.
Your therapy's on thursdays.
Got rescheduled.
Injecting dye.
Really?
I'm not gonna rat you out.
We're friends.
Just wanna make sure you're okay.
No filling defects.
Don't worry.
I'm okay.
You think we can be friends
when I get outta here?
Yeah.
We'll catch a ball game or...
Group sex show or something.
Put the cribbing in there.
Okay, now when the
beam starts lifting,
you're gonna feel pain.
It's gonna be like your
foot's gone to sleep
times a billion.
You'll notice that
I'm waiting till now
to tell you.
All right. We're ready.
Lifting.
I'm feeling the pain already.
That's good.
That means the pressure's coming off.
Much closer to getting out of here.
Aah!
Come on.
Pull her out.
Come on!
It's moving!
Pull hard! Pull!
Aah!
Hanna.
Hanna! What the hell happened?
I think the adjacent beam
snapped during the lift.
Mayday, mayday, mayday!
We had a secondary collapse.
We're all right.
How are you guys?
Rescue one, copy the mayday.
Main tunnel is fine.
Rescue's on the way.
Lift this up.
One, two--
Kit. Gimme the Kit.
All right.
No breath sounds on the left side.
Tension pneumothorax.
Okay, Hanna. One of
your lungs is collapsed.
I'm gonna have to
reinflate it, okay?
Uh...
Hey.
You better get back up top
and make sure you
didn't Nick an artery.
I'm gonna have to go.
That's okay. You're all right.
You're lucky this isn't worse.
You know who's even luckier?
You and just about
every other human being
Who wasn't down there.
What did the venogram say?
Clean.
Now the guy's starting
to spike a fever.
Subarachnoid bleed.
Meningitis? He didn't
say his neck was sore.
That's 'cause everything's sore.
He just took a 15-story
swan dive into concrete.
Do an lp. We also have to
consider other infections.
So you're suggesting we do an lp.
I guess I am.
Genius.
Hey, bad news.
Because of the collapse,
we can't try the airbag again
until we get
everything off the top.
Be five, six hours at least.
Then we have to amputate.
No.
It's been four hours already.
It used to be a long shot.
Now it's...crazy.
Crush syndrome is basically
a buildup of potassium.
If we remove potassium-- we're already
treating with sodium bicarbonate.
But not with glucose and Insulin.
We have glucose in the Kit.
There's gotta be a
diabetic here somewhere.
You wanna dose the Insulin
here in a non-hospital setting?
That is insane! It's not worth it.
Really? 'Cause I think
I'm the only one here who
knows what a leg is worth.
And fortunately, you're not
the one in charge--he is.
And he knows that I'd
testify against him
if Hanna sues for cutting off a leg
without exhausting every option.
Give us a minute?
I know you're angry,
but please don't put
her life at risk
just to get back at me.
Really? Wow.
So this is all about you now.
You took her side against me
right after you heard
about my engagement.
Yeah. That must be it.
It's not that you're a
pathetic narcissist.
I don't love you.
So just...Accept it
and move on with your life
instead of making
everyone miserable.
That's great.
A life lesson from a
middle-aged single mom
who's dating a man-child.
Screw you.
I'm sick of making excuses for you.
I'm sick of other people
having to tiptoe around you
and make their own lives worse
while they try to keep
you from collapsing.
I'm done.
Fantastic.
Just stay away from my patient.
What are you clinging to, House?
You're gonna risk her
life just to save her leg?
Really worked out well
for you, didn't it?
What do you have in your life,
honestly?
Tell me.
I'm moving on.
Wilson is moving on.
And you...You've
got nothing, House.
Nothing.
I'm going down there,
and I'm gonna convince her
to let me cut her leg off.
If you have any decency left,
you'll just stay out of it.
No.
Dr. House promised.
If there was any other way...
It doesn't hurt right now.
I can wait.
Dr. House.
Tell her.
Hanna...
We have to amputate your leg.
No.
You said... That there was time.
There was. And it's run out.
No.
You asked me how I'd hurt my leg.
I had a blood clot,
and the muscle was dying.
And I had all these doctors
telling me I should amputate,
and I said no, and they did this...
Very risky operation.
I almost died.
But you saved your leg.
I wish I hadn't.
They cut out a chunk of muscle
about the size of my fist,
and they left me
with this mutilated,
useless thing.
I'm in pain...every day.
It changed me.
Made me a harder person,
a worse person.
And now...
Now I'm alone.
You don't want to be like me.
You got a husband who loves you.
You have friends.
You can start a family.
You have a life.
And this... This is just a leg.
Okay.
I can't put you out.
It could depress your
respiration too much.
This should take away
some of the pain.
Will it be quick?
I'll use a scalpel to
slice through the skin,
muscle, and fat.
That should go pretty fast.
Then I'll switch over
to the electric saw
when I get to the bone.
It's two bones... About
as thick as a broomstick.
Takes about as long to get through.
I'm gonna cut as close
to the concrete as I can,
save as much of your
limb as possible.
Then the orthopedic surgeons
back at the hospital
will clean you up,
have you fitted for a prosthetic.
You'll be running circles
around me in no time.
How bad will it hurt?
Like nothing you've
ever felt before.
Aah!
Hanna.
Oh...Baby.
I'm so sorry.
Shut up. You always loved my legs.
I don't care about your legs.
Baby, I love you.
I love you.
I love you. I love you.
What?
He's fallen into a coma.
Lp was clean, but...
What are his vitals?
Excuse me, officer.
What do you mean, officer?
How long has there
been a cop there?
I don't know. Ten minutes.
He was being questioned
when he fell into the coma.
Was anything else
making him nervous
or worri before his other symptoms?
He was claustrophobic
right before the bleed
and before the fever.
We told him that he
probably did fall asleep.
Was his bp spiking?
But that didn't cause
his first symptom.
Yeah, it did. All the caffeine.
We thought the problem
was in his toilet--
by that, of course,
I mean his head.
Which distracted us
from the fact
that it could have been just a clog
in his sewer pipe,
and by that, of course,
i mean his spinal cord.
And blah, blah, blah, blah.
You get the idea.
An arachnoid cyst
on his lower spine.
That's why we missed it.
He's been sitting ten hours a day.
Spiked his spinal fluid pressure.
Run a ct--
Bp's 72 over 42.  Hanna?
Hanna? I can't breathe.
I can't breathe.
Breath sounds bilaterally.
It's not another pneumothorax.
Neck veins flat.
There's no tamponade.
Damn it. I waited too long.
Hanna, you've got a
clot in your lung.
I'm gonna fix this.
Iv streptokinase.
What's happening. What's going on?
Her body won't get any oxygen
unless we can bust the clot.
This is a blood thinner.
Is she gonna be all right?
It's gonna make her bleed more.
We'll take care of that next.
It's not busting the clot.
Maybe it's her heart.
What?
It's not a clot.
It's a fat embolism.
From the amputation.
Okay. So--so what can we do?
Come on.
Do something. Please, please,
do something.
Come on, guys, do something.
Come on.
Come on. Please, come on,
do something!
Come on, do something!
Do something!
There's no way to
prevent a fat embolism.
Even if you'd done this in an O.R.,
couldn't have saved her.
You can't blame
yourself for her death.
This wasn't your fault.
That's the point!
I did everything right.
She died anyway.
Why the hell do you think that
would make me feel any better?
You shouldn't be alone right now.
You're bleeding.
I'm gonna give you a
task as an employee.
Get out of my way.
What's that?
I'm asking for some time off.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Obviously not.
♪ ♪
you going to leap across the room
and grab them out of my hand?
No.
It's your choice if you want
to go back on drugs.
Okay.
Just so you know,
I'm finding it hard
to see the downside.
You need to re-bandage
your shoulder.
Is that why you're here?
Foreman sent you?
No.
You here to yell at me again?
Well, I'm running out of ideas.
Lucas...
Oh, great.
You're feeling uncomfortable again?
Probably means you just got back
from some quickie wedding in Vegas
or you're already pregnant.
I ended it.
What?
I'm stuck, House.
I keep wanting to move forward.
I keep wanting to move on,
and I can't.
I mean, my new house,
with my new fiance,
and all I can think about is you.
I just need to know
if you and I can work.
You think I can fix myself?
I don't know.
'Cause I'm the most screwed-up
person in the world.
I know.
I love you.
I wish I didn't.
But I can't help it.
How do I know I'm
not hallucinating?
Did you take the Vicodin?
No.
Then I think we're okay.
Yeah.
www.tvsubtitles.net