Announcer:
As the riders begin lap two,
Jeff Forster's leading the pack.
This is so cool.
Did we miss anything?
They've got like 11 laps to go.
We gotta find a good place
where he can see the sign
when he goes by.
Wait up, kids!
Turn six. Come on!
[Wheezes]
[Panting]
That's it, up there.
Can you see anything?
[Wheezes]
Did you bring his inhaler?
Oh, crap.
I think it's in the car.
I'll go get it.
[Panting]
[Wheezes]
Are you okay?
- Your dad's gonna be right back.
- I can see him. He's right up front.
Honey, you're wheezing.
- Here they come!
- Go, Jeff, yeah!
You're number one!
He doesn't look so good.
2x06 - Spin
Original Airdate (FOX): 15-NOV-2005
[Yawns]
Yeah!
We need to talk.
Oh, God.
Are you pregnant?
Because I really want to
finish high school.
You have to
renew your credential.
They're good
for two more months.
Three weeks, and
the paperwork takes forever.
Your application.
Your malpractice insurance.
Criminal records check.
And you know that's gonna
take some explaining.
You know,
our relationship was way better
when we were sleeping together.
Why did we stop doing that?
Did you get married?
Yeah. Otherwise
I'd be on you like red on rice.
Rice isn't...
Oh, I get it.
You're also behind
on your dictations.
I don't do dictations.
Cameron does them.
Or somebody.
You can't have your
sole female employee
doing your clerical work,
which you'd know
if you'd attended the required
sexual harassment seminars.
Now I'm gonna pause
so you can make a crack
about harassment.
Joke killer.
Cuddy:
House.
Got a patient.
[sighs] Sorry.
Can't play anymore.
My mom's calling me.
- We just admitted a world-class cyclist.
- You've gotta fire Stacy.
Yeah, I'll get right on that.
Jeff Forster.
Respiratory arrest
at 30 miles per hour.
She's loading me up
with pointless paperwork.
Well, you're way behind
on your pointless paperwork.
- O2 stats are in the...
- She's hostile.
You know me. Hostility
makes me shrink up like a...
I can't think of
a non-sexual metaphor.
She's gonna stand over my desk
with a ruler checking my spelling.
ER checked for lung infiltrates.
Nothing there.
Professional athletes, Cuddy.
It's like watching
an old movie at 2:00 a.m.
Reliving all the classic moments.
The part where
he denies it's drugs.
The part where the good guys
ride in tests a'blazing,
prove that it is drugs.
Oscar clip. He can't imagine
how they got into his body.
It's so familiar,
so comforting.
She can't handle
working with me.
[Elevator dings]
Oh, right. Yeah.
She's still got a thing to you,
making it impossible for her to deal.
Makes perfect sense.
Except for the pronouns.
Anyway, thanks for
getting me out of that meeting.
He's not denying the drugs.
I'm thinking
he's actually sick.
- Jeff Forster, this is...
- I'm a doctor.
You're a sick person.
And you...are a loved one.
Actually, manager.
We've been together
for seven years.
So what's the drug du jour
on the bike circuit these days?
Still erythropoietin?
Or you guys just
chugging battery acid?
There's no way
I'd touch EPO. [Gasps (<)]
Too many guys
stroking out (<) and dying.
Damn!
Ten bucks for the ticket,
six for the popcorn.
I do straight blood doping.
Plot twist.
That's a very
daring confession.
We've got
confidentiality, right?
Assuming
I'm more ethical
than your client.
So, injecting yourself
with donor red blood cells
for fun and profit.
Any other tricks
up your sleeve?
Well, nothing
much recently. (<)
I'm in town for a charity ride,
so it didn't matter if I won. (<)
The kids just needed to see me.
If you go slower,
they see you longer.
Let's say that our health
could be affected by things
we did before last Friday.
[Gasps (<)] Well...
Um, I usually sleep
in a hyperbaric chamber. (<)
I've been pumping up
electrolytes with an IV drip.
Anabolic herbal supplements,
amphetamines, (<) and diuretics.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But why would you be sick?
I know that
doping has risks. (<)
it's outside the rules. (<)
But I do what I have to
to kick ass (<) at my job. (<)
Don't you?
Dr. House is a firm believer
in good old-fashioned hard work.
Ahhh.
This guy doesn't even get sick
like a regular person.
Instead of a list of symptoms
and no cause, we have a list of
possible causes for one symptom.
Chase:
Is the symptom death?
Respiratory distress.
And insanity doesn't cause it.
I looked it up.
It's the doping.
Injecting extra red cells
boosts your endurance level,
but it also thickens your blood.
Thick blood equals clots
equals respiratory distress.
Not with a
clean spiral chest CT.
Guy's sleeping
in an hyperbaric chamber.
Over-oxygenation can cause
cell damage, and if the cells
in the lungs are damaged...
That'd cause pulmonary edema,
which he doesn't have.
The supplements
he's been taking contain yohimbe,
which can cause nerve paralysis.
Tox screen was normal.
All the tests were normal.
There's no clot, no edema,
and yet he still can't breathe.
So there's something
in here that we can't see.
Oh. Air.
Come to papa.
This guy's been
injecting himself
how many times a day?
All it'd take is
one slip of the needle
to cause an air embolus.
So air is keeping him
from breathing air.
Let's go with that
for the irony.
Get a VQ scan and
check his veins for bubbles.
Xenon 133.
It's just radioactive
enough for us to track
the air moving through your lungs.
My accident on the news?
Yeah. You made
plays of the week.
Few more of those and cycling
will be as popular as NASCAR.
We inject similar stuff
into your blood so
we can watch it circulate.
Now if you accidentally
injected a bubble, we'll see
good air flow but poor blood flow.
- Un-huh. I'm careful, man.
- [Foreman laughs]
With all due respect, man, ...
I doubt there's
anything wrong with you
that you didn't do to yourself.
There's this kid in oncology.
She's got a picture of Jeff
above her bed.
Mickey Mantle
was an alcoholic.
Cameron:
At least he hit his own home runs.
He didn't physically alter himself.
We take drugs to help us
fall asleep, to stay awake.
We don't make careers out of
who can stay awake the longest.
Really? Ever been to, oh,
I don't know, med school?
Uh, guys, he plays a game
for a living. Who cares?
You don't even like sports.
He's making
millions of dollars
ripping off fans.
Anyone who thinks
they should pay a guy money
because he can throw a ball
really far, or pedal really fast
deserves to be ripped off.
Yeah, stupid, stupid kids.
I've got an uncle.
He can spit a cherry pit 50 yards.
He's working part-time
at a lube shop. Life isn't fair.
[Scanner bleeps and stops]
Maybe it is.
Chase:
You were right.
Now there went
three wasted words.
There is a bubble in his lung.
We should do a
Swan-Ganz catheterization.
I love when you do
both sides of the conversation.
It's like white noise.
It's very peaceful.
Is there a light somewhere
that goes on when I have food?
Green for food,
orange for beverages,
red for impure thoughts.
That bulb burns out
every two weeks.
How's your biker?
Pumped an air bubble
into a vein in his lung.
The things people do.
Doping. Vicodin.
Hey. You're talking
about me, aren't you?
I'm just trying to function.
He's trying to win himself
some little yellow jerseys.
- Uh-oh.
- What?
Trouble in paradise,
two o'clock.
Your two o'clock
or my two o'clock?
There.
She seems perfectly happy.
Obviously, they huddled in the hall
and worked up this circus act
on the off-chance you'd be in here.
She was unbelievably
pissy three hours ago.
Hmm. Pissy with you.
Happy with her husband.
Yes, there could only be
one possible explanation for that.
When she's angry,
she gets sarcastic.
When's she annoyed,
she's funny.
But when she's frustrated,
she gets pissy.
Yes, yes, I'm with you so far.
She's miserable with Mark
because he's not me.
So she's gotta make me not me,
so she makes my professional life
miserable. If I can't do my job...
You really, really
need to get some.
Oh, I get some "some"
all the time.
That's why I always
need to borrow some money.
Stacy:
Hi, James.
Greg.
Gotten to that paperwork?
- I've been pissy.
- Pardon me?
I've been busy.
When you save someone's life,
they owe you forever.
You're right. Take Stacy.
Oh, wait. She'd probably
just leave you all over again.
House:
How's your recovery going?
Gotten around to
the small muscles yet?
It's not the size of the muscle.
It's where you get to put it.
My goodness. It's like watching
Oscar Wilde and Noel Coward
in the third grade.
Excuse us.
How awkward was that?
What's he doing here anyway?
He's got physio Tuesdays and Fridays.
Uh, Mark is in group therapy
for people coping with disability.
He was thinking about
developing a drug addiction,
but that would be stupid.
Hey, you're...you again.
Not gonna make some joke
about Mark being in therapy?
What's there to say?
He's doing the responsible thing.
I'm sure he's got
a lot to deal with.
You're making me nervous.
[Moira on phone]
Every time an athlete goes down,
you guys assume it's drugs.
Look, the doctors say
its probably acid reflux.
Yeah, look, call me tomorrow.
There's a good chance
he'll be released. Okay. Bye-bye.
[Hangs up]
So is this fixing him?
If his acid reflux isn't
worse than we thought, yeah.
I've gotta be
in Spain in (<) four days.
Shouldn't be a problem.
Great.
If I can just find the little bugger,
I should be able to suck it out.
Hmm. My legs feel weak.
You're under mild
sedation for the test.
It'll wear off.
[Monitor blips]
There it is.
Ah. Got it.
Oh, fantastic.
I'll pack his things.
Not yet. I want to monitor him
for a couple of hours.
Make sure he's okay.
Give him time to
sign a picture for me.
Maybe even a jersey.
"To Dr. Chase,
I owe you everything."
It doesn't have to
be that personal.
Oh. Not too many eBay shoppers
named Dr. Chase, huh? [Laughs]
Still trying to unload
the Barbara Walters spit cup.
Here you go.
Seriously, anything's fine.
Jeff?
Chase:
You all right?
Jeff, can you swallow?
Hosue:
What makes a guy
start drooling?
Chase, were you
wearing your short shorts?
Muscle fatigue
in his neck and jaw.
He's obviously got something
worse than an air embolus.
Why?
Because you don't
drool from your lungs.
Maybe the problem's
not the embolus itself.
Maybe it's the treatment.
Maybe you hit a nerve.
Literally.
The embolectomy was clean.
His legs were tired too.
I thought it was from
the sedation, but if not,
it means he's got
something systemic.
Which means
it would have nothing to do with
the stunts he's been pulling.
Lupus or polymyositis.
It explains the
progressive muscle weakness.
- It could be ALS.
- He's too young for that.
- Some type of muscular dystrophy?
- He's too old for that.
So what would be
just right, Goldilocks?
House:
Full blood workup,
including ANA for lupus.
And get a muscle biopsy.
Find out if we're talking
myopathy or neuropathy.
I'm late for my session.
Session?
It's all a part of the process.
- You get angry and then you get...
- Yeah, I'm right on schedule.
So when am I gonna be done?
No, I need to know because
I've got plans to make. I mean...
when can I safely
book a game of squash?
Mark:
When am I gonna
stop being angry?
Not today.
I've come for the healing.
Dr. Harper,
as you know, I, uh...Ahem.
I have a bum leg.
What you don't know is
I'm upset about it.
I need to talk.
You know House.
You know we have a history.
You've been telling me
for years that I should come by.
Here I am. Hi, guys.
Dr. Harper:
Got a Thursday group.
Poker night.
Monday morning?
Book club.
Well, look, if it's a problem,
I'll just go deal
with my rage privately.
Wait.
If you two could resolve
this tension, you could
really help each other.
I'm tired of fighting.
[Scoffs]
So either I say yes
or I'm the jerk?
Oh, God, I know that feeling.
I took the muscle specimen
from Jeff's thigh.
I figured that's where
we'd have the best chance
at finding something.
And the most painful
place to cut into.
I assume that's caffeine-free.
Wouldn't want to be artificially
boosting your performance.
Don't start her up again.
Caffeine's legal.
All about the rules, eh?
It's a bike race.
A completely arbitrary set of rules that
everyone complies with for no other reason
than that some committee says that they should.
- Huh.
- But that's the point.
That's what the game is.
So if you break an arbitrary rule,
Cameron damns you to hell,
but if you break a rule
that actually has a reason,
that's designed to protect people,
Cameron develops a crazy crush on you.
House doesn't pretend to
be some golden boy.
He does it to help people,
not to glorify himself.
So why don't you report Jeff
to the biking authorities?
Um, ethics.
Well, you wouldn't be
doing it to glorify yourself.
You'd just be trying to
make a better world.
Mark:
At least you can still
get around on your own.
Yeah, I know.
But you're starting to walk.
You're gonna get better.
Mark:
You have a job,
a way to be productive.
You have a wife.
Which gives greater meaning?
[Taps his cane 3 times]
A wife could make
things harder, too, I suppose.
This isn't about Stacy.
When it happened to me,
Stacy was great.
She kept telling me
not to rush it.
But I never believed her.
She means it.
I know, but...
Stacy...She didn't
have to wait, right?
And you know
she feels it too.
Means more time at work,
means more satisfaction from work.
She didn't get married
to be a nursemaid.
She wants a man.
Oh! [Scoffs]
How the hell could she have loved
a manipulative son of a bitch like you?
That's an interesting question.
Maybe she was attracted
to different things in the two of us.
She left YOU.
Then why was she
with me to begin with?
She made a mistake.
Maybe it's that simple.
Or maybe she saw something in me,
something she doesn't get from you.
- I'm not an ass.
- Maybe she wanted an ass.
She obviously did once.
Either he goes or I go.
You think
that's the kind of thing
you can just turn off?
Get him out of here!
Dr. House,
cancel your book group.
You're coming on Mondays.
Here's my new theory.
The drooling's
another competitive edge.
Nobody can drive behind him.
Road gets slick. He's the
only one not racing in the rain.
He can barely
move his arms or legs.
[Sighs] Paralysis?
No, just general weakness.
Muscle biopsy is
negative for polymyositis.
And ALS.
And muscular dystrophy.
Foreman:
ANA for lupus also negative.
Cameron:
Maybe his bike shorts
were just on too tight.
So by your rationale,
House shouldn't use a cane.
He should just drag his bum leg
around as God intended?
House has a handicap.
All he's aiming for is normality.
Chase:
And who decides what's normal?
What if we find a drug that
makes people live 20 years longer?
Should we ban that
because it's not normal?
Jeff doesn't want normal.
He wants super powers.
So why is he normal?
Oh, God. You too?
He's shooting
for extraordinary.
So why is everything so ordinary?
I mean, this guy's breathing,
drinking, and injecting himself
with everything he can find
to amp up his body chemistry,
and yet every test is normal.
He's artificially
raising his red blood count,
so why isn't it raised?
Maybe his count is raised.
Maybe what's normal for us
is out of whack for him.
Can't slip anything by you.
Well, if that's true,
his white cells are up too,
which would point to
some kind of infection.
Muscle weakness, exhaustion.
He could have encephalitis.
That's kind of a long shot.
Yeah. But it's been over an hour
since we poked the patient
with something sharp, so...
get a lumbar puncture and
order broad-spectrum antibiotics.
[On phone]
No, it's not about judging.
It's just that on a dating service
you should post a photo.
I have to go.
- I'm so sorry to bother you.
- No, not a problem. I was just, uh...
- ...accounting.
- I'm Jeff Forster's manager.
He's been here a whole day
and it doesn't seem like
we're any closer to a diagnosis.
Jeff Forster.
A whole day, huh?
Mm-hmm. I was just wondering
if I could help speed things up.
Your client's had
a muscle biopsy,
a full blood workup,
and he's scheduled
for a lumbar puncture
at 10:00 a.m. tomorrow.
Jeff is in the Lucas Wing.
If Mr. Lucas showed up
needing a lumbar puncture,
would he have to wait
until tomorrow?
Mr. Lucas is dead.
Good. Then there's an opening.
Jeff is used to doing whatever
he has to to be first, isn't he?
It's been very
lucrative for him.
He feels it's important that
he give something back.
I hear you've been
raising funds for your
nuclear medicine department.
Or whatever.
Thank you, guys,
for working so late.
[Wheezes]
Glad to be here.
The lumbar puncture will tell us
what kind of infection you've got.
In the meantime,
we're administering antibiotics.
Do you like being a hero?
[Harsh breath (>)]
It's a living.
You don't feel a
sense of responsibility?
There's kids out there
that worship you.
When I was a rookie (>)
on the tour, (>)
I got a letter from a guy
in Wisconsin (>)
who wanted me to
send a note to his son. (>)
Said he worshipped me. (>)
You know
what "worship" means?
(>) I looked it up.
It means to love...
unquestioningly and uncritically. (>)
So the kid doesn't
even know me, (>)
but he loves me (>)
unquestioningly (>)
and uncritically.
So you decided to
take advantage of that.
What should I have done? (>)
"Dear sir, (>) "I'm just a guy (>)
who rides a bike (>) pretty good. (>)
You and your kid are (>)
out of your minds"? (>)
(>) My arms feel funny.
[labored breathing and choking]
[Monitor starts beeping]
Foreman:
His SATs are dropping.
He's in respiratory arrest.
He can't be.
We fixed that.
Apparently not.
House:
So glad we cured
his respiratory arrest.
Freed him up to
develop respiratory arrest.
Foreman:
LP was negative
for encephalitis.
The white count's still the same,
but the red count's fallen to 29%.
What was my theory
yesterday?
That I screwed up
the embolectomy.
We'll get a chest x-ray to check.
I didn't screw up.
Why would you...
How can you be so petty,
Chase? He's down a quart.
Either he's losing blood
because you nicked something,
or he's just not producing blood,
in which place we're talking...
acute anemia combined
with a muscular disorder.
Paraneoplastic syndrome?
Either you screwed up
or he's got cancer.
I think I should
start smoking again.
You want a medical opinion
supporting that decision?
The symptoms started
as soon as I quit.
Symptoms meaning...
diarrhea.
A lot of diarrhea.
Ten or twelve times a day.
It's really embarrassing.
I'm a flight attendant and...
[Smack!]
On the upside,
my hiccups are gone.
You went to his group.
You were the one who was all,
"Greg, you need to
confront your feelings."
[Smacks again]
That was five years ago.
Well, I've been pissy.
Fine. You don't want help.
Does that mean
nobody should get it?
Mark's looking for help
because, what?, he's resentful?
Overwhelmed?
I'm asking because I care.
Not about him.
You still want to jump me,
so you don't care whose marriage...
Listen, I can get my rocks off
any time I want.
What I don't seem to be able to do
is my job without you
hanging over my shoulder.
[Resigned sigh]
How many packs?
A bit over one a day, but
they were lights and I quit.
You used to go out with her?
Yeah. What was I thinking?
I'm talking about the gum
you're chewing to replace
smoking as an oral fixation.
How many packs?
Six, maybe seven.
Stacy:
I'm trying to protect you.
Cuddy and I may be the only people
stopping you from jumping off a cliff...
- You're pissy.
- No, I am angry.
Pissy. You get pissy
when you're frustrated.
Shut up.
Okay, I'm wrong.
This is unbelievably
difficult for Mark,
which you should know.
Which you should
be able to summon up
some level of empathy for.
Right. The crippled boys.
We should start a band.
I have a good thing with Mark.
We are handling this
the best way we know how.
And none of this has
anything to do with me?
No, nothing. Except that
you can't or won't just let it go.
Let it go.
[Smack!]
You're being poisoned.
By gum?
Sugarless gum uses
sorbitol as a sweetener.
We use sorbitol
as a laxative.
Moira:
This'll tell you if he's got
cancer in his blood?
If he does, we'll see
abnormal cells in the marrow.
How long will the test take?
I'll get them in
as soon as I can.
And if doesn't have cancer,
what else could it be?
It's possible
some damage was done during
one of the tests we gave him.
So either one of your doctors
screwed up a simple procedure,
or he's got cancer.
We can't know anything for sure
until the biopsy comes back.
It stings, I know.
No, he wants the tube out.
Can't do that, Jeff.
Wilson:
If you want to say something,
you've got to write it down.
Okay?
Here.
[ Did I do this to myself ? ]
If it's cancer, it's possible.
There's no way to know for sure.
Phone not working?
One of the morgue attendants
asked me to bring this to you.
I wonder why
they're calling me.
Yeah, me too actually.
I was wondering why the Times
was returning your call.
You a doctor or
the bicycle police?
He's cheating.
He shouldn't get away with it.
[Sighs]
Have you actually
told them anything yet?
You worried
about the precedent?
I'm worried about you.
You gonna turn me in?
No.
He's made a mistake.
Revealing the truth
doesn't undo it.
Kids love him and
he's not who they think he is.
It's not right.
Who cares if he's
what he says he is?
Who the hell is?
If love's based on lies,
does that mean
it's not a real feeling?
Doesn't bring
the same pleasure?
Are we still talking
about the patient?
Have you ever cheated?
Well, I have.
You want to punish him,
good for you.
But you can't do it
without punishing the
people who love him.
Is that you justified
lying to you wives?
I always told them.
Foreman:
Well, he's negative for bleeds.
Congratulations, Chase.
It's cancer.
Clean him up and
let oncology have him.
Hosue:
It's their party now.
He doesn't have cancer.
Biopsy shows he's got
pure red cell aplasia.
There's no way PRCA could
manifest so suddenly.
Unless it's drug-induced.
He's lying about not being on EPO.
Why would he lie?
What does it matter?
People lie
for thousands of reasons,
but there's always a reason.
Philosophically interesting,
medically irrelevant.
Unless he's not lying.
[Sighs]
You've got a leak.
The press is all over
the Jeff Forster story.
On the off-chance that
one of you was stupid enough to
call from your own office,
I'm pulling your phone records.
Including your cell phones.
I assume if I point out the fact
that you have no right to do that
you'll interpret that as a sign of guilt.
Wilson's chatty.
House:
Plus he's got two ex-wives to support.
You want me to tell him he's fired?
Until we figure out
who's behind this,
I'm sitting in with you guys.
You have the ethics
of a four-year-old.
I'm gonna treat you like one.
How am I supposed to
practice medicine with a lawyer
sitting on my shoulder?
Responsibly.
You know I can't do that.
Cameron.
I'm not the leak.
Somebody once told me
that everybody lies.
And since you're the only people
who know he has cancer...
He doesn't have cancer.
Cuddy: The point is
you're his medical team.
He's threatening to sue.
Why would Cameron leak cancer?
How does cancer
make the guy look bad?
He's on EPO.
Your anemia is caused by
pure red blood cell aplasia.
This is gonna hurt,
but we've gotta talk.
What the hell are you doing?
He'll be fine. Sort of.
[Caughs]
I just don't have time to
watch him write out answers.
PRCA comes in two varieties.
Chronic and acute.
Since it came on fast,
you have the acute version.
He doesn't have cancer.
Is the good news.
The bad new is...
Pants are on fire.
Acute PRCA is caused by drugs.
Most commonly, EPO.
Ready, and...action!
But I haven't used EPO.
[Sighs] Okay.
But this time with more anger.
Remember, this guy's
accusing you of cheating.
I haven't used that stuff. (<)
Oh! Mwah!
I believed it.
It was simple. It was pure.
Did you believe it?
I guess
it's silly to cast someone
after the first audition.
Why don't you do a reading?
Give me that.
He doesn't do EPO.
Hmm. What did you think?
I mean, it's a different way to go,
but I don't know, I just didn't buy it.
Does she handle
any of your injections?
You think I'm giving it to him?
Test him.
Gee. That's a great idea.
I sure hope that
EPO's not one of those drugs
that's undetectable after six hours.
Hey, you know
what we can test for?
Phone calls.
Take her cell phone,
push the redial button.
Even money says you'll be
connected to the newspaper
that leaked your cancer story.
Okay.
Okay, I should've told you.
It's not just
about the races, Jeff.
It's about your image. Okay?
If you come back from cancer,
those sponsors will be all over you.
Okay, so I messed up.
Okay? But I did not give you EPO.
That stuff could kill me.
Meh meh meh meh.
House:
Come on, give her a break.
She's only doing what she
has to do to advance her career.
Don't you have that
tattooed on your tushie?
I would never do
anything to hurt you.
House:
Who are you gonna believe?
The manager
you've trusted for years?
Pff! I've been to college.
You're fired.
Okay.
You're basing this whole
diagnosis, everything,
on the idea that I was
slipping him illegal drugs.
Huh.
You're gonna kill him.
If Dr. House is so sure,
why do you need to stay?
He's a very cautious man.
You're breathing's better.
Let the prednisone do its job.
Get some sleep.
[Wheezing]
Jeff?
[Monitor starts beeping]
His red blood cell count
plummeted to 16%.
He passed out,
had to be resuscitated,
and he still can't move his legs.
That's not possible.
The drugs should be
flushing out of his system.
Can't leave
if they don't exist.
The EPO use explains
every one of his symptoms.
He's been lying and cheating,
and now it's coming back to bite him.
The only problem with that theory is
it's based on the assumption that
the universe is a just place.
If it were, then
his poor manager wouldn't
have been fired for no reason.
- Lambert-Eaton.
- His chest was clear.
Chase: So we run
an electromyography test.
Cameron:
You're still not
explaining the PRCA.
What's his red count now?
I had to give him
a blood transfusion.
He's back around 30.
He needed a transfusion?
Well, he was losing blood, so
I thought maybe he needed blood.
[Stirring his coffee]
Go forth and scan his neck.
His neck?
Or repeat everything
I say in question form.
She came into the clinic
and yelled at me.
Then she left,
then she came back
and yelled some more.
Hmm. Yelling.
That might be a clue.
Well, I know
what the yelling means.
It's the coming and going
I find interesting.
- It's not rational.
- Anger's not rational.
Some anger is.
She could've pulled me aside,
screamed at my privately.
Her beef is simple
and well-founded.
But she was out of control.
You're having fun, aren't you?
She's in my face.
I need to know why.
- Professional reasons.
- Oh. Why else?
Do you really think
this is going to end well?
For anyone?
After this,
let's scan some other
total random body parts.
50 bucks says
we find something.
Find what?
Don't have a clue. We on?
No way.
No. We'll find something.
Chase:
We found a thymoma.
Foreman:
How'd you know
to look in his neck?
Thymomas usually
present in the chest.
I knew it wasn't
in his chest.
All we've done
since he checked in is
look at his chest.
- Well, all the more reason not to think...
- There are two types of PRCA.
Acute comes on suddenly.
Chronic takes its time.
We all thought
Jeff's was acute because
it happened right in front of us,
but what if it had been there
for months? Maybe years?
There's no way.
It would've kept him
from racing.
With that kind of anemia,
he would've needed constant...
Blood transfusions.
Which he was getting in
convenient blood doping form.
[Elevator dings]
He was treating himself
without even knowing it.
Up to half of patients with
chronic PRCA have a thymoma,
and up to half the patients
with a thymoma...
I've always wanted to do this.
I'm not getting any better. (>)
Does that mean I'm...(>)
Ow.
You are healed.
Rise and walk.
Are you insane?
In the Bible, they just say,
"Yes, Lord," and then
start right in on the praising.
First you tell me
I've got cancer, (>)
and then you tell me
that my manager...
Huh!
Huh, huh!
What did you do?
No. What do you do, Lord?
Thymoma is a tumor
on the thymus gland.
He's a bit a wimp, but
he hangs with the tough guys.
PRCA and an auto-immune disease
called myasthenia gravis.
MG causes muscle fatigue,
including respiratory problems
and difficulty swallowing.
Oh. And it can
hit you that fast?
The treatment for PRCA
is blood transfusions.
The treatment
for MG is hyperbaria.
You were doing both as part
of your regular freak show.
When you took a break,
everything went to hell.
Which is not an
uncommon reaction to Jersey.
So...
The whole thing
with my manager.
Oops. No.
No EPO.
This has nothing to do
with anything you did.
You can let her know
she's in the clear.
I could. Or...
Ten perfect of a Nike contract
is a hell of a lot of cash.
God.
You don't need your thymus.
We take it out.
Everything else is manageable.
Manageable? I thought
you just cured me.
Un-uh. This is
just diagnostic.
Tensilon erases the symptoms
of MG for five or six minutes.
[Starts gasping again]
Sometimes less.
This is exactly why
I created nurses.
Clean up on aisle three!
If you've come to search my office,
you should wait ten minutes.
I'll be out of your hair.
Here. Start with my purse.
Just save me some mints.
What do you want to know?
My sex life with Mark?
My guilt over
crippling your damn leg?
Or are you just here to gloat
because you weren't the leak?
I want to apologize.
Maybe I've...
been punishing you
for a little too long.
And maybe
you've been punishing me.
If we're gonna work together,
I need to know.
Do you hate me
or do you love me?
Either way, I think
we've got a problem.
I hate you.
And I love you.
And I love Mark.
And you don't hate him.
No.
So what do we do?
We deal with each other.
Hmph. Right.
That plans been
working great so far.
It'll get better.
It'll get easier.
Why?
I don't know. That's
what my therapist tells me.
[On TV] In the professional cycling world,
we are subject to what seems like
constant witch hunts and finger pointing.
But I want to thank Dr. House
and the excellent medical team
here at Princeton Plainsboro.
My hope is that
this diagnosis will put to rest
any rumors that I would ever use...
He needs blood transfusions
every two weeks, which means
he can dope all he wants.
He's a got a doctor's pass.
It's medicinal.
He got away with it.
Mm-hmm.
He cheated and won a game.
Life's more complicated than
who gets to the finish line first.
I fell in love with
my husband's best friend.
Near the end, I was
at the hospital every day,
and Joe would
come by after work.
We'd go for walks and try to
talk each other through it.
We kind of clung
on to each other.
My wife...
wasn't dying.
She wasn't even sick.
Everything was fine.
I met someone who...Ahem.
Made me feel...funny.
Good.
And I didn't want to
let that feeling go.
What happened to you...
How can anyone
go through that alone?
You can't control your emotions.
No.
Just your actions.
You didn't do it, did you?
You didn't sleep with him.
I couldn't have
lived with myself.
You'd be surprised
what you can live with.
Hey.
I need you to open a door.
Not allowed.
Yeah, I was having therapy
in here today, and I left my cane.
Sorry.
Dude...
I'm crippled.
["None Of Us Are Free"
by Solomon Burke]
# Well, you'd better listen
my sisters and brothers #
# 'Cause if you do you can hear #
# There are voices still calling #
# Across the years #
# And they're all crying
across the ocean #
# And they're crying
across the land #
# And they will until we all
come to understand #
# That none of us are free #
# None of us are free #
# None of us are free
if one of us is chained #
# None of us are free #
# And there are people
still in darkness #
# And they just
can't see the light #
# If we don't say it's wrong
then that says it's right #
# None of us are free #
# None of us are free
if one of us is chained #
# None of us are free #
# None of us are free
if one of us is chained #
# None of us are free  #
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : Vaccine
www.tvsubtitles.net