Welcome! I'm here for illuding!
What is *** and what is magic?
This is what you've wanted.
Now I will astound you!
As you see there's
nothing up my sleeves.
And this hat...
just an ordinary old hat.
Watch as I wave
three times above the hat,
and whisper the magic words.
And now...
[Laughter and aplause]
Mom it's not working!
It's ripped!
It's okay baby,
it's just a little tear.
Hurry up, mom!
What are you so worried about?
Sally's going to make fun of us.
Sally Ayerson?
She said her mom bought
her dress at Bloomingdales.
You had to make ours.
We're going to look stupid!
Do you girls remember that music
we were listening to yesterday?
That lady who sang about respect?
Retha?
Aretha. That's right.
Do you think she had lots of money
growing up in Detroit?
What's Detroit?
It's a city. The point is that
she's one of the best singers ever.
If Sally's mean to you again
I'm just going to have to
key her daddy's new convertible.
Do you know what that means?
Good.
Piano intro for
"Little Bitty Pretty One"
# Mmmm m m mm #
# Wow wow wo wo wow #
# Little bitty pretty one #
# Come on and talk to me #
# Lovey dovey dovey one #
# Come and sit down on my knee #
# Wow wow wo wo wow #
Ahhh!
[Starts crying out in pain]
YeeeAhhhh!
Ahhhhhhh!
2x08 - The Mistake
Original Airdate (FOX): 29-NOV-2005
[Overhead speaker is calling for Dr. Lau]
"Dr. Lau, 2826. Dr. Lau, 2826."
- Hey.
Did you speak to
Chase and House yet?
The disciplinary hearing.
The McGinley case.
That's not for two weeks.
Tomorrow.
Scheduling disaster,
you don't want to hear it.
You gotta get the boys okay
to move the hearing up,
and you gotta do that
whole legal advice thing.
- Will you ask someone else?
- I'm asking you.
Let me work with Chase.
House should have separate counsel.
Stop looking for
whatever you're looking for.
For the last month, House has been
crowing that you can't work with him
because you're just swooning in love.
There is nothing approaching love
in what I feel about him right now.
Well if you can't work with him,
it amounts to the same thing.
[Sighs]
We had a fight. It's awkward.
Why not use another lawyer?
Because 40% of our lawsuits
last year were about House.
You can't work with him,
you can't work here.
House:
She's over-reacting.
Wilson:
You snuck into her shrink's office
and read her private file.
When Nixon did that,
he got impeached.
So you're saying
I'm not allowed to have oral sex
with an intern either?
- Yes!
- And yes.
The file got me
on the floor of her attic
with her pouring out her soul.
The only thing I did wrong
was get caught.
Stacy:
Where's Chase?
He's too busy to service you
until after work.
House:
I got a couple of minutes though.
Feel free to
say something like
"what'll we do with
the time left over?"
Or you could just stew.
That works as well.
She stews
before she gets violent.
This one says you're okay with
moving the disciplinary hearing
to tomorrow.
This one says I've advised you
of your legal rights.
Uh huh, any legal rights
I should know about?
Nope.
[Tosses her pen on to the table]
Great.
And you thought
this was going to be awkward.
You shouldn't sign it.
Postponing is almost always
the smart thing to do.
Tempers cool, memories fade.
- They rule on me it's done, right?
- Yeah, but...
Then let's get it over with.
- Have you ever done
a peer review before?
- No.
Good.
Here's a misnomer,
these are your bosses.
This will cost you
some money, some privileges,
or it could cost you your career.
All I can tell them is what happened.
There's an objective reality
to what happened and that
committee is never going to know it.
All they're going to know is
what they picture happened,
which depends a little
on what you tell them,
and a whole lot...
on HOW you tell them.
May 11th.
- Patient presented to the clinic...
- What's her name?
- It's in the file.
- Do you know it?
Then use it.
Kayla presented to the clinic
with multiple joint and stomach pain.
Chase:
Dr. Foreman was called in
for a neurological consult.
Sam:
What's the point of this, man?
Checking your sister's
cerebral coordination.
The thing is in her leg
and her stomach.
Wait in the clinic for six hours
so she can play patty cake?
She could have gone
to the ER last night.
Oh yeah?
You wanna come over
and babysit her kids?
Stacy:
Ok, patient comes from
a family of jerks, I get it.
Can you stick to the medicine?
Something wrong?
Chase:
There was some uveitis.
Stacy:
Meaning?
Her iris?
The colour part of her eye
was inflamed.
Meaning?
Worst case, blindness.
But there was an upside.
It was weird enough
to get House interested.
Young woman, joint pain.
Gonorrhea is a possibility.
It's probably articular.
Maybe rheumatoid.
It's typically small joints,
it's her knee.
Takayasu's arthritis.
Get a sed rate
and serologies.
Child proof.
How many kids are
hopped up on vicodin?
Gimme.
Right.
Like I'd ever get it back.
Chase.
Stacy:
Don't care about the vicodin.
[Pop!]
Might not just be her arteries,
could be all her blood vessels.
Vasculitis,
with stomach pain,
so... Bichette's.
No, she'd have oral sores.
Or genital.
Go find them.
I thought
she was Foreman's patient,
why did you do the exam?
Foreman:
She'd have oral sores.
House:
Or genital. Go find them.
Woah woah Foreman...
Chase can handle the pelvic.
Any pain?
Is it bad?
This will go a little easier
if you talk to me.
I'm sorry.
I umm...
I just really hate hospitals.
When I was 12,
had my tonsils out.
Got to skip school,
lots of ice cream,
made me want to be a doctor.
My mom... died
when I was 8 so...
I spent months
at Princeton General.
She died of TT's?
Your mom?
Bottles stashed around the house?
Mood swings? That whole deal?
You've been there?
My mom. Dad left,
mom crawled inside a bottle.
Made for a great Year 12
of high school.
You ok with your dad now?
No.
Does your dad have
anything to do with this story?
No, it's just...
Okay, I get it,
the two of you bonded, which is why
you probably haven't been sued.
Patients never sue doctors they like. But keep it brief, ok?
The panel doesn't like to think
they're being manipulated
when they're being manipulated.
She had some ulceration.
Confirming Bichette's?
I gave her some
prednisone, an antacid
and I ran a pathogy test on her arm,
takes 24 hours to confirm.
Told her any doctor could check it out.
You didn't make an appointment?
Nope. She just showed up.
[On the phone]
Uh huh.
Dr. Chase.
Hi.
All right, let's take a look.
Okay, those little pustules
means it's positive.
Talk to Nurse Previn,
get an appointment with
Dr. Broston in rheumatology.
Bichette's is very treatable. You're going to be fine.
Okay. Thanks.
And you were just chatting
on the phone to someone and
she just happened to run into you.
That's what happened.
No appointment?
No real examination?
Just gave her the test results.
So, lower standard of care,
you really couldn't be expected to
notice there was anything else wrong.
We didn't even go
into an exam room.
As your lawyer,
I can't stop you from lying,
I can't even be in the room,
but I would be remiss
if I didn't prep you until I'm better.
You wrote her a prescription,
which means there was an examination.
What really happened?
I was on the phone.
Dr. Chase?
Hi.
Kayla. I'm here
for the test... my arm?
Oh. Oh yeah... umm, okay.
It's positive. Talk to Nurse Previn,
get an appointment with
Dr. Broston in rheumatology.
I took that medicine
you gave me,  but
my stomach still hurts.
Bichette's can be stronger
than we thought, or it could be
reflux from the prednisone.
This is a stronger antacid.
Doctor...
Yes?
Nothing.
You didn't ask her anything
about the stomach pain?
I made one little mistake.
As little mistakes go,
that was a biggie.
She's only advising Chase?
Not you?
Well what's the committee
going to do to me?
I haven't even met this patient.
Your disdain for human interaction
doesn't exculpate you, it inculpates you.
Besides the charts,
you're responsible for
everything Chase does.
Which is why
this doesn't matter.
She protects Chase,
she protects me.
Unless her advice to Chase is
to make a deal and give you up.
[Poorly mimics Chase]
"I'm so sorry, if only
Dr. House had paid attention,
he'd never even met her,
he never does."
Chase loves me.
And isn't Turkish.
Cameron loves you.
Chase loves his job.
You really think
Stacy hates me that much?
I think right now
she hates you
more than enough.
You think
emotion only affects
doctor's judgments?
Everything stems
from that one interaction,
they're going to slam you on it.
Were you distracted,
your problem.
Overworked,
that's their problem.
Forgetful, yours, lazy...
I just figured
the stomach pain
was the Bichette's.
Any doctor would have
thought the same.
Then why did you call her
an hour after she left the clinic?
Nurse Previn said you asked her
to have Kayla come back in.
The way she hesitated
I thought she might have
had a doorknob question.
Patient comes in,
says he's got a sniffly nose,
you examine him for 10 minutes right?
Then you're leaving,
hand on the doorknob, and he says
"oh yeah and my penis has turned green".
Embarrassing question,
only important when
patient saves it for last,
so you knew
she was about to ask
the most important question...
and you left.
No. I didn't.
I figured it out later.
What changed?
Nothing.
Bad answer.
I wasn't thinking clearly at first.
Worst answer.
What was her doorknob question?
I figured it might be
blood in her stool,
which could indicate
a bleeding ulcer.
Talk to me.
35-yr-old female vomiting
massive amounts of blood.
LOC at work,
BP 80 over 20, heart rate 140.
Push flows?
3 litres in the field,
and we're boosting
another one right now.
It's gotta be a bleeding ulcer, doc.
Co-worker says that she's been
eating ibuprofens like candy.
I thought she had Bichette's.
1, 2, 3.
Chase:
I'm in her stomach.
There's too much blood, I can't see.
She burst an artery?
No, there.
Bubbling, just a bad ulcer.
Cauterizing.
- Can't see, use more saline.
- Hold on!
Okay.
[Sighs] Looks good.
Bleeding ulcer. We got it.
She was fine 2 hours ago.
[Alarms start beeping]
Systolic BP's 70.
House:
Where's the ulcer?
It's brown. I cauterized it.
It must be something else.
Chase: There.
Foreman: Second ulcer?
Not anymore.
It perforated.
Get her to an OR!
The surgeons were able to
suture the perforation.
But the contents
of the patient's ...
Kayla's stomach had
spilled into her body.
She got septic.
Then the infection
lowers her blood pressure...
50 over *** at one point.
It damaged
her liver and kidneys.
Listen, I know this looks bad,
I obviously got the diagnosis wrong
but I did everything by the book.
I couldn't have known
what was going to happen.
If I skip my coffee I get cranky.
Do you want anything?
Why did Chase screw up?
He forgot to ask her a question,
does there need to be a reason?
It might help him.
As far as I'm concerned,
he made a little mistake. It happens.
How far are you concerned?
You think I'm biased?
You're colleagues.
You've worked together
for over a year.
And everyone says
you slept together.
[Clears her throat]
Who says?
The correct answer is
"we're not involved
and I'm not biased".
We're not involved.
And I don't know
why he messed up.
House has worked with him
longer than I have.
You should talk to House.
Yeah.
Why did Chase screw up?
Because he doesn't
give a crap about patients.
Well he always gets
positive patient reviews.
Yeah.
He smiles all 84 of his teeth,
tells them his tonsil story.
It's a nice story.
He still has his tonsils.
As soon as
he's out of the room,
which is as soon as
he can be out of the room,
he starts in on the trash talk.
Thinks not giving a crap
makes him like House.
Like something to aspire to.
Am I going to have to testify?
I won't be
encouraging them to call you.
What'd House say?
[Coughing]
Two months like this.
Let me guess, no insurance.
Just heard about the free clinic.
It's a good move.
You don't want to skimp
on the essentials like
wristwatches, MP3 players.
I need to talk to you.
From the doorway?
- It's confidential.
- Cool. I love gossip.
Hear that crackling sound
like crumpling up paper?
Keep listening.
Let me know if it changes.
Two questions.
Why did Chase screw up
and how bad was it?
Wow. Talk about efficient.
I only need one answer,
Chase didn't screw up.
He said he did.
Well I'm not a lawyer,
but that seems like
a sucky legal strategy.
Look I don't wanna know
what you think a reasonable doctor
would have done in Chase's position.
If I thought
he was a 'reasonable' doctor,
I wouldn't have hired him.
God, you two are
a couple of geniuses.
Deny everything,
completely fool the lawyer
who's trying to help you.
Too bad the review committee
members are actually doctors.
Stacy.
[Sighs]
I'm in her stomach.
There's too much blood,
I can't see.
She burst an artery?
No. There.
Bubbling, just a bad ulcer.
Okay, cauterizing.
Looks good.
Bleeding ulcer, we've got it.
She was fine 2 hours ago.
If by fine, you mean she had fountains
of blood spurting out of every orifice
then yeah, I believe you.
[Alarms start beeping]
I'm guessing
those are salvatory bells.
Systolic BP's 70.
Show me the ulcer.
It's brown.
I cauterized it.
Sweep back, show me
the whole stomach.
Stop.
Foreman:
Second ulcer?
Not anymore.
It perforated.
Get her to an OR!
Let's go.
She was not fine
2 hours ago.
She mentioned
stomach pain?
Yeah, so I gave her a stronger...
You didn't do an exam.
She just came in for a follow-up.
The results of the pathogen test.
Did you listen to her stomach?
Check her vitals?
Maybe if she'd said something
about taking ibuprofen,
mentioned the rectal bleeding!
Yeah, why didn't she go to
med school like you did?!
Diarrhoea! Blood in the stool!
These are routine questions...
Doctors skip all the time!
It was a minor mistake;
I couldn't have known
it was going to happen...
Mistakes are as serious
as the results they cause!
This woman could die
because you were too lazy
to ask one simple question!
No! She might die
because I had the bad luck
to spill your damn vicodin pills!
And I responded
with a number of
trenchant remarks which
made Chase cry, none of which
I'm going to testify about.
Unless you convince
Chase to row on me.
Excuse me,
testify about what?
Uhh...
Chuck.
I'm going to break from
the parable of the wicked doctor
and tell a little story about a patient.
Let's call him...
Buck, who has low O2 stats
and crackling lung sounds.
Like I have?
Buck has idiopathic
pulmonary fibrosis.
His lung tissue's turning to rock.
There's no known cause,
no treatment.
He is slowly suffocating.
You're talking about me?
Lung transplant's
about a half a million dollars,
but this poor sucker's
got no insurance.
If he tried to sign up now,
he'd be excluded,
pre-existing condition.
But let me confirm
with my lawyer.
She confirms.
If only Buck hadn't been
diagnosed with fibrosis
before he got insurance.
So... back to the exam.
That's how you tell
this guy he's dying?
Oh relax. He's got a cold,
and soon, health insurance.
Such a hero.
Always righting wrongs.
Who cares
who you have to manipulate.
I'm sorry. I didn't realise
you and Buck were so close.
Stacy:
It's a point of principle.
Right. It's got nothing to do
with what I did to you.
There's nothing
for us to talk about.
That's why you're following me.
I read some notes...
If Chase screwed up...
I was wrong.
Terribly, terribly sorry.
If Chase screwed up so badly,
why didn't you fire him?
He has great hair.
What are you hiding?
I'm gay.
Oh, that's not what you meant.
It does explain a lot though.
No girlfriend,
always with Wilson,
obsession with sneakers...
Diarrhoea, blood in the stool.
Two simple questions you could
have asked her six months ago
and averted this whole thing.
You didn't ask either, why?
Judging from your question,
and your demeanour,
I assume you were
visiting with House.
Been over this.
I don't know.
- Good doctors don't make mistakes...
- Good doctors never forget to ask questions?
Then you've got your answer,
apparently I'm not a good doctor!
FYI, self-pity generally is not
a good strategy in these hearings.
What happened
after the operation?
The kidney damage
isn't so bad.
The liver damage is
more worrisome.
There's no dialysis for livers.
I know, but if she loses her liver
she can get a transplant, right?
We can put her on a list.
I could do it.
I could give her part of my liver.
Surgeons won't operate
unless the donor's had
a long time to weigh the decision.
There's black markets.
Those organs...
That's just...
Ooh... ohhh my stomach!
[Alarms start beeping]
- Are they constant?
- Ohh... oh yeah!
- Sharp or dull?
- Oh I don't know!
It's bad.
It's a little cold.
- Appendicitis?
- No, it's a clot.
Nurse! Call the OR,
we've got to prep her
for an embolectomy.
Oh, ohhh!
A CVC, PT and a liver panel.
Sepsis had lowered her BP so much
she got clots in her liver.
They blocked the hepatic artery,
cut off the blood flow.
Her liver was shocked.
Did Cuddy list her though?
With all the other problems?
Forget it. We can't give
a liver to a woman this sick.
Do you listen to
what you're saying?
There is no point in
giving a new liver to somebody
who also has vasculitis.
Treatable.
And kidney damage.
It's healing.
You know what's
really killing her?
Chase forgot to ask a standard
question about stomach pain,
so he missed the diagnosis,
so she perforated,
so she got sepsis,
so her BP tanks,
so she got blood clots,
so she lost her liver.
Livers are important, Cuddy.
Can't live without them,
hence the name.
And here's the big issue,
Chase is a hospital employee,
and Kayla is the sympathetic
mother of those 2 jury-friendly
moppets Kayleb and Cody.
Dory and Nicky.
Your point, beyond just trying to
make Chase wet himself seems to be
that the hospital faces liability here.
Well thanks for clearing that up.
I still need a medical reason to list her.
That is a medical reason!
The family wins
this hospital in a lawsuit,
they'll turn it into condos.
And people will die
waiting outside a condo
for medical care.
[Sighs]
Start praying for a 12-car pile-up
on the turnpike 'cause we're not
exactly swimming in livers over here.
When you're testifying,
skip the details on how
House convinced Cuddy.
I don't think the people who got
bumped down the transplant list
need to know why.
It didn't matter anyway.
Sam:
She next on the list?
Yes.
But she's AB negative.
Very rare.
How long can she
go on like this?
Probably another day or two.
I'm donating my liver.
Sam, we've talked about this.
I'm a perfect match.
6 out of 6 HLA proteins.
How'd you get
checked out so fast?
I know a guy
in medical testing
and I paid him to rush it.
Sam bribed someone
to rush his test?
Wouldn't you?
Someone's going to get
the blame for what happened,
so the more we spread it around...
might as well... you said
no surgeon would do a live donor
transplant on such short notice.
House took care of that too.
Your patient's hardly clotting.
Sub-Q vitamin K and
fresh frozen plasma pre-op.
Pretty risky.
Well that's why I came to
the best transplant surgeon
in the hospital.
She's dead without you.
Get her in this afternoon.
[Sighs]
Thank you very much.
My pleasure.
And this was right before
you ran the marathon, I suppose?
Was it the part where
he warmly clasped my hands
in thanks, was that too much?
What'd you do to him?
The hospital lawyer asks me
if I did something unethical.
If I did,
the last person I tell is
the hospital lawyer,
especially since she's gone
all 'old testament' on me.
You'll tell me.
Oh. Ok then.
One caveat,
I've moved past threesomes.
I'm now into foursomes.
If someone backs out then
you've still got a threesome.
If two people back out,
you're still having sex.
You'd be amazed.
Even if three people...
Anything you say
is attorney-client.
So you can get advice about
the bad bad thing you did,
knowing I'll be tortured
because I can't tell a soul.
Actually, it is kinda cool.
Are you completely
out of your mind?
She's dying on her own,
why would I volunteer
to be her executioner?
I'd just be inviting
a lawsuit from the brother,
no matter what!
5 grand.
And that's just ante money.
After the surgery,
you get another 15.
Though I warn you,
that includes the tip.
[Laughs scornfully]
I make 600 grand a year,
you think I'm going to risk tanking
my percentages for 20 thousand?
It's tax free.
For the record,
I hope the department
takes you and Chase
and drop-kicks both your asses
out the back door.
Great.
That means I don't have to
bother welshing on the 15 grand
I would have owed you.
If you don't do the surgery,
I'm going to tell your wife
that you've been sleeping
with a series of nurses.
Currently Nurse Cuttler
in Radiology.
Now what's 600 grand
divided by two?
Last Christmas party,
Nurse Cuttler handed you
one of those little hotdogs.
And you didn't thank her.
Well that only happens
when you're very very intimate.
That and the fact that
you've been practically dancing
around with your zipper open,
used condom stuck in your shoe.
Your wife is apparently
the only one who doesn't know.
There is no way you'll tell her.
Of course I won't.
I'm much too cowardly.
No, I'd just send
an anonymous letter.
Now I've uh...
I've got an OR booked
for 4 this afternoon.
Are you free?
Hmm. Oh, and
for the record,
you are the worst
transplant surgeon
in this hospital.
But unfortunately,
you're the only one who's
currently cheating on his wife.
You bribed him and then
you blackmailed him?!
She'd have been dead
in 2 days if I hadn't made
Ayersman do the surgery.
Leave the blackmail out of
the story you tell the committee.
Tried to leave it out of
the story I told you.
And then there was
that incident in the parking lot.
Don't do that! Wait!
What are you nuts?!
Please! I didn't do it!
I didn't do anything!
- No!
- Please!
Apparently, someone sent
an anonymous letter to his wife.
You blackmailed Ayersman
before he performed the surgery
and then you ratted him out anyway?!
Doesn't seem fair, does it?
You just can't
control yourself, can you?
No matter how stupid,
how self-destructive...
To make this conversation easier,
can we discard the fiction that
we're talking about anything
other than what I did to you?
You're not mad
because I broke into
your psychiatrist's office.
Yeah, I was
thrilled about that.
Okay, it was
a lousy thing to do,
but if what I'd found was that
everything was all kittens
and moonbeams in Markville,
- you'd be over it.
- No I wouldn't!
You're mad at me for
letting you know what I did
because you liked
where things were going.
And for that
I actually am sorry.
It was stupid.
Let me tell you a story
about a patient.
The patient we'll call Fusan.
Chase:
Because Sam had
rushed his tests,
we were able to get them
into surgery that afternoon.
Dr. Ayersman performed
the live donor transplant.
He ressected
the right lobe, hepatic vein,
and hepatic artery of Sam's liver,
and transplanted it into Kayla.
The operation was a success.
Kayla and Sam continued
to receive routine care.
Two months later,
she came by for an exam.
July 24th, be precise.
You did the exam?
- Honestly, I just wanted to...
- Honestly?
So you've been
lying up until now?
Let's make a deal.
I won't use the word
'honestly', and
you'll quit stopping by
to see House so you don't
take it out on me afterwards,
how about that?
I wanted to be as far away
from Kayla as possible,
but House was
rubbing my nose in it.
How are the girls?
They're great.
Dory had her first crush,
which was cute.
Oh yeah?
And then her first sort of
break up, which was not so cute.
[Thermometer peeps]
You're hot. 99.3
- You been coughing?
- No.
- Pain in urinating?
99's not that high, is it?
Immunosuppressants block fevers,
you shouldn't have one at all.
I'm sending a nurse
in here to draw cultures,
and I'm ordering
a chest x-ray.
I wasn't making
any more mistakes.
Another phrase to avoid
in front of the committee.
She spikes a fever
an hour later.
Her AST and ALT are up.
She's rejecting the liver.
No, it's just an infection.
One of our cultures
is growing a strep.
Just one?
Probably a contaminant.
She's dehydrated,
her haematocrit's way up, it's strep!
Transaminases are up too.
It's just stress
from the strep.
Geez, Chase,
you and this strep.
Get a room already.
She's not rejecting the liver!
It's just an infection,
she'll be fine.
Worst case
we could re-list her.
You House?
Umm...well that depends.
Are you going to hit.
Dr. House?
You haven't even seen my sister
and you're being cute with me?
Sam, we're talking about her
right now. Her fever might...
Could be Hep B, Hep C, right?
It's treatable. You give her
interferon, she's ok.
Right?
You know a lot
about hepatitis.
He just donated his liver.
You're flushed.
You sick?
I'm tired.
You're hiding
the fact that you're sick.
- Now why would you do that?
- Hey, wait, what are you...
Now either you specifically
asked for a tattoo of a heart that's
been left out in the sun too long,
or that is a really
bad home job.
It's a very common way
of getting Hep C, which you have.
You've had it a long time.
It was going to keep me
from giving my liver.
You paid off that lab tech
to say you were clean?!
It hasn't been active in years.
She was going to die if I...
You paid someone off?
That is TOTALLY unethical!
Get an MRI for him and
his sister right now.
She got Hep
from me, didn't she?
No! No no no, god no!
I think she got
cancer from you.
House was right?
Brother had an undiagnosed hepatoma
that was transplanted with his liver.
Grew a lot faster in Kayla
because she was immunosuppressed.
How could House have known?
Hepatitis can
cause liver cancer.
Plus her haematocrit,
red blood cell count was high.
Usually means dehydration,
rare cases ... cancer.
We probably
saved Sam's life.
We were able to operate on him
early enough before it metastasized.
Kayla had already started
rejecting the liver.
And you couldn't re-list her
because of the cancer.
Nothing we could do.
This is good.
The brother lying about his Hep.
It's an intervening act,
the proximate cause of her cancer and not your mistake.
She would have died six months ago
if he hadn't given up his liver.
Maybe. Can't prove it.
[Stacy's beeper goes off]
You need to come with me.
Just been served with papers.
Actually paper. One page.
Defendant
Princeton-Plainsborough hospital
and Dr. Robert Chase,
blah blah blah,
medical malpractice,
negligence, blah blah.
You're surprised
they're suing?
You think
people love Chase so much
they're gonna just forgo...
Punitive damages
in the amount of
10 million dollars.
Punitives?!
That means they're
alleging gross negligence.
Well he's obviously
out of his mind!
Larry Wusekus.
He's not crazy.
Ooh! I've been sued by him.
YOU have been hiding things
and lying to me all day!
I haven't lied
about anything.
Except for the parts that
I admitted I was lying about.
And I'm not the one
being sued. I feel funny.
[Sighs] Well,
what haven't you told us?
[Sighs] Before she checked out,
Sam found her a second liver.
- She had cancer, how could she...
- Black market.
There was a doctor in Mexico City
who was going to do the surgery.
Chase:
She's leaving from JFK at 5.
To meet some Mexican guy
in the back of a van with a pig's liver
and a hacksaw?! This is nuts!
You want to
rat me out to House?
He'll say if there's a chance
in a billion then go for it.
This is not what she wants!
She's being manipulated
by a morally guilty brother
and a legally guiltier doctor.
You think she wants to die?
She's dying either way.
Chase.
How many people you know
walking around with a black market organ
from a third world surgeon, huh?
Foreman:
This isn't going to
be your salvation!
It's just one more thing
they'll pin on you!
Go in there,
be the good guy.
- We need to talk.
- No, there's no time.
Two minutes.
Kayla, I made a mistake.
I wasn't as blunt
as I should have been
about you all the time.
Probably didn't
want to face it myself.
Dr. Chase,
please don't do this.
Stress of the travel,
the operation,
even then, the cancer.
Kayla, we are going!
My dad died.
Lung cancer.
I saw him a couple of months
before it happened,
we never talked about it.
I'm sorry
your father died,
but it has nothing...
He never even
told me he was sick.
I wish he had.
It wou...
[Takes a deep breath]
You're gonna die. Alone.
Thousand of miles from your children,
you don't want to do that to them.
Kayla...
[Whispers]
I'm sorry Sam.
Kayla, you can't give up.
If you do this,
if you go home...
I killed you.
No.
You gave me 3 months.
You gave Dory and Nicky
3 more months with me.
And when they
found my cancer,
they found yours.
And I got to
save my baby brother.
[Sam starts to cry]
Chase:
A week later,
Kayla died at home.
Sam was furious.
Gotta be why
there'd be a lawsuit.
Cuddy:
Are you buying this?!
Of course not,
there was no illegal transplant,
there's no causation.
He was ready to kill me!
Maybe he's lying to his lawyers.
Or you're lying to us.
Last thursday he saw you
for post-op care.
If you hate your doctor,
you find another doctor
before you find a lawyer.
This guy didn't sue
Cameron or Foreman.
He didn't even sue House.
Something personal here,
something you don't want us
to know before your hearing.
The guy didn't hate you
before that meeting,
he hated you after.
So how's everything else?
The girls?
Ah, you know...
a lot of crying.
Some nightmares.
We'll be ok, though.
Good.
Girls are not going to be happy
about leaving town, though.
They love that house.
The yard, their friends.
You're moving?
Ever since the operation
I've been on disability...
and there's the mortgage so...
moving out to stay
somewhere cheaper.
Anyways, thanks.
I killed your sister.
I mis-diagnosed her ulcer.
Killed her.
Shut up man.
She liked you, just...
I was hung-over when
she came back to see me.
I'd been up
half the night drinking,
had a headache,
and I just wanted to
get the hell out of there.
Couldn't care less what
your sister was saying
about her stomach pain.
[ Loud crashing noise]
May I speak to my
future former employee?
House:
Great story.
You think I'm lying?
It's exactly what I told him.
I'm sure it is.
But you lied to him.
You want him to sue you.
I killed his sister!
I ordered black coffee
this morning and got cream.
Everybody screws up.
They didn't put
poison in your coffee.
I've seen you hung-over.
You weren't the day
you blew his sister's diagnosis.
What does it matter why?
Is she less dead
if I have a good excuse?
If I thought you'd screwed up
because you were drunk,
I would have fired you.
You knew?
You were depressed
and distracted.
I assumed you'd gotten
a phone call from your step mom.
[On the phone]
This is Robert.
Umm...
what did he die of?
That's impossible.
I saw him two months ago,
if he had lung cancer,
he would have...
Dr. Chase?
Good news is, both your
parents are dead now so...
no reason to
screw up this bad again.
How'd you know?
There's this interconnected
network of computers,
or interweb where you can...
How did you know to look?
[Sighs]
When he visited he told me
he only had two months left.
When you screwed up
I did the math.
Why didn't you tell me
he was dying?
He asked me not to.
So you just hung me
out there to be blindsided.
Yeah Chase, it was all my fault.
Look, you got a choice.
You can either tell the truth,
hospital settles,
family gets some money,
they get to keep their house.
Or you can keep up this lie,
family gets punitive damages,
they buy a jet,
they move to park avenue,
and you have to
find another career.
You're not going to say anything?
I'm going to keep my mouth shut.
Legally, it's better for me
if you go down in flames.
Is Chase telling the committee
about his dad?
I don't know.
I thought you were going to
get him to sell me out.
- I wouldn't do that.
- Why not?
You're my client too.
Yeah.
And that's not going to change
unless you leave this job.
Or I do.
So how do you deal with
a coworker that you have feelings for,
positive or negative.
I don't want to end up like Chase,
I don't want to get emotionally
caught up and kill... you.
It's not all negative.
Maybe you were right. Maybe...
maybe that is the problem.
So what do we do?
I don't know.
Dr. House.
After considering the testimonial
and documentary evidence,
this committee in the matter
of Kayla McGinley
has reached a decision.
Dr. Chase,
your error resulted
in a patient's death.
You also lied,
both to your superiors
and the patient's brother.
But taking into account
the mitigating factor of
your father's death,
we've decided not to
revoke your privileges.
You'll receive one week's suspension,
and a letter in your permanent file.
Now as for Dr. House...
there is no evidence of a failure
to supervise that would lead
to disciplinary action.
And yet, there is enough
in the record to be very
troubled by your conduct,
including certain allegations
of black mail from members
of the transplant team.
And by your general refusal
to meet with your patients.
It should be noted that your patient's
cancer was diagnosed as the result of
a direct physical examination of...
Not of the patient,
I met the brother.
Never met her.
You want me to go to a family reunion
every time I take on a patient?
The committee has determined
that for no less than one month,
Dr. House will have his practice
supervised by another doctor,
to be designated by Dr Cuddy.
This proceeding is adjourned.
Did you know
this was coming?
They contacted me
about an hour ago.
What's happening to Chase?
Now you're fired!
No, he's not.
Dr. House, meet your new boss.
Synchro : Vaccine
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net