So there I am, on my 25th birthday,
driving from Wheeling, West Virginia
to Bensonhurst in a Dodge Dart with no radio
and a gun runner
named Barrelhead,
[Laughter (o<)]
who insisted we sing
every Jimmy Buffet song he could recall.
What can I say?
The man was heavily armed. [(o<)]
So 500 renditions of
Margaritaville later,
my first cover, 8,000 words on
how Barrelhead and his friends were
transporting handguns for sale to New York city.
The day the magazine hit the stands,
the D.A. hit me with a subpoena.
He wanted to know
Barrelhead's real name.
Greta had been managing editor
for three whole days.
So she invited me
across the street to the fancy bar,
where they use real glasses. [(o<)]
And after about the sixth
vodka and tonic,
she said,
"Fletch, I want you to know
the magazine is behind you."
Well, I was impressed.
I said,  "Do you think
you can get the DA off my back?"
And she said,
"No. But when you get out of jail,
you'll still have a job." [(o<)]
I'm 45. I've given up a lot.
I've given up the road, that life.
Thanks,  Elizabeth.
No regrets. My lovely wife.
I've given up drinking.
I've given up drugs.
Greta taught me there's
two things you never give up.
One's rock and roll.
The other's a source.
Greta Sims.
[Cheers and applause]
Great memories, Greta.
We'll miss you, Greta.
We'll miss you.
I only hope you can adjust
to the lack of stress in your...
Fletch!
Fletcher.
Fletch.
Fletcher!
Honey, sweetie.
Are you okay?
Oh!
I flung the investment.
[Laughter]
What did you say?
I flung the investment.
Why consign?
I'll call 911.
It's proficient.
Why disqualify the rush?
I'm tabled.
2x10 - Failure to Communicate
Original Airdate (FOX): 10 JAN-2006
[Whistles]
I need your advice.
What's the best diagnostics department
within 60 miles of here?
We are.
"We" aren't here.
House is in Baltimore lying
to Medicaid about his billings.
- So? I'm board certified.
- You are not House.
Why'd you put me
in charge of the department
if you think I can't handle it?
Because it's temporary,
and because I was ordered to.
- What are the symptoms?
- Oh, come on.
You're gonna diagnose him
without meeting him?
Prove that you're
as brilliant as House?
I need to know the symptoms to
know which hospital to recommend.
EMT's report...
patient struck his head
and is suffering from aphasia.
Hmm, neurological problem.
You know, I know a lot of
good people in that field seeing
as I happen to be a neurologist.
- You're pouting.
- Not at all.
Taylor's pretty good.
House was ready to hire him
till he got my resume.
It's Fletcher Stone.
Wrote 12 books.
Exposed three administrations.
- Before he exposes us...
- I get it. Famous patient needs
famous doctor.
- I'll call Taylor.
- Thank you.
Or maybe you should call him.
What if I say something stupid?
Oh, God.
House is easier.
Have you been taking any drugs?
I displaced my function.
Accolade.
He used to drink regularly,
but he's been clean and sober
for nearly a year.
Mr. Stone, you think
you're speaking normally,
but your speech is impaired.
He knows what he wants to say,
but when he reaches for a word,
he finds something else.
I grapple average.
Tanzer glisten.
He doesn't know
that he's saying it wrong?
It all sounds right to him.
I want you to write
your name and draw a face.
It's called agraphia.
Loss of ability to write.
Most often it's temporary.
How hard did he hit his head?
It was a pretty good crack.
It made a really ugly sound.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
Of golf.
Don't give me a sentence.
Just say yes or a no.
You understand me?
Yes.
Elizabeth. Fletch.
Is he okay?
We  don't know.
This is Fletch's editor.
Greta Sims.
I wanted to make sure that
the EMTs told you the right story.
How many stories are there?
He didn't trip.
He just fell.
Out of the blue.
His foot jerked a little bit first.
That's what made it look like a trip.
Stacy:
Don't say anything.
Don't attempt to defend
your billing practices.
Your billing practices
are indefensible.
We've  been over this.
If I thought you were capable
of listening, I'd shut up.
That makes no sense at all.
- [Sighs] Good afternoon.
- Good afternoon.
Every case you have rates a five
on the complexity scale?
Dr. House has a rather
specialized practice.
Ah. Okay.
Then let's go through these.
All of these?
If you have lunch reservations,
cancel them.
All right. Patient...
If he didn't trip,
something made him fall.
Stoke? Seizure?
30  people saw him trip.
One person says he didn't.
Who you gonna believe?
His symptoms can all be
explained by the head trauma.
Causes a contusion or a seizure.
That causes the aphasia.
We should get an EEG.
If it was a stroke,
it could be a clotting issue.
Even if he fell,
drug use is far more likely.
I'm ordering a tox screen.
Chase, we're not done
with the differential.
You're not my boss.
I'm House's boss.
House is your boss.
The math is pretty simple.
Are you signing my paychecks?
Are you hiring or firing?
This is not about that...
The only thing you've been
asked to do is supervise House
in case he doessomething insane.
Which might,
you know, save a life.
- Somebody's gotta be in charge.
- Why?
You think we should all just do
whatever we wanna do?
Maybe have a race
to the diagnosis.
I think it should be
a discussion among peers.
I think we're grown up enough
to reach a consensus.
Patient, 62 years old.
You prescribed Viagra.
I look in vain for the words
erectile dysfunction in the notes
for Delores Smith.
She had a heart condition.
And you ran out
of nitroglycerin?
She also had low blood pressure.
So nitro would be dangerous.
Little blue pills
improve blood flow.
They're vasodilators.
It's why you sometimes
get the headaches.
Stacy:
I think Dr. House understands.
House:
Oh, of course I do.
The woman has a heart condition
she's on her own.
A man can't nail his office assistant,
it's national crisis time.
Are you seriously expecting us
to foot the bill for
off-label use of medication?
Fine. I'll pay for it.
How much are the pills?
She took how many?
Put the money away.
- Are you trying to bribe me?
- No.
I could.
There's an ATM in the lobby.
My client's an idiot.
But is he wrong
about the pills?
Off-label use
is not sanctioned.
You're retiring
in three weeks.
You've been doing this job
nearly 20 years.
Aren't you tired of
administering policy
you disagree with?
- I-I never said I disagree.
- What can they do to you?
And Dr. House is sorry
about his earlier outburst.
Absolutely.
You do background checks
on Medicaid personnel?
I do what's necessary
for my client.
- Wow, new personal record.
- Yeah, timing's good for me too.
I got a reservation
at a little place in the Inner Harbor.
- You booked us dinner reservations?
- Best Maryland crab in...Maryland.
- Don't you have a plane to catch?
- Not for hours.
Your flight leaves at 7:00.
You did a background check on me?
And mine doesn't leave till 9:00pm.
It looks like
you'll be dining alone.
You checked on my flight
so you could be sure
to be on a different one.
I thought we were past
the avoidance stage.
I didn't think
we'd be finished this soon.
Where's your crucifix?
I left it at the jewelers
to be cleaned.
Right.
This will show us if there's
a problem with your carotid artery
that might cause a blood clot.
If it went to his brain,
that could explain the aphasia
and the falling down.
And you're giving him an EEG?
Is that for the same thing?
Uh, it's just a precaution.
I think the trauma caused some swelling,
and we need to keep him stable
until the bodycan repair the damage.
And you think
they're both wrong?
Foreman:
We're just covering all the bases.
- Being safe.
- [Chokes and coughs]
[Monitors start beeping]
His O2 sats are going down.
[Continues coughing]
- Fluid in his lungs.
- Push 40 IV Lasix.
- We need to intubate.
- He's losing his respiratory drive.
Now put him down.
Foreman:
And then there were two.
Aphasia and fluid in the lungs.
Seizure can't cause both.
Neither can a stroke.
Unless he had
an abnormal heart rhythm.
Chase:
And then there was one.
Urine test is positive
for amphetamines.
Amphetamines don't cause
pulmonary edema.
They doif you smoke 'em.
In one of his books he talked
about giving updrugs and alcohol,
how it changed his life.
Everybody lies.
When he started wanting to hear
every minute of my day,
it should have been a clue
he was the jealous type.
But you know,
in that first stage
of a relationship,
where it's like your body's full of
these chemicals that make you think
everything they do is charming...
[Cell phone rings]
Ah.
Excuse me.
Wilson: Hello?
Hey, honey, how are the kids?
They miss me?
This may take a minute.
House:
So what's new with Mr. Aphasia.
Cuddy called you?
Everybody covers their ass.
Wilson:
Pulmonary edema.
Chase did a tox screen.
It came back positive
for amphetamines.
He did the dance of victory.
I'm betting
there's another shoe.
I thought
the kids didn't call you.
[Thump!]
I know the way
you tell stories.
Foreman went to talk to Stone
about his drug test, found him
running a temperature.
So it's not the drugs.
They've just got such a bad rep.
[Thump!]
Mother:
Honey, you shouldn't do that.
Okay, I gotta hang up.
They're probably trying
to reach me.
- You don't have call waiting?
- I'm hanging up on you now.
Wilson:
It's $5.00 a month.
[Thump!]
Drugs don't cause fever.
Encephalitis or meningitis
are the obvious suspects.
Start him on antibiotics.
It could be
an autoimmune disease.
Lupus, Behcet's.
We could start himon a high dose of steroids.
[Phone ringing]
Except if he does have encephalitis,
steroids could weaken his immune system.
Foreman.
How high a fever?
Put me on speaker phone.
And why haven't you called me?
101.
How'd you know?
What? You think you guys can
have a party as soon as the parents
are gone, and I won't hear about it?
House:
Start with broad spectrum antibiotics
for possible bacterial meningitis
and an antiviral in case we luck out,
and it's herpes encephalitis.
What if it's autoimmune?
Well, then we're screwed.
Which is why we need
more information.
Any genetic issuewith the family?
Foreman:
The man can't talk.
His medical records are sketchy.
And the wife's only known him
a couple of years.
House:
MRI show anything?
CT scan was negative.
CT?
That's, like,
short for MRI, right?
Excellent.
That'll save us a lot of time.
We've got an MRI
scheduled in 20 minutes.
Earliest Foreman
could get the machine.
I teach you to lie,
cheat, and steal,
and as soon as my back
is turned you wait in line?
Get an MRI, and get
a better medical history.
The man can't talk.
Who cares?
He's probably gonna lie anyway.
My flight's a little late.
I'll be back in a few hours.
So you're in charge of us
because you're in charge of him?
Any family history
of neurological problems?
No.
You've been out of the country
in the last five years.
Yes.
Three years?
Two years.
He stopped traveling for work
two years ago after we got serious.
Any vacations?
His  last one was
six months ago.
It was a golf resort
at Key Biscayne.
No way it was
a golf resort.
Knowing Fletch, I assume
he was working his way
through every bar in the Keys.
Last hurrah
before settling down.
[Elevator dings]
- Alcohol?
- No.
- Amphetamines.
You tested positive.
Elizabeth:
He doesn't use drugs.
I told you.
When we got engaged,
we decided we wanted
a different kind of life.
And he dropped the macho journalism.
No more taking crazy chances.
That includes his health.
He asked me not to tell Elizabeth.
He's been lying to herabout his drug habit?
Well, yes and no.
BE...before Elizabeth...
he used drugs recreationally.
I wasn't crazy about it,
but that thrill-seeking behavior
is what made him the kind
of journalist that he was.
And now, AE?
The man's twisted himself
into knots for her.
- Completely cleaned up his act.
- But the drugs?
They're medicinal.
Sort of.
He was having trouble sleeping.
His  new suburban lifestyle.
Lack of excitement
was throwing him off.
So he started
with sleeping pills.
When they knocked him out,
he needed something to
perk him back up during the day.
Chase:
Every day?
No slippery slope there.
Keep the stain.
Knife can't force.
We're not gonna tell your wife.
We're not cops.
There's a little edema.
Brain swelling.
And an area of scarring.
Is that what's
causing the aphasia?
Actually, that's what's odd.
The scarring's not in the area of
the brain normally associated
with conduction aphasia.
And it's old.
Happened before he hit his head.
Maybe a small stroke or
some other underlying condition
that could be causing this, or
it might have nothing
to do with it at all.
Have you ever had
head trauma before?
- An accident?
- Uh-uh.
You ever had any numbness
on one side before?
- Dizziness?
- What is the durable?
[Softly] Shh...
No.
Announcement:
Boarding passengers
for flight number 870.
The plane will be delayed
by one half-hour. We apologize...
Thanks.
Got you some coffee.
So...what do you
wanna talk about?
The scarring on the MRI
could be anything.
MS,  toxins, any one of a hundred demyelinating diseases.
If it's meningitis,
we have to ID the bug fast.
We need to do
a lumbar puncture.
I'm not doin LP
with this edema.
- We could paralyze him.
- What does House say?
"The person you're trying
to reach is out of the area or
has turned off their phone."
So what are your orders?
- We need more information.
- There is no more information.
We'll break into his place.
Have fun.
How's the patient?
Fine.
- Where you going?
Foreman: - Dinner.
Oh, well I'll join you.
You can bring me up to speed.
Sorry.
Reservation for two.
When people
give themselves away,
it's by little things.
That woman over there,
she's not sneering at her coffee.
She's recovering from Bell's Palsy.
The cashier at the coffee place,
she doesn't want anyone to know,
but she's dying of ALS.
There's a particular
sort of twitchy stiff arm
that's characteristic.
And then there's you.
Why aren't you
wearing your cross?
I told you, I left it at...
You keep jewelry cleaner
under the sink so you won't
have to go a day without it.
True, you forgot it
that morning the pipes burst.
But then you went back
and waded through the flood
to retrieve it.
So...why no wading today?
Didn't you bring a book
to read or something?
Nothing.
Caffeine pills and amphetamines.
Same stuff he told us he was taking.
And Topamax.
An anti-convulsant?
He said there was
no history of prior seizure.
It's not even prescribed to him.
Still doesn't explain his fever.
Probably just using it for weight loss.
Just gives us another lie.
He must really be devoted.
Should we check the home?
If he wanted to hide something
from his wife, why wouldn't
he hide it in the office?
Maybe she's
hiding something.
Nothing but aspirin and
flu meds in the bathroom.
Looks like this stuff's
been sitting here for weeks.
Chase:
Hmm, home improvement.
He probably thought
he could take the project on,
then realized it was a little
more than he could handle.
You got a point to make, or did you just feel
like giving a long, unnecessary explanation
for something medically irrelevant?
What happened to the Foreman
who always has an answer?
The guy who practically
wears a sign saying,
"I'm as good as House,
but I'm nicer."
I never said that.
I guess it's safe to be confident
when House is there to overrule you.
Now that it's all on you?
It's different. Yeah.
Announcement:
Flight 106 to Nashville
has been delayed...
Either you left it behind
on purpose or by mistake.
The only reason you'd leave it
behind intentionally is
if it no longer meant anything to you.
But since it was
a gift from your mom,
that would mean
you had a fight with her.
And since you don't talk
to ghosts, that's unlikely.
- Leave it alone, Greg.
- Yeah, I'm good at that.
So that leaves
forgetting it unintentionally.
But then we have to explain
why you didn't go back for it
when you realized.
I didn't realize
until I got to the airport.
Nope, you were wearing makeup
when you got to the airport.
You can't put on makeup
without looking at yourself.
You can't look at yourself
without touching that thing.
Why does this matter to you?
It's an anomaly.
Anomalies bug me.
Then you're gonna suffer.
[Groans in pain]
I think it's his stomach.
I teal indigent.
Is it something you ate?
He keeps doing that.
I teal indigent.
- Are you hungry?
- No.
- He's in pain. Is it a sharp pain?
- No!
Teal indigent!
- Taste?
- Yes!
- Uh, metallic taste?
I'll be right back.
Ow!
Attention, passengers, flight 118...
House:
I suppose it's also possible
that the clasp broke.
But then you'd be carrying
the thing around in your purse.
We had a fight.
We had a fight, and I was angry
and not thinking straight.
And I walked out
without my makeup
and without my cross.
And I stopped at
the drugstore to buy makeup,
but I couldn't buy a cross
because they don't have an aisle
for personal talismans!
So you had a fight.
I'm sure it'll blow over.
- It was about nothing.
- Of course it was.
Mark's tired. He's worried.
He's got mobility problems.
It's normal to blow up
over little things.
I don't mind fighting over little things.
And I don't mind fighting over big things.
That I could understand.
But we fight over nothing.
You know, a mailbox with a sign
that says "Last pickup 5:00 p.m."
Does that mean last pickup to go to
the post office or last pickup to leave
the post office and be sent out of town?
You fought over mail delivery?
I tried to get him to drop
the subject, but he wouldn't.
I told him he was right,
he thought I was
being condescending.
You were.
He's pushing me
out of his life.
Or maybe you're
misinterpreting.
Did I misinterpret with you?
At least this time
I recognize it.
That's the benefit of
convincing the only two men
you've ever loved,
they're better off without you.
Yeah. It's all your fault.
You know,
"Stacy" in the original Greek
means relationship killer.
I'm gonna go wash my face
so I look like a grown-up again.
[Phone rings]
Hello.
It's for you.
House.
Do you know
your phone's dead?
Do you ever recharge
your batteries?
House:
They recharge?
I just keep
buying new phones.
I thought you should know
your aphasia guy is tasting metal.
Where's his creatinine?
6.8. He's got kidney failure.
Cameron's got him on dialysis,
and he's stable for the moment.
Unlike Cuddy, who's suicidal.
It's either meningitis
or encephalitis.
Or maybe autoimmune.
That's perfect.
Seems like you really
narrowed it down over dinner.
Here's the plan.
We talk to House...
Been trying.
He's not answering his cell.
It's obvious we have
to do the lumbar puncture.
There's no choice anymore.
[Phone ringing]
House:
You have to do it just right.
What are you talking about?
Either you've decided
to do a lumbar puncture,
or you have to fire me
so that I can't fire all of you
as soon as I get back in charge.
Is Cuddy there ranting?
If I'd known
you'd be out of contact...
They can handle it.
Right, so far only
three organ systems have failed.
Okay, they can't.
Doesn't matter.
The guy's not stable
enough to move.
So go rant in your own office.
Fine. Call me
when you're done.
What do you mean by
doing the LP just right?
We're not gonna screw it up.
The odds are this guy
knows something we don't.
He could know the answer
to the meaning of life.
The man can't communicate.
Have you had any indication
that he's tried to communicate
something important?
No.
That's because you guys
haven't scared him enough.
I'm sure you've been all,
"We'll take realgood care of you."
Why should he say anything?
When you prep him,
tell him he's gonna die.
Crush all hope.
Don't let Cameron do it.
Cuddy.
You got a problem
with any of that?
You're scheduled
for a lumbar puncture.
But you shouldn't count on
that having the answers.
If your husband
continues to decline...
You'll die.
If there's anything
you haven't told us...
How you holding up?
I know what you just heard
is scary as hell, but...
Couldn't tackle the bear.
They took my stain.
Your attention please,
due to the weather conditions,
all flights are grounded
until further notice.
Oh...
You gotta be kiding.
Cots are being provided
on the lower level.
We apologize
for the inconvenience.
I don't believee it.
You want me to run down and
reserve you a cot with a view?
Where's your knapsack?
I checked it through.
Oh, that's right,
I forget it's hard for you
to carry and walk.
I booked a room at the airport hotel
when I saw how bad the weather was.
It's the last one available.
Your leg can't handle
a night on a cot.
Thanks.
I'm ready.
Right.
Hotel's upstairs.
Does Mark know about this?
Mark knows when things are bad,
I always like to have
an escape route planned.
[Sighs] I have to know
what's going on here.
When you have a fight with Mark
and you try to avoid me,
I have to think that...
That I'm feeling vulnerable and
I don't wanna be around you
because it might lead to something.
Right.
But then a hotel room...
Might also lead to something.
Hmm.
So which is it?
Our relationship's
like an addiction. It's... like...
Really good drugs?
No, it's like vindaloo curry.
Okay, sure.
Really, really hot Indian curry
they make with red chili peppers.
I know what it is.
I didn't think
it was addictive.
You're abrasive and annoying and
come on way too strong, like...
vindaloo curry.
When you're crazy about curry,
that's fine. But
no matter how much you love curry,
you have too much of it, it takes
the roof of your mouth off.
And then you never wanna see curry
for a really, really long time.
But you wake up
one day and you think...
God, I really miss curry.
You're a jerk.
I know.
If you hadn't just had
a fight with Mark...
For once in your life,
will you shut up?
[Phone ringing]
Oh!
House.
You're on speaker phone.
How did the LP go?
Give me the Reader's Digest
condensed version.
Preliminary results are
some kind of infection
which...narrows it down.
From infinity. Yeah.
At the rate
his organs are deteriorating
he's got maybe a day or two.
Okay, well, call me back
when you have something.
Cameron:
He was trying to
tell us something.
What did he say?
You were wrong.
It wasn't the fear.
- He opened up to me when I...
- Sympathetic presence
after a traumatic moment.
Classic interrogation technique.
What did he say?
- You knew that I'd...
- Act the way you always do?
Yeah, I did.
What did he say?
He couldn't tackle the bear.
Now all we need is
the English-Aphasiac dictionary.
A fluent aphasiac retrieves words
that are stored somewhere
close to the one he wants.
They can be filed
by sound or by meaning.
So if he wants to say table,
he could say label,
or he could say chair,
or he could just say jabberwocky.
There's no way to tell.
He also said,
"They took my stain."
Hold on.
I'm gonna take this phone downstairs
so I don't disturb you. Is that okay?
Sure.
Keep him talking.
Write down everything he says.
Stacy...
[Sighs]
that new makeup you bought,
you mind if I borrow it?
What did you mean by stain?
Dirty? Soiled?
No. No.
Foreman:
What about rhymes?
Uh, pain. Brain?
Thane?
He's dying from some kind of infection,
and you allare playing word games?
Is there anything else
you haven't told us?
Foreman:
L-Let's start this again.
Bear.
Is it bare as in naked?
Crimson desire
shows up well on sheet rock.
That's why I chose it.
You must have gotten
one new phrase out of him.
Something.
We've been talking
to him for hours.
Maybe he's just given up.
You sure you told me everything
you found at his home and office?
Chase:
No, we're hiding something.
- Maybe it's not a rhyme or a synonym.
- What else is there?
You think we should just
start guessing randomly?
Maybe House is wrong.
Hope that's not
the end of the thought.
He mentioned stain once before
when Chase was giving him the MRI.
- Before we scared him.
- He did?
It's in your notes.
Chase:
So he only talks during MRIs
and lumbar punctures?
Your theory is he can only talk
with a needle in his back or...
Or when his wife's
not in the room.
The more devoted,
the more reason to lie.
That's cynical.
You disagree?
No, I'm just kvelling.
Our little girl is growing up.
Okay, what's the best way
to rip a woman from
the side of her dying husband?
He woke me up to lie
to a patient's wife?
Tell her there's been
a miscommunication over
their insurance coverage.
Not a big deal.
Tell me, if it is your aim to sell me
the same crazy ideas that House does,
how are you an
improvement on House?
I brought you a coffee.
Your flight's been boarding
for 20 minutes.
I'll take a later one.
Greg, they can't leave without you.
You checked your knapsack.
[Phone rings]
Are we in?
Yeah.
House:
Hi, I'm Gregory House.
I'm your attending physician.
Your wife's not there.
Start talking.
They took my stain.
I couldn't tackle the bear.
House:
Okay, shut up now.
Nice work, Cameron.
Give him the list again.
Let us know when
something sounds right.
Dirty?
Soiled? Pain?
- Brain?
- Yes!
Foreman:
Where does that get us?
We're already paying plenty
of attention to his brain.
We've got an MRI.
We've got a CT.
Are we sure he
wasn't reacting to pain?
He's been on painkillers.
House:
Come on, Chase.
Drugs didn't do this to him.
Even if he is an addict.
I dissuade the tonal category.
Oh please,
Mr. Sleeping Pills.
Amphetamines.
Bring me up.
Bring me down.
Announcement:
Will passenger Gregory House
please report to gate seven?
Gregory House to gate seven.
Ever hear this one?
You build a house.
Each wall has a southern exposure.
Big bear comes wandering by.
What color's the bear?
White. It's a polar bear.
You built your house in the North Pole.
House:
Polar.
Whatever your name is,
patient, are you bipolar?
House:
What? I can't see.
Is he nodding?
Yes.
Topamax isn't just off-label
for weight loss.
It's off-label
for mood disorders.
Plenty of bipolars are
manic in the daytime,
depressive at night.
He's been medicating
for years with alcohol.
Sleeping through the bad hours.
It explains
the danger journalism.
It explains everything,
including the kitchen sink.
Okay, technically
it's kitchen cabinets.
He starts a project,
then he stops.
Except bipolar disorder
does not cause seizures.
House:
And it doesn't shut down
your kidneys. But what it does do...
Guard:Excuse me, sir.
May I see your ID?
House: I'm on the phone.
Guard: Now, please.
House? What is it?
I'm a doctor.
This is an emergency call.
You have to come
with me, Sir.
I'm not going anywhere.
Do you think
you're gonna take me on?
I kick, and I bite.
You're either on that plane,
or you're going into custody.
Foreman:
House?
You still there?
Being bipolar
makes you take risks.
You seek excitement.
You make up stories.
I dime valutate a lever!
Fine, maybe your stories are legit.
But people would start to wonder.
Annoyed politicians.
Entire governments
would be on your ass.
So you couldn't tell anybody
you were bipolar.
Which was fine
until you fell in love.
And you wanted that life.
And you hear that
there's a surgical cure.
You can give the woman you love
the life she wants.
All you have to do is change.
Bilateral cingulotomy.
An experimental surgery
that some people claim
helps mood disorders.
And if it's done by gamma knife,
there's no trace of cutting.
That's the neural scarring
we saw on the MRI.
Which explained nothing because
it wasn't even in the right area.
It's not the surgery.
It's the secrecy.
What causes recurring fever?
Neurological problems,
lethargy that you fight with
caffeine pills and amphetamines?
It wasn't your secret
psych disorder.
[Door opens]
It wasn't your
secret daily drug use.
It was the secret trip
for your secret surgery
in Caracas or Buenos Aires.
Which, by the way,
didn't work, given the state
of your kitchen cabinets.
Cameron:
House!
Shut up.
What's going on?
Is he right?
Your doctors
know you better than I do.
That man on the speaker phone,
he never even met you, and
he knows you better than I do.
You love me?
Yes. Yes.
You just don't trust me.
House:
Get some blood on a slide.
Do not put it through
a computer this time.
Yep.
Foreman:
Cerebral malaria.
I'll get him started
on intravenous quinidine.
If a human being had
actually looked at his blood
anywhere along the way,
instead of just running tests
through the computer,
the parasites would have
jumped right out at them.
The price
of the electronic age.
Greta:
Fletch.
She'll be back.
Give her time to miss you.
Announcement:
Final boarding call for Flight No. 7...
I'm counting on you
to get me off the no-fly list.
Is your patient
gonna be all right?
Physically,
his chances are good.
Physically?
Two people who weren't
meant to be together.
Maybe they'll get a happy ending
just because they both want it so much.
Yeah, that's usually
the way it works.
He loved her enough to convince
himself he could change.
But he couldn't, could he?
Thank you.
You know what Woody Allen
said about relationships?
Irrational and crazy,
but go through it all because...
We need the curry.
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : Vaccine
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net