Previously on "House".
You high, Popo?
Caught with a sense of humor.
You can check the cop car.
Also check
his personal car, work, home.
Foreman, get out!
Am I the only one
who finds this funny?
- You stole my article.
- I wouldn't do that.
We're not friends,
we're colleagues.
Ow! Son of a bitch!
Now we're both exposed.
- I'm gonna die.
- You die, I die.
It's not gonna happen.
Time of death,
12:26 p.m.
I need a bone saw.
- I'm sorry.
- You said you--
- I wish I could.
I just want a little tiny slice of
this guy's brain, that's all I need.
Just enough to tell me
what's killing Foreman.
A thin slice of Joe's brain could
also causea public health crisis.
It's not a good idea to scream "fire"
every time somebody lights a match.
Don't downplay this, House.
You put both of them
in isolation for a reason.
Joe's death elevates this situation
to a biosafety level 3.
Ooh, level 3.
- You should call Jack Bauer.
- I called the CDC.
Well, tell them
I'll be really, really careful.
We don't have the proper equipment
for you to be really, really careful.
You can do whatever you want to Foreman,
but the CDC will do this autopsy.
Whatever. The point is,
we'll be lucky to get results in 3 days.
I told them
how urgent this is.
And they told you?
We'll have the results
in 3 days.
Aw, that's a shame.
Because Foreman will
never get to know what it was.
He'll be dead in 36 hours.
Maybe this is a toxin.
Maybe it's notcontagious at all,
and you're killing Foreman
because of a maybe.
Well, you have 36 hours
to figure out which one it is.
Foreman.
Come here, fast.
What's going on?
When are they
doing the autopsy?
You're doing it. Now.
You ever study how they used
to do ice pick lobotomies?
I read about it in med school.
Why would I--
Shove an ice pick into the eye socket.
Just above the tear duct.
Bang it a couple of times
with a hammer, get a sample.
What's going on, man?
Foreman, you can't do it.
You'll be in violation of--
Can't do the time
if you're not alive.
You. I need you to suit up.
Get that equipment away
from Dr. Foreman.
House:
Take your time, guys.
Why don't you just
tell him to go slow?
- Won't be your fault.
- Foreman.
We don't even know what kind of
contagion we're dealing with.
Which is why we need
to chop into the guy's head.
- It's dangerous.
- Not to you, Foreman.
There are other ways
to diagnose you.
Yeah?
You have the answer?
- Foreman, do it now.
- I am warning you, do not--
What are you doing?
That didn't feel right.
He's blind.
He thinks he can see.
Same as the cop.
I need something
to bag the sample.
Forget it.
You just biopsied a mattress.
No, no, no. I'm fine.
House, there's the sample.
Get it, test it.
You gotta test that sample!
Apparently I was optimistic
about the 36 hours.
Intractable, unbearable pain
is up next.
Sure you don't want to reconsider
that whole autopsy thing?
2X21 - Euphoria, Part 2
Original Airdate (FOX): 3 MAY-2006
Physically,
his eyes are fine.
Problem's isolated
to his brain.
Damage to the occipital lobe
extends from the primary visual cortex--
Should we test him
for bacterial meningitis?
If it was meningitis,
we'd all be sick.
- His CSF could show signs--
- That would be pointless.
We already did a brain biopsy.
It was negative.
- Toxic mold?
- If it was toxic mold, I'd be sick.
How do we know
you're not sick?
Do I seem happy to you?
Never.
[Snorts]
It was funny.
Well, let's assume
it's not blood-borne.
If you start cracking jokes,
we can re-assess.
In the meantime,
stay away from people and animals
that you care about.
Guillain-Barr.
Neither of them had
any sort of paralysis.
Joe could have died before
the paralysis had a chance to present.
What about arbovirus?
Start treatment.
For arbovirus?
You think our Jersey beat cop
has been spending a lot of time
exploring deep, dark Africa?
Treatment  for everything.
Likely or unlikely.
If you can think of it, treat for it.
Mixing that many meds will
create all sorts of toxic interactions.
We'll box his liver, trash his kidneys.
There's got to be a better way.
Of course
there's a better way!
It's that body
sitting in the room with him
that Cuddy won't let us touch.
Bacterials, virals,
toxins, fungals, parasites.
It's got to be one of them.
Where are you going?
To see if I can find
another brain to biopsy.
We're going to lock Joe up downstairs
until the CDC gets here.
Foreman, you can't see.
Right.
House wants
to start you on some meds.
They're in the airlock.
For what?
Leading candidate
is toxic mold.
Is Cameron sick?
I'm fine.
Thanks for asking.
You're  casting your net a little wider
than toxic mold, aren't you?
Guillain-Barr
is also on the table.
This is an oval shape...
Has either an L or a 7.
I'm guessing an L.
Levofloxacin, because
you can't rule out bacteria.
8, 0, 0.
That's the dosage for
the acyclovir in case it's viral.
Square...
No, more like a rhombus.
That's fluconazole for fungus.
There's about 8 others here.
You--
You're treating me
for everything.
You have no idea
what I've got.
House thinks this is
the best course of action.
House is desperate.
House is never desperate.
Something we give you will work.
Yeah, we should start
treating all patients this way.
When they get sick,
they just take everything.
It's better than doing nothing.
[Phone rings]
Hello?
I'm at the cop's place.
I need to retrace your steps.
You don't think the
"treat him for everything" approach
is enough?
Where did you
start your search?
The kitchen.
You will tell me
everything you did,
everything you touched.
If you went to the john,
I want to know when and why.
I started with samples
from the mold in his sink.
- What next?
- That's it. Then I left.
Foreman:
What do we do now?
Wait for Steve McQueen
to get giddy.
[Calling]
Hey, Dad.
It's Eric.
I'm not doing too good.
How's Foreman?
You're accessing a webcam?
Cuddy's shower.
Are you a fan of the Brazilian?
I-I--
Is that your kitchen?
Well, obviously
I couldn't bring him here.
He's been exposed to
whatever Foreman's got.
You infected Steve?
Why didn't you just get
a rat from the pet store?
Because... I needed one
with a clean medical history.
Who knowswhat kind of antibiotics they give those rats?
So this is your plan? Just sit here
and watch your rat all day?
Well, it shouldn't take long.
Got the AC blasting,
I soaped the floor of his cage...
As soon as he gets sick,
I do an autopsy.
As soon as he's dead.
Right after he gets sick,
there's a good chance he'll
get hit in the head with a...
cane-shaped object.
Normally you just use
your patients as lab rats.
It's a nice change.
First symptom is euphoria.
How do you know
if a rat's euphoric?
He doesn't usually climb
on his water bottle like that, does he?
The seizures only seem to happen
when she's in her car seat.
- She starts to rock and grunt.
- She responsive?
No, no, it's like she's in a zone.
And her abdominal muscles
become dystonic.
Big word.
Someone's been
on the InterWeb.
I looked up
a few articles on epilepsy.
You  know,
there's actually some really
great youth soccer leagues,
that would cater specifically
to her special needs, and...
I think it might explain
why she's been having
a hard time in preschool.
Let's confirm your diagnosis
before you have her held back.
Strobing lights and
high-pitched sounds
can provoke a seizure.
[Silly ghost noise]
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
You're a goof.
Takes one to know one, loser.
Wait, that means I'm a loser.
Scratch that.
These episodes.
She get sweaty afterwards?
Soaking wet.
And does she seem
upset by them, or just tired?
No, she kind of thinks it's funny.
You mix rocking, grunting, sweating,
and dystonia with concerned parents,
and you get
an amateur diagnosis of epilepsy.
In actuality,
all your little girl is doing is
saying "yoo hoo" to the "hoo hoo."
- She's what?
- Marching the penguin.
Ya-ya-ing the sisterhood.
Finding Nemo.
[Chuckles]
That was funny.
It's called
gratification disorder.
Sort of a misnomer.
If one was unable to gratify oneself,
that would be a disorder.
Are you saying
she's masturbating?
I was trying to be discreet.
There's a child in the room.
- Oh, this is horrifying.
- Epilepsy is horrifying.
Teach your girl about privacy
and he'll be fine. Here you go.
Thank you.
One afternoon, and
you're on pace to set the record
for most patients seen in a month.
You're upset that I'm doing clinic hours?
Wow, that is so like rain on your wedding day.
For the past 3 hours,
I have been on the phone with the CDC,
while you are--
Yeah, how's that going,
by the way?
They promised to expedite--
Tough to do an autopsy when
they haven't even picked up the body.
It's tough to treat your patient
when you're not even on the same floor.
Go. Clinic is covered.
I go watch the meds drip into his IV.
You think that'll make the treatment work faster?
Go to your office.
Play with your ball.
Write on your whiteboard.
Insult your team.
Do whatever it is that you do
to figure things out.
Feeling guilty?
It's not too late
to change your mind.
Go call the CDC.
Tell 'em you were just joshing.
Keep avoiding Foreman's case
until he dies.
Then I'll drown in guilt.
Feeling any better?
How are you doing?
I'm not the patient.
Is your sed rate elevated?
No.
So far, it looks
like I lucked out.
C ameron.
Looks like you left
a tourniquet on the bed.
You can see again?
The treatment's working.
The question is,
which treatment?
We'll start weaning him off
one at a time.
Which one do we start with?
I don't care
if you do it alphabetically.
Just stay on top of his vision.
First sign of regression means
we've taken him off the wrong one.
The latest blood work.
Foreman's  amylase and lipase levels
are 3 times normal.
Pancreas is failing.
A toxic side effect of his meds.
[Retching]
House:
Philosophical question.
How do you want to die?
Old age.
Your choice is currently
between 4 hours from now
and 14 hours from now.
So I'm assuming that means
you want the latter.
The cocktail's working.
My vision's almost
completely restored.
The meds are curing what's in your head,
but they're trashing your pancreas.
That's why you're puking and
you can't stand up without screaming.
So lower the dosages.
Less stress on my pancreas,
still battle the infection.
Lower dosages
will still be toxic.
I don't care!
I can handle the pain
of the pancreatitis.
I don't think
you can handle life
without a pancreas.
We keep you on these meds,
you'll spend the last 4 hours
of your life being able to see.
Take you off,
you'll go blind again.
But it'll give us time
to figure out what's eating your brain.
Fine.
What do we do next?
Man:
Eric?
Dad?
Yeah, you two can get caught up later.
Sir, I need you to come with me.
House.
Uh...what is this?
He isn't a what, he's a who.
They even have
the right to vote now.
Rodney Foreman, Cuddy.
Cuddy, Rodney Foreman.
- Nice to meet you, ma'am.
- This is Foreman's dad.
Yeah, I got that.
And Dr. Cuddy, here,
is the Dean of Medicine.
Remember that cool autopsy
I was telling you about, the one
that would save your son's life?
She's the one can give us
the green light to do it.
I understand
you don't want them to do it.
Dr. House didn't
seem to know why.
Mr. Foreman, I am doing
everything I can to get the CDC--
Won't be soon enough.
And my decision to follow
public health safety protocols--
Oh, don't blame the rules.
Don't want to hang this
on policy and protocol.
I'm well aware that
it may cost your son his life,
just as I am well aware that my decision has
a devastating effect on family and friends
without having them paraded in front of me.
Your son has an unknown,
contagious, deadly infection.
If we don't contain it here,
even more people could be at risk.
And I am capable of
empathizing with those people too
without having them paraded in front of me.
I understand.
What's wrong with your hand?
It's--it's called
a muscle contraction.
I thought this thing
was in your brain.
It is.
It just means the infection's moved
to the primary motor cortex,
which controls the muscles.
Aren't you glad
you sent me to med school?
Does it hurt?
No.
Is it gonna?
The-- the other guy...
He didn't seem to suffer too much,
he--just went in his sleep.
Steve still acting normal?
No sign of contractures.
They got the cop's body
in a locked, airtight bag.
And a guard on the door.
These Feds are seriously paranoid.
He hasn't gotten up
to peein hours. He's due.
You haven't sprinkled
Senokot granules on his doughnut?
His bowels would open up
like the Red Sea.
He wouldn't eat the doughnut.
Have you seriously
been down here for hours?
No.
I had to pee a couple times.
You've got to stop
blaming Cuddy for this.
Given that it is her fault,
that seems appropriate.
That part is her fault.
The part where somebody
wasted his time in the basement,
plotting the overthrow of
a government agency, that one's on you.
The only think I can do is think.
I can pretty much do that anywhere.
As long as no one's bugging me.
Rodney:
Did you call your brother?
No.
Did you?
It's not a big deal.
I sure would have liked
to see Mom, though.
You know
she can't travel anymore.
You tell her?
Why?
Just upset her for a while.
Then she wouldn't
remember for a while.
Think she should know?
She's lost
a lot of who she was.
She can't deal
with something like this.
And you can?
I still know you're
going to a better place.
It's easy for you, isn't it?
As long as you believe
I'm going to a better place,
dying ain't so bad.
I don't want you to be afraid.
If I'm not afraid of dying,
what the hell should I be afraid of, Dad?
I thought you believed.
I did.
I'm not so sure anymore.
I'm going to
pray for you, son.
I suggest you do the same.
"One Safe Place"
by Marc Cohn
# How many roads you've traveled #
# How many dreams you've chased #
# Across sand and sky and gravel #
# Looking for one safe place #
# Yeah #
# Hey yeah #
# One safe place #
# Yeah #
# Hey yeah #
# One safe place #
# Yeah #
# Hey, yeah #
[Phone rings]
Chase:
Field of vision is regressing.
And he's reached an 8
on the pain scale.
The disease pattern is following
the exact course as Joe's.
Only it's moving much faster
in Foreman.
Good! It's an anomaly.
Anomalies tell us things.
Why is this moving faster
in Foreman? What's different?
Could be a different strain
of the same disease?
Right-- we were wasting all this time
looking for an unknown disease.
We should have been looking for
a different strain of an unknown disease.
Joe's a cop.
He's into physical fitness,
he could have had a...
more powerful immune system, stronger metabolism.
Foreman's black.
What?
How long have you been
sitting on this information?
Lupus,  gout, glaucoma,
osteoarthritis, hypertension,
diabetes, stop me any time,
they all affect black people
more than whites.
Check everything.
Bacterials, fungals,
toxins, parasites.
Look for anything with
a documented racial disparity.
Wait.
The rat's showing symptoms?
No.
He's completely healthy.
Maybe that's the difference
between Foreman and the cop.
How are you feeling?
Why are you here?
Because you're a friend.
And I should be here.
I'm sorry House used my dad
to try and manipulate you.
You've got integrity, you aren't going
to change your mind just because
you're confronted by my father.
Thank you.
Just like I'm not going to forgive you
just because you come by here
and ask how I'm feeling.
You know I've had no choice.
Of course
you had a choice!
Regulations are clear.
And the punishment for
violating those regulations!
Is it death? Hmm?
Because frankly, I'm okay
if you get a fine, a suspension--
Hell, you can spend
a couple of years in jail
if it saves my life!
- You're dying too fast.
- Couldn't agree more.
Hey, Cuddy.
Having a nice visit?
What's that?
[Garbled]
Legionel--
Legionella pneumophila.
And why are you carrying
a vial of it around with you?
Foreman was perfectly healthy
before he got this infection.
Our cop wasn't.
He had Legionnaire's disease.
Our cop didn't turn into brain food
until we cured the Legionella.
Legionella
slowed down the disease.
- Why would that happen?
- No idea. I just know that it did.
- So you want to infect Foreman?
- Gonna tattle to the CDC?
Meds can't help me,
but a disease can?
Forget it!
Just take the pain away
and put me under.
If I put you under,
I can't monitor your pain.
If I can't monitor your pain,
I won't know if the Legionella's working.
I'm not consenting
to you giving me--
[Crash!]
Foreman:
What was that?
House:
Hmm.
I wish there could have been
a puff of smoke or something.
Would've been
much more dramatic.
Keep your slippers on.
Wouldn't want you
to cut your foot.
Are you feeling any better?
I can't breathe.
I'm dizzy.
And I can barely hear anything
over the sounds of my lungs crackling.
- That's the Legionella.
- Wow.
You figure that out from the symptoms,
or from the vial of stuff tossed in my room?
I'm trying to be professional here.
There's no reason to be nasty.
I'm in pain.
- So is House.
- And he's a delight.
He doesn't try
to kill his colleagues.
[Thermometer bleeps]
You can remove
the thermometer now.
It's down almost
a whole degree.
How's the pain?
Great. [Coughs]
This is the good kind.
How bad is it
compared to an hour ago?
No worse.
Wilson:
The Legionella helping?
Yeah.
- Good.
- Not great.
Didn't fix anything,
it just slowed it down.
The point was to give Steve
a little more time to get sick.
What are you going to do
if he never gets sick?
Brilliant.
Cameron, what type of illnesses
affect humans, but not rats?
Why are you asking me that?
Because I'm sure that
you spent the first 12 years of your life
dreaming of being a vet.
The rat is not getting sick.
Cameron is not getting sick.
Sorry.
It's okay,
it's not your fault.
Presumably, you're still healthy
because whatever it is, is not bloodborne.
Steve has no excuse.
He did everything that Foreman did.
Some bacterial infections
don't infect rats.
Foreman tested negative
for every bacterial infection
that would affect his brain.
And what infections
could he be positive for,
but test negative for?
When we test for infections,
we look for antibodies.
But what if the patient is infected,
but has no antibodies?
What if the body is
not fighting the infection?
- Why would--
- Eeeeh. I asked first.
Let's start with what,
we'll deal with the why later.
If the body doesn't recognize the infection,
our tests come back negative,
and the disease rampages
through the body unstopped.
Exactly like the cop
and exactly like Foreman.
And what if the patient was then
exposed to a second infection?
Like Legionella?
The body would recognize that infection,
increase the white count,
send in the troops to start fighting,
and the initial infection would get caught in the crossfire.
So the question becomes,
what type of bacteria infecition
affects humans but not rats,
and the human body
would be unlikely to recognize?
The answer is listeria.
I'm starting you
on *Ampengent.
(*AMP and gent?)
So you're basing this theory
on the test being negative
and your rat being healthy?
And in fact that
Legionella is helping you.
But the medicine
you want to give me
put an end to that.
Yeah.
And if it's not listeria,
the gent will do is cure
the Legionnaire's disease
and put
whatever is killing me
back into overdrive.
Stop asking me questions based
on the premise that I'm wrong.
The antibiotics are in the airlock.
I think the first biopsy
didn't give us the answer
because you didn't go deep enough.
I want you to do
a white matter brain biopsy.
Absolutely.
Don't blame you.
The world is such a complicated place
if you've got higher reasoning skills.
I'm often jealous of
small animals and retarded children.
Take the antibiotics.
There can be minimal damage
if it's done right.
If the surgeons drill
where I tell them to drill.
One slip--
you could spend the rest of your life
not being able to keep your drool in your mouth.
I'd rather be disabled than dead.
Sure, I make it look oh so sexy.
It's actually not as glamorous
as you might think.
The biopsy will tell us
for sure what's wrong.
The antibiotics
could do the same thing.
- Could, not will.
- We try it, we see.
The antibiotics will
bring back the pain.
Pain makes us bad decisions.
Fear of pain...
is almost as big a motivator.
Look, we still have time.
I will do that biopsy
if I have to.
But not a moment before.
Start Foreman
on I.V. antibiotics.
Where's his dad?
Where you supposed to be
when your son is dying?
He's not with him.
He's in the chapel.
I started your son
on a new course of treatment.
If it works, he'll get better.
If it doesn't, he won't.
While he's not getting better,
he's going to experience so much pain
that will have to put him
on a chemically-induded coma
while we figure out what to do next.
My son says you're
a manipulative bastard.
It's a pet name.
I call him Dr. Bling.
I assume you're here for a reason.
What do you want from me?
When your son is in a coma,
you're the one who's gonna have to
make the medical decisions for him.
Oh, whatever you decide is fine.
- You don't care what I do?
- I'm not a doctor. What do I know?
Except what Eric tells me.
He says you're the best doctor
he's ever worked with.
I need your help.
There's nothing
I can give you for the pain.
I want to be put out.
I can have a nurse in here
in 5 minutes.
No.
Want some help.
I might not come back.
I've never done a will.
I'll call a lawyer for you.
I want you to be
my medical proxy.
All the things that piss me off
about you in House's office--
you're too emotional,
too caring, too cautious--
they're all good things
on this floor.
- Your dad is--
- No.
- He cares about you.
- So do you.
I can't do this.
We expect family members
to make decisions about their loved ones
after a 10-minute briefing that
we're agonizing over even
with years of medical experience.
That's from my article.
I'm sorry, Allison.
I shouldn't have stolen your article.
I shouldn't have exposed you.
You were a friend.
I need to know that we're okay.
No.
I'll be your proxy,
but we're not okay.
You're scared you're dying.
and that's the only reason
you want to set things right.
We're going to
get you better first,
and then,
if you still want to apologize,
I'll be around.
I'll call that lawyer.
Any improvement?
Well, as far as we can tell,
the only thing the antibiotics
are treating is the Legionella.
I think we need to consider
alternate theories.
Like what?
- We do the biopsy. We--
- Give the antibiotics more time.
There is no more time.
The pain is almost unbearable already.
So he's almost in unbearable pain.
He's not almost dead.
Which means
we have more time.
Mr. Foreman?
We need to
put your son in a coma.
You should be there.
It's a medical procedure, right?
Yeah.
But once we put him out,
if--if we don't solve this,
he won't wake up.
What should I say?
Should I talk to him
like it's going to be... okay?
Or should I be
saying good-bye?
I need... to know
what people say when--
Just tell him you love him.
Hey, son.
Hey, Dad.
It's going to be okay.
You don't know that.
I.. know.
You don't.
I don't want to miss you.
I love you too, Dad.
[Sobs quietly]
Hey.
It's going to be okay.
- Can we do this now?
- Yeah, of course.
I accept your apology.
[Sniffles]
Why weren't you with Foreman?
I hang out in the basement, you rag on me.
I stay in my office, you rag on me.
- Honkey just can't buy a break.
- Do the biopsy.
Based on the cop's progression,
I figure he's got
about another 4 hours before--
You figure?
You're playing Russian roulette,
but the gun's pointed at him.
No, cutting open his head
is what's dangerous.
Oh, it's dangerous.
Well, what would people think?
The reason you don't see patients is
because if you know them,
you'll give a crap about them.
I know you.
If you give a crap,
you stop making outrageous calls.
If this was any other patient,
you'd have damned the risk and
cut their head open a long time ago.
He's out.
The EEG shows he's still in pain.
The antibiotics have had
more than enough time.
We're doing the brain biopsy.
Not unless you people can't
come up with something clever
in the next 3 hours.
Now.
We're doing it now.
Who died and made you boss?
Foreman.
It's legal.
House:
He's out of his mind.
Yesterday he was giggling
about a hole in a guy's head.
Then hire a lawyer
and challenge it.
In the meantime,
Cameron's in charge.
Why would he sign that?
It's nothing personal,
Mr. Foreman.
My son doesn't trust me.
How exactly is that not personal?
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
You're talking
about this man's son.
You're denying him the right
to be a part of--
Oh, shut up, House.
If you want to do the biopsy,
do the biopsy.
If House tries to interfere,
let me know and I will take care of it.
Yeah. You're a hero. If it wasn't for you,
we'd be cutting into a dead guy's head
instead of Foreman's.
Sorry.
Thanks.
- That was great!
- It was rude and unnecessary.
- Yeah.
- Go away.
Give me time.
- We're out of time.
- An hour.
What does "out of time" mean?
His O2 stats are
94 right now.
His lungs are about 90.
The danger of fatal arrhythmia
doesn't increase.
So what?
There's no point in waiting.
You were right. We should be
cutting into a corpse's head.
Yeah, we should be,
except the CDC's got
the cop's body and--
There's got to be
other bodies.
You think this thing
has killed other people?
No.
That apartment was a dump.
Just because Steve McQueen
didn't get sick doesn't mean
some other vermin didn't.
You give me an hour.
I go back there, I find a dead animal,
I cut its head open instead of Foreman's.
Foreman's already
on 100% oxygen.
Once his O2 seds hit 90,
I can't wait any longer.
Where's your suit?
Either you'll find the answer,
or I'll find the answer.
Doesn't matter.
Chase:
Prep the drill.
We've got to be ready to go.
Forget the signal.
[Cell phone rings]
92.
I found a blind bird.
Cameron:
Great.
How fast can you get it in here?
I'll know
in about 30 seconds.
[The irrigation pump starts working]
[Cell phone rings]
You better have the bird.
The surgical team's in place.
I screwed up.
How can you not
capture a blind bird?
That's not what I meant.
I screwed up the first time
through this place.
Foreman told you
everywhere he went.
It's not where, it's when.
He came here
early afternoon.
Me and Steve came through
2 hours too late.
You were 6 hours early.
It's the water.
The irrigation system only pumps--
House, I tested the water.
The water's clean.
[Cell phone rings]
House.
We tested the wrong water.
He stole cable,
he stole fertilizer,
and he stole water.
It's riddled with Naegleria.
I know.
You already did the biopsy.
I thought I had no choice.
How's my son?
He has primary
amebic meningoencephalitis.
It's a parasitethat goes through the nose
and migrates into the brain,
where it feeds on brain cells.
The Legionella attacked the parasite.
That's why the disease slowed down.
Is it treatable?
We started him on an antiparasitic, and
the amoebas will clear out of his system.
And he'll be okay?
Then--then we'll wean him
out of the coma--
Will he be okay?
There'll be no lasting damage
from the parasite.
But the surgery?
We don't know.
# How many roads we've traveled #
# How many dreams we've chased #
# Across sand and sky and gravel #
# But looking for one safe place #
# Yeah #
# Hey yeah #
# One safe place #
# Yeah #
# Hey yeah  #
Up and at 'em.
How are you feeling?
Can you talk?
I don't feel anything.
Are you numb?
No, I--
I mean...
I don't feel any pain.
Keep your head still.
Follow my finger.
I'm okay.
Your breath stinks.
And you're peeing into a bag.
What are our names?
You did the biopsy?
Thank you.
Names?
Cameron.
My dad.
And the manipulative bastard.
You remembered.
[Laughs tearfully]
How you doing, Dad?
Great.
Relieved. Great.
What did I have?
Naegleria.
Biopsy showed the amoeba.
CDC autopsy eventually
found the amoeba.
And House found it
in the water on the cop's roof.
Wiggle your left toes.
Foreman:
Wait, wait.
You went back and
she did the biopsy?
Your left toes, Foreman.
I just did.
No, you didn't.
He can't move his toes?
He can move them.
Raise your right arm.
What?
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : Vaccine
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net