(AMUSEMENT PARK MUSIC PLAYING)
All right. Stand here.
You're just tall enough.
I...
I don't...
I don't think I am.
It just goes around.
There's nothing to be
scared of, all right?
I didn't say I was scared.
It'll be fun.
Come on, when I was a kid,
this was
my favorite thing ever.
I don't like rides.
All right. All right.
(STUTTERING)
I just...
I thought it would be fun.
I shouldn't be
making you do this.
Uh...
Let's go home.
We can have fun at home.
No, Daddy. Wait.
The ride does look like fun.
Oh, this is awesome.
(SCREAMING LOUDLY)
MR. HARTMANN:
Alice? Are you all right?
Honey, you all right?
Alice? Alice? Are you okay?
MR. HARTMANN:
Nothing happened.
EDIE: Something happened.
It was a little kiddie ride.
She hates those rides.
I don't understand
why you insist on
making her...
Okay, I appreciate
the fullness of your answers,
but I just wanted
to know if she'd had
any history of
abdominal problems.
No.
The admitting doctor noted
no family history of...
I have an aunt
with Crohn's disease.
You didn't mention that?
I forgot what it
was called, okay?
Your aunt's got
a million things
wrong with her.
If you paid attention
for five minutes...
I doubt it's Crohn's.
She has none of
the other symptoms.
You're alone with
her for eight hours,
she ends up in the hospital.
I'm wondering if
we can focus on
answering the questions,
Mrs. Hartmann.
I'm not Mrs. Hartmann.
We're divorced.
I suspected.
And your past generosity
made me think of you.
We're half a million dollars
from our goal.
Of course,
this is a naming opportunity
for your foundation.
Is there a problem?
There's something
on your face.
It's, uh...
(CLEARING HER THROAT)
Excuse me.
Oh...
CUDDY: Oh, God.
I'm sitting in there
hoping it's a sniper,
because at least then
the sociopath isn't
my employee.
This baby won me second place
in the clinic's weekly
"weirdest thing pulled out
of an orifice" contest.
I am this close
to putting a new lab
in Oncology.
You do not want
to know what came in first.
House.
It rhymes with fucchini.
Give me his pills.
Where's my prescription?
No more
free-floating prescriptions.
Princeton P.D.
Has already forced
Wilson to shut down.
A cop says,
"Boo," Wilson shuts down.
Every doctor in
this place is afraid
to make a move
without covering his ass.
You think maybe
you're shouting
at the wrong person?
Tritter's obviously
out to get me.
He doesn't...
You forged prescriptions!
Allegedly.
Your pain has become my pain.
From now on,
you get reasonable doses
at reasonable times.
But I hurt in
an unreasonable way.
Then dip into
your secret stash.
Tritter took it.
Then move on to your secret,
secret stash.
I ran out.
Then move on to your secret,
secret, secret stash.
Parents say she's
not on any meds.
If the pancreatitis
wasn't set off by drugs,
and she hasn't been sick,
that leaves trauma
or some kind of
structural defect.
Put up the CT.
What's that density there?
Shadow.
Looks normal to me.
We got
a referral from...
HOUSE: Excuse me.
You stash your drugs
in a lupus textbook?
It's never lupus.
Who's got gallstones,
and why do we care?
Gallstones?
Biliary duct is dilated,
probably from
a stone lodged in it.
Must've caused a nasty
case of pancreatitis.
She's six. Six-year-olds
don't get gallstones.
So, she didn't
have pancreatitis?
Your theory is
an invisible gallstone?
His theory correctly
predicted pancreatitis.
You might want to wait until
he actually
tells us his theory
before you start
kissing his theory's ass.
My theory is...
Vanishing gallstone.
She had it and it passed.
Those things travel
in packs.
The rest of them are
probably hiding out
in her gallbladder.
Do an ultrasound.
If I'm right,
take out the organ,
so we can analyze the stones.
CHASE: I wasn't
kissing his ass.
FOREMAN: It must have
just looked that way
from our angle,
you on your knees,
House bending over.
He predicted
the pancreatitis.
It's his dad's fault.
My dad was an ass.
But you did
everything he wanted you to,
and in return,
you got
everything you wanted.
Yeah, it's that simple.
The strategy worked.
Dad got him a cushy job,
paid for his cushy life.
Cut me out
of his cushy will.
Told you.
It's just his nature.
Poor guy's
hard-wired to kiss ass.
House was right.
Gallstones.
I didn't know a kid
could get gallstones.
It's unusual.
That's why we need to
see what's causing it.
We'd like to remove
Alice's gallbladder
and analyze the stones.
Sure.
No.
Just 'cause I said sure?
I am capable of
my own thoughts.
It's a simple procedure.
The gallbladder
isn't essential to...
The doctor thinks
we should do it.
We should do it, Edie.
You think maybe we should
get a second opinion
before we start removing
our child's organs?
It's an effective use
of taxpayer's money.
I'm actually off this week.
I'm guessing
you don't have a family.
Most people have
enough going on
in their lives
that they don't have
to personalize every slight.
This isn't personal.
Not anymore.
My head of Oncology
had to shut down.
My entire staff are
afraid to make a move
without covering their ass.
I think you're angry
at the wrong person.
You think Dr. Wilson deserved
to have his assets seized,
his entire practice ruined?
No.
So, you just don't care?
This is how I get
what I want.
I put pressure on people,
and if it doesn't work
on Wilson,
it'll work on you.
You punish the innocent.
None of you are innocent.
Not one of you.
Not one of you has
told me the truth
about Dr. House.
The pills allow him
to cope with the pain.
No. The pills distort reality.
He is an addict.
He's not out robbing
a liquor store, or...
No, he's treating people.
He needs to find
a different way to cope
before he kills somebody.
If he hasn't
done that already.
If you're right,
he has a medical problem.
It should be dealt with
by doctors.
Not by...
It's not being
dealt with by doctors.
Doctors are covering it up.
The whole point
of the criminal
justice system
is to make things right
when everything else fails.
With all due respect,
you have failed.
Sorry, didn't know
you wanted your kid dead.
Although, for a couple of G's,
I can still make it happen.
Who the hell are you?
I am a complete stranger,
who apparently cares more
about whether your kid dies
than you do.
You're Dr. House.
You've seen my stage show.
She's not dying.
She has pancreatitis.
Once you've treated that,
I'm taking her home.
And do what, burn sage?
I want you
to do the surgery.
My father had gallstones.
They were totally harmless.
Alice had one bad one,
but it passed.
For all we know,
this is over.
And for all we know,
she could get
sick again tomorrow.
Then I'll take her
to her pediatrician.
She's six, Rob.
She shouldn't have
unnecessary surgery.
Or a moron for a mom,
but what can you do?
You're the doctor.
I'm the mother.
I outrank you.
Live with it.
I've read the file.
You've got 15 minutes.
It's people like this
who killed Copernicus.
Galileo.
Either way.
And they just
locked Galileo up.
They killed his spirit,
and nobody likes a show-off.
Luckily, Alice Hartmann
has a dad who's willing
to see reason.
Reason, as defined by
slavishly deferring to you.
Their doctor.
Your Honor,
I've had no opportunity
to consult my attorney.
There's no time.
All I want is
a second opinion before...
No time.
Your testimony is
their child will die
if I don't grant
this motion right now?
Am I under oath?
Let's say yes.
My testimony is
that this child
might die if you
don't grant this motion
right now.
Literally no time
for a second opinion?
Wouldn't be as good
as the first opinion.
Dr. Cuddy,
what do you think?
She's not
a specialist in this area.
Her opinion is worthless.
Dr. Cuddy, what do
you think of Dr. House?
Is he as big a jerk
as I think he is?
Bigger.
But he knows what
he's talking about.
Got a page.
She's complaining
about her stitches.
The nurse just said
that's completely normal.
Did you get the test results
for the gallstones?
Any minute now.
No time for a second opinion,
but the test takes three...
My skin hurts.
I know I no longer
have the right
to demand it but could
you please take a look?
Sure.
She's pissed,
so now she's just looking
for things to go wrong.
You're right, I'm so petty
I hope she dies so it
vindicates my opinion.
I didn't mean that, sweetie.
Mommy was being sarcastic.
She's a few years away
from grasping sarcasm,
don't you think?
Guys.
I already gave
you that number.
Simple surgical procedure
turns a little girl
into The English Patient.
What gives?
Must be allergic
to something we used
in the surgery.
Cameron,
C-A-M-E-R-O-N.
This is my office.
I'm talking.
There are people
here who work for me.
They're not listening.
Explain this to me.
Tritter froze my account.
They're checking theirs.
I'm on hold with a lawyer.
Call Wilson's lawyer.
He'll tell you exactly how
and why you're screwed.
This kid has no
history of allergies so...
You gotta talk to Tritter.
You gotta make this go away.
CHASE: Yeah, great plan.
The man is obviously
open to reason.
Well, here's the plan,
we do nothing.
HOUSE: We while away the time
diagnosing the patient.
The stones were
calcium bilirubinate.
Pigment stones.
Which are non-conclusive.
Kid presented
with low-grade fever,
mild anemia.
That, plus the stones,
indicates bacterial infection.
Bacterial infections
don't cause a vesicular rash,
and doing nothing
is not a plan.
It's specifically
a lack of a plan.
We cut into her belly,
the bad boys escape.
They swarm over,
colonize the wounds,
and kaplow, vesicular rash.
Allergic reaction is
100 times more likely,
with or without a history.
Fever and anemia
could have been
symptoms of pancreatitis.
Hello?
CAMERON: Thank you
for your help.
They froze my accounts.
"Thank you for your help"?
It's not her fault.
He hasn't gotten
to mine, yet.
I'm gonna withdraw
as much as I can,
as fast as I can.
Lunch is on me.
Do a scratch test.
Check for allergies.
When it comes back negative,
start broad-spectrum
antibiotics.
Bullies bully.
They don't get a reaction,
they lose interest.
Now go do what I ask
before I stick
your heads in toilets.
How'd Otter get here?
Daddy got him last night.
It was at the dry cleaner.
They close at 6:00.
How'd you get it?
I drove over there,
and I knocked for
about 10 minutes,
and then I begged.
How about some ice cream
for when this is through?
My tummy hurts.
Ginger ale?
Yeah?
I'll take over.
Be right back.
He's always been really good
at the big romantic gestures,
but ask him to do the dishes,
or show up for a meal
on time, or drive her...
Almost done here.
What are you doing here?
I work here.
You passively-aggressively
gave up your practice.
I have clinic hours.
And now you're
passively-aggressively
spreading peanut butter
with a big sign
around your neck saying,
"Wilson doesn't
have enough cash
for the cafeteria."
You know,
before Lenny Bruce died
of a drug overdose...
(EXCLAIMING)
If you're going
to confront me
with everyone who
ever abused narcotics,
I think I'm gonna have to get
something to read.
...he was arrested
on obscenity charges.
He went through
a series of arrests
and trials,
because he just couldn't
stop challenging the police.
He became obsessed
with his own legal problems,
and his act turned into long,
humorless rants
about fascist cops and
the violation of his rights.
I get it, I get it.
I need to change
my nightclub act.
You think more props?
House, scratch test
is getting results,
a lot of results.
MR. HARTMANN: How can she be
allergic to everything?
She can't be.
It has to be an infection.
You see
a positive allergy test
and decide it's infection?
The bacteria got
into the scratches
in her back.
The infection's radial.
The shape of this isn't.
Eat this.
I don't feel like eating.
It'll make you better.
A sandwich?
Magic sandwich.
There's no such thing as...
Just take a damn bite,
okay, kid?
Amazing how she
didn't go into
anaphylactic shock.
That's
diagnostically ridiculous.
Right, she's allergic
to everything except peanuts.
If she is allergic,
antibiotics could cause
a massive systemic reaction.
If she's allergic,
but she's not.
FOREMAN: Chase, you're right.
The shape indicates allergy.
The tests indicate allergy.
Just because she's
not allergic to peanuts,
doesn't mean
she's not allergic
to lidocaine or...
Chase, hang the bag.
You can grow
a backbone tomorrow.
No, I'm not giving
my daughter drugs
that could shut
her system down.
You know what else
shuts down systems?
Death.
Sorry. I can't let you
do this.
Luckily,
Alice Hartmann has a mom,
who is willing to see reason.
You were in here yesterday,
telling me
her father's guardianship
was best for her.
I honestly figured I'd get
a different judge today.
You agree with Dr. House now?
Now my kid actually is sick.
She was sick yesterday.
Her pediatrician
doesn't know what's wrong
with her,
says Dr. House is the best.
She loses guardianship,
and all of a sudden
House is a hero.
It's got nothing to
do with me deciding...
JUDGE: Hey, zip it!
I've heard enough.
This lawyering thing is easy.
You shut up, too.
Arguing over every decision
is a waste of her time
and mine.
Since her parents can't,
or won't, agree,
I'm awarding
temporary guardianship
to a doctor,
who'll place
the health of the child
above all else...
I don't think Dr. House
is capable of...
...Dr. Cuddy.
Yes, Your Honor.
No, I was finishing
my sentence.
The kid's all yours.
HOUSE.: 3.:00, give me
the pills.
I don't even know this kid.
How am I supposed to decide
what's best for her?
Fine, I'll choose.
I'm going to side with
the angry doctor's opinion.
Give me my pills.
We're not gonna
go broad-spectrum.
If there's any chance
that she's allergic...
There is no chance.
Of course there's a chance.
I'm appealing.
No, you're not.
If you think it's bacterial,
pick one antibiotic.
It's not going to be enough.
We need to go broad-spectrum.
It kills bugs.
That's what you want.
We'll go with metronidazole.
TRITTER.: You don't have to
testify he's broken any laws,
though I'm sure you could.
Just how many pills
he takes in a day.
'Cause I'm fairly confident
I can prove that he didn't
have that many
legitimate prescriptions.
I really hope no one dies
while I'm sitting
here not talking to you.
I, uh, I had a, uh...
Had a buddy at Trenton P.D.
Do some digging.
Your brother,
locked up for drugs.
Your own flesh and blood,
and you don't even visit.
But your boss
practices medicine on drugs,
time to start
lying to the cops.
If I run out for coffee,
will I get back
before you make your point?
You testify,
I can make sure
that Marcus
goes free on parole
in less than two months.
My brother and I, uh...
We grew up in the same home.
But...
I made something of myself.
He didn't.
Dr. Foreman,
the way you talk,
you'd think
you never committed
any crimes yourself.
Now, you and Dr. House,
you are both cold bastards.
You don't give a damn
about your brother,
and you can't stand House.
But I do expect you
to take this deal,
because you hate
hypocrisy more.
House has had 1,000 chances.
You've got two chances.
Why is your brother
stuck at one?
CUDDY: Well, if she were
allergic to this antibiotic,
we would have seen it by now.
I think we are
out of the woods
as far as that goes.
Guess they occasionally
get one right.
You're going to
be glib about this?
You almost killed her.
I made a choice.
The same choice
you made yesterday,
only when I make
it I'm an imbecile.
Every decision you have made
has been wrong.
When this is over,
I'm suing for sole custody.
Because I trusted
doctors when you didn't?
Because it's not just about
the past two days.
MR. HARTMANN: Like you have
the hotline on what's best
for Alice. She loves me.
EDIE: She never does
her homework
when she's with you.
She never brushes her hair.
Her heart's racing,
pressure's rising.
The two of you get out.
I'm her mother.
You can't just...
You fight,
she has an anxiety attack.
The two of you are
making her worse.
Get out, and don't come back.
How's the kid doing?
Much better as of
about two hours ago.
You got any money for lunch?
If you like
parsley and croutons.
Tritter finally
froze my accounts.
Really?
You surprised?
Why wouldn't he?
I figured if he
was singling you out,
you must have done
something different.
What? Like talking?
Yeah.
And now that he's
frozen your accounts,
you probably will.
You need the cash, right?
He doesn't freeze my accounts,
I'm guilty.
He does freeze my accounts,
Is Alice having
some procedure done?
She's fine. She's resting.
Where?
In her room.
Where you're not supposed...
I was just at the window.
There's no one in there.
Her backpack
wasn't there, either.
You don't think her
father could have...
Call Security.
Get a gurney.
MR. HARTMANN:
She's stiff. She can't move.
I don't know what happened.
She seemed fine.
Help her. Please.
On the plus side,
she could medal in luge.
Muscle rigidity
is almost
exclusively neurological.
Neuroaxonal dystrophy?
She's the right age.
CHASE: Except that her liver's
starting to shut down.
No dystrophy would...
Metronidazole, great idea.
"Let's not go broad-spectrum.
"Let's not take any chances
on actually curing her."
House, can you focus
on the case?
No, because I'm in pain,
'cause you think
that compromise
is the answer to everything.
I need more pills.
Muscle rigidity
plus liver involvement
means Wilson's.
No. No corneal rings,
no mental changes.
CAMERON: Then what?
I need more pills!
No! You are
on a reasonable...
What the hell does
"reasonable" mean?
Keep it quiet.
Her BP reacts to stress
and yelling is not...
If you think that
I'm not in pain,
then don't give me anything.
Keep me away
from the aspirin,
but if I'm in
a butt-load of pain,
I need a butt-load of pills.
Fine. You need more pills.
You're not getting them.
You can have all
the aspirin you want.
FOREMAN: I say we draw straws.
Loser drives down to Trenton
and scores him an eight ball.
Which one of you two
gave her an aspirin?
What?
Her symptoms fit
Reye's Syndrome.
Which doesn't make any sense,
unless she took aspirin.
Rob?
No way. She's a kid.
I've read
the 800 warning labels.
I'm not even angry.
I just want her to be okay.
HOUSE: She's lying.
She's angry,
'cause you kidnapped her kid.
She'll be angrier
if the kid dies.
I didn't.
One aspirin
combined with
a pre-existing infection,
that's all it takes
to set off an attack.
I'm not lying.
Well, sure, you've
certainly earned our trust.
Where was Alice
the night before she came in?
With me. Well, at my house.
I went out.
She stayed
with the babysitter.
Where were you?
None of your business.
You hired someone
that might have
poisoned our daughter.
She's 15.
She's very responsible.
Is she a 15-year-old
pharmacist?
Or just some kid
from down the street
who needed 20 bucks
for lip gloss
and a couple of Tiger Beats?
Put your kid
on charcoal hemoperfusion.
Shouldn't we see
what the babysitter
has to say?
I know what she's gonna say.
She's gonna lie
to save her business.
I need more pills.
We are going
to use this machine
to clean your blood.
It goes out of you
and through a filter,
like the filter
in a fish tank.
It's kind of cool, actually.
I'm scared.
It won't hurt.
It takes a while,
so it'll be boring,
but it won't hurt.
It's going to
make you better.
They hate each other,
don't they?
We're never going
to be together again.
Well, you never know.
You're going to break
out the rubber hoses,
the bright lights?
I'm not going to testify
just because I have
to borrow lunch money.
I know.
Women don't give up guys
that they're in love with.
I'm not in love with House.
The guy is
unhinged and unethical,
does what he wants
with no concern for others,
but you stand by him.
It can't just be
loyalty and respect?
No.
I'm a girl, so I must
be in love with him.
Not because you're a girl.
Because 10 years ago
you got an A in calculus,
until you ratted yourself out.
Showed your professor
a mistake he missed.
Because you married a man...
Don't go there.
You used to be someone
who did the right thing.
House has changed you.
Do you think it's all
been for the better?
How's it going?
Boring.
Told you.
FOREMAN: So far so good.
Just like five minutes ago,
and 10 minutes before that.
What's the matter?
(WHIMPERING)
(YELLING)
She's thrown a clot.
Let's get her out of here.
I'll call the OR.
You said it wouldn't hurt.
(YELLING)
Found it.
She's burning up.
Give me a sec.
Foreman, she is on fire.
Almost there.
Get me some
cooling blankets now.
Right away.
Every time we touch this kid,
something goes wrong.
Bad mojo is not a diagnosis.
You really have to
flash your private stash
in front of me?
You find it
easier to lie for me
if it's more subtle?
Fine.
You told your associates
that I had
frozen your accounts.
Yes.
Smart lie.
You figured they'd
think there was a reason
that you'd been singled out.
Like that you'd agreed
to testify against House.
Yeah, I assume
that's why you did it.
You have a reputation
as a bit of an opportunist.
You already gave
your boss up once
from what I heard.
To save my job.
He goes down now,
I lose my job.
You lose your job,
you find another one.
You get fired,
your chances
don't look so hot.
Why would he fire me?
Because you rolled on him.
I haven't rolled on him.
I think you will.
And he's gonna
think you already did.
As far as he knows,
my accounts are frozen
just like everyone else's.
In 24 hours, all three
of you will have access
to your accounts again.
Why would you do...
If I was looking
at this as an outsider,
I would say
it was because
Detective Tritter had
what appeared to be
a very pleasant lunch
with Dr. Chase.
(TRITTER CHUCKLING)
(SIGHING)
Yeah.
The two of them appear
to be working together.
CUDDY: How the hell are
there no ice packs
in the OR?
Clot's out.
Ice packs aren't
gonna hold it for long.
FOREMAN:
Where are the blankets?
CUDDY: In the ER.
They're dealing with
a four-car collision.
We need to cool this kid down
before her brain melts.
What are you doing?
She got a major
dose of heparin
to thin her blood
for the procedure.
Could have induced
thrombocytopenia.
That's unlikely.
The charcoal
would have absorbed
a lot of the heparin.
She's been anemic.
Could be
a primary blood disorder.
Or we never
cured the infection.
Are you saying
she never had Reye's?
We just put that
little girl through
excruciating pain.
The pain wasn't
House's fault.
Even if
the clot was a reaction
to what we gave her,
we still had to...
I don't need you
to cover my ass!
What I need is my Vicodin!
Two pills every six hours,
like I'm on an allowance.
She's giving a cop leverage
over medical decisions.
What the hell?
Why don't we get
a plumber in here,
ask his opinion?
Hey, Cuddy,
you know any rodeo clowns
who can weigh in...
Where the hell is she?
Look at her arm.
I told you it
was an infection.
We fixed the infection.
Well, apparently not.
I asked you for
broad-spectrum.
You put her on
the bare minimum.
It's a good thing you failed
to become a mom,
because you suck at it.
What's so good
about this rash?
Good guesses, but no.
It's on parts of her body
that we haven't touched.
She's got a fever of 103.
She's in and out
of consciousness,
but it's not
a reaction to anything we did.
Our mojo is off the table.
Which means...
Oh, so close.
Means thanks to Cuddy's
candy-ass approach,
broad-spectrum antibiotics
are no longer an option.
This thing has
grown horns and fangs.
We've gotta figure
out what species it is,
go in with a spear
to the heart.
Okay, you guys are sulking.
I don't really care why,
but apparently
I can't do my job
without finding out.
Tritter released
our bank accounts.
Horrible, horrible news.
Wow, I'm glad we didn't
let that fester.
If she did have Reye's,
then it could
be varicella.
They're associated.
He released our money.
You do know what that means?
The correct question is,
how could it be varicella
given that she's not itchy?
Rickettsial pox causes rash,
fever and muscle pain.
CAMERON: Pain, not paralysis.
Rocky Mountain spotted fever,
on the other hand,
rash, fever,
anemia, paralysis.
And I didn't say
anything to Tritter.
Neither did I.
Maybe he wants us to think
that one of us talked.
It worked.
You were with him.
We were all with him.
We weren't laughing with him.
Maybe he just gave up.
Start the kid on
chloramphenicol
for Rocky Mountain
spotted fever.
Can we talk?
No.
I really think we...
Either you screwed me
and you want absolution,
or you didn't and
you want applause.
Either way,
I'm not interested.
I'm busy.
You okay?
Yeah, sure.
What I meant by
"Are you okay?"
Is "What
the hell did House do?"
Nothing.
What did he say?
I've seen House be rude
1,000 times,
usually to achieve something.
I have never seen him be mean
just because he can.
Seriously?
What did he say?
Nothing. It doesn't matter.
Well, I've seen
House be rude to you
1,000 times,
but I've never seen it
get to you.
People think House
has no inner censor,
but the fact is he
holds himself back.
Because when he
wants to hurt,
he knows just where
to poke a sharp stick.
I have been trying
to get pregnant,
and House knew.
He told me I would
fail as a mother.
And you're this upset
because you think he's right?
I've had three
separate implantations.
The first two never took.
The last one, I lost.
I'm sorry.
You didn't fail.
Those were physical events.
A little girl is scared
and in pain.
I was awkward,
terrified of
doing the wrong thing.
That's normal. That's...
I didn't hug her.
I didn't even reach out
and hold her hand.
I told her it
was gonna be okay.
She needed reassurance.
I told her, her folks
might get back together.
When I see people
with their kids,
it's so natural.
It's like they have
an instruction book
imprinted on their genes.
Maybe I just
didn't get a copy.
Maybe my wanting to
be a mother is like
a tone-deaf person
wanting to sing opera,
or a paraplegic
who wants to...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Well, I see what you mean
about House poking
the right spot.
Chloramphenicol
isn't working.
What dose
did you give her?
Yeah, maybe Chase
screwed up.
You always end up there.
Just getting a jump on it.
I doubled her up.
The infection's morphed.
It's moved into
her muscle sheath.
Necrotizing fasciitis?
That's impervious to drugs.
The only treatment
is to cut away
the infected area.
So, we amputate.
Arm and leg?
CAMERON: We can't cut
a six-year-old kid in half
without a confirmed diagnosis.
Moves too quickly,
and we waited too long.
We don't have
time for a culture.
We can at least observe her
for a few hours,
confirm the rash is spreading.
It spreads, she dies.
You're talking
about crippling her.
We're not even certain
this was an infection.
Right! She's six!
She's cute!
She can't have
flesh-eating bacteria!
It's just wrong!
Let's cure her
with sunshine and puppies.
Cute kids die of
terrible illnesses,
innocent doctors go to jail,
and it's because
cowards like you
won't stand up
and do what's required.
You can sit around
and moan about
who's the bigger weakling.
I'm going to go do my job.
EDIE.: What kind of quality
of life will she have
without...
HOUSE.: Great thing about life,
it's got qualities.
MR. HARTMANN.:
And if we can't agree?
CUDDY: I don't know.
He's yelled at us before.
Because he thought
our theories were dumb.
Not because our theories
were sending him to jail.
He's going
through withdrawal.
Could be causing
mild paranoia.
It'll pass. We just
have to suffer through it.
We never ruled out allergy.
We gave her drugs.
She had no negative reaction.
We cut open her belly,
she got a rash on her belly.
We did a scratch test
on her back,
she got a rash on her back.
I know House ruled out mojo,
but it can't be
a coincidence...
A little late to
play differential games,
isn't it?
Get that thing away
from me.
I don't want to get burned.
Laser pointers
don't burn you, genius.
Skin, no. Retina, yes.
You don't trust my aim?
Maybe you should
cover any sensitive...
He was wrong
about the puppies.
House! You got to stop
the surgery.
She doesn't have
necrotizing fasciitis.
Oh, good.
She's got
erythropoietic protoporphyria.
She's allergic to light.
It's genetic.
Either parent
could have carried it.
I know what it is.
Infection fits better.
She gets worse
every time she goes
under surgical lights,
dad takes her outside...
Her liver's shot, too.
Did she swallow a flashlight?
Stop the surgery.
Get the hell out of my way.
No, I'm...
Light damages
the blood cells,
the damaged
blood cells contain
protoporphyrin,
the protoporphyrin
builds up in the liver.
That's why
the liver's shutting down.
(PHONE RINGING)
Stop.
How can she be
allergic to light?
She's never had
this problem before.
The negative reaction
starts at birth.
It reaches critical mass
around this age.
CUDD Y.: Her blood cells
create chemicals
in reaction to light.
When they reach the liver,
it tries to filter
out the bad cells.
The chemicals
damage the liver,
and one
byproduct is gallstones.
So, she'll just
keep getting worse?
EP can be managed.
We'll give her beta-carotene.
She's gonna need
special light bulbs
and filters on the windows.
She's probably gonna need
to be home-schooled.
Her life will be complicated,
but she will live.
How do you get
something like this?
It's genetic.
So, one of us...
Both of you must be carriers.
She's gonna want to see you
when she wakes up.
So, don't screw it up.
So, what's new?
House missed one.
That's happened before.
He nearly maimed
a little girl.
And I got it right.
And I told him,
and it didn't matter.
Chase, you solved one.
You helped a patient,
that better be
enough for you.
Beckett was going
to call his play
Waiting for House's Approval,
but decided it was too grim.
Trust me,
I'm not waiting anymore.
I'm gonna need
30 pieces of silver.
www.tvsubtitles.net