There were some nice guys there,
but they're all so quiet,
awkward smiles and sweaty palms.
I'm not expecting Brad Pitt
to walk into St. Theresa's,
just someone who makes me laugh,
has a nice smile, full head of hair.
You know, someone
like you, Mr. Franklin.
It's a shame they're
going to cremate you.
Can I help you?
Martin!
My purse is right there. Go
ahead, take whatever you want.
Irene, you call me?
Irene?
Irene!
How are you doing?
I'm fine.
FYI, if you ask me, it's more
the guys' fault than yours.
And House isn't blameless, either.
If he hadn't pitted us
all against each other...
It was my fault. My mistake.
Was that always there?
Hello?
Sure.
It's House.
Good morning, angels.
As you will see from the file, we
have quite the interesting case.
It's not often you get a
patient who sees dead people.
What file?
What the hell?
I gave it to Bosley a half-hour ago.
It was not a half-hour,
it was 10 minutes.
And he made copies of
the ER records first.
Less lip, more whip.
I only agreed to take this case
because you said that this mocha
frapalicious would have whip on it.
Fine. I'll refer the case to Foreman.
Can't. Mercy fired him.
Gimme. He got fired?
He disobeyed a superior officer under
fire. He's lucky he wasn't executed.
How do you know about it?
You keeping tabs on him?
Girls talk.
When Bosley drags his
ancient ass in there...
I'm here.
Twenty-four year old funeral cosmetician
suffered a grand mal seizure at work.
Why does he get to be Bosley?
You want to be Bosley? Bosley's,
like, the asexual messenger boy.
She had a vision of being raped
by a cadaver before passing out.
Seizure rules out psychiatric illness.
No history of epilepsy,
head trauma or drug use.
Bosley keeps his job while they
replace five angels over three seasons.
Could be a tumor to the temporal lobe.
Not with a normal CT scan.
You mean, it appeared
normal to the doc in the ER.
Way to get right back
on that horse, Thirteen.
No, that was Amber.
Nice try, Cutthroat Bitch.
That was the worst Thirteen
imitation I've ever heard.
Funeral home prep rooms are
filled with toxic chemicals.
And cadavers. Everybody in that
place obviously died from something.
I have a question. Is he
the one who's not a doctor?
Bullets aren't contagious,
but infections, parasites...
You said one of us wasn't a
doctor, and you called him a fraud.
He's not a doctor. Continue, Bos.
Could be an STD.
Why isn't he fired?
You're breaking up.
Going into a tunnel.
Dark Religious Nut.
What did you call me?
I'm sorry.
What do you people want
to be called this week?
Cole.
No, I'm never gonna remember that.
Take Bosley and the other visible
minority to the funeral home.
The rest of you young, white
people, the world is your oyster.
Do an MRI with contrast,
EEG, LP and a blood panel.
And, angels, be careful.
Just because he's religious,
doesn't mean he won't kick your ass.
You want to bet? No.
I want you to stop
being such a jerk to him.
$100.
Smart call. The guy's a wuss.
He'll be the next one on the train.
Define "kick your ass. "
Any physical confrontation?
Or verbal?
Define verbal.
Anything over 70 decibels.
And you can't start
suddenly being nice to him.
You realize what
you're encouraging here.
Yeah. Someone kicking your ass.
The space inside is
smaller than I thought.
Don't worry, Reena.
The doctors are gonna take
good care of you, right?
Once the Valium kicks
in you'll feel better.
And then we'll have some nice,
warm milk when you're done.
I'd rather have more Valium.
Oh, Reena!
Let's wait just a bit, see how it goes.
Try to lie as still as possible.
Guess Father Time's a
lock for one of the spots.
Thirteen's a lock.
He doesn't have a medical
license and he's still around.
She killed a guy in a
wheelchair and his dog.
He doesn't care about our
qualifications, our ideas,
he just wants to have fun.
And she's the ultimate fun,
because he can't figure her out.
This game is insane.
So quit. Happy to lose the competition.
If it's gonna be on your résumé, it's
got to be better to quit than get fired.
Either quit or shut up.
Actually, with House, getting
fired might look better.
Dr. House is a dangerous egomaniac.
That's why I left. We had
different ideas on how to practice.
Glad to hear it. Tell me about Mercy.
To be honest, I don't think Dr.
Schaffer really gave me a chance.
Obviously not. You were
there for three weeks.
What happened?
I saved a patient's life.
That's usually not
grounds for dismissal.
Have you spoken to her?
Yes.
Then why are you
asking me what happened?
You have an excellent résumé.
I felt I owed it to you to
hear what you had to say.
What did she tell you?
That you defied her instructions
and hospital procedures.
That's what happened, nothing
more I can add to that.
You could tell me that you were wrong.
Sounds like you didn't leave
House quite soon enough.
Cadavers were clean, so is her food.
It's all organic, unprocessed crap.
It's got to be the embalming fluid.
Ethanol can have
psychoactive effects and...
Bosley, tell whoever's
talking that he's an idiot.
Bosley?
Either tell him he's an idiot,
or tell me why I'm wrong.
You're an idiot.
You actually think that I'd take a patient
who had a seizure in a funeral home,
if the ER hadn't already
ruled out embalming fluid?
I thought we weren't
supposed to trust...
Idiot!
From the old French, idiote,
meaning effeminate,
mentally deficient Moor.
I found something in the
mortuary's files from '05.
A 48-year-old male's cause of
death was listed as pneumonia,
but the symptoms in the
autopsy report didn't fit.
Confusion, memory loss, depression...
Mad cow. Very cool.
No, she's a vegetarian and only
ate organic vegetables, at that.
Tell him he's an idiot again.
The disease can be
spread by brain tissue.
Which is very cool. Run with it.
So, because the answer might be cool,
you want us to do a brain
biopsy on a 24-year-old woman?
No, because the answer
is something cool,
I want you to do a brain biopsy
on a 48-year-old dead guy.
The guy's already been buried.
We dig him up.
I'm not digging up a body
without a court order.
Don't think of it as digging up a body.
Think of it as keeping
another one from being buried.
I can't do it.
Are we gonna have another one
of those ecumenical discussions
where I tell you that your beliefs
are ridiculous and you totally cave?
I just got to be home at 6:00.
The Sabbath.
The Lord works for six days, then
tells the union he needs a rest.
You know, if I was all-powerful I
think I'd take at least two days.
It's Thursday.
Well, then it must be the kid.
You have oatmeal on your pants.
Do you have a camera in here?
Nope, I was guessing.
He had oatmeal on his pants
yesterday and the day before.
Have one of your wives
look after the spawn.
I'm a single dad.
Where's the single mom?
I have no idea.
Interesting.
You claim a lapse of judgment,
or are you gonna admit that a lapse
in judgment is a lapse in faith?
He's gone.
Fair enough.
Family comes first.
Dr. Cuddy? I'm Amber Volakis,
one of Dr. House's new fellows.
Sexual harassment claims go through HR,
stress-related leaves
through workers comp,
and any accusations
of criminal activities
go directly to the
Princeton-Plainsboro police department.
Actually, I was wondering if you needed
any extra help in the clinic tonight.
You're not gonna score any points
with House by kissing my ass.
Understood, but I hear Dr.
House hates clinic duty.
If he were to hear through the grapevine
that I was willing to work overtime,
take some of it off his hands...
My advice to you is to do
whatever House wants you to do tonight.
And then tomorrow
night you can come back
and I will give you extra clinic duty.
Does everybody around
here have trust issues?
I don't know what House wants you
to do and I don't want to know.
But if you really have a
problem with it, quit now.
It's only gonna get worse.
All right. Who's up?
Not me.
You haven't done any digging yet.
I'm a surgeon.
If anything happens to
these hands, I'm screwed.
Let Bosley do it.
As long as he can keep folding laundry,
His career...
Someone's coming.
Hey, shouldn't we be running?
If it's a cop, run.
Security guard, I say we take him down.
Sorry I'm late.
Where the hell have you been?
I got lost.
We've been here over three hours.
Really lost.
I brought coffee and donuts.
So, Thirteen, you grow up around here?
We're digging up a grave
and you want to chit-chat?
I'm just making conversation.
It's what people do.
Why are you hiding everything?
And I'm asking you that question
because you're hiding everything.
There's something
seriously wrong with you.
I'm worried.
No, you're not.
Fine, but I am freaked, because
I don't think you're a freak.
I think you're doing this on purpose
because you know House will be intrigued.
Yeah, I grew up around here.
Honey, I'm home.
Get the crowbar.
No, there's not enough room to
maneuver a crowbar down here.
Oh, God help us.
What the hell?
What is it?
Ankles. They buried the
guy the wrong way around.
The doctors' lounge is covered in mud.
Thirteen and Cutthroat
Bitch had a disagreement.
Cafeteria was out of Jell-O.
There were pickaxes.
Either you had them dig up a body,
or you're building a railroad.
A little, tiny piece of
his brain. Seemed a waste.
He wasn't using it anymore.
That's your defense?
"We just dismembered him. "
They're looking for Creutzfeldt-Jakob.
You get the results yet?
Does my breath smell bated to you?
Yes. Let me know when you hear anything.
And get that mess in the
shower area cleaned up.
I know just the guy.
How many of them agreed
to dig up a grave?
Six. But don't worry, the one who
didn't, didn't stand on principle.
He just had a diaper to change.
I really think there are no
bad choices in this group.
You guys don't wipe your feet
when you come in the house?
Doctors' lounge, let's go.
Why me?
Well, I can't ask the black guy
or one of the chicks to do it.
That would be insensitive.
And you can't ask Bosley
because that'd look like you only hired
the non-doctor to do non-doctor stuff.
You keep stalling, you're
still gonna clean up,
but I won't let you have the mop.
Sample came back negative
for Creutzfeldt-Jakob.
Well, that discussion didn't last long.
I just don't know what else there is.
We had an idea, it was wrong.
Well, we could go home.
I mean, we have no idea
what's wrong with her,
which means it could
be completely benign.
Or, on the off chance that it's killing
her, we could take it again from the top.
You've already done everything.
We may have missed something.
I just want to go home.
I'm sure I'm fine now.
Reena, the doctors know best.
You had some serious symptoms...
If I have another one,
I'll come right back. Okay?
If you have it while you're driving...
You can drive me, make
sure I take it easy.
Who can?
My mother.
Your mother's here?
What are you talking
about? She's right there.
You sampled every bodily fluid,
peeked in her brain, violated a
cadaver's privacy, dug up a body,
but missed the fact
that she was still seeing
things that weren't there.
Neurological symptoms are getting worse.
It'd be nice if one of you
angelslmorons had a clue why.
We did a full history. She never mentioned
seeing or hearing anything unusual.
Well, as long as she never said
anything, how were you to know?
Same thing with the spinal
fluid? She tell you that was fine?
The labs were all clear.
Then either we're about to
meet the Alpha and Omega,
or you missed something.
We missed the new symptom.
It's not a new symptom. We always
knew she had hallucinations.
Seeing your dead
mother's a hallucination.
Not knowing she's dead is a delusion.
You keep this up, you're gonna have
to start wearing sexier clothes.
Carbon monoxide could also cause
delusions. A lot of haunted houses...
There's no headache, no tachycardia.
I guess they didn't cover
that at your medical school.
What about a hereditary
connection? I mean, she's 24.
Her mother died when she was 25.
In Ukraine, 20 years ago. Good
luck trying to get those records.
So we start new records.
Test for every hereditary
disease that fits the symptoms.
There are at least 40 different
mitochondrial disorders,
another couple hundred...
Start with amyloidosis and you keep
going until you reach zamyloidosis.
Now what are you testing for?
Or should I ask what
you are not testing for?
Well, we could narrow it down if you
could remember what your mother died from.
My mother is not dead.
She's sitting right there.
Do you think we're lying to you?
Leave it alone.
Convincing her that her mother's
dead isn't gonna make her better,
just miserable.
You lose your mother?
Do you think we're trying to
trick you? Why would we do that?
Because you're mean, and
you're not good at your job.
Reena, stop. You're being cruel.
They're wasting time,
doing exactly what the guy in
the wheelchair said they'd do.
A guy in a wheelchair was here?
You know who I'm talking about.
He's been hanging around
ever since they brought me in,
complaining about how
incompetent everyone is.
He said you killed his dog.
It doesn't make any sense.
I'm not interested.
If you weren't interested,
you wouldn't be here.
I thought it was social.
No, you didn't. You always
think there's an agenda.
That's why I left.
That's why you're good.
You need a job. I'll find a job.
I need someone that understands House.
They'll learn.
I need someone that can control House.
Keep looking. It might take a while.
I'll cut the salary of
everyone else on the team 15%,
give it to you.
That's more than you'll
get anywhere else.
What does House say about this?
You're the one person on the
team that he always respected.
This restaurant is 20 minutes out of
your way, half an hour out of mine.
You picked it to make sure
House didn't drop in on us.
It's my decision, not his.
You tell him that, then run back to
your office while I get to deal with him.
I left for a reason.
That reason hasn't changed.
So,
what's the news?
Everything's negative so far.
Yes. Why wait to finish
before reporting to me?
I have things to do, you know.
She's seeing someone else.
That's not news, that's olds.
Damn it. Why did God design
the human body this way?
A guy in a wheelchair.
In a hospital? That's enough
to give you the heebie-jeebies.
He had a dog. She's seeing
Stark, our last patient.
Well, if it's Stark, he
wouldn't be haunting a patient,
he'd be haunting the
doctor who killed him.
She probably just overheard
someone talking about it, or...
Probably?
You think there's a possibility
that the alternative is true?
No. Then go away.
We're wasting time. We ran 32
gels, we could run 100 more.
Without knowing how her mother died...
You're gonna have to run 100 more.
By you, of course,
I'm only referring to the people
who care enough about human life
to put in a full day.
You want to carpool?
How do you expect me to
respond to this stuff?
Exactly like you just did.
I have a theory. Maybe
you can help me out.
Black Mormon means
masochist, means kinky.
I'm thinking that someone got hurt
making the bastard. Am I right?
You leave my son out of this.
I wasn't referring to your kid's
hypocrisy. I was referring to yours.
Why don't we just ask her how she died?
Because she won't tell us. She
thinks her mother's still alive.
I don't mean ask the patient.
I mean, ask her mother.
Cool.
Come on.
What the hell does that mean?
You guys talking your own language now?
I'm sorry. I'll try to include
some visual aids next time.
Now, what?
I'm Dr. House. Is your mom around?
Why should I tell you?
You're just gonna tell
me I'm lying or crazy.
I'm not gonna do that. I really
need to know what she has to say.
What do you want?
When you were young, was she...
No, not you. Him.
The man in the wheelchair?
No. He's old.
Actually, looks like you.
Yeah, that's Grandpa House.
Tell him to call back on a landline.
Terrible reception in here.
How much pain was your mom in?
It's Walter.
He says his name is Walter.
Can I help you?
My patient's talking to my Grandpa Walt.
You have a Grandpa Walt?
Nope.
Which is what made me suspect
that maybe she's not actually
seeing into the afterlife.
What is this sudden
obsession with the afterlife?
My only obsession is with the
idiots in the right-here-and-now life
who think there's an afterlife.
And you want me to... Nothing.
Just needed a place to hang low for
a while. I'm pretending to be spooked.
Because?
Because if my soon-to-be-brain-dead
patient thinks that I believe her,
maybe she'll let me chat
with her mother's ghost.
The one you don't believe exists.
Exactly.
The ghost is a hallucination,
which is the result of a delusion,
which most likely is the
result of a hereditary disease
that her mother died from
when the patient was four.
And you think you can tap
into her subconscious memory
by tapping into her hallucination.
Mmm-hmm.
She might not know what
caused her mother's death,
but she will know how
she acted before she died.
You're quite impressed with
yourself right now, aren't you?
Who wouldn't be?
Well, that should be long enough.
Back in a flash.
Take your time.
Is my grandfather still here?
No.
He should be right back.
He just went to get some warm milk.
But your mom's still here, right?
Yes, of course.
I know she's fine, now, but when
you were four or five, she got sick.
No.
You sure? She wasn't in any pain?
I wasn't in pain.
No, she was just tired.
And sometimes she would
stay in bed all day.
Did she ever fall down?
Of course.
Everyone falls down once in a while.
Sometimes, not that often.
How often?
Maybe it was actually
more than once in a while.
Remember that time in the bathroom?
Mmm.
A few times.
Once she hit her head on the bathroom
sink. There was blood all over the floor.
I got it on my sweater. I...
They took her away.
Yeah, to the place where
the doctor made her better.
But before that, what
about her arms and legs?
Did she ever walk funny,
like, sort of bent over?
I thought that was from
growing up on the farm!
What about her hands?
Did she ever have any difficulty
sewing, buttoning a shirt?
No.
But sometimes my hands would shiver.
Like I was cold, but I wasn't.
I never quite understood.
She used to get the
shivers. Like she was cold.
Start her on L-dopa and bromocriptine.
It's just Parkinson's.
Cole, how's it going with your patient?
Still seeing stuff.
I hear House is treating you like crap.
He treats everyone badly.
Yeah, but I heard you're special.
Well, I can handle it.
Maybe you shouldn't. He's gonna
walk all over you if you let him.
That says nothing about me, just him.
House respects people
who aren't afraid of him.
Get in his face. Yell, if you have to.
I don't need his respect.
You do if you want the job.
Thanks for the advice.
You have to hold still.
I'm trying!
Damn! Hold her down!
No!
Stop it! Let me do it.
No, no.
Hold her down!
No! No!
No!
Irene?
You stabbed me.
You were having a
nightmare. It wasn't real.
My arm is bleeding.
No. It's okay now, your arm's not...
Lesions aren't explained by Parkinson's.
Any theories?
What, ghost got your tongue?
I'm fine.
What about vasculitis?
MRI didn't indicate
any cerebral ischemia.
But she has shown some focal
weakness, urinary retention.
Yes. Those are her big mystery symptoms,
not the hallucinations that
vasculitis doesn't explain.
Unless it's retinal vasculitis.
House, this guy may be smart, and I'm
sure he's great to share a beer with,
but if he doesn't know that visual
symptoms are an electrical issue,
not vascular, two separate systems...
So are the banks and the power grid, but
if I don't pay my bills my lights go out.
Vasculitis restricts blood flow to
nerves, messes with electrical function.
Acute intermittent
porphyria is a better fit.
If you're wrong about porphyria,
the treatment could box her kidneys.
Vasculitis is treated with
corticosteroids, relatively harmless.
Start her on the steroids.
House, he's not...
Then test for both so
he can stop whining.
Big Love, have I humiliated
you in the last half-hour?
No.
Check your e-mail.
How's it going?
Great.
The only way he can turn any more
cheeks is by pulling down his pants.
He's not a wuss. It takes
a lot more strength...
We didn't bet on how strong he was.
So, you're gonna collect $100 and
fire him because he has principles?
What's your agenda here? You
obviously don't care about the 100.
He's a decent, smart...
You don't care about the team.
Does it annoy Wilson when you ask
questions and ignore the answers?
Very much.
You only care about who
I hire and who I fire
because you miss going through my mail.
You can't stop controlling me.
No one controls you.
Want your job back? No.
Too bad, you can't have it.
She'll take care of this.
You can take it out of the
100 you're gonna owe me.
I met House at a conference
about five years ago.
He's quite a character. Yes, he is.
Probably one of the best
medical minds of our generation.
I agree. I learned
an awful lot from him.
I'll bet you did. I see here
you just did a stint at Mercy.
Great.
It says here "'07 to Present.
" How long were you there?
About a month. Dr. Schaffer was great,
but it just wasn't the right fit.
Wait, was that you with Dr.
Schaffer and the lymphoma patient?
It was... It was a tough situation.
I probably could've handled it better.
No, Dr. Schaffer's got a stick
up her rear, good for you.
What made you so sure it was lymphoma?
There was an unusual lactic
acid level in one of her labs.
I had a similar case a few months ago.
Beautiful. God, I
wish I had your stones.
Well, my stones are on the market.
No, I mean, seriously,
I wish I had your stones.
I could cram you down
the board of directors.
But I don't. I'm sorry, man.
Good luck.
When your retinas see something,
they send electrical
signals to your brain.
These lenses will pick up those signals.
If the signals are
misfiring, it'll confirm
that an old man without a medical
license is smarter than all of us,
that your hallucinations
were caused by...
They're not hallucinations.
Tell them, Mom.
Honey, they're doctors.
They must know what they're doing.
If they know what they're doing, how
did they kill that poor man's dog?
Come on, this has got to be
freaking you out a little bit.
I appreciate your concern.
There's nothing to be ashamed of here.
If the ghost of a man you killed
doesn't screw with your head,
there's something wrong with your head.
See, that freaks me out.
Someone must have left it in here.
Absolutely, that makes sense,
some dog was in here
getting his eyes checked
and forgot to put his jewelry back on.
This isn't working.
You're just making me
sicker, like he said you...
What's wrong?
My stomach, it hurts.
Code in the eye lab.
Lean forward, Irene.
You're gonna aspirate.
I can't. It hurts.
Why won't you help me?
Spleen's ripe to bursting. You
guys thought it was vasculitis?
You used to be on House's team, right?
Yeah. Got a lot of
blood in here. Sponge.
You got any advice for me?
Nope.
You always put up with his crap?
Yeah.
Was it a mistake?
It was irrelevant.
Well, he fired you.
He'll fire you either way. Eventually.
Dr. Cameron told me
about... Don't want to know.
Why not? Because House is watching.
Not a metaphor. Look up.
You guys gonna shoot the breeze,
or you gonna do something
about all that bleeding?
That's not coming from
the spleen. It's the liver.
It's necrotic.
She's dying from the inside out.
Enlarged spleen and liver
failure are classic AIP.
It's porphyria and it's moving fast.
PBGs were negative. If
you read the reports...
PBG tests are only conclusive
if done during an attack,
which you would know if
you were a real doctor.
That is just great.
What is? Which one of us is?
Both of you. Together.
Fighting. Passionate to
prove the other one wrong.
Couldn't care less about the patient,
but it all works out the same.
I hate Thirteen.
Not as productively. Continue.
It could still be vascular.
Vasculitis is off the board.
Steroid treatment didn't help.
Vascular isn't just vasculitis.
Something's got to be cutting off the
blood supply to her liver and spleen.
Do a visceral angiogram.
This is a joke, right?
He can't be right every single time.
You're feeding him your
ideas just to embarrass us.
If I wanted to embarrass you, I'd
have you mop up the doctors' lounge.
Heavenly Father, I pray thee that
thou shalt give the Holy Ghost
unto all them that shall
believe in their words.
Irene, what are you doing?
I need to touch it.
Put your hand down.
No! Give it to me! I want it!
Give it to me! No!
What the angio say?
We couldn't finish.
She started groping me.
And you couldn't let her get to
second base just to get the test done?
I think that's third base.
She was convulsing, delirious
and hyper-salivating.
We had to knock her out with lorazepam.
Well, that's definitely not vascular.
What do you want us to do?
The question is, what
would Joseph Smith do?
This isn't the time for anti...
Casting out the demons?
The patient's not possessed. She's
dying. You can mock me tomorrow.
You believe that the
book has all the answers.
To morality, not science.
But the book is
inconsistent with science.
You know how many epileptics were
tortured because they were possessed?
How many teenage witches
were stoned to death,
because they took mushrooms?
Just shut up already.
We got a patient dying.
You either got to prescribe an exorcism,
or admit to me that Smith was a horny fraud.
I know what she has.
You couldn't have
spoken up 10 seconds ago?
You would have saved me 100 bucks.
Mushrooms weren't the only thing
that got people stoned to death,
jimsonweed, belladonna,
mandrake root and moldy bread.
It's ergot poisoning.
You'd need damp grain that's...
Completely unprocessed and untreated,
like what's in that organic
rye bread she's been eating.
Should I be going home? Is it 6:00?
It's why she got worse
on the bromocriptine.
It's an ergot derivative.
There hasn't been a case in 50 years.
She kept asking for milk. Dairy
products counteract the effects.
You think she knew what
she had and was treating it?
Cravings based on actual needs,
it's a fairly common
evolutionary development.
You okay with an answer
based on evolution?
Yeah.
Hypocrite.
It's the stuff they make LSD from.
The treatment you're on should...
So, I've just been tripping?
It explains the hallucinations,
seizures, delusions...
Constricts the blood vessels,
which explains the necrosis.
She's not here?
I'm sorry, no.
The fact that you're even
willing to accept that answer
means the medicine is starting to work.
But you'll live.
You're beautiful, Reena.
You too, Mama.
I'm going to miss you.
Mama.
As you know, there
are seven of you and...
One, two, three, four...
Only six roses.
Those are peonies.
But I'm sure they're
part of the rose family.
Actually, I'm surprised
there are seven of you.
You punch your boss and stick around?
Give me the flower and shut up.
Don't overdo it.
Now, I would love to keep all of you,
but not enough to do anything about it.
So, according to my arbitrary
schedule, one of you has to go.
You're kidding!
I came up with the answer.
I robbed a grave. I...
Planted a dog collar in the procedure
room just to screw with my head.
No, I never.
What, you don't believe she did it?
I'm sure she did it.
That's why she's getting the flower.
It was beautiful, she just overreached.
She got into your head. No, I...
She owned you.
Planting the idea was good.
Letting it fester was good.
Leaving the collar was stupid.
Well-known fact, ghosts don't
leave things lying around.
So, am I gone then?
Oh, my goodness. I totally
forgot about you two. Well played.
Sorry, Henry.
We had some giggles.
You agreed with everything he said.
You finished each other's sentences.
That's why I got to go.
Don't need someone to tell you
what you're already thinking.
Funny, I was gonna say that.
If you want to hang out... Yeah, I know.
Call Wilson.
The rest of you, 8:00 tomorrow.
Cash will be fine.
I bet you say that to all the guys.
Take your blood money.
Who are you gonna protect next?
If I told you, it wouldn't work.
I've re-thought some things.
Glad to hear it.
I'm prepared to come back
on a number of conditions.
I want the raise you
promised, plus five percent.
I want my own office
and a personal assistant.
That's not unreasonable.
I will give you none of those.
You can come back at
your original salary.
What's going on?
You haven't re-thought anything.
You've just been black-balled.
You're "House, Lite" now.
The only administrator that will touch
you is the one who hired "House, Classic. "
The good news is she'll pretend
she's not doing you a favor.
I can start Monday.
www.tvsubtitles.net