And now, coming to the line,
last year's Rookie of
the Year, Casey Alfonso!
In lane two, nine-time
national champion, Tony Kumer.
Tony's got his light on in lane two,
and now Casey is approaching the line.
How do you feel? Great.
I feel like throwing up my guts.
You always feel like throwing up.
Come on, Dad. Let's get
this digger on the line.
You sure you don't
wanna go to law school?
I hate lawyers! Yeah, so do I.
Go get 'em, baby!
Okay, looks like we're ready to go!
Let's hear it, folks!
And it's Casey Alfonso, by
less than half a car length!
What a spectacular finish
for the young female.
Casey Alfonso, with an amazing finish.
What'd you do at the end there?
Yeah, yeah.
At about 250 feet, the
car got out of shape a bit,
but about halfway down, I just
got into the zone or something.
I pedaled it back into the groove.
It was the coolest ride of my life.
How does it feel to be
nine-time national champion...
I'm sorry. Can you repeat that?
Casey? Casey! Casey! Out
of the way. Out of the way!
Casey! Casey! Get me an ambulance.
Ron, get the ambulance! Casey?
Sixty-eight year
old male, non-smoker.
Sixty-eight's a good run.
That'll leave something in the
lock box for the rest of us. Next?
That's your breakfast?
Technically, it's Wilson's lunch.
Twenty-month old baby,
persistent rash, fever...
Too much crying.
Female college student
with... Too much drama.
You don't care about
the crying or the drama,
'cause you won't see the patient.
And you'd treat Methuselah if
his snot had an interesting color.
Means you've already decided
which case you wanna take next.
Tell me about speed racer.
Female, seizure with visual and
auditory processing deficiency.
I did a consult, and...
What kind of race car?
Dragster.
Continue.
You're gonna take a case
based on the car she drives?
Nothing says, "Thanks
for saving my life"
like a test drive in a car that
accelerates faster than a space shuttle.
You can't save her life,
'cause she's not dying.
Her labs show signs of dehydration,
means the problem's
just likely heatstroke.
Kind of hard to get heat struck
in four and a half seconds.
Not when you're wearing a
three-layer fireproof suit.
Excuse me, Dr. House?
No. Lazy ass called in sick again.
We can give him the message.
May we talk in private?
So, either it's heatstroke, in
which case we take the afternoon off,
or it's one of the diagnoses that you
guys are gonna have for me in two minutes.
You're in charge.
I know.
Cop? He's not packing.
Your dad's either a
cop or a security guard.
Or she carries a weapon.
You're with the CIA.
One of our employees just
returned from an assignment sick.
Now, we believe he may be the
victim of an assassination attempt.
Sure.
You wanna close the door?
Door?
Well, I assume you're gonna drop
trou at some point during the dance,
I don't see why I should share.
This isn't a joke.
If you're willing to help
us, we need to leave now.
If I have to walk somewhere, there
better be at least five girls involved.
And they better be working
their way through college.
Okay, what have you got?
Hereditary brain disorder,
transient ischemia
or paraneoplastic syndrome.
None of those go away with
IV fluids. It's heatstroke.
Or Cushing's or calcium deficiency.
Who's your friend?
We use the term life partner.
Get a fresh history, neurological
exam and an MRI of her head.
Fifteen minutes for the lap dance,
a half-hour to scrub
the guilt off my soul...
See you in 45!
Dr. House, we need to hurry.
Yeah, we need to hurry.
Little advice.
I mean, obviously the Village People
played out the whole cop thing.
But come on, CIA?
You seriously expect
anyone to believe that?
It helps when you have props.
Keep your eye on my pen.
Very good.
Any nausea or vomiting
before the seizure?
No.
My dad had some, but he's
always like that before a race.
Could have been food poisoning.
You two eat breakfast together? No.
Any history of sciatica
or spinal injury?
No.
Abnormal deep tendon reflex.
Really? Let me see.
It's there. I didn't
say it wasn't there,
I said it was abnormal.
We're gonna give you an MRI to be sure,
but I'm guessing your symptoms were
caused by just dehydration in the heat.
You're guessing?
Look, I make a living
driving 300 miles an hour,
which makes the ability to stay
conscious kind of important.
I'm sure it's just heatstroke,
but we're gonna do an
MRI to be extra careful.
You said you left your
cell in your office.
I lied.
I wasn't going to take it.
Just tell you to turn
it off for take-off.
I know.
I just wanted to see if you
could tell that I was lying.
Useful information. Yeah?
Where are you?
I'm on a top-secret
mission for the CIA.
Right.
There was nothing on
your race car driver's CT
and the history and
physical were normal.
Her deep tendon reflexes
seemed a bit weak to me.
Areflexia could mean Miller Fisher.
Yes, areflexia could mean Miller Fisher,
but since the reflex was weak, not
absent, it doesn't mean anything.
I'm releasing her. You can
go back to your poker game.
Poker's illegal.
The CIA would never
allow illegal activity.
Have you considered Miller Fisher?
Why? What happened?
She just had another seizure. And now
she's getting a vertical nystagmus.
We think it's Miller Fisher,
an inflammatory process.
In rare cases, it can cause
respiratory failure, but...
Wait, wait. She could stop breathing?
You said there was nothing
wrong. You said you were sure.
You just had another seizure.
Clearly there's something wrong.
So, why should I trust you
to figure out what it is?
Where's Dr. House?
I'm at this hospital...
It's gonna be all right.
We just need to start
the plasmapheresis.
No.
It's not going to be all right,
because you obviously don't
have a clue what you're doing.
I'm not letting you touch me.
Honey!
I wanna see House. Where is he?
It looks a lot better on 24.
I take that back.
Dr. Samira Terzi. It's a
pleasure to meet you, Dr. House.
We really appreciate the
consult on such short notice.
There's nothing that gives me more
pleasure than helping out a colleague.
This is Dr. Sidney Curtis
from the Mayo Clinic.
He's also agreed to
help with the diagnosis.
Dr. House.
Curtis on Immunology, Sidney Curtis?
You've read it?
Nope, but it is keeping my piano level.
So, where is the poor sick fella?
What do we do? I don't know yet.
She needs treatment.
This is a test, right?
You're reporting back
to him everything we do.
Yeah. And I asked the
patient to be uncooperative.
Personally, I think she overplayed it.
She's being uncooperative because
you made us all look like idiots.
We're only gonna look like idiots
if we can't figure out how to
get her to agree to the treatment.
What would House do right now?
Pop a pill, insult us
and trick the patient.
We can do that last part.
She's never met House before, has she?
Who's got a cane?
House isn't here.
We're not gonna act like him.
What do you want?
I'm gonna do what doctors
aren't supposed to do,
admit I made a mistake.
I shouldn't have been so
quick to dismiss your symptoms.
But you need to let us
start the plasmapheresis.
What do you want?
Case? Honey, do you know where you are?
She's burning up. Start the treatment.
I can't. You've got my permission.
She's obviously confused.
Doesn't matter anymore.
Miller Fisher doesn't
cause delirium and fever.
I don't know what this is.
I'm afraid there are gonna be some
limitations on his medical history.
Just let me know what you need
and I should be able to provide it.
FYI, my malpractice insurance
doesn't cover alien autopsies.
That's fine.
X
- files are the next wing over.
Where was the patient
when he first fell ill?
Sorry, that's classified.
But assume there aren't too many
places in the world John hasn't been.
And, yes, John's a cover name.
And what makes you think it
was an attempt on his life?
Sorry, can't tell you that, either.
Well, what can you tell us? Yeah.
Did Oswald really have
sex with Marilyn Monroe?
Good Lord.
Very professional.
Five days ago he was 185
pounds. Perfect health.
Cool.
Fever and delirium rule out...
He's not gonna hire you just
because you called him the most,
especially since it's obvious
he doesn't want to be called.
Symptoms rule out Miller
Fisher. MS fits better.
Progression's too fast.
More likely meningitis.
Areflexia doesn't fit as well with...
Does with amyloidosis.
That's even slower than MS. It's lupus.
I'm with the little man on this one.
It's attacking the body and
the brain, classic autoimmune.
Flirt all you want, but I should
warn you, shiksas are for practice.
Lupus this aggressive
wouldn't spare her kidneys.
It's primarily neurological.
Let's start her on...
Then why no plaques on her MRI?
MRI was inconclusive.
Start her on...
So, now you're sure that it's MS.
Just like you were sure
it was Miller Fisher.
An hour after you were
sure it was heatstroke.
The symptoms fit.
Start her on interferon.
We're not gonna score
any points with House
if we solve this just
by running your errands.
I get that you wanna
be right. You don't?
I'm just trying to save the patient,
not score points with my boss.
Would it hurt the patient
if you let us run some tests?
You've got three hours.
We've run six complete tox screens,
tested for every heavy metal, poison
and biological agent we can think of.
It says here he ate a lot of chestnuts.
Hold on a second.
If the squirrel liberation army
is involved, I'm out of here.
Those little rodents are...
Horse chestnuts are poisonous.
If someone switched them...
Horse chestnuts may look like chestnuts,
but they taste like a
horse's lower than chestnuts,
which makes the theory that he
accidentally ate a couple of hundred
slightly less persuasive.
Seeing as how he was prowling
the back alleys of Tehran...
It wasn't Tehran, it was...
You almost got me.
Unless we know the local environmental
factors, the poisonous flora...
You know I can't tell you that.
Well, then why are we here? You
might as well just Google "poison. "
All they would tell me is he spent
the last 11 months in Bolivia.
Who you gonna kill in
Bolivia? My old housekeeper?
We don't kill people.
I'm sorry, who are
you gonna marginalize?
If it is my housekeeper,
she has it coming.
Cleaning the windows
means cleaning both sides.
Am I right or am I right?
What does it matter what he was doing?
The guy's dying. Not anymore.
I know what's poisoning him, and who.
John.
It's just pancreatitis.
He's not an alcoholic.
And unless his pancreas
is in his fingers...
Spies can't get fungal infections?
And the burns on his skin?
Spies can't get sunburns?
Bolivia doesn't have sun?
So, either we go with his
theory of the non-drinking drunk,
or he was poisoned by some group
with the resources to make
it completely untraceable,
some customized isotope.
Let's treat for radiation poisoning.
The iodine's to protect your thyroid.
Antibiotics are to handle infections.
Should start working
in a couple of hours.
We should celebrate
with a beer or eight.
I don't drink.
Oh, methinks he doth protest too much.
He's deathly ill. Why
would he lie about drinking?
Guilt over killing a man would
make anyone hit the sauce.
We don't kill people.
Right.
You just lie to your friends and family,
establish false identities, trick
people into betraying their country.
He'd never cover up his
drinking. He's too honest.
Hey! Something I've
always wanted to know.
That poison lipstick that
Ginger used to kiss Gilligan,
why didn't that kill her?
Okay, drum roll!
LP is negative for meningitis.
Sorry, Cole.
Fat pad biopsy is... Wait for it...
Negative for amyloidosis
and Thirteen goes down!
Could we hurry this up? My son has...
Can I have a kid, too?
I'm working too hard.
I could hook you up.
If I had two minutes and
some anti-nausea meds,
I'd take you up on that.
And for the gold...
Protein's 65, glucose, 70.
It's MS, start her on interferon.
Now, turn to the last page.
Sed rate's 95, ANA's weakly positive.
Positive, it's lupus.
Weakly, not lupus. It's MS.
We obviously don't know
what it is. Treat for both.
No. I gave in on the tests.
We're not treating her for two
completely separate diseases
because you think lupus
will win you a prize.
Still think it's lupus?
Yeah.
Me, too.
In case of emergency,
go to the emergency room.
Could be lupus.
That's what we figured.
Then why are you here?
You're an immunologist.
We wanted to confirm...
Who are you looking for me to help you
sell down the river? House or Cuddy?
Foreman.
Sorry. He's pushing MS.
Thinks that because he's in charge,
he has to prove he's the
smartest guy in the room.
All I've heard about you, you put
the patient above everything else.
That's why everyone
finds you so annoying.
All House cares about
is results. I know.
I'm talking about how
to deal with Foreman.
So am I.
Fever's down to 101.5.
Treatment's working.
Why are we out here?
Trying to figure out
which treatment's working.
It's kind of tacky doing
it in front of the patient.
You put her on steroids, too?
We had no choice.
The sed rate pointed to lupus.
And the ANA ruled it out!
Doctors!
Legs hurt?
I can't feel them at all. I
don't think I can move them.
Vitals stabilizing.
Tummy ache's gone as well.
So, the treatment's working.
You wanna ditch Dr. Killjoy
and hop on the company jet?
Little trip down Mexico way,
and I'm not talking about
the country or the plane.
Do you think acting like an idiot
and talking about sex works on girls?
Well, if it didn't, the human
race would have died out long ago.
You're pretty cheery for someone
who was just proved wrong
about his pancreatitis theory.
I'm appropriately cheery for
someone who's been proved right.
John hasn't vomited in six hours.
What's to vomit? I'm eating his lunch.
Withholding nutrients is the
treatment for pancreatitis.
That, and the antibiotics
you put him on.
I did unhook your iodine, though.
Didn't seem to fit with the whole "I'm
just jerking you guys around" Gestalt.
You're unbelievable.
Let's ask John if he'd rather be
sick honestly or cured dishonestly.
John? John?
Any chance he's just
overwhelmed with gratitude?
Paralysis.
It's a new symptom?
Big white space on the
board where it would fit.
Nice, multicolored markers.
I'm not writing it because we
can't know if it's a real symptom.
When these two went rogue and pumped
her full of steroids, we lost...
Steroids don't cause paralysis.
She was also on interferon.
Giving her both probably
fried her immune system.
Who knows what infection
you could cause...
We consulted an immunologist,
she said we have...
She? You talking about Dr. Cameron?
She thought lupus was... She
tell you to start treating?
Yes! They've ignored
you, they screwed up
and it's fun watching you spank them.
But, can we get back to the medicine?
The last thing any of you give
a damn about is the medicine.
Look.
I'm not saying you're
bad doctors or bad people.
But House is.
He created a nasty
little cutthroat world,
planted you in it, and
is watching you play.
And none of it works
for anyone except him.
And whoever wins.
Given its quick progression,
we gotta assume botulism.
I'll go to her place. Check
out her fridge and pantry.
It's not botulism. It's polio.
Brilliant. We should search her home
for FDR's remains or a time machine.
She could have contracted it from
anyone who's been to Africa, or...
She's been vaccinated.
Vaccines wear off.
There hasn't been a single
American case in over 20 years.
I've seen this disease.
I know what it looks like.
That's why you're finding it,
because you're looking for it.
Polio?
It's crazy. House wouldn't think so.
So, go find House and
tell him your theory.
Take a personal day.
Seriously. Get out of here.
You don't have the power to fire me.
But I do have the power to
kick your ass off my case.
I'm starting the botulism treatment.
The rest of you, look for confirmation.
He should be brought up on charges.
Okay, relax.
I'll take your book
out from under my piano.
He's dying of radiation
sickness. He's obviously in pain.
All of which could have been
avoided if you hadn't interfered...
What was that for?
Radiation sickness kills
specific cells at specific times.
His hair should be coming out in
clumps before he's writhing in pain.
Since it's not, I know
who's trying to kill him.
God.
It's blood cancer, Waldenstrom's.
Radiation can cause infections,
which set off neuropathy...
If you had any real
evidence of foul play,
you'd be torturing Bolivians
instead of putting me into a state
of anticipatory sexual arousal.
Can we treat for both?
Bad idea. Unless you're the
one who's trying to poison him.
I'll arrange for
plasmapheresis and chemo.
Are you gonna trust
him after what he did?
I don't have to trust
him to agree with him.
You make a good point.
I've been wrong every time and
she still won't listen to you.
So, either she really likes
me or she really hates you.
And I got a ride in the jet.
Oh, hi. What are you doing here?
Just came to say hi.
Hi again.
Where's Mrs. Bearman?
Sent her home.
I was scheduling her for an MRA.
If we gave MRAs to every
patient with a headache...
This wasn't just a headache,
it was the worst in her life.
And lucky for you, I'm a neurologist.
She went to a wine and cheese
tasting. Both triggers for migraines.
She's never had a migraine before.
And I never had a blueberry bagel,
but for the first time I had one.
Bagels don't kill people.
This is a classic ticking bomb aneurism.
Wow. This taught me a lesson.
I guess when I mess with
other people's patients,
I risk looking like an officious bitch.
We're gonna have to
track down Mrs. Bearman.
Wait. Never mind.
It's funny.
It's not funny, it's totally immature.
It is funny.
You just can't appreciate
it, because you're the victim.
Yeah. I deserve shame and
ridicule for offering a consult.
Unheard of for a doctor.
You didn't offer a medical consult.
You offered a
dealing-with-Foreman consult.
For the good of the patient.
It's what House would have done.
Maybe House will hear about
it and tear up with pride.
You think I'm trying to impress him.
I think that for someone
who's not involved in his team,
you're remarkably involved in his team.
Let it go.
Let him go.
And that's mature.
One-twenty over 80. Let 'er rip.
Now we got the medical
stuff out of the way,
why don't we meet back at your place
for some enhanced
interrogation techniques?
My safe word is, "Help,
please, please, stop. "
It's two pleases. Anything
less than that, you keep going.
You actually cure this guy, I'll
show you my private water board.
We need to consult an
oncologist about the chemo.
Oh, I'm sorry. I thought
you were still euphemizing.
My valet knows a little oncology.
I was wondering when you'd
grow bored of avoiding my calls.
Oh, I could never grow
bored of ignoring you.
What's the latest
protocol on Waldenstrom's?
Where are you?
CIA headquarters.
How much fludarabine do you need...
Either you're sprawled naked on your
floor with an empty bottle of Vicodin
or collapsed naked in
front of your computer
with an empty bottle of Viagra.
Please tell me which, because
Chase has another pool going.
They flew me in to help
deal with a sick employee.
How much... Hallucinations?
Damn, I shouldn't have
bet on the Viagra. Okay.
Call the Langley switchboard,
ask for extension...
Thirty-five, seventy-eight.
Three, five, seven, eight.
He asked an awful lot
of questions for a valet.
You know, I happen to have a
position available on my penis.
Wait a second, I think
I screwed up that joke.
You offering me a job?
I'd settle for that.
As tempting as a position on
your staff is, I like it here.
Pays better, and we've only
had one assassination attempt.
And I'm sure you're a great boss.
That's why your fellows left
en masse a couple of months ago.
I have satellite images.
Inspector Gadget?
My God, you're actually at the CIA.
You've gotta get down here.
They've got a satellite aimed
directly into Cuddy's vagina.
I told them the chances of
invasion are slim to none, but...
Waldenstrom's.
Recommended dose is 25
milligrams per meter squared.
They do a background check on you?
Twenty-five milligrams.
They did a background check on you,
they did a background
check on your friends.
Relax. I'm sure they already know that
you brought heroin back from Afghanistan.
That's not true.
I've never been to Afghanistan.
House?
She's getting worse.
Her fever's risen slightly.
But it's definitely... What? Botulism?
Right? Because if you're wrong again,
and you're treating her for something
that she doesn't even have...
The anti-toxin hasn't
had time to work yet.
I know it's hard, but try to be patient.
Excuse me.
I know you're pissed I interrupted,
but you're gonna be even
more pissed in a second.
You tested her without telling me?
Yeah. I know, I'm really,
really sorry, but...
On the other hand, it's positive.
She has polio.
Now what, boss?
Where's House?
He's blown off four hours of clinic.
He's consulting for the CIA.
Seriously, call Langley,
and ask for extension three,
five... It's three, five, three, six?
It's definitely two threes.
I wrote it down. I have it somewhere.
He's gonna make up twice his
skipped hours in the clinic.
Okey-doke.
And for protecting him, you're
gonna make up twice that.
Why are you punishing me worse than him?
Because House never learns. You might.
How are you feeling?
Like crap.
Yeah. Cancer can be that way.
My hair is falling out.
Is that the chemo?
No, that's too quick.
So, what does it mean?
It means you don't have cancer.
Someone actually did try to kill you.
You're stubborn. You're arrogant!
There's no need to yell.
You may have cost that man his life.
He's getting the radiation treatment.
Twenty-four hours too late.
I didn't yell at you when
I thought you were wrong.
I wasn't wrong.
This isn't productive.
There is no "productive," it's too late!
Because of your inexperience,
your poor judgment
and your failure to
recognize a reckless fool.
Cordyceps sinensis.
It's an herbal treatment
derived from a parasitic fungus.
Comes from caterpillars.
Along with dimercaprol chelation,
it's been shown to
mitigate bone marrow damage
from radiation poisoning
in monkeys.
Sorry. I was stubborn and arrogant.
Self-recriminations won't help her.
Nothing's gonna help
her, she's got polio.
There's no cure, but
there are treatments.
No, she's dying.
Yeah, every death's a tragedy.
Funny how you weren't so depressed
when she was just dying
because me and Amber screwed up.
And I'm also self-centered,
thanks for clarifying.
Don't forget self-pitying.
Vitamin C. Extremely high doses.
It was experimental treatment
protocol in the '50s...
And they haven't finished yet?
They lost funding.
That's because there's no logical
reason vitamin C would cure polio.
Well, someone thought there was.
Someone thought black people
made excellent farm implements.
I'm not talking about hurting anyone.
I just want to force-feed
her some orange juice.
You wanna throw in some
bacon and eggs as well?
If there's anything you learned today,
it's gotta be that you can be wrong.
John, can you hear me?
We're gonna start you on
an experimental treatment.
Tea?
It's a Chinese herb
which has been effective.
I'm dying, aren't I?
Probably.
We're gonna attempt an
experimental protocol.
A new drug?
An old one. Vitamin C.
Ultra-high doses have been shown
to destroy the polio virus
and heal nerve damage.
She could regain use of her legs?
It's unlikely.
But we're gonna try.
Don't give up.
Nausea's not as bad.
Radiation sickness has a latency period.
You'll get better before you get worse.
Wanna know what I really did down there?
Only if it's interesting.
The women there,
during Carnival, they...
They do this dance.
They call it the devil dance.
Not interesting.
I spent the whole 40 days with this
attaché to the Minister of Defense.
The most buttoned-down
woman you'd ever meet,
except when she did this dance.
She agreed to tell me stuff.
Okay, you got half a good story there.
Karma.
Best way to rid yourself of that
guilt is to confess your sins.
This pain, it's right. It's comforting.
It makes me think that
somehow it all makes sense.
What do you mean 40 days?
When they found out
what she'd told me...
Carnival in Bolivia's only eight days.
You have any idea what
a chestnut looks like?
You idiot!
Who are you calling an idiot?
Whoever knew that John was
stationed in Brazil, not Bolivia.
Brazil?
Well, then, I guess I'm
talking to you, idiot.
It's the same region. It's the
same parasites, same diseases.
But not the same language.
In Bolivia, chestnuts are chestnuts.
Brazil, on the other
hand, has castanhas-do-pára
literally, chestnuts from Pára,
because it would be stupid for people
from Brazil to call them Brazil nuts.
So, he ate Brazil nuts. Big deal.
No, he ate a lot of Brazil
nuts, which is a big deal,
because they contain selenium,
which in high doses causes
fatigue, vomiting, skin irritation,
discharge from the
fingernail beds and hair loss.
Any of that sounding familiar?
Can you treat it?
We already started.
Treatment's chelation, the
same as for radiation sickness.
The only difference is it works
a lot better on nut poisoning.
So, what's the problem?
You're an idiot.
Why is she shivering?
Low serum calcium is a side
effect of the treatment.
I can give her a calcium supplement.
My arm hurts.
The infusion rate has to remain
high for the treatment to work.
Is it working?
You feel that?
Yeah, it hurts.
It's working! This is fantastic.
There's a lot you could
learn at my fellowship.
If you knew the procedures
I could teach you...
Of course, we'd need a nurse to prep.
I know how to kill a man with my thumb.
Actually, I was just trying to
make another euphemism for sex.
So was I.
Oh, God. How can you
flirt with this idiot?
He lied to us again and again.
He broke laws, ethical codes...
I was right.
That doesn't mean everything.
It means a lot.
Dr. Curtis, Dr. House.
I appreciate your help.
Hey. Hey.
When you were dying,
you tried to infect me,
because you knew I'd fight for you
if I thought I was dying, too.
Are you bringing this up now so I'll
forgive you for messing with my patient?
I'm happy I changed jobs.
But I know I'll never have that sort of
excitement.
You miss people trying to kill you?
No.
I miss people doing whatever
it takes to get the job done.
I guess that's why I'm
having trouble giving it up.
I shouldn't have helped
them mess with your patient.
They had to screw with me.
I've gotten everything wrong.
I don't believe it.
You're not gonna get everything right.
But you're never gonna
get everything wrong.
Morning!
Where have you been the last two days?
Overslept. We saved speed racer.
She had polio. We
cured it with vitamin C.
Yeah. I cured depression
with tonic water once.
Actually, I think there
was some gin in it, too.
A hundred and fifty
grams over six hours.
It worked.
No, it didn't.
I told you, you can't cure polio.
It means either she's not
cured or she never had it.
Since she's walking out of here,
I tested her blood from admittance.
No polio.
Means Brennan screwed up the lab tests.
Or you screwed up your lab tests.
You must have. She got better.
So, it's relapsing and
remitting. Maybe porphyria.
Well, that's a stretch.
If she had porphyria, you'd
have seen purple urine.
You think it's more
likely he cured polio?
Well, they believe it.
Her symptoms fit perfectly.
Any alternative is
unbelievably convoluted.
Some doctor would have to poison her
with thallium so it looks like polio,
then fake a lab test,
then give her vitamin C
and stop the poison so
she magically gets better.
Actually, it is kind of doable, right?
So, what do you think?
Shall we test her for thallium
before you contact Stockholm?
You poisoned her?
The really shocking thing
is that Foreman was right
about the heatstroke.
Vitamin C cures polio. I've seen it.
Yeah. In some bush clinic.
You needed polio in a
place with a proper lab.
The only problem is that places
with proper labs don't have polio.
There is no money in finding cures for
diseases that only kill poor people.
This will make them do research.
What do you care if I faked a lab test,
if it saves a few thousand lives?
I did what I had to do.
Isn't that what you hired us for?
Which is why I'm not gonna fire you.
You're gonna quit.
Go on, get out of here.
So, you're just gonna let him go?
Absolutely.
And I'm gonna let him get as far away
as possible before you call the cops.
Guy's a nut job.
Who the hell did I leave in charge?
Foreman.
There was a reason for that.
Next time, listen to him.
Where have you been?
And don't say the CIA.
Okay.
By the way, one of my employees...
Either you're gonna have
to get someone from the CIA
to call and confirm your story,
or you're doing eight clinic
hours and Wilson is doing 16.
I was in the Hamptons.
I was helping some rich hedge
fund jerk treat his son's sniffles.
Fascinating as that sounds.
For your honesty, I
will forgive your hours.
Thank you.
No!
The only thing less likely
than your helping the CIA
is your helping some
rich guy in Long Island.
You're doing your hours and Wilson's.
I know how to kill a man with my thumb.
Who doesn't?
Hi.
I'm gonna take you up on your offer.
Yeah?
Well, I live a couple
of miles from here.
That's not the offer I meant.
I gave notice today.
You said you were happy at the company.
I lied.
Doubt you'll hold it against me.
I'll see you at 9:00 on Monday.
www.tvsubtitles.net