Whoever thought walking
in a circle at two miles an hour
would be draining?
Fresh air, exercise.
You know, some things
do have their negative sides.
Our income just
got cut in half.
And we get to spend twice
as much time together.
More, if you don't leave
before your lunch hour's over.
Out of my way.
We have a legal right
to hold you up for 15 seconds.
15...
- 14,
- One.
11,
10,
Just trying to do
my job.
Hey, relax, three more seconds,
and you can go.
Are you telling me
what to do?
It's okay.
Just take a breath.
Get the hell off me.
I think it's been 15.
You okay?
Oh, my God, Jeff!
House M.D.
Season 4 Episode 13
"No More Mr. Nice Guy"
Paging Dr. Spencer.
Paging Dr. Statham,
Dr. Statham, please.
This place is a mess.
Welcome to a world
without nurses.
Here, you can start
with these.
It's not my fault.
I didn't lose nurses.
Cuddy was looking for you.
Said she'd send you
down here.
I know, that's why I'm here.
Because cuddy hasn't
found you yet.
She's gonna look everywhere
except the place
she wants me to be.
Hey.
I've got an aortic
dissection here.
What's with the idiot?
Fainting spell and recent
history of dysgeusia.
Everything tastes
like lemon meringue pie.
You want to take him?
No.
Sir.
Why do you have two
lunches in front of you?
Been here for two meals.
And you're happy with that?
No, I just don't see
much use in complaining.
Seriously?
It's a very useful tool.
Complain, you make
people miserable.
They do what you want
to make the misery go away.
You probably should say something.
Maybe I can call one
of the doctors I work with-
They're doing their best.
What the hell?
I'm sure it was an accident.
Is he Canadian?
Uh, he's a low priority...
Is that a yes?
He's just-
Happy.
I gotta stop this
before it spreads.
You guys are done.
This could be
a metabolic disorder,
toxic exposure,
carcinoma of the tongue
metastasized the brain,
epilepsy, M.S.
Or it could be the flu,
and we should all be
back in the E.R.
No, you're ignoring
The big symptom.
What if we're looking at both
the flu and decent parenting?
Okay, you two are
perfectly healthy.
This guy wasn't pandering.
He wasn't vanilla nice.
He was nice without any aspiration,
personal gain.
I'm thinking genetic defect.
Niceness is a defect?
Three cavemen see a stranger
running towards them with a spear.
One fights, one flees,
One smiles and invites him over
for fondue.
That last guy didn't last
long enough to procreate.
And how long has the
patient been suffering?
At least as long as his
wife has known him.
11 years.
The chances of him having
an undiagnosed pathology
- for that long-
- What are you saying?
That evolution is wrong?
Where do you think we are,
21st-century America?
He's saying that statistics
are true too.
The world is a bell curve.
Most of us fall within
the standard deviation,
but there are outliers,
and if we believe
in the existence
of extreme jerkiness, which
I suspect that we do...
then we also have to accept
the existence
of the opposite extreme.
You want it to be a symptom
because then we're
supposed to be jerks,
which means you don't even
have to try to be nice.
Okay.
Maybe I'm biased.
Let's take a vote.
Who thinks that niceness
is not a symptom?
And who thinks
that their vote counts?
You two, check out
his home for toxins.
- Taub and Thirty-One...
- Thirty-One?
Oh, I'm sorry,
I thought that either way
was good with you.
Taub and Thirteen,
MRI for tumors and
EEG or nerve damage.
Test whatever comes out of him
for everything else.
Too much axis tilt.
Don't release until your thumb's
at the bottom of the ball.
I assume Wilson was busy.
Again.
No axis tilt.
With Amber?
Again.
Still, it was nice
of you to invite me.
This is fun.
No, it wasn't.
No, it isn't.
I didn't invite
you to be nice.
I invited you because bowling
isn't one of the two things
guys do by themselves.
What's the second thing?
Other hand.
If people are incapable
of being nice, why
bother having the word?
The ontological proof
of niceness.
The existence of the word
proves the existence
of the concept.
Look out for those minotaurs
on your drive home.
And I thought motives
didn't matter.
Only results mattered.
So what are you gonna do
to screw up Wilson's relationship
so you don't have to listen
to me while you bowl?
I wish the best for them
and their tragically
deformed children.
Well, she's good at being bad.
You might not be able
to destroy her.
As long as I give
it my best shot.
I'm gonna hold my head high.
Cameron had this one
insufferable friend.
She wasn't gonna
get rid of her,
and I sure wasn't
gonna join 'em.
So I just said,
"See her on Thursdays."
I know it's not as exciting
as an exploding birthday cake,
but, hell,
I don't want to hang out
with her every night anyway.
That's amazing.
Cameron only has one
insufferable friend?
Joint custody.
Of Wilson?
Unless we have another love child.
Deal with him.
He needs a mother figure.
I'm not saying you're not entitled
to spend time with him.
I'm just saying I'm entitled too.
I don't know how
to deal with him
when he's being reasonable.
This is reasonable?
This is crazy.
You're not a child.
You can make your own plans.
No, crazy is
what House would normally do
in this situation-
Swap your lubricant
with superglue.
The man knows me.
This is his way
of accepting us.
It's actually a
very touching moment.
I'm proposing I get
every other day
and every other weekend.
I have yoga Wednesdays.
You can have him then.
But you have to have him
home by 11:00.
We can swap weekends.
Mondays and Wednesdays,
and midnight.
If he's not home
till midnight,
we won't be asleep
till almost 2:00.
Wilson, make a ruling.
No.
You two are like dogs
circling each other
in the park.
And I say that with all
the love in the world.
You need to sniff
each other's butts,
bare your teeth, and arrive
at some strange detente.
Otherwise, you'll end up
biting each other's eyes out.
Again, with all the love
in the world.
I'll let you sniff first.
Take my deal, or
get out of my apartment.
Take my deal, or I move in.
This guy worked for
Habitat For Humanity
In Costa Rica.
And coaches handicapped kids.
You think we should do a work-up
on the other coaches?
It is possible
he's too perfect.
I'm not saying he's perfect.
I'm saying he's trying to be.
That's what people do.
What?
That's not what people do.
People usually suck,
but they want to be good,
- want to be nice.
- House?
Exception that proves the rule.
What sort of argument is that?
A bad one.
That might be relevant.
Hydrofluoric acid.
lowers his calcium,
causes the fainting
and taste issue.
But not the niceness.
Wouldn't that be nice?
You are King Solomon.
If you want us to cut him
in half, we're cool with that.
My boyfriend's too
much of a wuss
to make the call for himself-
And I mean that
with all the love
in the world.
I'm gonna piss off
one of them,
and they both scare me.
"Your treatment of patients
is reprehensible."
You're reading his
performance review?
I'm busy.
We have a nurses' strike.
"Your management of employees
borders on abuse."
Let's go.
No, why-
I want to hear it.
"You are overtly contemptuous
of hospital hierarchy."
And covertly.
I suppose you didn't
know about that.
"Your attitude towards
supervisory personnel
"is disrespectful,
"and a disturbingly large
proportion of your comments
are racist or sexist."
That top makes you look
like an Afghani prostitute.
Would be an example of that.
Sign this.
House.
- I got the-
- It can wait.
I will sign, if you
will give us a ruling.
I will give you a ruling,
if you do the reviews
on your team.
I'd be happy to continue
the mockery of this process.
What'd you offer him?
- Wednesdays till 11:00 and alternate weekends.
Yes.
Wednesday nights are
ladies' nights at Cheetah's.
Calcium's normal.
- Wow.
- It really could wait.
Everything's normal.
And you thought
it wouldn't be.
He's a carpet cleaner.
He's got a home full
of hydrofluoric acid.
That doesn't mean his
calcium should be low.
Yeah, it actually kinda does.
HF causes lower levels of-
Lower, not low.
- Lower than normal.
- Lower than yesterday.
Yesterday might have been high.
What's lower than high?
He actually has hypercalcemia,
which is being lowered
to normal by the HF.
So what gives us
elevated calcium,
bad taste, and fainting?
I take it you know?
Get the team.
This is gonna be fun.
Hello, again.
These people think
you are not too nice.
Too nice?
For what?
For life as we know it
to have evolved without
an intelligent designer.
I'm going to
prove them wrong.
Your wife is very ugly.
Get out of here.
Deb.
He's obviously trying
to prove a point.
I think I just did.
You're either perfect
or you're sick.
In my experience, sick
is much more common.
He's not sick.
He's nice.
Nice in the sense
that your toaster is nice
for making you breakfast.
It's the only thing his wiring
will let him do.
He has Williams syndrome.
Your husband is
missing the genes
that make him suspicious.
You're wrong.
- He's
- Relax, there's no cure.
He's gonna go right on
tasting lemon meringue pie,
Fainting, and being a sap.
What about the other symptoms?
He has no other symptoms.
But williams does.
He's got teeth,
glasses.
Williams cuts I.Q. by 20-
He doesn't work in
the physics department.
Except when they spill
a black hole on their carpet.
Elfin appearance?
Yeah, he's more Legolas
than Keebler,
but I bet you he can still crack
off a batch of pecan sandies.
Perfect pitch?
You love to karaoke, right?
I suck.
Modest.
- Another symptom.
- No, he really
does suck.
Give us a warble.
You know any Cher?
No.
But I know Bread.
What's the matter?
He's stroking.
And a moment too soon.
You were wrong.
Why do people say that
with such pleasure?
It's very hurtful, you know.
It means the patient gets
to keep being nice.
Why does that offend you?
It's the way he said it.
He wasn't relieved,
he was excited.
He was also wrong.
And I say that with
no sense of pleasure.
Patient tested negative
for Williams,
which means the stroke and
everything else wasn't caused-
You have a friendly demeanor,
but you sometimes get too involved.
You relate well to your
peers and patients.
And you complete tasks
in a timely manner.
Please sign.
What the hell was that?
I have to give each of you
performance reviews.
Plenty of other conditions
can cause debilitating niceness.
How is that supposed to help him?
I don't know.
How's it supposed
to help Wilson?
Cross out Wilson's name
and the date,
and then fill in your own name.
The point of a review
is to give feedback to help.
I'm thinking neurosyphilis.
Wouldn't show up on the MRI
without contrast.
I'll go run the tests.
He doesn't think
it's syphilis,
but he's gonna go run
those tests anyway.
Because he doesn't know.
That's why we do tests.
Because he's a wimp.
Because he's afraid of you.
You want me to intimidate him
into not being afraid?
Not sure I know how to do that.
Reviews make a difference.
People have to listen,
so they have to learn.
I don't think that the right time
to tell the dog not
to pee on the rug
is semi-annually.
You don't want to
do the paperwork.
I am concerned
about the rainforest.
I'll do it.
I know.
I don't have syphilis.
You don't know.
How many ways are
there to get it?
You can know who
you had sex with.
- You can't know who she-
- I do.
Not for sure.
It's a waste of time.
I had a stroke.
You can't keep wasting time.
We were tested for
the peace corps.
Ten years ago.
You haven't been with your wife
every minute of every day.
You think I'm naive, don't you?
I think you're... yeah.
I know my wife.
She's not perfect.
I'm not perfect.
But she loves me.
And she's always loved me.
Every minute, every day.
You're 15 minutes late.
Have you heard the good news?
Miley Cyrus is playing
a third night at the Spectrum?
Happiness is possible.
And not just in this life,
but in the next-
Oh, you're selling religion.
I'm sorry, I bought
some Islam yesterday.
Well, it's where your light
shows signs before mending-
Have a good evening.
You're late.
15 minutes.
16 minutes, my 16 minutes.
So keep him an extra 16 minutes.
- You hear that?
- She doesn't care.
- You're going mini-golfing.
- What's it matter?
You got a tee off time?
It matters because you don't get
to decide what matters.
It was my fault.
I had to take a shower.
Which was my fault.
I had to take a dump.
Anything else
I don't need to know
before you leave?
Have fun on your playdate.
You've got mommy's numbers,
right?
Daddy needs a drink.
I was thinking, if we discount
the niceness issue-
Sit down.
I think it's a heart defect.
Nothing on the echo.
Could be a patent foramen ovale.
It explains the stroke,
and the syncope, and
a PFO wouldn't show up
on a routine echo.
I'm gonna do a bubble test.
You got a minute first?
Sure.
I think you've shown
remarkable strength
in a difficult situation.
Are you giving me
a performance review?
A good one.
I'm gonna do a bubble test.
There was enough
blood left over
from his admission work-up
to run the VDRL.
You doubted your patient.
No, what I thought didn't matter.
House said he wouldn't
let us go on
until we ruled out
neurosyphilis.
It's not neurosyphilis;
it's a PFO.
It's neurosyphilis.
The tests were positive.
It's always the same conversation.
They tell you you
must be mistaken,
which is why I always run
the tests twice,
and then they blame
the other guy,
which makes sense
if they're innocent,
but obviously,
half of 'em aren't.
They don't seem to get
that they're busted.
Scientifically proven.
Unless your spouse cheated too.
Exactly.
That's what you're praying
for in that moment.
That she cheated too.
And then if she doesn't kill
you, you know that she did.
You know she betrayed you.
And then, you realize
that that sucks worse.
The test must be wrong.
I ran it twice.
Not that test.
The one I took ten years ago.
What other explanation is there?
He really sees no
other possibility.
Did you have an affair?
No.
Then why aren't you
angry with him?
You ever know anybody
who's just too nice?
No.
It's annoying-
Then you realize
it's annoying because they
remind you of what you are not.
That you'll never be
as good as they are.
And then you think,
why can't I?
And before you know it,
that naive idiot you laughed at
has made you a better person.
You really think
I've been in love all these
years with a symptom?
If syphilis caused
lesions in his brain,
and the lesions caused
personality changes,
you may notice a change in him
as his condition improves.
I know my husband.
He's not gonna change.
You should get
yourself tested.
So much for the bell curve.
How can House be an ass
without it being an illness,
but niceness is a
biological crime?
You got five bucks?
Uh, yeah.
Niceness just cost
you five bucks.
Being an ass generally
turns a profit.
Kutner, could you excuse us?
I need to do Taub's review.
You can stay.
I think it would be better
if this was done privately.
This isn't gonna be done.
What is it with you guys?
I've given you advice before.
Not as our boss.
What's the difference?
Advice is advice.
Fair enough.
I'll go first.
You demonstrate a
great air of confidence,
which is really
pissing me off.
House authorized me-
- How long have you known him?
- He's using you.
I volunteered because
I knew he wouldn't.
He could care less
about the paperwork.
He's using you to
screw with you.
He knows it'll annoy us.
We'll stand up to you,
which will force you
to confront the fact
that even though you think
you're our superior,
you're no different from us.
He gave you authority
to keep you in your place.
It's true.
Thanks.
Not him, what'd he say?
Nothing, what's true?
There's something
wrong with this guy,
it means there's something
wrong with House.
Are you trying
to get me drunk?
What time is it?
10:30.
Ooh. She'll kill you.
I'll get you home
before lights out.
Great.
Then she'll kill me.
If I get-
If I get any more drunk,
then I'm-
it...
might not work.
If you, uh, know what I mean.
Really?
You'd think that one or more
of your ex-wives
would have mentioned
that to me.
They told you?
Wait.
Why do you want to get
Amber angry?
Because I'm your friend.
No, no, no.
You said you approved,
you said you were taking-
the high road.
For how long, the first exit?
Hello, and thank you
for saving me
from being righteoused
to death.
Patient's vomiting blood.
Hematemesis could indicate-
Don't put it on the board.
You don't think it's a symptom?
I think it's my marker.
He has syph.
And what?
And syph, it can
cause hematemesis.
Not everyone agrees.
How-
How could you-
You wouldn't have woken me up
in the middle of the night.
If it was just syph,
he wouldn't be getting worse.
He's already on penicillin.
Bleeding's probably
from liver damage,
probably caused by ethanol
in the cleansers
or the penicillin.
Two more probablys
than I like to hear.
Liver tests and serologies
are gonna take a full day.
Full night, actually.
Guy not might make
it to brunch.
Yes, I knew about your
issue with alcohol.
Yes, I intentionally
got you drunk to provoke an
argument between you and Amber.
Why I would do such a thing
is an interesting question.
What's more interesting
is that you knew
as much as I did
and you're the one who's
pouring down the drinks.
Why?
Because I thought I was out
having fun with a friend.
I didn't know the
drinks had subtext.
I gotta get home.
GGT's normal.
Rules out alcohol.
How about serum protein?
It's positive.
Kinda assumed he had protein.
It's how much protein
he has we care about.
It's positive for syphilis.
You mind if I give you
a performance review?
Not the patient.
House.
He has syphilis.
What happened?
Every time I searched my soul...
I found Anna.
Are you gonna tell Marie?
I have to.
It will destroy her.
Could it be any worse on her
yhan loving somebody
who can't love them back?
Yes?
You might want to
turn off the TV.
Don't you think I know that?
I'm multi-tasking.
Also doing my taxes.
And Cuddy.
What'd you find out?
The patient has hepatitis.
I assume from your omission
of the word 'viral'
before the hep that
it's not another STD.
Put him on steroids
and test him for sarcoid
before the liver failure
becomes liver failed.
We're all doing this.
There's more?
You have syphilis.
No, I don't.
One of us found a vial
of your blood in the lab-
Which one of you?
It's treatable.
We filled a prescription.
You okay?
So this is why he
is who he is.
We don't know.
We know.
It's not just a coincidence.
Wilson says he's always been a jerk.
But he got worse.
After his leg.
The leg was a coincidence.
Did you sleep with him?
So what's gonna happen?
What's gonna change?
Maybe he'll be less
of a jerk.
Or less of a doctor.
You gotta be a jerk
to be a good doctor?
I don't know.
Maybe House does.
Why aren't you answering me?
Because it's none
of their business.
It's none of your business.
I think the STD
makes it my business.
Humans are complicated.
Humans are simple.
A million different things
make us who we are.
You change one,
you change everything.
If Mozart was better adjusted,
decides to play catch one day,
maybe there's no Magic Flute.
You did, didn't you?
There's something
I need to tell you.
You returned him drunk.
On time.
Drunk.
No tag backs.
The purpose of the time
was to give me time.
So you didn't have sex?
I like sex.
Then you can have it tonight.
The l word is on.
You don't get to
decide what matters.
Either you're genuinely afraid
I'm gonna make him miserable,
Or you're afraid I'm
gonna make him happy,
or you simply can't
stop screwing
with anything that moves-
It doesn't really matter
because whatever the reason,
you'll only get worse.
Until either I stop
seeing wilson,
or I stop you.
What do you think
I'm gonna choose?
If you terminate
the agreement,
it's not gonna bring peace
in the Mideast.
I'm not terminating
the agreement.
I'm amending the agreement.
I'm adding penaltylaus c.
Fine.
Whoever violates it
gets their finger cut off.
- I'm serious.
- So am I.
You want people to drive safer,
take out the airbags
and attach a machete
pointing at their neck.
No one will drive over
three miles per hour.
- I'm not cutting-
- We'll figure it out.
On your time.
You know she's
certifiable, right?
I got the forms in my desk.
Where is she wrong?
What were you gonna tell me?
Nothing.
You're punishing me?
I needed to tell you
something privately.
I'm not gonna tell her.
You'll tell her.
She's your girlfriend.
You should tell her.
You're my friend.
It's not the same.
Don't sulk.
Where am I wrong?
Your management style
is counterproductive.
You gave me authority
over the team,
just so they could undercut-
Critiquing the clap-addled?
That's sort of tasteless.
I didn't feel like waiting
until your genitals cleared up.
You need to formalize
my authority over the team.
No, I don't.
You don't think I'm qualified?
Compared to those three?
You wanna punish Cuddy
for hiring me without-
I like Cuddy.
I like parts of her.
You wanna crush the
team by crushing me?
I want to empower them.
Those three idiots
need to respect you.
They should respect you.
They should be
afraid of you.
So I have to humiliate you.
'Cause if the team fears you,
they won't question you;
if they don't question you,
they won't get any answers;
if they don't get any answers,
they're useless.
Mocking me saves lives?
The hospital will probably
build you a statue one day.
You know, with a "kick me"
sign on the back.
So when you think about it,
the more I mock you,
the more it shows I
have respect for you.
Or you made up that BS
because you like humiliating me.
Wouldn't rule that
out completely.
- You busy?
- Almost done.
Uh, so just remember,
the rabbit goes around the tree
and jumps down the hole.
Negative for sarcoidosis.
Run him for everything
you can think of.
Lepto, schisto, hemo,
and the fourth Marx Brother
nobody ever heard of.
You bitch!
I just went to get us some lunch,
you were asleep.
You moved my book.
Jeff.
Calm down.
It's just the drugs.
The drugs didn't move my book-
Jeff?
My husband's having a heart attack-
Can somebody help me,
please?
Somebody help me,
Please!
She saved his life.
Or she scabbed.
Depends on your point of view.
So what do we think?
New symptom?
Or just a wife beater?
Hey.
Time for you to take
this baby for a spin.
We, uh, loaded him
full of prednisone
to try to fix the liver.
Good news is, he's running out
of organs to fail.
Prednisone could cause
'Roid rage, which could cause
hypertension,
Which results
- 'Roid rage after six hours?
At that rate, by sundown,
he'll have eaten most of us.
Uh, it still could be
penicillin.
Allergic reaction.
How does a fried liver
put him into a rage?
It's not frying his liver,
it's frying his syphilis.
The penicillin's working.
The real patient is emerging,
so syphilis prevents
domestic violence.
I'm gonna be more
attractive to the ladies.
I was gonna test
for a heart issue
before the syphilis.
PFO could explain
the heart attack
and reduced blood flow to the
brain could explain the rage.
Well, all good ideas.
Okay,let's take a vote.
How many think
it's the 'roids talking?
And who's for the penicillin?
And how about
whatever she said?
Someone hasn't
raised their hand.
Whatever I decide?
You're setting me up.
Why would I do that?
PFO.
The PFOs have it.
I just hope the bubble
test is positive.
Or it's no more
Mr. Nice guy.
We gave Van Gogh
chelation therapy.
Turned him into a house painter.
Maybe not.
Maybe we just
put Hitler on ritalin.
Are you comparing
House to Hitler?
Oh God.
Just because I don't
think he's Hitler
doesn't mean I slept with him.
I don't sleep with everyone
who's better than Hitler.
Maybe Taub is right.
Maybe this is good.
This is not good.
Well, he respected
our opinions,
he mocked himself,
he was civil, he shared.
He didn't care.
He never cares.
He didn't vote.
He always cared about one thing.
Solving the puzzle.
But he was irrelevant
to that diagnosis.
He had no opinion of his own.
He now cares about nothing.
You had no choice;
you had to treat him.
What's done is done.
You know that thing
I was gonna tell you,
I gotta tell you.
I gotta tell someone.
You've got to swear
not to tell C.B.
Whatever.
Well, that's not swearing,
that's shrugging.
It's actually the opposite
of swearing.
I won't tell Amber.
My team thinks
that I have syphilis.
Do you?
Not yet.
Why do they think you do?
Because I knew
that they had access
to an old blood sample,
and I knew they'd test it
sometime for something.
Why would you swap your blood?
What are you afraid
they'll find?
Shut up,
you're missing the point.
Now, they think
that I'm on penicillin.
Is this some clever
practical joke
that I'm not aware of?
And as I get better,
I get nicer.
That's brilliant.
Foreman thinks I actually
value his opinion.
Thank God he said PFO, or I'd
have had to do some dancing.
You got time for bowling?
Come on, it's work hours.
I'll get my shoes.
- So we don't need to talk about
- No.
- You're gonna keep screwing-
- Yeah.
You're gonna keep
talking about it.
We are who we are.
I'll get my shoes.
Okay, got a good view
of the heart.
What if we lower
House's dosage?
Maybe stabilize him,
he doesn't get worse,
he doesn't get better.
Quite the line to walk.
If we're wrong, he
dies of neurosyphilis.
If we don't, other people die.
Other people who
aren't our boss.
People.
This sucks.
The guy had a gift.
I'd kill-
Hi, what-
House doesn't have syphilis.
He switched the blood samples.
How do you know that?
House told Wilson.
I wanted to ruin House's day.
See ya.
We're idiots.
We're not idiots.
Positive blood test means
positive blood test.
Apparently not.
There they are,
let's see if they-
Uh, what are you doing?
We're not done.
He doesn't have syphilis.
I know.
Patient tested positive
for syphilis, right?
Is this some sort of recap?
But why did he test positive
for syphilis?
Oh, I know this.
Either one: he has syphilis-
I was gonna say that.
Or two: the test
was wrong twice,
or three, he gave us
someone else's blood.
Who?
Amber.
Get that idiotic smile
out of my face.
I gotta go on a killing spree.
Or, four, he has something that
tests positive for syphilis.
It's not Chagas.
He worked in Costa Rica
before he was married.
Is two a spree, or do I
have to kill you too?
Chagas wouldn't explain
the niceness.
I've heard of remote tribes
that actually practice
acts of kindness.
Or the Chagas caused
encephalitis.
The MRI showed no sign-
Until we started him
on steroids,
compromised the immune system,
and let the infection flare up.
I did another one.
It's not much.
It's plenty.
You figured this out
because I don't have syphilis?
Damn.
That should have been
my epiphany.
Good news, bad news.
Good news is
we know what you have,
it's treatable, you're gonna live.
Really?
What's the bad news?
The cure is a grueling
course of pills.
It's like one a day
for a month.
Now you're just trying
to make me laugh.
Yeah, like that's a challenge.
You have Chagas disease.
It's a parasite.
It's been asymptomatic
for ten years.
Not quite.
- Your brain's been swollen-
- Not enough to see,
but enough to alter
your personality.
Now we're back to that.
He screamed at you.
You don't think he could change?
That was because of the drugs.
So you think drugs are more
powerful than parasites?
I mean,
the ones we're gonna give you to treat
the parasites obviously are-
I stand by the principle.
I'm not worried.
Neither am I.
But that's because
I don't care.
Reviews?
It was brought to my attention
that on occasion,
I am not respectful
of hospital hierarchy.
The word was "contemptuous."
Well-phrased, thoughtful.
Identically phrased.
These are all the same.
Because, underneath it all,
we are all the same.
And Foreman refused
to type his up.
Well, it's more
than I expected.
There's an extra one in there.
"Your treatment of patients
is non-existent
because you're not a doctor,
you're an administrator."
Foreman convinced me
that these could be helpful.
"Your management of employees
is, well, let's face it,
they're outside carrying signs."
The strike ended.
The nurses have been back
for two shifts already.
You'd think I'd have noticed.
What exactly did they do
around here?
"You act like employees
"should fear and respect you,
but your eyes tell us-
"but your eyes tell us nothing
"because we're looking
at your boobs,
"which tell us that
you're desperate
"to have someone jump on you
and tell you they love you
"one grunted syllable
at a time.
"What you want,
you run away from.
"What you need,
"you don't have a clue.
"What you've accomplished,
makes you proud.
But you're still miserable."
Please sign.
I got a call
from Amber today.
Says there's been a
violation of your contract.
You've been seeing
Wilson on her time.
She breached confidentiality.
You can let it slide,
officer.
We're even.
Yes, you are.
You're both losing fingers.
Look what I found.
Nice.
They think you might be able
to come home tomorrow.
Oh, yeah?
That's good.
What's the matter?
The ketchup.
There's something wrong
with that.
Tastes fine.
Anything else?
Everything else is great.
I'm just-
I don't know.
I guess I don't like
ketchup anymore.
Wonder what else
I don't like.
Roll over.
We need a tougher punishment.
Come over to the poopy side.
Where are you two
going Friday night?
Dinner at L'Auberge.
You're lying.
Of course I am.
www.tvsubtitles.net