Do you see them anywhere?
Why don't we go back to their house,
wait for them there.
Yeah,
'cause they'll probably answer
the door the sixteenth time I knock.
There they are.
Hi. I'm sorry I followed you here.
I just really wish you could
give me a few minutes of your time.
**Chinese language**
I know you would never agree
to make it an open adoption,
but I just figured
maybe you never had a choice.
I mean, it's china, right?
**Chinese language**
- What did he say?
- He wants you to leave them alone.
Please...
**Chinese language**
I just want ten minutes.
Learn what you're like,
tell you about my life.
**Chinese language**
He said they have no daughter.
I am sorry you wasted a trip.
I know that's them.
How does that work?
How do I pray?
You make a wish and lift the buddha.
I wish they could understand
how badly I need this.
Now make the wish again.
If you cannot lift the buddha
this time, your wish will be granted.
Are you okay?
**Chinese language**
House - Season 05 Episode 04
"Birthmarks"
Synchro: ShalimarFox, mpm, IceFreak
www.house-fr.com
I picked cameron's pocket
down in E.R.
I came up a doozy.
Your mother called, twice.
She's still healthy.
This 25-year-old woman,
on the other hand...
Her messages
sounded kind of urgent.
Well, that's the way women sound
when their spouse of 50 years dies.
Your dad died?
- Are you...
- Yep. Fine!
Our patient,
who's been known to take
a few drinks on non-occasions,
vomits blood and collapses
on a trip to china.
Chinese surgeons
cut out a foot of bowel,
but the pain is worse now
than it was before.
House, call your mom.
What are you, my mom?
We can continue
this differential in five minutes.
Are those bags under your eyes?
You were up all night.
- You told her, didn't you?
- I don't know
what your daddy issues are,
but don't deflect them on me.
Told his wife
he's been getting some strange.
She kicked
his adulterous tuchus to the curb.
- Seriously, you told her?
- Yes, I told her.
But no,
she did not kick me to the curb.
We stayed up late talking.
We're going to continue talking.
Much like House should be doing
with his mother right now.
Anybody read chinese?
Otherwise, we have no idea
what these doctors did to her.
Kutner, you're sort of asian, right?
Get it translated.
What about meckel's diverticulum?
If the surgeons
didn't remove the diverticulum,
it can cause pain, bleeding.
Too high up for a colonoscopy.
CT could Miss it.
Ultrasound's fastest.
And since I'm fastest
with the ultrasound...
House, let me do the ultrasound.
You need to deal
with your dad and...
I'm not deflecting because
I'm avoiding something deep.
I'm deflecting because
i'm avoiding something shallow.
Seriously, I'm fine.
I didn't even like the man.
No meckel's.
Were you there for the rice
or the reeducation camps?
I was there to track down
my biological parents.
Like a salmon returning
to the stream where it was born.
Did you become whole again,
or did you get eaten by bears?
They denied my existence.
Four parents, and not one of them
taught you to cover your mouth.
Oh, my god!
You look like they cut you in half.
- Doctor, we're her parents.
- I'm just a technician.
Her doctors will be by later.
You can schmooze then.
Can you let them know that we,
we went by her apartment
and collected all her medication.
I'm a technician and a doctor.
- You went through my apartment?
- We found alcohol.
We thought you'd quit.
- Did her drinking cause this?
- No.
Can you tell her it did?
Licorice root.
No, thanks I'm good.
I threw it to you for a reason.
That's what
the chinese doctors gave her.
It contains glycyrrhizin.
They were treating her for sars?
Not very effectively.
But sars explains the cough,
causes hypoperfusion,
which explain ischemic balance,
it's perfect.
Lung involvement isn't very severe.
Okay, well, so call it "ars."
Start her on ribavirin
and interferon.
- Sorry about your father.
- I'm not.
Are we done emoting now?
If there's anything
I can do, just...
You know, you're right.
I don't think I can sleep alone tonight.
And you can tell me that
that is liquid vicodin.
We giving I.G. shots to everyone
who came in contact with your patient.
Shockingly, none of the nurses
volunteered to administer yours.
It goes better in a large muscle.
Drop your pants.
You know, I usually pay
tens of dollars to hear that.
The funeral's tomorrow.
My mom called you?
There is 3:40 flight out of Newark.
If you leave now,
you can be in Lexington tonight.
Your mother wants
you to deliver a eulogy.
"Eulogy."
From the greek for "good word."
Now, if she asked me
to deliver a bastardogy,
- I'd be happy to...
- Then be a grown-up.
Call your mother back and
tell her that you're sick with grief,
- but you're too busy to be there.
- She knows when I'm lying.
Then start writing.
They yanked my brother
and sister of college.
Can you please tell them
I'm not dying?
You have sars.
I'm wearing a mask.
It's a big deal.
Cut 'em some slack.
But I am gonna be okay, right?
That's what all this stuff is for.
We're gonna need the names
and numbs of everyone
you came in contact
with here and in china.
Flight numbers, dates...
that doctor
that i coughed all over...
Is he gonna be all right?
So far he's fine.
It's back.
This is where the pain all started.
She's tachycardic.
Get a crash cart in here!
What's going on?
I need to know what's going on.
That's my daughter.
Her liver's failing.
It's not sars.
I am not doing this because I care.
Cuddy drugged me.
She...
My mom didn't call cuddy.
She called you.
I knew you couldn't stay away
I knew you loved me too much.
I'm doing this for your mom.
I'm not doing this at all.
If there were something to be done,
I would have done it
in the year he spent dying.
You took my vicodin?!
I'm in pain.
One?!
So the vicodin is my leash.
One'll take the edge off,
but it won't give me enough relief
for an escape back to plainsboro.
Where's my phone?
That's the team.
It's their ring tone.
Forget it.
The patient's blood
is on your hands.
House? You there?
I'being held against my will.
Call the police!
Nicole had a clot
in the epatic vein.
Chase sucked it out,
saved her liver.
No signs of a tumor or venous
malformations. Nothing that could...
- She's an addict.
- Drugs and alcohol wouldn't
She's a smoker.
Combine smoking with any one
of a dozen genetic disorders,
and she's a clotting machine.
Multiple blood clots would tie together
bowel ischemia, lungs, and the liver.
We need to pinpoint
which defect she has
so we can start her
on the right anticoagulant.
Draw her blood,
let's find out which genetic gift
her genetic parents gave her.
Thanks for calling.
My ring tone for you
is "dancing queen", by ABBA.
Nicole?
I need to pee.
Pull over at the next stop.
I'll just pee on the floor.
You bought used floor mats?
That is brilliant.
There's a rest stop in five miles.
- Cane.
- The restroom's right there.
You can make it on your own.
I suppose I could talk about the summer
he decided he wasn't speaking to me.
Two months, not one word.
Anything he wanted to say, he typed up
and slipped under my bedroom door.
You don't want to say anything,
don't say anything, but go.
Tell your mom you're sad for her.
Just by being there, i'd be lying.
She wants to think,
for a moment,
that she had a happy family.
So give her a gift, lie!
Give me my cane...
I'll go to the damn funeral.
I said I'd go to the funeral.
I didn't say when.
We have these two categories:
inside and outside.
Patients stay inside.
Then, when they're better,
we let them go outside.
Thanks.
But they don't let you smoke inside.
So why don't you go back there
and give me five minutes outside?
Make a fist.
It's such a beautiful day, we thought
we'd do all our doctorg outside.
People stare at me any time
I'm out with my family.
It's like a puzzle.
"Which one of these things
doesn't belong?"
Belonging's overrated.
I was adopted by a white family
when I was nine.
I like being different.
The view's better
from the outside looking in.
Must be easier to be different
when you're a success.
Is that a problem?
This is why we prefer inside.
You actually keep a flashlight
that doesn't need batteries
in the trunk?
Next to the jacket,
emergency water,
nail clippers, tooth brush,
space blanket...
When things go wrong,
I like to be ready.
Will you... please hold the flashlight
for a minute?
You know, those aren't
just my car keys.
My house keys are on there too.
Amber gave me that key chain.
No, she didn't. Not unless
your pet name for her was "Volvo."
A man who would lie about a gift
from a dead girlfriend...
Is probably responding to a childish,
pointless act of petulance.
The struggle to resist most captures
is never pointless.
Vive la resistance!
I hate to break it to you, che,
but simple delay won't work.
Your mother will hold
the funeral till we get there.
My father was a punctual man,
beholden to time.
Two minutes late for dinner,
you didn't eat.
My mother would never disrespect him
by starting the funeral late.
Yeah, you clearly have
no issues to work through.
Come on, forget the keys.
Call a locksmith.
We go inside and play "guess that smell"
with the truckers while we're waiting.
Join me on the dark side.
The dark side's done, House.
I'm delivering you to your mother,
and that's it.
I have moved on.
What do you think House would send,
the "gentle comfort" arrangement
or the "warm thoughts" bouquet?
I mean, if he wasn't an ass.
Send one of those giant cookies
shaped like a coffin.
His mom would believe
it was from him.
I didn't tell you
so you could send anything.
You need to know the extent to which he
is disconnected from the human race.
Took a six-pack of FFP
to stop the oozing.
She's bleeding and clotting?
Plus schistocytes on her smear means
it's DIC, which means she's got cancer.
- She's young. It could be leukemia.
- Normal WBC makes that less likely.
- The belly pain toward a G.I. Tumor.
- House did an ultrasound.
He wasn't looking for a tumor.
Go run a CT.
I don't buy it.
Ct can find small intestinal cancers
- that an ultrasound...
- I don't buy House.
When my father died, I wound up
killing a patient. And I hated the man.
Whatever House says
or doesn't say,
I'm sure the guy's a mess.
So he was a bastard.
He was still your father.
You're biologically programmed
to have feelings for him.
No, I'm not.
Feelings aren't rational.
I know you have trouble with anything
that can't be quantified and counted.
He's not my biological father.
I figured it out when I was 12.
Of course. You were a brilliant,
socially isolated 12-year-old,
and you create a parallel universe
in which your life doesn't suck.
I look at the facts.
First of all, he was deployed
on training exercises off Okinawa
during the time
I had to be conceived.
And since you're 150 years old,
air travel was impossible.
His second toe is longer
than his big toe.
- Mine isn't.
- This is sad.
You don't believe
your mother screwed around...
I have a distinctive
red birthmark on my scalp
that matches a certain friend
of the family.
If you believed this story, you wouldn't
tell me about his birthmarks.
You'd be telling me
about the genetic testing you had done.
And since you haven't mentioned it,
obviously, you didn't do it.
Because you don't want...
What are you doing?
Get your... get off the...
There's a cop!
Nicole, lie still.
This'll only take a few seconds.
One millimeter cut
through upper abdomen.
She was adopted when the parents
thought they couldn't have kids.
Then they had three more. She took
the message as "thanks for playing,
but we have our real children now."
And the real children
probably think they're accidents
while she was hand-picked. Everybody's
got problems with their parents.
She's an addict.
Something went wrong.
And it has to be the parents?
Magnifying pancreas.
- I'm not saying the parents screwed up.
- You're saying you like her.
So you don't want her faults
to be her fault.
But they're someone's fault,
and the other people you know are...
I think we may need
to call House again.
You lost track of your speed?
I think that was Hitler's excuse.
Lost track of the Jews.
No one held him
responsible.
- I'm not playing house.
- You were protecting me.
Anybody in their right mind
would have ratted me out.
I'm just trying
to speed things along.
You are going
this funeral.
Make it fast. I don't want to miss
the anal cavity search.
Looks like a mass
in the pancreas.
Not to me. This is radio.
- And I want a full play-by-play.
- It's fluid-filled.
Would you get out of the car, sir?
Officer, if you want to give me
a ticket, I totally understand.
- Just get out of the car, sir.
- Cyst?
Large cyst.
Something going on there?
Wilson's getting arrested.
How large?
SUV sized, or mid-range sedan?
Seriously?
What'd you do?
I'm obviously joking.
If Wilson was getting handcuffed
on the hood of his car,
Would I be carrying
on a differential?
Diameter is at least
eight centimeters.
- Is it in the tail or in the head?
- The head.
You too, sir.
Out of the car.
We've got a construction site.
A steamroller is plowing...
Out now.
No can
James Evan Wilson,
there's a warrant
for your arrest in Louisiana.
What are the traits
of a steamroller?
Powerful.
Maybe pancreatic cancer.
Great idea, except the only symptom
it matches up with
is being steamrollerish.
You don't think House
is onto something?
I think he thought he had an idea.
I also think his metaphors
are tough enough to decipher
after he's said them.
- We need to focus on the medicine.
- No answer.
There's not gonna be an answer.
They've been arrested.
- He was joking.
- He reacted to the size and location.
That's what we should be
focusing on. Not playing mad libs
while our patient's exploding noun
destroys her life-sustaining noun.
I'll try to get Wilson on the line.
What if it's not how a steamroller
works, but what it does?
Clears things.
This is a waste of time.
I need that phone call.
I'm a doctor, and when someone tries
to call you three times,
it's code for "pick up the damn phone
before someone dies."
I'm sure there's
other smart doctors.
You'd be surprised.
- You told me you'd taken care of this.
- I did.
- First words you ever said to me.
- I took care of it.
You must've screwed up somehow.
Sir?
Not to hurry you,
but we need to be at a funeral...
Nobody is going anywhere
or taking any phone calls
till I hear back
from Louisiana.
It's a really old warrant.
Isn't there a statute of limitations
on this kind of thing?
It's suspended
when you flee the state.
I didn't flee the state.
I left the state.
Because I don't live in the state.
And the charges were
just so minor...
"vandalism,
"destruction of property,
assault."
There is a simple explanation.
There was a medical convention
in New Orleans...
You don't need to explain to me.
I was fresh out of med school.
I didn't know anybody at the convention.
You heard the man, Wilson.
You don't have to explain.
I am not gonna sit here wasting time
just so you can avoid
your father's funeral!
He's my father.
- I have the right to avoid his funeral.
- Not if your mother's alive, you don't.
Explain.
Did House react
to the eight centimeters?
He whistled.
It's huge.
Anyone would think so.
He doesn't whistle because he's
impressed. He wasn't expecting it.
It means he changed his mind
at that point.
A single super-sized cyst
ruled out a diffuse process
like scleroderma or lupus.
Rule out diffuse process, you're stuck
with a process only affecting pancreas.
Gallstones
or pancreatic divisum.
What he asked next
would narrowed that down.
He asked the location.
Heads it's gallstones,
tails it's divisum.
It's at the head.
She's got gallstones.
- The steamroller means potholes...
- Relax. We got it.
You figured out
she's got gallstones?
I was at the hotel bar
trying to unwind, have a drink.
There was this guy
who kept playing
Billy Joel's leave a tender
moment alone on the jukebox.
- Leave a tender moment is a good song.
- It's a great song. He was out of line.
Not as good as scenes
from an Italian restaurant or...
So I... I asked the man
to stop, polity.
You yelled politely.
I was polite
the first couple of times,
but courtesy made
no impression on this ass.
So
I threw a bottle
into the mirror,
which successfully conveyed
my message.
And smashed a ten-foot
antique mirror.
And set an example to two other patrons
who threw shot glasses.
I had nothing to do
with that fight.
The assault charge was totally bogus.
And I paid for the mirror.
I think I have the picture.
I assume you're the guy
who was playing the song.
No, I was the guy
who bailed him out.
That's how we met.
I was in jail.
This guy was a total stranger to you,
and you bailed him out?
It was a boring convention.
I had to have somebody to drink with.
And there's the foundation
of our entire friendship.
If you hadn't been bored
one weekend, it wouldn't even exist.
There were 3,000 people
at that convention.
You were the one who wasn't boring.
That says something.
It also says that you lied to me
about getting the charges dropped!
I got a lawyer.
He cut a deal.
You didn't call the guy?
You've to go at the arraignment.
Everybody knows that.
Everybody with
your misdemeanor experience.
You can go.
What?
He's a fugitive from justice.
That whole story was lies.
He stabbed a man.
Louisiana doesn't want to pay
- to get you back.
- Forget louisiana.
He was driving recklessly
through your comatose village.
Do the put lead
in the jelly doughnuts here?
Stop acting
like such an ingrate
and go pay your respects
to your father.
The CT confirmed gallstones.
Normally not dangerous.
Almost everyone has them.
- But sometimes...
- They kill you?
Unless I take 'em out.
We do it laproscopically.
- How long has her urine been brown?
- Kidney's were fine this afternoon.
They're not now.
It's not the gallstones.
Well, of course it's not gallstones.
Who thought it was gallstones?
- You said "steamroller."
- I also said "construction site."
Gallstones could cause
a pancreatic cyst.
Just turn around.
The thing is two hours over already,
and that's the third time
we passed that colonial
with the cross burning out front.
I'm not lost.
I'm not talking about what caused
the cyst, but what the cyst caused.
Everything.
Cysts are symptoms, not diagnoses.
Unless it's a multiple cyst,
with connections to other organs...
Like a steamroller.
That's a long road
down to the kidneys.
How do we prove it?
Won't be visible in a scan.
Chase isn't gonna go groping around
when she's got kidney failure.
- Bubbles.
- Is that your new stripper name?
Yes. And also, we inject bubbles
into the cyst and foll where they drift.
If they end up in other organs, we know
you're right, cut it out, she's fine.
Bubbles is right.
Go echo.
I'm not lost.
Nicole, you gotta stay still.
I'm nervous.
- You're not nervous.
- It's the DTS, isn't it?
I haven't had a drink
since I got here.
Good heavens,
we haven't missed it after all.
It's like the end
of Christmas carol.
I'm so glad you're here.
Oh, it's a load
off of my mind just to see you.
- Thank you, James.
- Mom, how could you delay the funeral?
Honey, your dad is dead.
He's not going to care.
Do you know what
you're going to say?
I don't know.
Just let the minister
orne of his buddies from the corps...
You're talking. I don't care
that you didn't like him.
He was your father,
and he loved you.
The war is over, greg.
Please do this for me.
Stop looking so worried.
I know he's gonna make me proud.
I'm sure you know him
better than I do.
Her liver's been compromised.
And the dts will cause her muscles to
continue to twitch, even under sedation.
We need to paralyze
her to do this procedure.
I wanted to stop.
A phenarbital coma will not only
allow us to inject the cyst,
I'll treat the dts.
When she wakes up,
she won't be in withdrawal.
We've seen her through
withdrawal before.
We've seen her through everything.
We've been...
supportive, we've been combative.
We've picked her up from
bars in the middle of the night.
We've let her spend the night in jail.
I used to say it'd be okay.
That I'd get it together.
I don't say that anymore.
Let's make you healthy.
Then we'll worry
about making you sober.
The lord is my shepherd,
I shall not want...
I am not talking.
We were strangers who shared
some geography 30 years ago.
Right, he had no
influence on you at all.
The father who was
compulsive about punctuality.
His issue.
Which I deliberately
made not my issue.
Thereby making it your issue.
Compulsively showing up four hours late,
ignoring discipline, ignoring rules.
Oh, god, he's here.
Who's here?
The one
you're pretending is your father?
Nice pick.
He looks like Sean Connery.
So back when you were devising
this fantasy,
did you tell your father:
"dad, I refuse to recognize
your existence because
I have chosen james bond as my dad"?
I used different words.
What?!
Hearing your own son
hates you so much
he's replaced you in his mind?
That's gotta suck.
How did he take it?
I already told you.
He didn't speak to me for a summer.
It means more to me than...
Than I can say to have
all of you here today.
And now, our son Gregory
would like to say a few words.
Greg?
There's a lot of people here today.
Including some from the corps.
And I notice that every one of them
is either my father rank or higher.
And that doesn't surprise me.
Because if the test of a man
is how he treats those
he has power over,
it was a test my father failed.
This man
you're eager to pay homage to,
he was incapable of admitting
any point of view but his own.
He punished failure,
and he did not accept
anything less than...
He loved doing what he did.
He saw his work as some kind of...
Sacred calling.
More important than
any personal relationship.
Maybe if he'd been a better father,
I'd be a better son.
But I am what I am because of him...
For better or for worse.
And I just...
I just wish...
Put it back.
He's not gonna miss it.
I'm done enabling.
You can't even let them put
him in the ground
without making it serve your agenda?
You real want to do
this in front of everybody?
You wanna punish me or them?
How can I still feel surprise?
You would take,
even this, a moment of
real human grief,
and turn it into a farce.
Oh, cut the crap.
You enjoy what I do.
I never had to force you.
You like coming along for the ride.
- Yes, that's why i'm cheering you on...
- This is about you needing
to be prepared for the worst.
So you become an oncologist.
No surprises there.
Worst happens all the time.
But Amber, she was young and healthy.
Her death came out of nowhere.
Don't bring Amber into this.
And you weren't ready.
That makes you angry.
The world sucks, and
you didn't have time to brace yourself.
What happened out there
is your show!
You're scared to death
of losing anyone that matters.
So you dump the person
who matters the most to you!
I'm not scared to death.
I'm moving forward!
Because no one can take away
from you what you no longer have.
Your father's death is about you.
Amber's death is about you.
I can'imagine why someone
wouldn't want to be your friend!
Admit it, you're angry and
you're scared of losing me.
I'm not angry,
- I'm not scared.
- Admit it.
- I'm not afraid.
- I've lost people. It happens.
- Admit it. Admit it!
What are you, five?
- Stop repeating...
- Admit it. Admit it.
Admit it. Admit it.
Admit it.
Come on, admit it.
Admit it!
Still not boring.
Did you know I was gonna do that?
Because I didn't know
I was gonna do that.
I know
you have trouble losing people.
In new orleans, I saw you carrying this
express package around the conference.
And you wouldn't let it go,
but you wouldn't open it.
So I peeked at the return address.
Diamond, fairbairn.
Divorce attorneys.
Your first wife had
just served you with papers.
Did you know that
when you bailed me out?
Were you...
Doing something nice for me?
What did I say about being boring?
We owe your mom an apology.
Hello?
It's House.
How'd the bubble test go?
The problem wasn't the cyst.
It's advanced dilated cardiomyopathy.
We did a three-dimensional echo.
Showed a mass in the left atrium.
Looks like an atrial maxoma,
but the ultrasound images are
a little grainy, so it's hard to tell.
House
The images aren't grainy.
They sure look grainy.
I've seen pictures of
you where you look tall.
It's iron overload.
Creates speckles on the image,
makes it look grainy.
Also makes her pancreas fail,
her blood clot, and her intestine...
Atrial myxoma is more likely.
MRI for a better view.
Call me back and tell me
you're embarrassed
because my eyesight
is better 500 miles away.
I need a phone number.
I'm a doctor in new jersey,
treating one of your clients.
A young woman looking
for her biological parents.
You know, you could just wait for
the MRI to have your cursity satisfied.
What person who is nothing
like me are you saying that to?
Did the parents look tan?
The disease she has is genetic,
which means they should have it too.
They don't look more
tan than anyone else.
- Discolored teeth?
- They're farmers...
The village
doesn't even have a dentist.
Right. Thanks.
But if it matters,
I'm not convinced
they were her parents.
Why not?
Because they said
they have no daughter.
The man was adamant,
and the woman seemed confused
and frightened.
Thank you.
Differential.
Say
you're a middle-aged chinese woman...
fine.
Say it.
I'm a middle-aged chinese woman.
Girl comes to you,
says that she's your long-lost daughter.
Why would yo be frightened?
I'm frightened
because she's a threat?
Maybe she knows something?
She hasn't seen you
since she was an infant.
Maybe an inheritance issue.
They're peasants.
Her very presence is a threat.
She--
What year was she born?
'83.
She's not supposed be alive.
China introduced the
one-child policy in 1979.
Say they didn't want a girl.
- They tried to kill her.
- Maybe the baby doesn't die.
Maybe the father panics
or regrets it.
Takes the baby to an orphanage.
Maybe he doesn't tell his wife.
Who freaks out like she's seen a ghost
25 years later when the girl shows up.
Why does attempted murder
from 25 years ago
suddenly become relevant
to her health now?
Maybe they gave her something toxic.
It would have to be fat soluble.
This is fun, isn't it?
- Let me see the MRI.
- We don't have one.
She started vomiting as
soon as we started the scan.
Then let her vomit through the MRI.
That's what nurses are for.
Her parents tried to kill her.
I don't know how,
but I know it caused her to get sick
25 years later trying to lift a buddha.
Explain.
I already had this conversation
with Wilson--just go with it.
- Poison?
- Buddha wouldn't make it worse.
Maybe the weight stressed
her back, which...
makes sense if she's never
lifted anything in her life.
She actually didn't get sick till
she tried lifting it that second time.
I'm guessing the weight changed.
Anybody have Taub's pager number?
What's up?
Maybe give him a call.
If he tosses that switch on the MRI,
she's dead.
X-ray her brain.
Pins.
Push them rough the soft fontanelle
of an infant,
you skewer the brain, and the hair hides
the entry wounds.
It's the perfect crime.
She's had them
in her all these years.
- What changed at the temple?
- Same thing that changed in the MRI.
Shockingly,
not all religious leaders are honest.
I'm guessing these particular monks
are bilking the faithful by pushing
a magnet up buddha's butt.
There's another one under the table
that'll repel or attract, depending
on how you shift them.
When she picked up that magnet,
it moved one of the pins deeper into the
sympathetic nervous center of her brain.
This sent a signal
through the nerves
to the blood vessels in
her small intestines,
which caused the symptoms in china
and in the giant magnet
we call an MRI.
She's lucky.
We're all screwed up by our parents.
She's got documentation.
The pins will be removed surgically,
and she'll be fine.
We'll wake her from the
coma after the operation.
Is there any way
you could not tell her?
Please.
She's fragile.
She desperately wanted
to know her biological parents.
For her to find out
that they wanted her dead...
I don't know what that'll do to her.
She may not be as fragile
as you think.
We know our daughter.
See this pin here?
It's been pressing directly
on her addiction center.
It's not her fault.
And it's definitely not your fault.
She's not who you think she is.
I hear
your patient's gonna be all right.
Is that why you're here?
A colleague checking up
on a patient?
Something going' on?
I'm celebrating.
My mom hated him too.
Your DNA test showed no match?
That's incredible.
At the age of 12,
you actually figured out
your father wasn't your birth father
that's what you wanted, wasn't it?
Why should it depress you?
It doesn't depress me.
Doesn't make any difference at all.
That's what depresses me.
I guess nobody gets
to choose who their parents are.
I'm not even sure anymore if
we get to choose who our friends are.
I spoke with Cuddy.
She hasn't filled my position yet.
If you're coming back
just because you're attracted
to the shine of my neediness...
i'd be okay with that.
I'm coming back
because you're right.
That strange,
annoying trip we just took
was the most fun I've had
since Amber died.
You hungry?
My dad's dead.
Yeah.
My sympathies.
www.house-fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net