- What time?
- 4:30.
- Why so late?
- Medical test and social studies.
- Did you invite Shelby for Saturday?
- No.
- Do you want me to call her?
- That'd be great,
you calling a 12-year-old girl
for a sleep over.
- It'll be fine.
- I'll make you a deal.
I'll call a friend
when you call a friend.
- It's your birthday, do as you want.
- Thank you. Bye.
Bye.
- What'd you forget?
- Nothing.
- Then why'd you came back?
- 'cause I live here.
Come one,
you're gonna be late for school.
What are you talking about?
It's 4:30.
Are you okay?
I...
Tired, I guess.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
House - Season 5 Episode 6
"Joy"
TS: Ragbear.com
Synchro: ShalimarFox, mpm
www.house-fr.com
Great. That's all I need to know.
You're late!
Okay, bye.
37-year-old male with
recurrent blackouts.
Tell him to switch from tequila
to bourbon. It worked for me.
The three doctors he's already seen
already ruled out drugs and alcohol.
Then it's epilepsy.
Tell him to buy a hockey helmet...
ET's clean so is the CT.
Relax.
Just 'cause you got
approved by an adoption agency
doesn't mean you'll
get approved by the birth mother.
You're a single mom.
That puts you somewhere below
couples that quitted
in daycare scandals.
You're welcome, Dr. House.
It is an interesting case.
What time are you
seeing the mom?
You're having
your guy follow me?
I just trash your social value
as a mother
and all I got was a little sarcasm.
It means you don't feel
the need to defend yourself,
which means you're not worried
about getting a kid,
which means you've
already got one.
We're meeting at 11:00.
She's due to deliver
a baby girl in two weeks.
I'm sure the mom will be thrilled
to hand her crack baby off to a doctor.
- She's not a crack baby.
- No, mother's perfectly healthy,
she just had to give up the baby
in order to continue her work
on the human genome.
She confessed to some past meth use.
What they don't confess to is almost
always more interesting.
This is a mistake.
Because a kid you don't know
may have some problem
that you don't know about that
she may have passed on to a kid?
You're a control-seeking narcicist.
Which is fine,
good even in some jobs.
But you're not equipped to handle
a real kid nevermind a factory second.
Where are you meeting her?
In a little place called "Follow me
and your urologist
will be buying himself a new yacht."
They explained
the returns policy, right?
- It's worse than video games.
- Not changing my mind.
- Could be post-concussion syndrome.
- Not without a preconcussion.
- Pick a number.
- For what?
Cuddy pool. She got the inane.
The little tweaker is doing 14 days.
That's great news... I think.
It's good news.
The great news is...
she insisted that she's
not gonna change her mind,
means she's actually
thought about changing her mind
means she's not sure
if she's ready to be a mom,
means she's not ready to be a mom,
means she's gonna change her mind.
Only question is when.
$100 buyin'. Less than seven
means the next seven days.
But she's been dying
for a kid for three years.
- No way she's gonna back out now.
- Not one of the options.
Many strokes can cause
blackouts, memory loss.
Nine hours is a lot of time
to be out from a mini-stroke.
And there'd be residual damage
on the CT.
Guy works at home as
a consumer product tester.
He could've been exposed to a toxin
that caused short-term memory loss,
wouldn't show up on imaging.
Cavernous sinus thrombosis could
cause absence seizures and memory loss.
- I'll take 7 to 14.
- We have a player.
You just said it was great news.
Now you want to bet against her?
It's only great news if
she wants it to be great news.
House knows her better than any of us.
I'd rather you use a pseudonym.
Good thinking.
I say she's gonna
meet the mom and bolt.
I'm going for the early fold.
Check his home for toxins and
his sinuses for thrombosises.
Maybe he Oded on cafeine.
Apparently, he didn't drink
the coffee. Just smelled it.
Did they just move here?
- Six years ago.
- This is no way to raise a kid.
He's a single dad.
I'm sure he's doing his best.
Which is why single
people shouldn't have kids.
You got a problem with
what Cuddy's doing?
You think single mothers...
I think the traditional
family is a fraud.
Even married moms are single moms.
Daddy just pays some bills
and reads just enough bedtime stories
to not kill himself out of guilt.
My dad was great.
After my mum died...
He might be the exception.
On the other hand,
you are fairly screwed up.
No booze, no meds, no drugs.
And no view.
The building's half empty.
He's rather have a view
at the turnpike than the park.
Park views are probably 50% more.
Are you surprised the guy's a
pragmatist after looking at this place?
Guy's not a pragmatist.
He's a flagellant.
Looks like mold.
A mom would've, cleaned better.
Exposure to certain types of mold
can cause short-term memory loss.
- We're testing both of you.
- I feel fine.
I'm sure you are...
We're just being cautious.
Where do you guys go
other than home and school?
Nowhere. Dad works
at home and I go to school.
What about sports, friends, travel?
Like I said, dad works
at home and I go to school.
Must be hard not
having your mom around?
I was only 4 when
the accident happened.
Still, I'm sure you both
miss her sometimes.
Not really...
- You're strong.
- No,
I just don't get what the big
deal about death is, you know?
Yeah.
How is she?
Physically, she's fine.
Mentally, she's weird.
I'm sure she's just
freaked out about her dad.
Mr. Harmon?
Mr. Harmon.
Where are you going?
I have an appointment. I have to go.
We haven't finished
with your treatment.
- We're waiting test results.
- I have an appointment.
- You're gonna have to reschedule.
- I really have to go.
- Mr. Harmon, do you know where you are?
- Why are you trying to stop me?
His eyes.
Is he having a seizure?
His pupils are responsive.
I think he's... asleep.
He was just asleep.
Means no memory loss.
Sleepwalking doesn't kill.
- Unless he walks out a window.
- Sleepwalking's not a diagnosis.
It's a symptom. As long as we
can't figure out why...
Stress-induced insomnia.
Lots of people sleepwalk.
Not in the middle of the day before
they've even put their head on a pillow.
- Could be some sort of narcolepsy.
- Which is caused by...
There's usually genetic history.
Or?
If you know the answer,
can you tell us the answer?
I don't know the answer.
Which brings us back to... or?
Some sort of environmental trigger.
- Which means?
- It's a toxin.
- So we are?
- Being lead down an annoying path.
I honestly don't know
where this is going.
- Just following the clues.
- We're right back where we started.
The mold we found
doesn't cause these symptoms.
And there's nothing else
at his home.
- And?
- And you're obnoxious.
- He never goes anywhere else.
- Which we know because?
Because he says so.
Because his daughter says so.
Because they have no reason to lie.
Which proves he never
goes anywhere else...
When...
He's...
Conscious.
Oh, my god, you're right.
- He said he had an appointment.
- Next time, let him keep it.
Send him home.
See where his dreams take him.
Becca?
- Dr. Cuddy?
- Lisa. Nice to meet you.
- Oh, you want one?
- No thanks.
I can't stop eating them.
I guess it's, like, a craving.
I must have, like,
a dozen a day.
Oh, and this is decaf.
How have you been feeling?
You know, tired, fat, nervous.
Is there anything
you want to ask me?
Yeah, actually,
I just have one question.
What are you gonna call her?
I'm not sure.
It's all been
rather sudden, you know?
I like Joy.
But as I said,
I haven't really decided yet.
Well, is there anything
you want to ask me? It's okay.
The agency web site is filled
with prospective parents.
Their photos, their biographies.
There's so many wonderful people
out there.
Wonderful couples.
Why did I choose
a single mom?
My grandmother was married
for 37 years
to a man that treated her
like garbage.
And my mom would've stayed married
to my loser dad that long,
but he dumped her.
You know, I never understood
how you could fall for the same crap
as your mother.
Then I met Tony.
When I read your bio,
a doctor, a head of a hospital,
I saw your picture...
I don't want her raised by a loser.
How long have you had that rash?
I don't know. A few days?
- Have you had any joint pain?
- Yeah, I'm pregnant.
All my joints hurt.
They shouldn't all hurt.
Have you been using?
Not in seven months.
Not since I found out
I was pregnant.
That needs to be checked out.
You sure you don't want children?
You know, just because
we're stuck here and I'm lying down
doesn't mean we need to get deep.
You're afraid you'll make the same
mistake you made with your wife.
Get caught taking some
other kid to a ball game.
I like my life as it is.
- Alpha waves increasing.
- Any change in demeanor?
No, nothing.
He just got up.
Maybe it's a result
of the blood pressure change.
Delta waves out of nowhere.
He's now asleep.
Brain's supposed
to turn off motor function.
If the brain was doing what
what he has to do, we wouldn't be here.
He's leaving.
Come on.
She's 38 weeks.
- You think it's fifth disease?
- What's that?
It's a viral infection.
It can infect the fetus.
Usually in the first
20 weeks of pregnancy,
in women who have trouble
with their immune system.
History of drug abuse could've
compromised her immune system.
I told you I haven't used
anything in seven months.
It does look more
like a heat rash to me.
Yes, well, maybe we want to look
at the actual blood tests.
Of course.
- She work for you?
- Yeah.
Everybody here works for you.
When this happens for real,
are you okay to deliver here?
- Yeah, sure.
- Good.
Blood work's normal.
- Test it again.
- Tested it twice.
I'll get you some topical cream
for that rash.
I'm admitting her.
- There's nothing wrong.
- There are dozens of other things
this rash could indicate.
I want a full fetal work up.
You're losing it.
That's what happens
when you have kids.
Ceaseless crying and nagging
leads to irrational fears.
It's impressive that you didn't wait
for the actual crying and nagging.
She had a lace pattern rash,
joint pain, and a history of drug abuse.
You would've done
exactly the same thing.
And I'd be an excellent father.
Hey! What are you doing?!
Baby barf.
Maternity ward was handing out
free samples.
Well played, sir.
You leave me no choice
but to change.
- My clothes, not my mind.
- That's exactly my point.
It's not gonna be me and a cup.
It's gonna be eight times a day.
If you can't handle wearing
that stain, you can't handle a baby.
Why do you even care?
It's not like I'm ever gonna ask
you to babysit.
I'm a humanitarian.
- We should stop him.
- The whole point was to...
Let him plow
into some innocent bystander?
- His legs are working.
- Obviously, his eyes are working too.
His reaction time could be slower.
- He's stopping.
- Yeah, I see.
He's having sleep sex.
Maybe.
Pull up to her.
I know.
- What'd that guy want?
- Piss off.
- Go after him. She's not a hooker.
- How do you know?
Do you want me
to describe the clues,
or do you want to stop him before
he finishes the drugs he just bought?
Apparently,
rip's a coke fiend.
So sleeping beauty
has a Jones for snow white.
Coke explains the narcolepsy.
Narcolepsy explains the sleepwalking.
But it doesn't explain the rip
in the space time continuum.
Coke leads to sleepwalking,
which leads to coke,
which leads to sleepwalking.
What caused the first sleepwalking?
The coke he took
while he was wide awake.
Says no.
Wouldn't be the first time
somebody lied about drug use.
He has no reason to lie. He's sick.
His job doesn't drug test.
No relationship.
His daughter wouldn't find out.
Maybe he just forgot.
Forgot he did cocaine?
You're going with forgot over lying?
Fits.
Cocaine explains the narcolepsy.
Narcolepsy explains
the sleepwalking.
Whatever is in the cocaine other than
the cocaine explains the memory loss.
Dealers cut this stuff
with all kinds of garbage.
Great, we'll start him on immediate
treatment for all kinds of garbage.
- You can narrow it down in the lab.
- Not without a sample.
So get a sample.
You want us to score cocaine
from a drug dealer?
- It's exciting.
- It's a felony.
It's necessary.
There she is.
Amniotic fluid looks good.
Good fetal movement.
Heart's beating nicely.
- What?
- It looks like pulmonary hypoplasia.
What's that?
The baby's lungs are underdeveloped.
She won't be able to breath on her own.
- She might die?
- I don't know.
If She was born, she'd be in trouble,
but, we're not gonna let that happen.
We'll put you on magnesium
to prevent labor and steroids
to grow the lungs.
It's a good thing
dr. Cuddy brought you in.
How do you know
what a drug dealer looks like?
I'm not doing drugs,
if that's you're asking.
I just noticed that she had cash
in her hand. Obviously came from him.
He didn't have enough time
to perform any other services.
- I didn't notice her holding...
- There she is.
Uh, we're not cops.
- Cops aren't allowed to say that?
- Yeah, they can say it.
But if you were a cop,
you'd know that.
What do you want?
I would like to buy
some cocaine, please.
Definitely
not a cop.
Thank you.
Wait.
It's good.
- Glad you like it, Pablo. Can we go?
- No.
- You gave us the wrong stuff.
- What are you talking about?
- You got my best.
- I know. I don't want the good
"get your new
customer hooked" stuff.
I want the stepped on "keep the old
ustomer coming back for more" stuff.
- Are you crazy, bitch?
- No, I'm a just a bitch
who knows what she wants.
Looks like this kid thing
is really working out for you.
All of the shopping,
none of the stretch marks.
Not a good time.
Right, kid's getting worse.
Blessing in disguise.
Although a completely
predictable one.
You take in strays,
don't be surprised by the worms.
- Still wearing the sweater.
- I didn't say you weren't stubborn.
- I said you weren't maternal.
- Thank you. Go away.
- You're getting crankier.
- Baby's sick.
Sorry I'm not finding
the fun in that.
Is it really worth it?
Just for the pursuit
of unconditional love?
Only you could see that
as a bad thing.
It's a fake thing.
There's no unconditional love.
It's just unconditional need.
Don't make this child a victim
of your biological clock.
Victim?
You think she's
better off staying...
Yes!
Because at least she knows
she's not qualified for the job.
Let me guess.
I'm gonna tell her not to play ball
in the house but she's not gonna listen.
No, actually, I was going for
she sneaks her boyfriend in
while you're sleeping,
and he wants to do it on the desk.
And at first she says no,
but she has issues
with self-esteem.
- You're gonna pay for that.
- I'm paying for it right now.
With wisdom.
Get out.
We found lactose.
The coke was cut
with milk powder.
Makes it nutritious.
Not much of a toxin.
- It is if he's allergic to milk.
- He's not. He has milk in his fridge.
- How does he like his coffee?
- I don't know. What does...
What type of cereal's
in the cabinet?
Cocoa-something.
Why, what does it matter?
He likes his coffee black.
Milk's for the kid.
- How can you be sure?
- Because if he drank the milk,
he'd know
that he's lactose intolerant.
Ask him, then treat him
for allergic reaction.
If he gets better,
we all get
to go home early.
Steroids make you
more prone to infection.
You'll have to stay here for the next
two weeks so we can monitor you.
The baby's lungs, is that
because of... the meth?
Could be.
You must hate me.
If you'd done everything
right in your life,
I wouldn't be getting a baby.
You're not scared?
I am scared.
You got, like, this perfect life.
Not yet.
- What's that?
- Heart rate's climbing.
What's wrong with her?
It's not the baby.
It's you.
I need two units
of o-negative, stat!
The mother had a stage two
placental abruption.
She's losing blood.
So deliver the baby.
The lungs are
ten weeks premature.
So deliver now, risk the baby.
Deliver later, risk the mom.
It's not your baby yet.
It's not your call.
She'll do whatever
I tell her to do.
Self-worth issues.
That's genetic, you know.
You should deliver now.
Right.
Are you serious?
You're not?
- You just told me...
- The wrong answer.
You can give the mom more blood.
You can't give the fetus more lungs.
The lungs might work.
It's the right decision medically.
And yet you're here.
To get your opinion,
not to get jerked around.
See, this is what's
screwed up here.
You're not sure that this
is the right call,
you're sure that this
is what you want to tell her.
And that scares you because
your motives aren't medical.
Some part of you
doesn't want this baby,
and that part
wants to tell her to kill it.
This is an impossible situation.
I'm advising her to take
the safest route.
Right.
Doesn't explain why
you changed your sweater.
I need your advice.
It's not cancer.
Can you remove spleens
with your mind too?
You're here to talk about Cuddy.
The file is a pretext.
Why the hell haven't you come
to talk to me about Cuddy?
I've been doing all sorts
of insane stuff.
If she can't handle your insanity,
she can't handle a baby.
- That's exactly my point.
- No, it isn't.
You're feeling threatened
because she's going on to high school
and leaving you behind
to repeat the eighth grade.
She's sleeping with the math teacher
to get a diploma.
Adoption is cheating?
Are they giving her a fake kid?
That's the problem.
She gets to have a relationship
with a kid,
but she can't handle one
with an adult.
So she's gonna kill it.
Well, it does seem cleaner.
I've seen the file.
She's making a judgment call.
Decisions are never made
in a vacuum.
Just like your decision
to make her miserable.
You're doing this
because we no longer
have inkwells and Cuddy
doesn't have pigtails.
Why do you think
I did that?
How you doing?
Not sure.
Been keeping an eye
on the clock like you said.
- I don't think I lost any time.
- The machinery agrees with you.
That means your problems
were caused by the coke.
- Can't believe I did coke.
- You were asleep.
I chose to do coke.
In your sleep.
You weren't responsible.
Something inside me wanted to do it.
Something inside of me
didn't think it was wrong.
It's like a dream.
We all do stuff in our dreams
we wouldn't do when we're awake.
I don't.
What's that?
Did I fall asleep
and hurt myself?
- I don't see any cuts.
- Because there aren't any.
I think...
You're sweating blood.
Guy's bleeding out of his pores.
What does that tell us?
Other than you don't want
to play basketball against him
and he's dying?
And neither cocaine
or allergies are the answer.
It's gotta be systemic,
hemmoragic varus.
You think it's ebola?
His white blood cell count would be
through the roof. It's not an infection.
- D.I.C.?
- Coags are normal.
It's cancer.
Leukemia explains everything.
- No fever.
- Bleeding.
- No weight loss.
- Rash.
- No headache.
- Fatigue.
Leukemia'd be obvious from the CBC.
Leukemia has false negatives
all the time.
So we have four reasons
for leukemia,
- four reasons against.
- Only need one against.
Yeah, if we had one reason
for anything else.
Go do a bone marrow biopsy.
What would you do?
I think...
I think you should wait.
But if I wait...
I could die.
There would be
more danger for you, but...
Is this your opinion
as a doctor or as a mother?
It's my medical opinion.
- It's my personal opinion...
- I don't want to wait.
It might only be one week.
We will keep you on plasma.
This is not my baby.
I have already sacrificed
nine months
for this stupid mistake.
I don't... I don't want
to sacrifice any more.
Becca, you asked my opinion
because you wanted to do
the right thing.
You are giving up this baby
because you don't want
to make the mistakes
your mom made,
her mom made.
You have a chance
to break this cycle,
to do something great
for this baby.
No.
I need you to hold still.
Wait.
Have you been testing
any tanning creams or sprays?
No.
It's not a tan.
Means it's not leukemia.
Chem panel confirms
kidney failure, end stage.
Got him on dialysis?
- BP's too low.
- Too bad.
It would've been nice to have more
than an hour or two to solve this thing.
Hemachromatosis?
- He have tiny testes?
- No. Scleroderma.
His skin's darker, not lighter.
As much fun as 20 questions
tends to be,
he's blowing blood
out of every orifice,
- you think it just might be vascular?
- Vasculitis?
If I had said it might be
"vitas gerular,"
would you have said
"vitas gerulaitis?"
Test him for vasculitis,
angio and blood.
Even if we're right, he's gonna need
a kidney transplant.
- Test the daughter.
- She's 12.
Small kidney. It just means he
won't pee as much.
Great for road trips.
I meant she's a minor
and daddy has a conflict,
so we're gonna need Cuddy's signoff.
- So get it.
- She's... kind of busy.
Clamp.
Suction.
Entering the abdominal cavity.
There's the head.
Got a minute?
Get out of here.
- Who's that?
- Dr. Gregory House.
He's the one you'll be suing
when you develop sepsis.
- Why is he here?
- Better question is why is she here?
You're an administrator.
Administrate.
I have a patient's daughter
needs a guardian ad litem.
Tests are inconclusive. But either way
he's gonna...
- House, get out!
- This doesn't need you. I do.
Head's out.
- Later.
- Later's too late.
And there she is.
Come on, cry.
Come on.
Joy, cry.
Cry, joy.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
That's the sound we like to hear.
Apgar's nine out of ten.
You hear that?
You just got your first "a."
She's... yours now.
Mazel tov.
Now it's time
to say those magic words
you'll be telling her
for the rest of her life.
Mommy's gotta go to work.
Have the risks of the transplant
been explained to you?
Damn it. I was hoping you
weren't going to ask her that.
Of course she knows.
Can you just sign the paperwork?
Dr. House explained to you
that all surgeries carry risk?
- You could die.
- And if you don't do it, dad will die.
Stop pressuring her.
Sorry.
Daddy's perfectly healthy.
But we want you to give him a kidney
because it'd be cool if he had three.
Shut up.
Do you understand the risks
of living with one kidney?
And you still want to proceed
with the transplant?
Okay, go ahead.
I'm saying you can proceed.
I'm saying I can't.
Whatever he has, she has too.
She's sleepwalking.
If we don't give him a new kidney,
he's dead in a week.
We have to transplant.
When your remote has a dead battery,
you don't replace it
with another dead battery.
Whatever's killing the dad's kidneys
is gonna kill the kid's too.
It is possible the sleep issues
aren't medically related.
Maybe they're both insomniacs
due to the turnpike noise.
Maybe they both drink
too much coffee, maybe...
- House is right.
- How do you know?
Because she's sweating blood.
If they have the same thing,
there has to be a common cause.
Which means it has to be
a toxin, infection, or genetic.
And since we've ruled out
infections and toxins...
It narrows it down to any one
of a dozen genic disorders,
each of which takes more
than a week to run.
Call foreman.
Get to work.
Cuddy is positively aglow.
What's your theory? She's only acting
happy to make you miserable?
I need a genetic disease.
I'm sure you're carrying a few.
Symptoms are kidney failure,
bleeding, and insomnia.
You paid off the pool?
Technically, anyone
who didn't enter is a winner.
It's not over yet.
Everyone's happy until they
unwrap that pretty present
and find they got a wall clock
in the shape of africa.
Adoption's a cheat, remember?
There's no real pregnancy, so there's
no stranded dopamine receptors,
so there's no postpartum depression.
Cuddy will be the happiest
new mother you've ever seen.
I've just given you
the answer, haven't I?
And now you're going to walk out
of here without saying a word.
Nope!
Good news.
I know what you have,
and you're both gonna be fine.
What? Are you serious?
Yes and no.
- So you do know what they have?
- Yeah.
- But they aren't gonna be fine?
- no idea.
They might be.
Why the hell would you
say they were?
To make them happy.
For two seconds?
Technically, to see
if they can be happy.
We should've seen a grin, a twinkle,
a sigh of relief, something.
They're sick. They're tired.
They're anhedonic,
incapable of experiencing pleasure.
Something's bushwhacked
their dopamine receptors.
They're depressed.
Mom's dead. Dad's dying.
You should know that being bummed
isn't necessarily a pathology.
Being bummed doesn't explain
their lack of friends
or their indifference to each other.
Why their place had no music,
no view, no decor.
But if you can't feel pleasure,
what's with the cocaine?
Really? Is that why you do drugs?
Because you're happy?
Most people do 'em
because they want to be happy.
His subconscious craved it,
needed it.
Most common cause
of anhedonia is schizophrenia.
- Sure, in white folk.
- They're black?
They're liars.
What's your name?
Jerry harmon.
Your real name.
Hosarian?
Herzog?
H'ali-baba?
Hammoud.
Jamal hammoud.
Changed it when we
invaded Iraq the first time.
How'd you know?
You and your daughter
have familial mediterranean fever.
It's a genetic disease
contracted by people
of Mediterranean descent.
Sephardic Jews, Armenians, Arabs.
Causes anhedonia,
seizures, kidney failure,
even lactose intolerance.
Symptoms are set off
by age and stress.
Kid couldn't get happy, but she
could get stressed by daddy dying.
- You don't know if we'll get better?
- Treatment tends to be hit and miss
once you reach
the sweating blood stage.
Start them on colchicine
and melphalan.
His kidneys are fried.
If he doesn't have fmf,
the colchicine will kill him.
Boy, sure hope I'm right.
Mr. Harmon?
Mr. Harmon, I need you
to open your eyes.
Feeling better?
How's samantha?
Healthy enough to toss you a kidney.
- Dad?
- Sammy.
Labor & delivery
the baby's doing great.
I...
I can't imagine how hard
this must be for you.
I was... I was stupid and selfish.
- You were scared.
- Yeah, but you wouldn't have been.
- That's not true.
- I mean, you would've been scared,
but you would've done
the right thing anyway.
And I want to be like that.
I don't...
I don't want to be a loser.
You're not a loser.
When I saw you hold her
and the look on your face,
it was the most beautiful thing
I've ever seen.
And that's
when I realized...
I can't.
Becca.
My life, it's always been about pain,
and anger, and disappointment,
never about love.
And that's when I realized,
you know, it could be.
And I can't give that away.
Becca, don't do this.
What you're feeling is natural.
But you're filled with hormones,
and emotion, and fear,
and...
You just can't make a huge
decision like this right now.
You have to give it some time.
I am...
I'm so sorry.
It's a decision
that changes everything.
Changes the rest of your life.
I hope so.
It's really not
the greatest time for gloating.
There's more
than one baby in the sea.
The world is full of teenage boys
riding bareback.
I'm done.
I can't go through that again.
You're quitting.
- Just like you quit IVF.
- Yeah, just like that.
There, you just did it again.
It's too bad.
You would've made a great mother.
You son of a bitch.
When I was getting a baby,
you told me I'd suck as a mother.
Now that I've lost it, you tell me
I'd be great as a mother.
Why do you need
to negate everything?
I don't know.
Good night.
Merci  EntaraXia
www.house-fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net