Excuse me.
I've been waiting here
for over an hour.
All I need is a refill
on my migraine medication.
- We'll get to you as soon as we can.
- You can get to me now.
It'll only take you two minutes.
- You're not an emergency.
- This isn't an emergency room.
And it's not gonna go any faster
by pissing me off.
- Got a minute?
- No.
Routine checkup can wait.
What else you got?
I'm consulting on some clinical trials
that involve C.N.S. Compounds.
While it's true
that no sometimes means yes,
- in this context...
- One's a new Huntington's drug.
Phase three trials
are showing real results
delaying neuronal degeneration.
I can probably get you in.
No, thanks.
Are you doing anything about it,
following any kind of program?
No. Now am I looking for a consult.
Excuse me, I'm looking
for Dr. Cuddy.
Well, she's either not here,
or she's under the desk.
You're gonna have
to wait outside until I'm finished.
- Do you know when she'll be back?
- Yes, which is why
I need you to get out
and leave me alone.
Sorry.
Nice try. Love to help.
Shut up!
- You wanted to see doctor...
- I said shut up.
I'm sick, and I want to know why.
I want the best doctor
in this hospital here, now...
Or I'm gonna start killing people.
What seems to be the problem?
House - Season 5 Episode 09
"Last Resort"
TS: ragbear.com
Synchro: ShalimarFox, mpm
www.house-fr.com
Close those blinds.
You, push the sofa
in front of that door.
You, move that table
in front of the other door.
Now!
Just move it.
You don't have to point the gun man.
We're gonna do whatever you want.
No, we're not.
That's a bathroom you're barricading.
It might come in handy,
especially since
you've cleverly decided
to take a bunch
of sick people hostage.
Do it!
My medical records.
I need you to read them.
You really think that
reenacting dog day afternoon
is the best way to get diagnosed?
I'm sure you've been waiting for hours
in an uncomfortable chair, but...
you should watch the movie
all the way through.
I've been to 16 doctors
in the last two years.
Had three full-body CTS
and two MRIS,
seven blood panels,
and one homeopathic consult.
And all that was missing
was the threat of violence.
What's missing is an answer!
I can't breathe!
I'm tired... All the time.
I get skin rashes,
and heart palpitations,
and insomnia.
That's a cool constellation
of symptoms.
It could be something minor.
At least compared to life in prison,
which is what you seem to prefer
to seeing 16 more specialists.
Shut up and do your job.
You barely looked at the file.
No need. Symptoms...
Those are the things
you keep whining about.
Tests-negative,
or you wouldn't be here.
History-shy, quiet kid.
Kept to himself.
Collected comic books
and missing children.
Excuse me, my wife feels sick
to her stomach.
Next time pack some heat,
maybe we'll look into it.
I'll be okay.
If you ask me,
keeping an open line of communication
is the best way to resolve conflict.
What kind of breathing problems?
Shortness of breath.
And...
sharp pain when I inhale.
So you figured your wife left you
because you couldn't breathe, right?
Me, I rarely kidnap someone
unless I've got
a serious health problem.
Since you're not almost dead,
it means you're armed
`cause you're blaming something
other than your health on your health.
I've never been married.
- Got a match?
- Why?
Because I'd rather not stand here
while you try
and negotiate a hostage trade
for an incentive spirometer.
- I'll look in Cuddy's desk.
- Stay out of the desk!
She doesn't smoke.
He does.
- No, I don't.
- Right.
You brush your teeth
with coffee grounds.
Look, sir, I've never smoked
in my life, OK?
Jerk.
You figure that two people
snuck weapons into the clinic today?
I'm sorry. It's just...
I got a lighter.
Slowly.
Hold it out as far as you can.
Try to blow it out.
Decreased lung volume.
Heart palpitations,
fatigue, stomach pain.
An intermittent rash-
Could be 100 things.
If you add on that final symptom,
it can only be
pulmonary scleroderma.
What final symptom?
Those were all my symptoms.
Last one is the 16 doctors
who missed it.
Simple alkylating agent,
case solved.
See you on visitor's day.
- Crime scene!
- What's going on in there?
- Is everyone all right?
- About to be.
Assuming he's not lying.
But he seems like a pretty
straight arrow to me.
I'm gonna need some propofol
to prove that
it's pulmonary scleroderma.
- Then we all get to go home.
- Propofol?
- Have one of the guards bring it in.
- No, no guards. No cops.
- I'll go get it.
- No one's leaving.
She's not a cop?
Dr. Cuddy brings in the drugs.
Alone.
She might be armed.
I'd have her deliver it shirtless.
Who is it?
Oh, god, House.
- Maybe we should wait for...
- Guys with even bigger guns?
- Who know how to talk to armed...
- Say good-bye or I shoot her.
Roll up your sleeve.
Give it to someone else first.
You're the only one who needs it.
Give it to someone else.
If it goes in okay, you can give
a second dose to me.
I don't care who. Just pick someone.
Again, had your brilliant plan
included a roomful of hostages
that don't have fetuses,
bacterial and fungal infections,
leaving their immune systems too week
to deal with the metabolic strain,
or are already on pain killers
that have fatal interactions...
He's not on pain killers.
I heard him tell her in the clinic.
Come on, man.
Don't take it out on us.
You got a problem with doctors?
Take it out on the doctors.
Give it to her.
She's sick.
You are a very large creep.
Take off your shirt.
Satisfied?
Fine.
Roll up your sleeve.
You think I'm an idiot?!
That's what you think?!
I thought I had a little more time
with a guy that size.
You're not gonna do anything.
You still need me.
Come on!
What are you doing?
He didn't do anything.
You're right. I need you.
I also need you to know
you can't screw with me.
It's for you.
Lieutenant Bowman, Princeton SWAT.
Dr. Lisa Cuddy, dean of medicine.
We just heard a gunshot,
but I haven't been able to make contact.
We'll handle that once
we secure our perimeter
and set up our positions.
By "perimeters,"
I assume you mean snipers?
- We have to put an end to this.
- Got a husband in there or a loved one?
- No.
- Don't worry,
we'll decide when to start shooting.
House is gonna get someone killed.
Guy's ready to kill for a diagnosis,
I can't think of a better doctor
- to be trapped in there with him.
- How'bout someone who's not gonna
keep pushing the whack job's buttons
until he cracks?
It's House.
- Joe's bar and grill.
- It's foreman,
and every fellow you've had
in the last five years.
What causes low lung volume,
heart palpitations, fatigue,
stomach pain,
insomnia, and a rash?
This is pathetic.
If I strap a bomb to my chest,
do I get seven doctors
attending to me?
Dr. Robert chase.
On the off chance you have
some brilliant escape plan
and are the vengeful type.
You think he's the only guy
in New Jersey with an unsolved illness
and a pistol?
- I'm not playing this game.
- Seriously?
You're walking out?
No, he's just kidding.
He's right here.
Throw me that marker, will you?
Chest pain, the lung problems,
fatigue, rash.
Sounds like chronic lung infection.
Heart palpitations and fatigue
could be a cancer
that's spread from the lungs.
- Next!
- If his diaphragm's not working,
- his nerves are freezing up.
- I think he's going into shock.
First rule of triage,
guys with guns go first.
Next!
The shortest distance between
stomach pain and insomnia
is bad circulation.
Plus troubled breathing.
Could be a heart defect.
You needed to write
four things down to remember 'em?
It's not my wall.
You're gonna get
some special deliveries.
We're gonna draw blood.
Run tests for infection and cancer.
Cameron, comb through
his medical records.
See if any of his past
900 medications
could have screwed up his heart.
Taub, Kutner, go to
his apartment,
check for neurotoxins.
873 Marshall, South Brunswick.
Back window's unlocked.
Giving out your address.
Clearly you're not going back there.
Means you do have an end game.
Lieutenant Bowman.
How's everyone doing in there?
Got one lower limb flesh wound,
another guy unconscious.
Unfortunately, not the guy we hoped.
We're gonna need someone
to deliver his blood.
- It's gonna be hard to play doctor...
- Shut up.
Open that blind.
Just a few inches.
- Why me?
- Just open it. Open it!
Why me? Anyone can do it.
Why pick me?
Get back! Get back!
I will kill her unless you back
the hell out of there now!
Interesting.
Anybody else hear those guys
outside?
Anybody?
He's got hyperacusis.
What does that mean?
It means we have a favorite.
It's nerve related.
Amped-up hearing could be linked
to nerve palsy.
Puff out your cheeks. Come on.
Big mug shot smile.
Left side facial weakness.
Seventh nerve palsy.
Plus intermittent rashes.
Plus migraines.
It's post-herpetic neuralgia.
Herpetic? You think I have herpes?
I'm not judging here.
This thing is just as likely
to be caused by chicken pox.
I need proof now.
There is a test.
It's dangerous and painful
while the treatment
is safe and painless.
But you make a good point.
You need proof now.
I'll order up the test.
If you have neuralgia,
you won't feel it going in.
It only hurts
if your diagnosis is wrong?
Win-win.
Jason,
don't hang up the phone again.
- You're gonna send in...
- Capsaicin.
- 200 micrograms.
- And two syringes this time.
And we'll give you the blood
and his records.
No more meds, Jason,
and no deliveries
without something in return.
You've gotta give us a hostage.
You can have two.
Great.
Then I'll send an officer
right in with the transfer.
Everything gets brought in
by Dr. Cuddy.
Jason, I'm not gonna let her
do that.
First-don't use his name so much.
It doesn't sound reassuring,
it just creepy.
Second-come on, he's not gonna shoot
the one person he trusts
to bring in his medication.
He's gonna shoot hostages
if she doesn't bring it in.
I'll get back to you.
The guy's demanding that
you do all the transfers.
Okay.
Okay?
- What am I supposed to say?
- You're supposed to say no.
It's not your job.
If you got a conflict here,
if you have stakes in this that
you're not telling me about,
then I can't trust you.
Got it.
I'm okay.
Can you tell him I'm coming in now?
Who's taking the first dose?
Anybody here got a long-standing
case of neuralgia
that's killed their nerves
so this won't hurt at all?
How bad does it hurt?
- You're looking to be the hero?
- Well, I've been beaten up a lot,
- and I can handle pain.
- How old are you?
The guy's got a gun.
I think that covers
the parental consent issue.
And that stuff can also cause
nerve and muscle damage.
I'm not taking that crap.
- Come on.
- You have to.
It's the rules.
I'll do it.
This is a level of risk taking
beyond anonymous girl-on-girl action.
They're patients. I'm a doctor.
With a degenerative,
drug-unfriendly illness.
Everything's not some
fascinating character flaw.
This is a genetic flaw.
This is your huntington's speaking.
This is you waving
a white flag at the world.
Yes, I have a shortened lifespan.
Another reason why I'm
objectively the right choice.
I would have laid money
you had herpes.
Your turn.
Why are we here?
We've ruled out
immediate risk of death,
lost love.
That just leaves...
Work?
You're defined by your work.
But you kept seeing doctors,
kept missing time.
Couldn't focus.
Maybe you made a huge mistake...
Got fired.
I just want an answer.
I know.
I'm asking why.
Guy knew he wasn't coming back.
Everything's laid out for us.
I'll check for toxins in the kitchen.
He must have $6,000, $7,000
in unpaid medical bills.
I've got debt,
you don't see me acting like a lunatic.
There's no excuse for what he's doing,
but you've got millions of people
thousands of dollars in debt
because they're sick...
At least one of them's
gonna do something inexcusable.
Especially if it works.
White blood cell count's normal.
It's not infection.
So either his heart's on the fritz,
or he's got cancer.
Found a picture of his mom. She's got
a droopy eye, fat face, thick neck.
- Classic signs of an upper-lobe tumor.
- Or she's just ugly.
There are also signs
of an adrenal problem.
It's his heart.
- You can't be sure what...
- His neck. Distended jugular.
- What are you doing?
- I am going to try to strangle you
- faster than you can pull a trigger.
- He needs to check your pulse.
It's racing. 160.
We need to get paddles.
Or maybe we could just do nothing.
If I get any weaker...
And they don't fix it...
I'll shoot...
- You!
- Don't.
- He didn't mean...
- Shut up!
All of you.
What are... What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- Carotid massage...
Gotta slow your heart.
It's 200.
Well, get the paddles.
Whole point of those things is
to make your muscles contract.
They don't discriminate
against trigger fingers.
Nobody gets my gun.
Send in paddles!
- Don't!
- Get the damn paddles!
Or I'll shoot you.
Threatening to shoot the guy
who's diagnosing you
makes a lot of sense.
Actually doing it, not so much.
- Give him your gun so he can save you.
- Just let him die.
Stop.
We can cardiovert chemically.
- If we ignore what heart rhythm...
- If we don't try, he'll kill someone.
- I get the drugs.
- Don't move!
If she doesn't come back,
There are plenty of other people
you can't shoot.
You, come here.
All right...
30 seconds.
She's gonna go.
She's gonna come back.
She should go.
He'll kill him.
But not her.
That your version of morality?
If you don't think your life is
worth more than someone else's,
sign your donor card
and kill yourself.
Shoot me.
- You really want-
- Yes.
She just needs time!
She needs more time to find the right...
the right drug...
She needs time, time...
It's me.
She takes it first.
Adenosine slows the heart.
Which is fine,
if it's beating fast like yours.
Not fine if it's normal, like hers.
- Following the math on this?
- She takes everything I take.
I don't want anything
that cross-reacts.
The martyr's heart is beating
dangerously slow.
Are we good to go?
Your heart's back to normal.
No tachycardia.
No sign of a heart defect at all.
But you're sweating.
I nearly had a heart attack.
You're surprised I'm sweating?
On one side of your face,
but not the other.
What does that mean?
A tumor is pressing
on your sympathetic nerves.
You have lung cancer.
Pulse is down below 50.
So's her I.Q.
Help her up.
Get her heart going faster.
I need proof it's cancer.
Of course you do!
It's gotta be a pancoast tumor.
Patient's got dyspnea,
seventh-nerve palsy.
He's sweating on one side
of his face.
- Everything okay in there?
- Take your time.
It's not like I've got a gun
to my head.
Lung cancer usually shows up
lower than the seventh nerve.
- Did you check his throat?
- Spit on the floor.
What?
If I do it, I can't tell Cuddy
that it was medically necessary.
I'm gonna ask you to piss
on her chair next.
Dry mouth.
His parotid glands aren't working.
It there's swelling, it's
a pancoast tumor that's metastasized.
Feel that.
Right there.
If it's cancer,
there must be a test.
- You just did it.
- What about an x-ray or something?
Good idea.
Oh, damn.
I left my CT machine
in my other pants.
How many hostages
do you think it would cost me
for a trip to radiology?
So...
What made you snap?
- Hmos?
- Shut up.
You saw 16 doctors.
- How bad could they have been?
- Shut up!
Humiliation?
Doctors treating you
like a piece of meat?
Too many fingers and tubes
up your holes.
You hate doctors.
You want to take back control.
If so, I apologize for the fact that
you are a piece of meat.
I just want an answer.
That's all.
Everyone stays in here with me.
If you need anything
from in there, get it now.
Move around.
Anyone moves...
I fire.
That's not all.
Curiosity's not enough.
There's gotta be a deeper reason.
You never did anything
just because you had to know?
Never shot anyone.
You're not me.
This is my body.
This is my life.
And there's a truth out there.
I'd rather rot
in jail knowing than...
I can't handle not knowing.
Hold that.
You want your answer,
you gotta give me the gun.
- What's this?
- Starburst artifact.
The metal from the gun
is ruining the image.
Show him.
Starburst.
Now, unless you think
we pre-arranged that,
just in case we were ever held hostage
by a guy who needs a CT,
we're not lying.
So you have two choices.
You can give me the gun
and get your answer.
Or you can shoot me.
I'm not gonna give you the gun.
- Why did he release you?
- House got him to give up his gun.
We just ran.
- Why are you still here?
- Curious.
It's safe now, right?
They're gonna be here at any moment.
Just show me the tumor.
There isn't one.
I don't know what you have.
So...
It's over.
Thanks for trying.
You had four theories.
You ruled out four theories.
Maybe no one can cure me.
He overpowered me
and got the gun back.
You're a coward.
You need to know everything
because you're afraid to be wrong.
You're so afraid of being ordinary,
of being just another doctor,
just another human being,
that you'll risk
other people's lives.
I'm arrogant.
You're the coward.
You're terrified of death.
You just want to cheat it
by making it come sooner.
Gives you the illusion of control.
Can I go?
Sorry.
We might need you.
How do they expect me to think?
- Is he lying?
- Why would he do that?
Over time, hostages
start to root for the captor.
- House isn't the rooting kind.
- No, he's the obsessive, defiant kind.
Mic the door.
Get a frame charge.
I hope your boyfriend knows
what he's doing.
- Are you insane?
- He's quick for a sick guy.
Dyspnea,
anemia, seventh-nerve palsy,
tachycardia.
Long passes.
Anything.
- Go.
- I don't believe it.
Chase was right.
You're gonna kill someone.
I don't want to be a part of it.
Loa loa filariasis.
You ever been to cameroon
or on the ogowe river?
- Next.
- Could be Q fever
- if he's had exposure to goats.
- No goats.
Histiocytosis X
explains the lung involvement and...
We have a new symptom.
He is turning his head,
favoring his left ear.
Means he's partially deaf
in the right.
Three hours ago,
he had superhero hearing.
Cushing's causes fatigue,
breathing problems, fluctuating hearing.
Even increased aggression
and risk-taking.
I'm doing this by choice.
It's not a symptom.
We'll keep that between us
till you talk to your lawyer.
I need dexamethasone
and enough time to provoke
a respiratory reaction
- and confirm Cushing's syndrome.
- You need more time?
House, we're not negotiating
with you.
- Actually, we're through negotiating.
- I've still got three hostages left.
I'll give you one.
And no more testing drugs
on a sick doctor.
Fine.
Send in the drugs.
Son, come here, come here.
House, you can't...
If you have Cushing's,
this will slow your breathing.
Give it to her first.
Those were not the terms.
I lied.
These drugs could be fake.
Why would I do that?
I gave you back the gun!
You wouldn't.
They would.
She has Huntington's.
If these drugs are real,
it could screw up her liver.
Chances are slim.
Chances of him shooting one of us,
- on the other hand...
- Don't do...
How long do you have to live?
Eight, ten years.
Killing her is your chance
to get personal?
Huntington's doesn't have...
Doesn't have a cure?
So if we get out of here...
If she were clinging to hope,
she wouldn't be standing in line
waiting for you
to order up more drugs.
Take a deep breath.
Not knowing what was wrong
with me...
Made me miserable.
Maybe that's insane.
Doing this...
Insane.
But I had something to gain.
You can't take risks
with no upside at all.
I can't decide which is riskier,
taking crazy risks
or taking advice on crazy risks
from a crazed risk-taker.
Heart's racing.
Fever.
And your breathing's unchanged.
- That means...
- Means I was wrong.
Her kidneys are shutting down
because of the meds you made her take.
We have to get her out of here.
The dexamethasone
is making 13's kidneys fail,
but not the patient's. Why?
He's been
on 50 different medications.
Maybe his kidneys should be failing,
but something's protecting them.
I need to slap you.
For diagnostic purposes.
Seriously.
If I was jerking you around,
I'd say I needed to kick you
in the groin.
That twitch is Chvostek's sign.
Don't ask me how Chvostek
discovered it.
He has calcium deficiency.
Drugs that block calcium
tend to shield
against kidney damage.
He's been on protein pump inhibitors
for years for his stomach pain.
Those drugs have been protecting
his kidneys for years.
He has something that has
a long incubation period.
Something that should have
wrecked his kidneys.
Something that explains
breathing problems,
heart problems, jumpy nerves,
and weak blood.
- Leishmaniasis.
- Would make perfect sense
if our patient was
an arabian bedouin.
Melioidosis.
Bacteria gets into the lungs,
spreads to the heart.
- It explains everything.
- Except that if you read the history,
you'd know that our patient
has never been to a tropical climate!
Is he absolutely sure of that?
Mexico. Costa rica.
- You've never been-
- I've never been south of Florida.
You idiot.
Florida counts?
Well, not to the supreme court.
But it's warm enough for germs.
You keep blaming doctors
when you can't even give
a halfway decent history.
Negotiation's over.
It will be as soon as you get us
three grams of ceftazidime.
He comes out, he gets
all the medicine he wants.
You can have Dr. House.
- Why are you getting rid of me?
- I need to trade you for the answer.
- You're gonna give her the meds.
- No...
Come on, give 'em to me instead.
She's taken everything I've taken.
The combination of meds
could knock me out.
Her kidneys are failing.
You give her those drugs,
she'll be dead by the time
they get the cuffs on you.
- I need my answer.
- Your obsession is gonna kill her!
Your obsession gave me back the gun!
It is pointless
to give her those drugs.
Even if they are screwing with you,
this is your last diagnosis.
Only if you're right.
House, get out of here.
Shut up.
I'm not leaving.
Who's the martyr now?
Either the drugs kill me
or he kills me.
Doesn't seem to make
a lot of difference.
You really don't feel bad
about killing me?
Not if you don't feel bad
about killing yourself.
- I don't want to die.
- Yeah, you do.
You just don't have the nerve
to actually do it.
You just want it out of your control.
Well, it is.
'cause I've got a gun.
- Don't do this.
- Either I do this with you alive, or...
Please.
Sometimes you just have
to trust people.
I don't want to die!
Why are you still alive?
He didn't make me take it.
A week of temporary dialysis,
your kidneys will be okay.
I'm sorry I backed out
of the differential.
About that Huntington's
drug trial...
Test confirmed melioidosis.
Easy to miss on a stain.
- Scans and x-rays vary widely.
- Is that all you care about?
A moron storms the clinic,
bullies his way
into life without parole,
you enabling him every step.
If he hadn't done what he did,
he'd be dead.
Good thing you enabled
my every medical move.
You think I handled this
differently because you were in here?
I don't know.
Let's try it again without me.
This is why you and I
can't be a... thing.
If you're suggesting
that you screwed up
because of a non-relationship
with me,
I don't know how I can help you.
'cause the only change you can make
from a non-relationship is...
You want a relationship?
God, no.
Just trying to follow your logic.
www.house-fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net