(marina)
mr. Randall?
They're here.
(pete)
$52 million includes
over $6 million
Already issued pursuant
to the over-allotment option.
When can we close?
It would be subject
to regulatory approval
In both toronto and--
I didn't say, "how," oliver.
I said, "when."
What?
You sure this
is a direction
You want to go,
roy?
This would move us
from energy service into--
You don't think oil's
going up?
Of course it's gonna
go up.
The question is when.
The question is always when,
and if we wait
Until the deal makes sense
to everyone else,
We're gonna be waiting
in line behind everyone else.
All I'm saying is--
The same cover-your-ass crap
you always say.
We're gonna have
to wrap this up.
I got to go.
Where are you going?
Upstairs.
Get the regulators on it.
I want to close by
the end of the month.
Come on, roy.
There are ten other items
on the agenda.
Which will have
to wait until next week.
You can't drag us all out
of the office,
Get halfway through,
and then just kick us out.
Yeah, I can.
(dr. Johnson)
the antibiotic treatment
had no effect.
Both the fever and the pain
are getting worse,
Which means it's not
clostridium difficile.
But you said that was the only
diagnosis that made sense.
It was.
We need to get him
to a hospital.
(jack)
dad?
I don't want to go.
I know, buddy.
But we may need to.
Am I gonna die?
No, of course not.
How do you know?
Well, I just do.
And I'm always right,
aren't I?
Yeah.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
House 6x04 Instant Karma
I want house.
I understand,
but I told you
Dr. House isn't available.
Dr.--
Call him.
Tell him I'll have
a private jet
Pick him up from
whatever island--
He isn't on vacation.
Dr. Foreman's one
of our best doctors.
Is house in jail?
No.
Foreman is currently working
with two of house's
Most veteran associates.
Rehab?
No.
Mr. Randall, your son will be
in good hands.
My son...Has already been
in good hands,
And he's still dying.
I'm through dealing
with good.
I want the best and everyone
I've asked says that's house.
So unless he's dead,
comatose,
Or insane, I want him
treating my son today.
You could have said no
in good conscience.
(cuddy)
the kid'll still
be foreman's patient,
But his dad wants you
making the decisions.
Then he's not
my patient.
You want to give me none
of the responsibility
And all of the liability?
Which means I get--
Oh, cool.
Don't let him
do anything crazy.
When is he getting
his license back
So we can stop
playing this game?
Maybe never.
This game is fun.
You also need to prepare
president dibala's case
For this week's morbidity
and mortality conference.
Ohh, unfortunately I'm overdue
a mani-pedi appointment.
Not you.
Foreman's department.
Oh, right.
Well, he's got all the time
in the world.
We made the wrong call.
He died.
There's nothing
to present.
It obviously garnered
a lot of curiosity.
And we don't have more
important things to do
Than satisfy everyone's
idle curiosity?
It's not idle.
The question of how we deal
with two possible diagnoses
Whose treatments
are contraindicated
Is worth discussing.
Abdominal pain increasing
in severity and frequency,
Fever, dehydration,
Diarrhea, weight loss.
Mom died from kidney
failure caused
By type one diabetes,
which has been ruled out.
(house)
17 doctors.
Everything's been
ruled out.
Which means we have
to re-rule out.
Get a new history
and physical.
Unless that's crazy,
boss.
(cameron)
you been out of the country
Or on any
recent camping trips?
No camping.
But we were in montreal
back in January.
We went to see the nhl all-star
game for my birthday.
Awesome.
Where's dr. House?
In his office.
He's really more of
a decider than a doer.
He's decided we should
start over.
Never know what previous doctors
may have missed.
Like this.
Does that hurt more
when I push there?
Not really.
What is it?
I'm not sure.
Just keep it clean,
simple.
We did a test that
called into question
Our initial diagnosis,
so we changed our mind.
And if they ask
how the test was done?
Why would they do that?
It's a routine lab test.
Routine lab tests don't involve
blood you stole
From a corpse
to trick me
Into giving the guy
the wrong treatment.
Yes, and if you brought
that up,
It'd certainly make for a
lively debate about the morality
Of murdering murderers.
But since you burned the only
evidence of that--
To cover for you,
not me.
You're protected.
The decision was a coin flip.
There was no right
or wrong answer.
The body's underground,
8,000 miles away.
Nobody can prove anything.
That room will be filled,
not because of the coin flip,
Not because of the patient,
But because house's
department screwed up.
They're gonna be like sharks
in a chum-filled swimming pool
And there's no way
I'm jumping in
Unless I'm
in a steel cage.
So what do you want?
I want to know you
have everything covered.
(house)
got what covered?
We're just reviewing
the dibala case.
Making sure we didn't
miss anything.
We didn't.
Except of course the thing
that killed him.
(cameron)
he's constipated.
Physical revealed a mass
in his abdomen,
So I repeated the x-ray.
Old one was clean.
New one shows that his colon's
almost completely impacted.
Obstruction would explain
the pain.
Think they just
screwed up the old x-ray?
Nope.
Hirschsprung's?
It's a congenital disorder
of the nerves in the colon.
Very rare in a child
your son's age.
Most doctors would never
think of it.
And you came up with this?
It's house's idea.
We need a barium enema
and biopsy to confirm.
Let me guess.
It tastes really bad,
But it's gonna make me feel
a lot better.
Actually, you're not
gonna taste it.
[fanfarlo's fire escape]
You should try searching for
"misty may digs for gold."
Make sure you put it
in quotes.
I'm making travel plans.
Just need to get away.
Have some time to myself.
You getting the hint?
So that's it?
You're done with your little
experiment with foreman?
It wasn't an experiment.
It was a relationship.
You may want to look
into the difference.
I'm glad you're better,
house.
I actually liked
working for you.
But I'm not coming back.
Good.
'cause if you came back,
Foreman would try
and save the relationship
And he'd give up
being the boss.
Are you here to try to save
my relationship with foreman?
God no.
Trying to save my
relationship with foreman.
Right now I'm kobe
playing the game I love
However the hell I want.
Phil jackson has to listen
to everyone else bitch about it.
Enjoy cabo.
I'm going to thailand.
Really?
Interesting.
Good-bye, house.
Good-bye, thirteen.
(cameron)
last week, yesterday, today.
I can't believe it.
He's pain-free for
the first time in months.
He's even hungry.
I'm starving.
Still waiting
for the biopsy results,
But obviously it's
a good sign.
You're gonna want
to take it slow.
Don't try to regain all
the lost weight in one meal.
[chuckles]
What's wrong?
Abdomen feels normal,
but it looks bigger.
Jack, are you feeling--
jack?
Hey, jack, you okay?
Right eye's fixed.
Lateral rectus palsy.
[electronic beeping]
He's seizing.
Need five milligrams
of diazepam.
What's happening?
Put that on his head and
turn off the lights.
I need to see
his optic disk.
Heart rate's elevated.
Come on, come on, hold his head.
I'm trying.
Wait! Where's house?
Mr. Randall,
we need you to step back.
(foreman)
his optic disk is swollen.
He's got intracranial
hypertension.
Furosemide.
20 milligrams iv.
We could intubate him--
Need five more milligrams
of diazepam.
Dc the monitors.
Push 500 milligrams phenytoin.
We can't push that much.
We got to remove the pressure
or his brain could herniate.
Oh, my god.
50 milligrams
of phenytoin.
Page chase.
Tell him to meet us in the o.R.
We need your consent.
What's happening to him?
Pressure in his skull's
too high.
If we don't reduce it,
It could irrevocably
damage his brain.
But he was just talking.
He was smiling.
We need to drill
burr holes.
Drill into his head?
Phenytoin's not working.
Paralyze him.
Three milligrams pancuronium.
Then intubate
and hyperventilate.
Where's house?
House isn't here.
Do we have your consent?
Ready?
One, two, three.
Three milligrams pancuronium.
Look at the monitors.
He's still seizing.
We need to do this now.
Go.
Electrical seizure
activity's stopped.
Intracranial pressure's
declining.
Come on.
Keep going.
Pressure's down to eight.
I'll tell the dad.
What happened?
I have no idea.
He hasn't had
any more seizures,
And cytological examination
of the subdural fluid
Showed no abnormalities.
Don't usually see brain damage
after a rectal biopsy.
He was fine after
the procedure.
No headaches.
No mental status change.
Wasn't anything we did.
It's not just his brain.
He's continuing to build up
fluid in his abdominal cavity
As well as the dura.
We've inserted shunts
to drain it.
Got to be some sort
of systemic infection.
Not after spending the last week
getting pumped
Full of iv antibiotics.
Notice anything odd about the
shape of the fluid collection?
Oh, god, it's...
The virgin mary.
The edge should be tapered,
Lens shaped.
Unless...
The dural layer was already
separated from the brain
When the fluid started
to build up.
Get a dural biopsy
to confirm brain cancer.
Nice catch.
Bangkok.
Flight 799.
Wow.
Bangkok.
That sounds awesome.
How long?
Not sure yet.
Luckily I have
a friend
Who's staying at my place
taking care of my dog.
He's really big,
so he needs a lot of exercise.
Remy hadley.
H-a-d-l-e-y.
What, you think I'm gonna
rob the place?
No, of course not.
In case you haven't noticed,
I have a job.
Look, I'm sorry.
I don't know you.
You're either honest
or dishonest.
I figured
the safer choice is--
Is to treat a stranger
like an ass.
Nice way to live your life...
Bitch.
I said I'm sorry.
Oh, hello.
I was wondering if there were
any business class seats
Open that I could use
my miles to upgrade to.
I don't know you,
but I assumed I could trust you.
Welcomed you in my car.
Okay, you're a saint.
That's impossible.
I confirmed my reservation
last night.
So rebook it.
Well, obviously it was a mistake
on your end, not mine.
No, I'm on my way
to the airport
Right now.
They didn't
believe you, huh?
Brain cancer?
We should know for sure
by the morning.
[sighs]
Our luck just keeps getting
worse, huh?
Treatment options are getting
better every day.
There's no visible mass,
so even if the biopsy
Comes back positive,
we've caught it early.
Oh, so you're telling me
this is good news?
I'm saying we will do
whatever we can.
Right.
[cell phone rings]
Sorry.
I got to go.
Foreman needs more help
with the m and m prep.
Okay, I'll come up and help
After I finish
the biopsy.
We can handle it.
I'll see you
at home later.
If you're here,
I might as well be.
Go home.
Get some rest.
'cause I'm gonna be waking you
up as soon as I get home.
Stay out of my life.
Okay.
I know you canceled
my reservation.
You obviously
saw me log in
When you were spying on me
in the coffee shop.
I was talking to you.
I was spying on the milf
in the running shorts.
I'm not coming back
on the team.
I don't want you back
I cannot work for, with,
or around foreman.
Which is why I don't want you
back on the team.
Now that you're out
of the picture,
He's better than ever,
which is gonna make me
Less miserable than ever,
which is why neither of us
Gives a damn how, when,
or on what island
In the bahamas you want
to get from it all.
The bahamas?
[sighs]
costa rica?
I told you thailand.
I assumed you were lying,
Because it would have been
idiotic of you to tell me truth.
Yet another reason
I have no use for you.
(foreman)
we've got a problem.
When cameron sent
dibala's blood to the lab,
She specifically asked for the
anticentromere antibodies test.
So?
The printout
they sent you included
Just the anticentromere
antibodies,
But the lab also did
a full blood panel.
So, I'm not an idiot.
I obviously made sure the
cadaver I got the sample from
Had the same blood type.
You apparently didn't check
his cholesterol.
How far off?
20%.
(chase)
dibala didn't die
of high cholesterol.
Why would anyone even bother
to compare the two reports?
The same reason I did.
Because they're looking
for anything
We might have screwed up.
We could claim
the blood analyzer broke.
We can't.
Cameron documented that
it was perfectly calibrated
When she did the test.
So the numbers are off,
it's weird.
Who cares?
If it comes up,
just act surprised
Like it's some
irrelevant curiosity.
I can't do this.
I can't go in there
and stack lie upon lie.
You've got to figure out
a way to explain this.
Hey.
Missed you this morning.
Yeah, sorry.
I needed to get in early.
I didn't want to wake you.
I thought you did want
to wake me.
At least that's
what you said last night.
I'm out of here.
No, no.
I have the biopsy results.
It's not cancer.
How can so much be wrong
with nothing being wrong?
Since when has cancer been
considered nothing?
I just said
it's not cancer.
The cell morphologies
were all normal.
And so are the most recent
ct scans.
On the other hand,
andenocarcinoma of the stomach
Would cause pain,
constipation,
Nutritional deficiencies.
That could cause seizures.
And wouldn't show on a ct.
You're right about the cancer,
Just wrong about the place.
Continue to say nothing
if you agree.
Go scope him.
Get another set of biopsies.
I'd get canceling
her ticket
If you then showed up
With two more
to somewhere better.
What are you
talking about?
Or showed up at all.
But how does just
ruining her plans
Get her to agree
to yours?
You talking about thirteen?
Where's she going?
Well, nowhere this week,
thanks to you.
I didn't stop her.
I'm not gonna stop her.
I've already done
all I could.
Now all I can do
is move on.
I think...
I actually believe you.
If you're telling
the truth,
You're even more
rational than I--
Well, not more.
Then again,
more sane.
You're gonna
be a good boss, boss.
(chase)
I told you there's
nothing wrong.
There's obviously
something wrong
And I'm not even saying we need
to talk about it right now.
I just don't see
why you have to deny it.
I'm not.
Now you're denying
you're denying.
No, I'm denying that there's
anything to deny.
Robert, you can't do this.
You can't hide things
from me.
There's a problem with
the dibala m and m.
The hdl numbers on one
of his early blood panels
Don't match
a later panel.
That's weird.
Yeah.
It's no big deal.
Cholesterol didn't have
anything to do with his death,
But, you know,
after being let go from mercy
And then that thing
with thirteen's drug trial,
Foreman's paranoid about about
people questioning the way
He handled the case.
That's ridiculous.
If anything, foreman should be
feeling secure.
He's the one who had
the right diagnosis.
We're the ones who
talked him out of it.
I know.
Don't tell him
I told you.
He doesn't want to show
any signs of weakness,
Especially now that house
is claiming
He wants him
to stay in charge.
All right.
So it's still cancer?
It's just somewhere else?
That's what we're
looking for,
But it would explain
all the symptoms
And all the normal test
and imaging studies.
(chase)
got biopsies of the mucosa
and the submucosa.
Moving towards
the pylorus.
It's my fault.
Adenocarcinomas
aren't caused by diet
Or environmental
factors.
I inherited a $10 million
pipeline business
When I was 24.
By the time I was 30,
it was worth over a billion.
Since then,
I have been involved
In over 50 deals
that make that first one
Look like a loser.
Everything I do,
everything I touch
Turns to gold...
Except my family.
First, my wife.
And now...My son.
This is my fault.
It's karma.
That's obviously not true.
[electronic beeping]
He's seizing again.
Get the scope out.
Five milligrams diazepam.
How's the icp?
It's...Eight.
But the shunt's
open and clear.
This isn't
intracranial pressure.
Then what the hell is it?
(chase)
seizures stopped, but he hasn't
regained consciousness.
No sign of any masses
In his stomach
or esophageal lining
And he's still accumulating
subdural and peritoneal fluid.
And every time we look to see
where it's coming from,
He starts seizing.
You think we're
setting this off?
I think something is.
One of his stomach biopsies
shows an arteriole
Partially occluded.
(cameron)
but with no abnormality
in the other layers
And no evidence of a cellular
inflammatory reaction.
It's definitely not cancer.
Then it has to be some sort
of infection.
We already ruled out
infection.
Only because he was treated
for it and got worse.
Seems like a sound reason.
Unless it's
a drug-resistant strain.
Drug-resistant strain of what?
Bacterial cultures,
Viral serologies,
a.N.A. And a.N.C.A.
Were all negative.
Everything's negative.
We obviously missed something.
Maybe the seizures aren't
a new symptom.
They're an old one.
No doctor noticed
a thrashing kid?
Abdominal epilepsy.
The seizures would just
look like pain
Until it spread
to his motor cortex.
It wouldn't explain
the fevers.
Protein malnutrition
can cause fevers
And nothing causes
malnutrition
Like excruciating
stomach pain that gets worse
Every time you eat.
I'd be a lot more certain
if it was my idea,
But it's the best we got.
Start him on gabapentin.
Hook him up to
an intracranial eeg
For continuous monitoring.
I gave him statins.
What?
If they ask about
the cholesterol,
Just say I prescribed
a statin
And forgot to put it
in the chart.
You want to solve a problem
in the records
By creating another problem
in the records?
It's not a problem
with the records.
It's a problem
with my record keeping.
There's no way anyone
can prove me wrong.
How'd you get access
to the statins?
You gonna get someone
in the pharmacy
To confess to yet another
record-keeping problem?
I saw an open cart.
Just took it.
Why would you
steal a drug
You could just
as easily ask for?
'cause I'm trying
to get you off the hook.
A story that raises more
questions than it answers
Only puts the hook deeper
down my throat.
It's all right.
I'll handle it.
How?
By telling the truth.
The truth is I don't
have the time,
I'm not in the mood,
and I don't see the point.
You don't want
to do the m and m
Because you're not
in the mood?
This kid is dying
and I've got house
Trying to push all his
responsibilities onto me.
They're not
his responsibilities.
They're yours.
You're the one who wanted
to be in charge.
I wanted
to be in charge,
Not a figurehead.
Then do the m and m.
It's all yours.
You want me to get flogged?
For what?
So you can have
an academic debate
About a diagnostic dilemma
no one's ever gonna face again?
What the hell's
going on here?
I just don't want
to do the m and m.
Did it work?
Not even close.
Everything okay?
Just waiting for whatever
is about to go wrong.
Thirteen called.
She have a theory
that makes more sense
Than abdominal epilepsy?
She said someone hacked
into her email account
And canceled
an airline reservation.
I'm guessing foreman.
Really?
You're accusing foreman,
not me?
Cool.
You really want foreman to stay
in charge of the team?
Makes sense.
He loves power,
and I love puzzles.
You love power and puzzles.
True.
When I had them both.
It wasn't foreman.
How do you know?
He said he's moved on.
And you believe him?
I believe
that he believes it.
[pager beeps]
Looks like it's time for me
to get off the bench.
What's up?
Are you dr. House?
I understand you're
a big fan.
I'll have my guy send over
a signed glossy.
Continuous eeg shows
no interictal spikes.
It's not abdominal epilepsy.
You paged me to tell me
what it's not?
I paged you
to show you this.
That I did not expect.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
Darn it.
I knew I should have
stayed outside.
Fantasy's always much better
than the reality.
You think this is a joke?
That's my son,
he's dying,
And not one of you seem
to have the slightest clue hwy.
I know.
That's why it's
so interesting.
Fever, stomach pain,
seizures,
Peritoneal and subdural
fluid collection
And now spots.
Could be an allergic reaction
to one of his meds.
That suddenly developed
eight hours
After he started the meds?
If it's not cancer infection,
it has to be autoimmune.
Systemic lupus complicated
By a cns vasculitis
would explain the rash, fever,
Ascites--
Cns vasculitis would cause
a stiff neck
Along with a headache.
And would've showed up
on the dural biopsy.
What about polyarteritis
nodosa?
It can occur in kids.
Except you can't have arteritis
without inflammation.
Okay, you come up
with something better.
Go on.
There was some inflammation
in the skin biopsy,
Plus he's got elevated
diastolic pressure.
It's barely elevated,
which you'd expect
Given the number of procedures
he's undergone.
Well, barely is more
than not barely.
Not my decision.
But if it was,
I'd say start him on prednisone
And get a testicular biopsy.
If he's gonna have
any real inflammation,
It'll be down there.
Cameron and I will do it.
Why?
It was chase's idea.
Kid's father
is not gonna be happy
About a fourth set
of biopsies,
And you've got
a better rapport.
What's really
going on here?
You need chase to help you
over-prep for the m and m?
Yes.
Then say so.
Don't be a child.
Is it on his penis?
Kid's rash?
Yeah, why?
Means it's most likely affecting
the small blood vessels.
That's why we didn't see any
inflammation on the biopsies.
It's not polyarteritis.
It's degos disease.
I'll do it.
Your son has degos disease.
Causes microblood vessels
In the brain, skin,
gi tract
To break down,
clot off.
It sometimes manifests
early on
With atrophic papules
on the penis.
In your son's case,
we don't know why,
But they came much later.
What's the treatment?
There isn't one.
It's incurable.
You're wrong.
You've already been wrong
a bunch of times.
We've rechecked
the biopsies.
It's definitely degos.
I'm sorry.
I wish there was something
we could do.
How long?
Not much longer.
What does that mean?
Day at the most.
All right, great.
We need to talk.
Unless it's life or death,
it's gonna have to wait.
It's about dibala.
Well, let me rephrase.
Unless it's a current life--
Foreman can't present
the case at the m and m.
I know you guys are busy,
but he's just
Gonna have to suck it up
and make the time.
It's not the time.
Then what is it?
The anticontromere
antibodies test.
The test that caused us
to change the treatment
From blastomycosis
to scleroderma...
It wasn't--
Wasn't what?
(diane)
dr. Cuddy?
They need you
in the pediatric icu.
Who's they?
I don't know.
But I think they're lawyers.
If you guys screwed something
up, just come clean.
It's not gonna be that bad.
(ken)
with all due respect,
You don't know what's
at stake here.
What's going on?
You need to stop him!
He's about to
ruin his life.
Like you give
a damn about my life.
Roy, he's right.
You're borrowing money
to buy options
That are already out
of the money.
Even you won't be able
to cover the losses.
Your house, cars,
bank accounts.
You'll lose everything.
(house)
that's the point.
The billionaire thinks
that the gods
Will treat him better
if he's broke.
I suggested he give it to me.
(roy)
there's got to be some
sort of balance.
You can't have
all the good fortune
In just one area
of your life.
It's not how the world
is supposed to look.
Who said the world
is supposed to work?
Don't just wipe
everything out.
Put your assets in a trust.
Give it to a charity.
I can't get anything back.
He's insane.
He's irrational.
So are most people.
Unfortunately it doesn't make
him insane.
If he signs that paper,
He's not only gonna destroy
his own life,
But the lives of thousands
of people who rely
On this company
to make a living.
If he is insane,
we will sue this hospital--
(cuddy)
mr. Randall...
I know you're upset.
You shouldn't make a decision
like this right now.
Give it some time.
My son doesn't
have any time.
Your son's dying from
an incurable disease,
Not bad karma.
No.
He's not dying.
It's not gonna happen.
I'm not gonna let it.
Roy, please!
(roy)
I'm sorry.
I can't let him die.
People don't get
what they deserve.
They just get
what they get.
There's nothing any of us
can do about it.
Deliver it
or I'll make sure
You end up the ones
with nothing.
[flatline tone]
Call a code.
He's flatlining.
(thirteen)
thanks.
You're welcome.
For what?
For thinking I was worth
Breaking the law
to keep around.
That's just the way I am,
But still don't know
what you're talking about.
Cuddy had I.T. Trace all
the I.P. Addresses
Who've logged in
to my email account.
There were two.
Mine and yours.
Obviously house decided he needs
you more than he's--
I already asked house.
And he'd certainly
never lie.
No, he'd lie.
Except he wants me gone.
And he'd do a lot better job
of lying than you just did.
Really?
It was that bad?
No, actually.
But it doesn't
matter anymore.
Why?
Because of house
or foreman?
You're good for both
of them,
But foreman's
not my best friend.
House will be fine.
Maybe.
But with you on the team,
he'd be better.
He needs someone...
Who doesn't need him.
You're the only one
He's never really
been able to suck
Into his crazy house vortex.
Keeps him grounded.
His ego in check.
Why didn't you just
come to me?
I figured you'd only stay
if house asked
And I knew
he would eventually.
Bye, wilson.
This is a great job.
Maybe even better now that house
is at least trying
To have real relationships
with people.
I said, "trying."
It doesn't matter.
The job you love
doesn't matter?
Don't throw it all away
Just because
of a bad break-up.
Bye, wilson.
[sighs]
I just confessed.
I told thirteen I was the one
who canceled the plane ticket.
Why?
You mean why did I confess
or why did I do it?
I know you didn't do it,
so I guess the first.
You want her to stay because
you want her back
Or because foreman does?
Why would I care
what foreman wants?
Because you're not as big a jerk
as everyone thinks.
Yes, I am.
No, you're not.
I just made a $10,000
short sale on a stock
I know is gonna crash
because of what I saw
A grief-stricken dad do
on his son's deathbed.
No, you didn't.
Yes, I did.
You are a jerk.
She's making a mistake.
So you did it for her?
She's a good doctor.
So you did it for you?
I'm not the one
in charge anymore.
So you did it
for foreman?
She's a smoking hot,
newly single bisexual.
Why don't you just admit that
you like having her around?
She's good for you.
You need her.
Because I was born with a heart
three sizes too small.
No, you weren't.
Yes, I--
What?
He still alive?
(foreman)
yeah.
Good.
Start him on heparin
and iv immunoglobulin.
For degos?
The cardiac arrest
wasn't just a
"everything goes to hell
in a handbasket" arrest.
It was a coronary event.
Coronaries are large vessels.
Mean's it can't be degos.
But the biopsies confirmed--
Obstructed blood vessels.
But they can't be obstructed
because of degos.
Means it's primary
antiphospholipid syndrome.
You sure?
Nope.
But I will be if he responds
to the heparin
And the immunoglobulin.
By the way,
Someone screwed over
your girlfriend
And she ran to me, cuddy,
and wilson.
Everyone but you.
She's not over you.
Or she is.
Where'd you find it?
Find what?
The niacin bound
chromium supplements.
It was right
on top of the file.
You don't know about it?
No.
Been here all night.
One of dibala's previous docs
was prescribing
Ultra high doses of niacin bound
chromium to boost his hdl.
So?
So it gives us something
to point to.
We can explain the wide
variation
Between the hdl numbers.
We're safe.
We're covered.
You really didn't
request the info?
No.
And obviously
you didn't either.
Which means...
It worked.
The medicine worked.
[chuckles]
How'd you find it?
Fat old black guy.
Knew he had to be taking
something for his cholesterol.
And what now?
I'm not the boss.
You don't think
I should be fired?
Why?
I doubt we'll ever be treating
a genocidal dictator again.
Better a murder
than a misdiagnosis.
Whether you want to be
in charge or not...
You are and you
always will be.
[ray lamontagne's sarah]
[alarm buzzes]
(foreman)
75-year-old african man
Presented to our hospital
following
A rapid onset of hemoptysis.
He'd been fine prior to onset.
No chest pain, fever,
coughing, or chills...
* when we first met *
* we were kids *
* we were wild *
* we were restless *
* after a while *
* I grew coarse *
* I grew cold *
* I grew reckless *
* I hold this memory *
* hold you so close to me *
* whispered we'll be
always happy *
* now I see *
* just how young *
* how scared I was *
* eyes closed tight *
* throwing punch after punch
at the world *
* sarah *
* is it ever gonna be
the same *
* sarah *
* is it ever gonna
be the same *
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net