I'll be right there.
Take your time.
You mind if I get a drink of water?
No, not at all. Help yourself.
Not exactly beach reading.
Do you understand?
Most of these I can get through,
but that one?
Can't get past the dust jacket.
- Where's Ted?
- Laid off.
Company's going
with per diem workers.
You don't have to pay overtime,
health insurance.
- That sucks.
- I don't mind. Really, I'm not...
a 40-hour-a-week kind of guy.
If I could just get you to sign.
Right.
Hang on one second.
I want to show you something.
You're gonna laugh,
but I swear, this guy James Sidas
looks exactly like you.
Wait a second.
This guy is you.
I saw a profile Nova did on you.
You're, like, the youngest guy
to ever graduate MIT?
- Standards were lower back then.
- You got an IQ of 178.
Published three books and 35 papers
all before the age of 18?
Sorry, I really need to get going.
So if I could get you to sign off.
All right. I'll trade you.
I'll sign...
if you'll sign.
- I'm not that guy anymore.
- Come on.
This is the most exciting thing
that's happened in this place in years.
Come on.
Don't be like that.
I'm paying you a compliment.
It's not that...
My hand's not working.
You okay?
.:: La Fabrique ::.
R[H]ésus AB+ Team
Benj
ShalimarFox
Arrow
- $2.32.
- Put it on Dr. Wilson's tab.
I don't know who Dr. Wilson is,
and we don't have tabs.
Do you know who I am?
Good.
But, sir...
I got it. It's all right.
Thanks.
Although I should make it clear
that for two bucks all you get
is top half, over the clothes.
Any plans for turkey day?
Go to my sister's for dinner. Why?
Just making pleasant conversation.
I've heard tell of folks doing such.
How'bout we talk about this?
15-year-old.
- Recurring migraines, blurred vision.
- Great.
- Really?
- Sure.
There's no point in putting
a band together if we don't play.
Hold on.
Take this instead.
- I was expecting more resistance.
- That was the old me.
New me is static-guarded
and friction-free.
Enjoy your drumstick.
Ready to save some lives?
32-year-old courier.
Ataxia, anemia, mild cough.
- CT was clear. Tox screen negative.
- What're you so excited about?
Why not?
Got all my starters back,
and a couple of first-class free agents.
I feel like Mike Tomlin.
Probably not as much as you do,
but you get the idea.
Ataxia and anemia could be viral.
Maybe West Nile?
No fever, lymph glands were normal.
- Anybody seen Wilson?
- Hyperbilirubinemia?
Yeah, like that's a real thing.
- Meningitis.
- Anemia's a stretch.
Page Dr. James Wilson at 558.
What about sickle cell?
- Guy's white.
- Whites can get it.
We get the tennis elbow
and all the money.
Let them have sickle cell.
- TTP's a better fit.
- He's right.
You thought I wouldn't agree with him?
Ever?
You didn't.
That's why he dumped you.
Oh, sorry. It was mutual.
We're cool, okay?
Nobody's angry, nobody's hurt.
Sounds passionate.
- TTP makes sense to me.
- Not to me.
- What if he had a history of...
- One big, happy family.
TTP it is.
Confirm with a blood smear
and adamts13 antibodies.
Dr. James Wilson, please dial 558.
- Can you cure it?
- TTP isn't completely curable,
but the symptoms are manageable
with the treatment.
Is this the treatment?
No, first we do a blood test
to confirm it.
- But he's gonna get better.
- Honey, that's what she's saying.
- I'm gonna be okay. Don't worry.
- How? You're in the hospital.
I'm gonna be fine.
You're sure
everything was fine before?
Given your educational background,
you'd could at least
find a job with a medical plan.
We have money.
Don't worry.
It's not that, it's just...
I want to make sure we have
all the information we should.
- My husband wouldn't lie.
- It's okay. He's just doing his job.
He just wants to make sure I'm not
a secret drug addict or an alcoholic.
Or hiding a history
of mental illness?
I work as a courier
because I want to.
- It's easy. I don't have to think.
- It's too hard to think.
No, just unpleasant.
No matter what I did,
it really wasn't good enough.
Then I met Dara.
She didn't care how smart I was
or what I might accomplish later.
It was the first time in my life
that I was really happy.
So I decided
I would rather be happy than smart.
You all right?
Sorry. I know you're not okay.
I mean...
She left.
Went back to Chicago.
Any chance of reconciliation?
Sure you don't want to grab a drink?
We could talk
about the perils of dating doctors.
- I wasn't dating Cameron.
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean to...
I know what you're doing
and I appreciate it,
but I've got it under control.
That's what you said
about the Dibala incident.
And obviously you didn't.
And talking about it
obviously made things so much better.
Didn't you think there was
something weird about that guy?
Not really. In fact,
he seemed pretty normal.
That's my point.
Guys with IQs off the chart
are usually completely...
abnormal.
Speaking of House,
why'd you come back?
- You must've taken a major pay cut.
- Life's too short to worry about money.
- And your wife?
- She's happy
to cut back on some things...
like sex.
- Why'd you come back?
- Why wouldn't I?
Like Foreman said, nobody's angry.
Nobody's hurt.
Schistocytes.
That means TTP.
Which is what we thought it'd be.
Remember? This is a good thing.
This is an easy thing. And House
doesn't take cases that are easy,
which means it's not TTP,
and he wants to see
how long it takes us to catch up to him.
Schistocytes suggest TTP.
Good. Now what?
Normally, we'd try plasmapheresis,
but the patient
has an albumin colloid allergy.
So?
So that means we have
to give him a splenectomy.
Yes, it does.
- Do you know where he is?
- Not in here.
You're sure you want us
to take out his spleen.
Is that what a "splenectomy" is?
I thought it was an ice cream treat.
So you do really think he has TTP?
You're not just testing us.
Yeah, like I have time for games.
- So why did you really take this case?
- Isn't it obvious?
I'm fishing for a dinner invite.
Missed you
at breakfast this morning.
And lunch.
I had a dentist appointment.
You know where Cuddy's sister lives?
You see, this is why
I don't answer your urgent pages.
Because they're not urgent pages.
I've decided what I'm gonna do
about Cuddy and Lucas.
- I'm going to break them up.
- Of course.
It's given me a purpose in life,
a goal, a raison d'etre.
Albeit a selfish,
mean-spirited, childish raison.
I think of it more as benevolent.
There's only two outcomes
for their relationship.
They split, or they stay
together forever.
If it's split, then the sooner
it happens the better for everyone.
If it's stay,
then my meddling won't matter.
In fact, if they survive it,
it might even make
their bond stronger.
How you manage
to elevate your narcissism
to beneficence is masterful.
And I've decided
to do a Thanksgiving dinner.
Just 'cause I'm sentimental.
Dinner is at Cuddy's sister's,
which brings us back...
House, don't.
I fished for an invite.
Cuddy wasn't biting, I'll have to crash.
I have no idea
where Cuddy's sister lives.
Ask and thou shalt receive.
You can't honestly think
I would help you with this.
Not help me, help Cuddy.
Remember?
If you don't get it, I'll be forced
to use more nefarious methods.
Happy holidays.
Looks great.
So he's all better?
Probably be on some long-term meds,
and he's about ten ounces lighter.
Other than that,
won't even know it's gone.
Did you hear that, honey?
You're gonna be just fine.
When can I get out of here?
Everything checks out,
less than a week.
Good, 'cause those boxes
aren't gonna deliver colors.
- Colors?
- Green...
and orange...
and ceiling.
- Mr. Sidas, do you know where you are?
- Chewing.
Shirt...
He's stroking.
Call the cath lab now.
My God.
Blood flow's restored.
There appears to be no permanent damage.
Good news is it turns out to be
an exciting, action-packed
thrill ride of a case after all.
Bad news is
we took out his spleen for nothing.
Thank God he's still got
his appendix and tonsils.
So what looks like TTP,
acts like TTP,
tests like TTP, but isn't TTP?
CNS vasculitis explains ataxia,
and anemia,
- maybe the stroke.
- CT would've picked up something.
Hi, I'm Greg House,
a friend of your sister Lisa.
Could be DIC.
Lisa Cuddy.
Sorry. Wrong number.
- You gonna ask?
- He's got a logical explanation.
Can't be DIC.
No hemorrhaging.
And I'm calling all 12 Julia Cuddys
within a 100-mile radius.
See?
Completely reasonable.
- Acquired pancytopenia.
- WBC's normal.
You're...
You're Lisa's sister, right?
You sure?
'Cause you are number 12.
Maybe she got married
and changed her name.
- Otis Campbell.
- Probably kept her first name.
The mnemonic for toxins.
O for organophosphates,
- t for tricyclics, i for insulin.
- Or as I remember it, "moist place".
That's "place" spelled
with two "l"s and a silent "b".
- Except the tox screen was negative.
- Standard...
Unstandard toxins
don't show up on it.
You two do an unstandard tox screen,
you two search his home.
Otis Campbell's
got to be hiding somewhere.
Smartest guy in the world,
and this is the best he can do.
Maybe he's doing what he loves.
Delivering boxes was a childhood dream.
Soda, processed cheese,
marshmallow spread.
Nothing in here
is capable of going bad.
Ibuprofen, eye drops,
cough syrup.
You want to come over
for Thanksgiving dinner?
You never asked me over before.
Why now?
I never thought of it.
But now that we're both
on the team...
And my wife left me?
Is that a bad reason?
But I'm okay.
On both the food and friends.
Mice.
Leptospirosis could explain
the ataxia and the anemia.
But not without a fever.
You have someone to talk to?
- Yeah.
- Who?
What, you want names?
Look, you lost a friend.
I get it.
But I'm not Kutner.
Good, 'cause Kutner never
used to come over for dinner.
I'm gonna pretend there's something
interesting over here so you'll shut up.
Actually, there is.
He's got sketches
of atomic structure,
This one's full of math proofs.
They're all old.
Nothing since '96.
This isn't some homework assignment
his parents forced on him.
This is passion.
Why would he stop?
Marriage destroyed his soul.
Maybe...
it was just the booze.
- Thank you, you've been wonderful.
- As have you.
- Be well.
- Thank you.
You're helping.
Voluntarily.
- He's done six already.
- Figured you might be backed up.
Holiday season and all.
Which one of us slipped through
the wormhole into another dimension?
I have always loved to travel,
and paint.
Lucky number seven.
You're trying to be nice,
but I know you have an agenda.
Sexy and smart.
- Lucas is a lucky guy.
- The question is,
is this a bad agenda or a good one?
Either you're trying
to screw with me,
or you're trying to show me
that you've really changed.
So which is it?
I'm dying to know.
What are you doing for Thanksgiving?
Peace in our time.
Cost me 45 minutes of clinic duty.
This is a three-hour drive.
Have you considered the possibility
this is a fake address?
She'd send me
to a vacant lot for Thanksgiving?
- If she's smart.
- She is.
I ran it through motor vehicles.
- Good as gold.
- This cannot end well.
I don't want it to end well.
You should come as my date.
You're not gonna want to miss this.
The unstandard tox screen
was as clean as the standard one.
But we found vodka
stashed away in his place.
What's with the ties?
Makes me look adorably
non-threatening.
Party or party hearty?
Liver failure
would explain the symptoms.
Party.
So, guy's a brainiac,
and his secret drug of choice
is booze?
- Kinda pedestrian, don't you think?
- Talk to him, he's a pedestrian guy.
With pedestrian alcoholism.
Biopsy can wait
until after Thanksgiving.
Assuming the biopsy's gonna tell us
exactly what we expect,
it can wait till after New Year's.
On the other hand, Taub and Thirteen
can do it today.
- Why us?
- Juniority.
Welcome back.
- What do you want us to do?
- Same as me.
Have a happy Thanksgiving.
I'm not an alcoholic.
You just hide vodka
around the house for fun.
I drink, just not a lot.
Since when do you drink at all?
I have one shot when I get home, baby,
that's it.
- So why lie about it?
- Because it's not important.
- What difference does it make?
- That you drink every day by yourself?
I have one lousy drink, okay?
Ever seen me drunk?
You've obviously
been drinking enough to hurt your liver.
- My liver is fine.
- Hold still.
There we go.
This test is a waste of time.
All right. Very good.
Here, we got this.
Julia?
No, I'm the house sitter.
They're in Hawaii for the week.
- Happy Thanksgiving.
- Happy Thanksgiving, you guys.
You must be Dr. House.
I was told I should offer you
a turkey sandwich.
Tuna salad.
Closest thing they had to turkey.
Thanks, but I'm hoping
I can get out of here
to catch the end of dinner
with my wife.
- Anything?
- No cirrhosis,
- no scarring, no infection.
- Blood panel?
Elevated albumen: 7.2.
- That's it?
- Everything else is fine.
So it was a waste of time.
Unless it's not his liver
that's elevating his albumen.
- It's his kidneys.
- Renal failure. Explains the anemia.
If he developed hyperkalemia,
that would explain the ataxia.
- But the stroke...
- Ischemic encephalopathy.
Nice.
Except we have to stay
and test his kidneys.
Key under the mat.
- There's no key under the mat.
- Right.
You need to replace
one of your kitchen windows.
I helped myself to your wine cellar.
I'll leave a buck on the way out.
- You're not right for her.
- And you are?
Less wrong.
Then I started thinking...
What was I saying?
You were saying it's late, and...
She invited me.
She didn't know if she should.
She was trying to figure out
if I really have changed or...
if I'm still the same old S.O.B.
I've always been.
She always gave me a chance.
832 chances.
And I used up every one of them.
832's her limit.
Make a note.
How 'bout a cup of coffee?
It's just instant, but...
I'm pathetic.
I don't deserve her.
Maybe you should crash here.
It's a sofa bed.
I love her.
Patient's liver's fine.
His kidneys are shot.
And where is House?
He left a message.
He's not coming in today.
What causes kidney failure?
- Rhabdomyolysis.
- No edema.
- You had a wonderful Thanksgiving?
- I don't remember.
So I guess I did.
Multiple myeloma.
- No bone pain.
- You got drunk alone?
That would be a sign
that I need to talk to you about this.
- Polycystic kidney disease?
- No UTIs or flank pain.
What if his cough
is more than just a cold?
He hasn't been coughing.
It's in his history,
and we found cough syrup in his cabinet.
It could mean Goodpasture syndrome,
affects kidneys and lungs.
Start him on immunosuppressors
and dialysis.
- After we run it by House.
- He's not answering his pager.
- Looks like he's leaving it up to us.
- Us, not you.
And since we don't disagree,
you can save your fight
for another case.
How long
do I have to be hooked up for?
Four to six hours a day
- until we see an improvement.
- What if you don't?
- We keep doing it until a transplant.
- You were sure it was his spleen,
and then you were sure
it was his liver,
which he told you it wasn't,
and now it's his kidneys!
It's definitely his kidneys.
We just don't know
why it's his kidneys.
Any word from Cameron?
I started seeing a counselor
after my diagnosis.
She's really good.
Why does everyone assume
everyone works in the exact same way?
We pretty much do.
Our egos want us to think
we're all snowflakes, no two alike,
but really
we all want the same things.
Love, forgiveness...
Chocolate.
What I want
is for everyone to leave me alone.
How do I get that?
What did you say
to Lucas last night?
I know there were
a lot of consonants.
I don't remember how I got here,
never mind what I said.
I talked to him.
And he said it'd be better
if we stopped seeing each other.
Said he didn't realize how much
there still was between you and me.
And he didn't want to get caught
in the middle of us.
I was drunk.
- Whatever I said, he can't...
- I've had enough, House.
I actually felt bad
about scamming you.
But then you lived down
to my expectations
and then some.
There is no "us".
There never will be.
It worked.
Tell me you're talking
about a medical procedure.
They split up this morning.
You're the very first one I've told.
And you think
she'll start dating you?
I'm sure she hates you.
But her eyes say,
"How will I ever pay you
for that tennis lesson?"
- What a shame.
- They'll get over it.
- I meant for you.
- I'll get over it faster than they do.
Can't believe Lucas fell for my
"I never say this
because it's so personal
"except that I'm drunk"
profession of love.
Second-oldest trick in the book.
You're right.
It's his fault because he's stupid.
He certainly is.
You're stupid.
Well, I'm rubber, and you're glue.
He's not pedestrian, he's stupid.
At least stupider than he should be.
He's a DXM junkie.
Dextromethorphan, as in cough syrup?
He wasn't taking it for his cough.
It's cheap,
available at your corner drug store,
and taken in high doses,
it's a dumb drug.
Dumb drug.
Well, he obviously hasn't...
He's smart compared to you.
He's a moron
compared to what he was.
Robotripping
lowers the IQ.
It also causes brain damage.
Unless taken with the proper amount
of ethanol.
About one drink per day.
He wasn't abusing the booze
and taking the cough remedy medicinally.
He was abusing the cough meds,
and taking the booze medicinally.
Bravo.
Why would you do that?
If you had a gift,
why would you just throw it away?
I didn't throw it away.
I just turned it down a little.
When my brain was on low,
everything didn't seem
so miserable anymore.
Life was bearable.
I thought that I did that.
You do.
Long-term abuse of DXM
explains all your symptoms.
Even, oh, sweet irony, your cough.
Whole bowel lavage,
activated charcoal.
We get all traces of it
out of your system.
You'll be the unhappiest
little courier in no time.
I don't think I can live without it.
You'd be surprised
what you can live without.
Make him a genius.
I can't believe it.
He looks so much better already.
We were thinking about calling GQ.
Lavage has removed all traces
of DXM from his body.
You're drawing again.
What is it?
- Just doodles.
- No, it's not.
Come on, Jimmy, I want to know.
This is a toroidal
helicon plasma device.
It determines
the amount of energy expended
by he subatomic particles.
I'm thirsty.
Could you get me a juice or something?
Of course.
I'm so happy, Jimmy.
I told you.
Do you know what the difference
between her IQ and mine is?
91 points.
In relation, she's closer to a gibbon
than she is to me.
Having sex with her
would be an act of bestiality.
I assume you didn't marry her
for her skill in applied physics.
I wish she could spell it.
You think you'd be happier
with someone who could spell better?
That's the problem.
I'm the one who's a jerk.
But I owe her everything.
I want to want to be with her.
And when I'm clear, I...
I can't.
Fainting, dizziness,
shortness of breath?
Sometimes.
Is the wait always this long?
Only on days that end in "day".
Diarrhea, weight loss?
A bit.
Don't you ever shave?
Yeah. Once a week.
How'bout you?
- Stomach pain, tenderness?
- Every now and then.
Are you this rude
to all your patients?
Yes. Don't think you're special.
So we've got a lot of vague,
unverifiable symptoms.
Yet all the physical signs
are perfectly normal.
- What do you think I have?
- I'm not sure, but I think it's...
a lame job.
What?
You're a rat.
Insurance company sends you out
to check on the quality of medical care.
- That's ridiculous.
- Is it really?
'Cause you seem a lot more interested
in asking questions than answering them.
Handwriting on your medical records
isn't a doctor's, I can almost read it.
When you went out
for a urine sample,
I looked in your purse.
Found the questions you were supposed
to memorize
before you came to the clinic.
- I was looking for gum.
- You're an ass.
Put it in your report.
I tell you what.
I'll give you 20 bucks if you'll pretend
that I'm not when we leave this room.
Remember, first ice, then heat.
If you have any problems,
don't hesitate to call me.
Thank you, Dr. House.
Wait a second.
Where's Cuddy?
Gone for the day.
I can't remember if I've mocked you yet
for being a male nurse.
I think this counts.
Fair enough.
That isn't the man I married.
Yes, he is.
He's just smarter.
- Give him some time. I'm sure...
- He hates me.
His body is going through
withdrawal.
- He's adjusting.
- Maybe he never loved me. Not really.
Maybe we never really
had anything at all.
Somebody help!
I can't feel my legs.
I can't feel them.
Anywhere.
Nothing.
We have to talk about this.
It's late. I'm tired.
I know it's a big pay cut, but I'll
always have the chance to make money.
I won't always have
the chance to do this job.
That's what you think?
That it's about the money?
So it's that I didn't consult you
before I took the job?
That was offensive,
but it's not about that either.
So then...
Can you give me the first letter?
When we got married,
you were an intern working
30-hour shifts doing grunt work.
We both put up with it because we knew
that it was leading to something better.
In your private practice,
you are the boss.
You call the shots,
but now you're 40 years old,
you're still doing grunt work.
That's what this is about?
You think I'm a wuss?
He made you miss
Thanksgiving dinner.
Vitamin B12 deficiency?
Gives us anemia, numbness.
- Not a stroke.
- If he has a vascular malformation...
Anemia's not macrocytic.
Sorry to inconvenience you.
Dying patients can be so thoughtless.
Don't.
Great comeback. Is that Oscar Wilde?
Come on, people.
- Bone marrow malignancy.
- Wouldn't produce schistocytes.
- Lupus.
- Thanks for coming in.
ANA was negative.
What about you?
Got any predictable drivel
you'd like to add?
- They've given you enough already.
- At least they're trying.
They're not sitting there like roadkill.
Give me something.
Something,
or I'll get your ex-smarter half
on the phone and ask her.
You're gonna be pressing charges?
Against the ottoman I tripped over?
Against Chase.
I'm pretty sure the ottoman
was acting alone.
- You free for dinner this weekend?
- At least three other people saw him.
Mass hysteria.
Either night?
I can't have doctors
punching each other out.
My God, who got punched?
And more importantly,
for Chase's sake, I need to know
if he's able to handle himself
or if I should be getting him some help.
He couldn't have punched anyone.
He was with me
when I tripped over the ottoman.
If you're not planning on eating,
maybe a movie?
I'm not doing this.
It's not fun anymore.
Just do your job.
I need your help.
What happened to your face?
I was mowing the lawn
when the phone rang.
You're a computer.
I'm gonna feed you data,
and you analyze it.
What, are you gonna feed me
20 years of medical knowledge too?
It's not gonna work.
I know.
But I don't have anyone else to ask.
It's lonely, isn't it?
It's not that bad.
Then you're not that smart.
You ever tried to kill yourself?
- Not quickly.
- I did.
12 years ago I jumped off
the top of my eight-story building
into a dumpster bin
the day before pickup.
I broke my collarbone,
my leg, and three ribs.
When I was in the hospital
they put me on narcotics
and suddenly everything
was just better.
I didn't feel isolated or lonely.
That's where I met my wife.
She was... so happy.
And dumb.
And I was...
smart...
and miserable.
You tell me who the genius is.
I fell in love with her
buzzed out of my head,
and I knew I wanted
to stay that way forever.
Enjoy.
Easier on your conscience
if I die an idiot?
What's a conscience?
Which ribs...
did you break in the fall?
They on the left side?
Bottom three.
That was 12 years ago.
This probably cost me my marriage,
so it better be awesome.
Ferrous oxide contrast?
Gets absorbed by the spleen.
Unless he doesn't have one.
In which case
it's absorbed by the liver,
- and fries that.
- You're killing him?
I opened him up
and didn't take out his spleen?
All organs do look kind of the same...
red and squishy.
Accessory spleens.
Okay, that is amazing.
12 years, eight stories,
and a dumpster ago,
he broke three ribs,
damaged his spleen.
Bits of it split off,
circulated through his bloodstream
until they landed
and attached somewhere else.
So it is TTP.
I just didn't remove...
- All of his spleens.
- 16 splenectomies.
Pretty sure he gets
a set of steak knives with that.
I can outrun you.
Sorry about the nose.
And the eye... and the...
eyebrow.
Guess I deserved it.
If I thought that,
I wouldn't be apologizing.
Your fist slipped?
Everybody kept bugging me,
asking if I was okay.
So you busted my nose
to keep people off your back.
Pretty much.
Making people even more
worried about you.
Maybe.
But at least
they're not talking to me about it.
Fair enough.
Cheers.
- Thank you.
- Don't be so grateful.
You'll be delivering packages
for 70 years to pay for it.
Well, thanks for our talk.
It's been a while
since I had a stimulating conversation.
- So what're you gonna do?
- Go back to my life.
Which one?
The one that has my wife in it.
Robo tripping.
- How's she feel about that?
- She doesn't have to know.
It's worked for 12 years.
Tell your brain I said good-bye.
Einstein's giving himself a lobotomy,
and you're cool with that?
Ignorance is bliss.
Hold that pose.
I'll start with t-shirts and mugs,
and see how it goes.
Home early.
What happened to him?
- You beat up House?
- Just one right hook.
Why? What happened?
You were right. I told him we need
to lay down some ground rules,
- got a little heated.
- That's not what I meant.
Is he okay?
Are you gonna be fired? Arrested?
Everything's fine.
Can we at least be civil?
How's your nose?
It's okay.
Does your kid like animals?
I got tickets to that holiday carnival.
I hear they have a nice petting zoo.
- I think I was pretty clear before.
- I don't mean with me.
Here. Take 'em. Enjoy.
No, thanks.
They're not fake.
I didn't steal them.
One of the nurses was selling 'em
for her kid's scout trip.
It doesn't make
things right between us,
I just wanted to do something nice.
I don't want them.
I'll see you tomorrow.
They didn't split up.
She wouldn't take the tickets.
Of course.
Wind talker code
for "we never split up."
She told you multiple times
she wants nothing to do with you.
I wasn't gonna be there.
She just felt guilty
that I felt guilty,
so she couldn't take them.
Either that
or she didn't want to appease you.
These weren't reparations.
Just a simple gesture of remorse,
and she slapped it down.
They didn't break up.
She just wanted me
to think that so I'd back off.
Dare I ask what you're gonna do?
Nothing.
I said they'd either break up
or they'd stay together.
They didn't break up.
And you're okay with that?
It is what it is.
Good for you.
House knows I lied.
Why? What'd he say?
Nothing.
I could just tell.
You want to stage another breakup?
It seems like
he's gonna leave us alone.
Why would he do that?
I'm not completely sure.
So...
we have his blessing?
I guess so.
I made you some meatballs.
Maybe House isn't so bad after all.
That would be nice, wouldn't it?
www.sous-titres.eu
www.tvsubtitles.net