♪ ♪
How about the name Brooke?
She just doesn't seem
like a Brooke anymore.
Brooklyn.
She's a baby,
not a city.
What do you think, bud?
Got any suggestions?
Toadette.
I'm hungry.
I'll get you guys
something to eat.
You're okay.
Okay.
♪ ♪
I was paged?
What are you doing here?
Can we talk somewhere?
I was thinking Doroth--
Sarah?
Yeah.
Where's the baby?
No one saw anyone
go in or out,
and the baby's
not in the nursery.
What was her condition?
Five weeks preterm.
C-section because
her mom's preeclampsia.
Is that the father?
Mr. Lozinski.
I'm Dr. Lisa Cuddy,
Dean of Medicine.
How long were you
out of the room?
Um, 15, 20 minutes
tops.
Was there a proximity alarm?
No alarms.
What's that?
The bracelet on your baby's
ankle has a microchip
that would set off alarms
if she was carried
through an exit.
Call the police.
Shut down all the exits.
We are on lockdown.
Nobody moves
until we find that baby.
♪ House 6x16 ♪
Lockdown
Original Air Date on April 12, 2010
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.com --
♪ ♪
Why won't you sign
the divorce papers?
It's been on my to-do list.
Sorry.
Will you sign them?
Not until we have
a real conversation
about our marriage.
Okay. I made a mistake
coming here.
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna leave...
This copy here.
Code seven. Code seven.
All non-essential personnel
and guests
please remain where you are.
Security personnel should report
to their staging areas
and await
further instructions.
All patients,
please remain in your rooms,
and use call buttons
if you need medical assistance.
Please remain calm and wait
for hospital personnel
to come to you.
Do not try
to leave your room
until the code seven
has been lifted.
Please clear hallways.
Nurse, just leave it.
Leave it. You need to get
into the room now.
Please notify hospital personnel
or police immediately
if you see anything suspicious.
We cannot allow anyone to leave
the hospital at this time.
All personnel should remain
in their staging areas
unless otherwise instructed
by security.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
gotta clear the--
Thank you for your patience
and cooperation.
And did anyone
other than your nurses
ever come by
asking about your daughter?
No. No, just those two.
I'll check in soon.
Wait.
What are you doing?
No, I need to help them look.
Ow!
You have to stay in bed.
You pulled a stitch.
Lay back down.
I got it.
Why don't I give you something
to help you relax?
No, no, I don't want
to relax.
I want to find my baby.
The police are searching
room by room.
Who would take her?
What if she needs to be fed?
We're gonna find her.
Why aren't the police
talking to our nurse?
What now?
Truth or dare?
Oh, no, you don't want
to mess with me.
True or dare queen
at Newton north.
I was kidding.
I'm sure we can find
something interesting
to talk about without relying
on some juvenile game.
Sure.
Truth.
They think I took the kid?
Do you think
I would do something--
no, I'm just asking questions.
The day I let
the older brother
hold the baby
for the first time--
so I put her
in his lap.
After a few seconds,
she shrieked.
I'm pretty sure
he pinched her.
I need to know this stuff.
Anything out of the ordinary.
It was sibling rivalry.
I thought
it was kind of ordinary.
Hey.
What are you doing down here?
I was looking
for McKenna's patient file.
Oh, you mean
this file?
The one I said
I'd get?
Two hours ago?
Seriously,
you don't trust me
with the immense responsibility
of fetching a file?
If you already found it,
what are you looking
through those for?
Do you know what these are?
The staff credentials files.
Those should all be
in H.R.
Down here
to be digitized.
And we're locked in,
and whoever's supposed
to be watching 'em
is locked out.
Could look up anything
on anyone.
Malpractice records,
felony histories
put them away.
Come on.
We have a tiny window
of opportunity
to gain some insight
into our colleagues.
Okay. What if we just snoop
on the boss?
I think I can live
with that.
You're on two milligrams
of morphine an hour.
How the hell
are you still awake?
No, don't tell me.
Ischemic cardiomyopathy.
If the blood's not reaching
your gut,
you have
intestinal hypoperfusion.
That'd be stronger
than the narcotics.
The nurse said I might only have
a day or two left.
She was being kind.
You're Dr. House,
aren't you?
Oh, God, don't tell me
we used to date.
The limp.
I read about you.
I sent you a letter
before they knew
what was wrong.
I tried to get you
to take my case.
Yeah, well,
you should have kept reading.
Heart disease
is kind of below my pay grade.
It started
as tooth pain.
No one got it
that it was a heart problem.
Till I had a series
of massive heart attack--
This doesn't bother you?
You talking
with your mouth full?
A little.
I meant the fact
that you're standing here
watching me die
because my file bored you.
I take maybe 1 in 20 cases.
A lot of the people I turn down
end up dying.
It's really a good argument
for there being
more than one me
when you think about it.
Truth.
All right.
Have you ever had
a threesome?
No.
You haven't?
Wait, just--
just because I'm bisexual?
Well, yeah.
Do you understand
what bisexual means?
It doesn't mean you have sex
with two people at once.
And by the way,
you didn't ask me
if I'd had a foursome.
Truth or dare?
Wait.
You've had a foursome?
No, but now you've asked me
two questions,
so I get to ask you two.
You see
why I was the queen.
Oh!
Walker wouldn't do
anything.
He's my son too.
I don't mean
to sound cold,
but he's your stepson.
We can't ignore
any possibility.
Walker's been getting
in fights a lot
at school lately.
Last week, he hit another kid
with a book
hard enough
to draw blood.
If he did something
to the baby...
We were working
on it.
And we failed.
No, you had a conversation
with house,
then came back,
informed me
I'd been forever poisoned
by him,
and started packing.
It's interesting how your story
leaves out the part
where you murdered
another human being.
A dictator
who was committing genocide.
You thought
about doing it yourself.
But I didn't.
Right.
Because you're not toxic
like I am.
What do you think
is gonna happen here?
You're gonna logic me
into coming back?
There must be over 30
malpractice settlements
in here.
He did a brain biopsy
without ct mapping,
causing brain herniation
and death.
Look at this one.
Patient lost
four liters of blood
from a botched penisectomy.
On a patient
named Lisa Cuddy?
Damn it.
They're all named Lisa Cuddy.
He's not even here,
and he's screwing with us.
Where's the joy in that?
You really want
to get into his head?
Yeah, but I decided against
stabbing myself in the leg
or getting addicted
to pain pills.
You can, uh...
Skip the stabbing.
Where did you--
confiscated them from
a drug seeker in that clinic.
Didn't get a chance
to turn 'em in.
It is after hours.
I'll take one.
Walk in House's shoes
for a night.
One?
I believe he wears
a larger size.
♪ ♪
no cards,
no flowers,
not even a phone call.
Let me guess.
Lighthouse keeper.
I was a classics Professor
at Princeton for 26 years.
Mostly research.
So your closest colleagues
died 2,000 years ago.
That must be it.
Not that you have no friends
because, say,
you're a miserable bastard.
What do you care?
The next few hours
are gonna be grim.
There'll be nausea, pain,
no company,
as soon as I can
get myself out of here.
I can unlock
the regulator.
You can put yourself
in a narcotic haze,
sleep blissfully
to the end.
Oh, is that a favor
to me or to you?
Win-win.
No, thanks.
Are you trying to guilt me
for not taking your case?
You think a classicist
doesn't believe in fate?
You think Odysseus
would lie whimpering
like a loser
in a hospital bed?
Come on,
take my offer.
Take the drug holiday.
Numb yourself out.
I think you're the one
who wants to numb himself out.
Truth.
How did your dad react
when you came out to him?
He made me tea.
Seriously.
Doesn't matter what I tell him.
He smiles, tells me
he supports me,
and makes me
some peppermint tea.
Truth or dare?
Um, truth.
Are you dating
anyone?
Now? No.
Interesting.
You added a modifier.
Truth.
Um, when you were dating
Foreman...
No, no. No.
What?
If it was something personal
about him or us,
I just don't think
that's right to answer.
We all work together.
That's the whole point
of this game--
something personal,
preferably embarrassing.
Just pick something else.
You see,
this is your problem.
You act like
you're so liberal and open,
but you are the least--
I changed my mind.
Dare. Just no nudity.
Yes, nudity.
I want you
to show your breasts
to Taub.
That is the most
idiotic dare ever.
Have you ever played
this game?
Well, I thought showing me
your breasts
would be
a little exploitative.
Your dare
is in the future, genius.
Hey, if you're saying
you won't do it...
No, no, no, of course
I'll show my breasts to Taub.
Tomorrow, perhaps,
or maybe some time
next year, you know,
because I'm honor-bound.
Truth or dare?
It's understandable that you
wouldn't be happy right now.
Your world is changing.
You scared?
And how do you feel
about your sister?
I hate her.
Walker,
this is important.
Did you do anything
to the baby?
Did you move her
somewhere?
Hide her?
No.
Nobody'd be mad
at you.
I said no,
so stop asking me.
Bad pain day?
Bad pain month.
Since I'm not using it...
Oh, if you don't
want the morphine,
you must have something
of your own, Hmm?
I was in rehab.
I had a little problem
with the something of my own.
Now all I take
is ibuprofen,
and it's two flights up.
For the whole month?
The pain's migrated.
I think the arterial wall
is damaged.
What, you don't know?
I haven't had
an arteriogram yet.
And you don't want the test.
In case the arterial wall
is fine.
Which would mean
that the pain
is coming
from something else.
What's her name?
Interesting...
That you jump from physical pain
to long-lost love.
You're projecting.
So what's her name?
What time is it?
What does it matter
to you?
It's "t" minus four hours.
8:20.
Now tell me
who she is
and what are
the pathetically long odds
that she's gonna visit
or call.
Why that's a reason
not to take the morphine.
♪ ♪
dude.
Dude.
Is the room
still spinning?
Mine is.
Maybe we shouldn't have taken
so many.
I'm gonna try
to stand up.
You be careful.
Oh, yeah.
That's working.
I can't feel my face.
No way.
Way.
Hit me.
What?
Hit me
in the face.
Seriously?
You know
you've always wanted to.
Now's your chance.
That's a great idea.
We start a fight club.
Maybe we...
Oh, my God!
You--
that is so cool!
Okay.
I can still feel
my hand.
I wasn't ready.
What were you gonna do?
Flex your goatee muscles?
Wait a minute.
This is your credentials file?
Hey, give me that.
That's why
you came down here.
Not for the patient file.
You wanted...
Okay, Robert.
I will answer
whatever questions
you want.
But then you're gonna have
to sign the papers.
Did you ever love me?
How can you even ask that?
The first time you slept
with me
was because you were
on crystal meth.
I was on the drugs
because I was emotional.
It was the emotions
that led to the sex,
not the drugs.
Not true.
After that, you refused to let
it go further than just sex.
Because I knew
I was falling for you
and I didn't want to.
And that never changed.
You broke off
our vacation
because I bought you
a ring.
I got cold feet.
I'm not proud.
And then you almost
called off our wedding
because you couldn't
give up the idea
of having
your dead husband's baby.
Don't!
Don't bring him up!
Because even then,
you weren't sure about me.
Maybe if I was dying
when you married me,
it would have been
a bit different.
That's not fair.
It's not only fair,
it's exactly the point.
He was dying
when you met him,
and he was gone just a year
into the marriage.
So it was all
a honeymoon with him.
And I could never
match up to that.
The first time
reality intruded--
stop this.
Just tell me the truth.
About what?
Did you ever love me?
I don't know!
Thank you
for finally telling me.
Truth.
You said
you weren't dating anyone now.
Does that you mean
you recently were,
or soon will be?
Oh.
Look who's guarded now.
You had no problem
talking about your sex life,
but your love life...
Fine.
Dare it is.
No nudity
now or in the future.
♪ ♪
you're too much
of a nice boy, Wilson.
Let's let the bad boy
out for a bit.
You have to go steal
one dollar right now.
From who?
Oh, come on.
Uh, interned at Hopkins.
Old news.
Here we go.
Academic probation.
I am asking you
to please stop reading.
I'm afraid
I can't do that.
Faked a lab result.
Very wrong!
And you came down
to destroy the record
before it gets digitized.
Permanentized.
Even wronger.
I...
I needed to beat
all those elite, spoiled kids
around me,
to show no weaknesses,
to win at everything.
Why'd I just tell you that?
I always talk too much
when I'm stoned.
Why'd I just tell you that?
It was stupid.
You had great grades.
One lab result
shouldn't have mattered.
Except I didn't think
I deserved to be
at a top med school
in the first place.
Again.
Faking lab results
is one thing.
But you needing to come down
here to destroy the records
12 years after the fact...
This isn't about med school.
You don't think
you belong here.
At the hospital.
Dr. Taubmma,
Christopher Michael.
So this
is what it comes down to
in the final hours.
Deifying some lost love.
Hoping to get her on the phone
and make everything perfect.
It's pathetic.
Either you left her
for a reason
or she left you
for a reason.
A phone call is not--
it's my daughter.
So why isn't she here?
I left my family...
When Gracie was six.
I was sort of
forced out, actually,
after I'd had an affair
with a student.
For sex
or love?
Neither.
I'd only married Gracie's mother
because of the baby.
But I didn't think
I could handle commitment,
and, like any decent academic,
I proved myself right.
And what time it is
matters because?
She's a dance teacher
in Atlanta.
She gets home from work
at 9:00,
and I just wanted
to speak to her one more time.
That's my story.
What's yours?
Same thing.
Pretty much.
I'm gonna be dead
in a few hours.
Your secrets
couldn't be safer.
Unless you're keeping them
from yourself.
I like being alone.
At least I convince myself
that I'm better off that way.
And then I met someone
at a psychiatric hospital,
of all places.
She changed me.
And then she left.
We're better off alone.
We suffer alone,
we die alone.
Doesn't matter
if you're a model husband
or father of the year.
Tomorrow will be the same
for you.
But yesterday
would have been different.
Hey, Dar--Daria.
Dr. Wilson.
Could you cook me up
a chicken sandwich?
Grill's closed.
It's important medically.
Dr. Hadley needs
a high-protein meal right now.
She doesn't like
to talk about it,
but she has hypoproteinemia.
We got chicken salad.
Yeah.
That's cold.
She needs to eat warm protein
for this disease?
Well, we could give her
cold protein
whose uptake enzymes
haven't been activated,
as long as you don't mind her
risking liver and kidney failure
and eventual death.
But, hey, it's worth it
so you don't have
to flip on the grill.
You don't have
to be obnoxious about it.
♪ ♪
How do you look
so okay?
I spent months wondering
how I made it go bad.
If you never loved me,
then--
then I didn't
do anything wrong.
Hey.
Allison, come on.
It's all right.
I still don't know
why I said that.
It's not even true.
I did love you.
Just...
Not in a way
that wouldave ever worked.
Why not?
Because everything
you said is true.
I'm a mess.
I married a man
I knew was dying.
So God knows how screwed up
I already was.
Him dying messed me up
even more.
I pushed you
out of my life.
And I-I'm unfixable.
Not you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
Truth.
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
No, I didn't even play fair.
You asked me
how my dad reacted
when I told him
I was bisexual.
And the huntington's.
No tea party?
I never told him.
He's been through enough.
So he just visits his
heterosexual, healthy daughter,
and you go out to dinner
and a movie
and talk about your garden?
I work late.
He's staying
at my house.
It's easier
if I stay elsewhere
as much as I can.
You can't suppress your life
for his convenience.
You don't see
a little irony in that?
That's exactly
what you do for house.
When he moved in with you,
you bought a bigger place
for him.
No wonder
you're not dating anyone.
You're right.
That woman, the woman
I'm not involved with,
her name is Sam carr.
But in 1990 and 1991,
it was Sam Wilson.
Your ex-wife?
No, my mother.
Yes, my ex-wife.
Ex number one.
She friended me
a few weeks ago.
We started emailing.
It turns out
she's recently divorced,
and I wanted
to ask her out.
You can't take a woman
to dinner,
or else house
will go running
straight back
to the loony bin?
You're not worried
about house.
You're worried
about yourself.
Because she's an ex.
So even dinner will mean
it's immediately serious.
What are your favorite parts
that you remember?
I liked how I would wake up
in the middle of the night,
you'd put your arm around me,
and you wouldn't even wake up.
I liked watching you stand up
to your dad at christmas
when he yelled
at your mom.
How you didn't even know
you were strong.
But you were.
What do you miss?
I miss a lot.
But when I think
about missing you,
i think
about that dance class
that we took
for the wedding.
It's weird.
I think, he's never
gonna hold me like that again.
♪ ♪
Oh, God.
♪ Oh, it's so funny
to be seeing you ♪
♪ after so long, girl ♪
♪ and with the way you look ♪
♪ I understand
that you were not impressed ♪
♪ but I heard you let
that little friend of mine ♪
I'm gonna miss this too.
♪ Take off your party dress ♪
♪ ♪
published in
The New England Journal at 26?
Finished all the lab work
a year earlier.
Led a group of surgeons
to fix cleft palates
in Bangladesh?
What can I say? That concert
was very moving to me.
I have to take a knee.
I don't get it.
This has got to be the most
spectacular file down here.
Why are pretending
to be ashamed?
I would trade mine
for yours in a second.
When I was in med school,
I thought I'd be house
some day.
Instead, I am
a fellow
working with--
working for people
years younger than me.
So we both have
a few regrets.
You should be proud
of yours.
Your life's been trending up.
No news.
How you holding up?
You let them sedate you?
Yeah.
Do you have kids?
A little girl.
I adopted her
last year.
I adopted Walker right after
Donald and I got married.
What if I can never love Walker
the way I love my daughter?
Does that make me
a horrible person?
Let me get you
some tissues.
Did you request
some extra towels?
No.
What--why?
There are eight towels
in Sarah's room.
Okay.
There should only be four.
Housekeeping handles towels.
I need you to track down
their logs,
figure out
who was up there and when.
Because they got
extra towels?
Just find the logs.
Now.
Adrienne,
you okay?
Sure.
What's wrong?
Adrienne, give me
your arm.
The hair on her left arm
is standing up.
Asymmetric
neurological function.
She's having
a pilomotor seizure.
She seemed fine
a minute ago.
She was.
She's probably been having
complex seizures all day.
She would be
basically functional,
but more or less
acting on autopilot.
She probably dropped
the towels off twice.
She could have taken
the baby.
We never really did
have a proper good-bye.
It's 9:00.
It's Gracie.
I can't come to the phone,
so please leave a message.
I guess
she's running late.
You don't seem
that surprised.
That's what you expected
to get.
You waited until you knew
she'd be out.
Her aunt said
that she starts work late.
Every now and then,
I just call to hear
her voice on the machine.
I was never there
when she needed me, so...
What right do I have
to need her now?
None.
Just means
you're a hypocrite.
'Cause apparently
you do.
Forget about rights.
Just tell her
what you need to tell her.
It's Gracie.
I can't come to the phone,
so please leave a message.
Gracie...
This is...
Your father.
I love you.
anything?
We've covered every room
on maldonado's logs.
Been everywhere she's been.
Where's the other cart?
Isn't there usually
another cart in here?
Hey.
Okay.
Hi.
Oh.
♪ ♪
♪ the birds areinging ♪
♪ in your eyes today ♪
♪ sweet flowers blossom ♪
♪ in your smile ♪
♪ but my soul is stormy ♪
♪ and my heart blows wild ♪
♪ my sweetheart
rides a ship ♪
♪ on the sea ♪
Anyone in there?
Lockdown's over.
♪ ♪
I should go.
Yeah.
I just asked Sam
to dinner.
Little baby's
all growed up.
You gonna tell your dad?
I'll stop by his hotel,
talk to him.
Hotel?
You said he was staying
at your apartment.
Was there any truth
in anything you said?
The part about it being
a good idea for you to call Sam.
That was true.
Good night, Remy.
Good night, James.
Code seven has been lifted.
Repeat, code seven
has been lifted.
You want your file?
Nah.
Good for you.
All hospital personnel may leave
their staging areas
and report back
to their departments.
Thank you
for your cooperation.
We don't have
to tell anybody what we--
mm-mm.
You got
the patient file?
I'll grab it.
Thanks.
See you tomorrow.
I think I'm ready
to take you up on your offer.
Dr. House?
Lockdown ended
a few minutes ago.
Yeah. I know.
I'm sorry
I didn't take your case.
Me too.
Gracie...
Was the cutest six-year-old
you ever saw.
♪ Once in a blue moon ♪
♪ you will find
the right one ♪
♪ once in a blue moon ♪
♪ find your dear
delight one ♪
♪ then with a thrill ♪
♪ you'll know
that love is true ♪
♪ once in a lifetime... ♪
interesting night, huh?
Interesting.
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net