My lords, and ladies.
Today your queen
will choose her champion.
Here, he will battle
for not only her honor,
but for a title of his own.
But only if he can defeat
the captain of my guard,
sir Horace the black!
Sir William...
Wouldst thou fight for my honor?
To the death, your majesty.
Let's hope it does not come to that.
I choose sir William as my champion.
Attack from his left side.
I saw his squire
bandaging that shoulder this morning.
I wish thee luck and strength.
I fear I shall need all I can get.
The captain of my guard,
sir Horace the black!
Are you sure you wouldn't like
to reconsider your choice, my queen?
I believe I chose rightly, my king.
Brave knights,
in the honored tradition of our lands,
have at ye!
I fear you chose
most poorly, my love.
What is it?
Your eyes.
We need an ambulance
at the Camden fairgrounds.
.:: La Fabrique ::.
R[H]ésus AB+ Team
You're new.
You're naked.
And, for the record,
a little bit cold.
I'm sorry, I didn't know
that anyone was home.
James had an early call,
and I was just leaving.
- Without breakfast?
- I'm fine, thanks.
I'm Sam, by the way.
Nice to meet you.
It'd be nicer if you'd put this on.
So you and Wilson...
Thought you were staying
in New York last night.
Sorry, must have missed the...
"if this trailer be a-rockin'"
sign out front.
I'm really late, so...
if there's any chance that we can
pretend this never happened,
I'd be completely fine with that.
An eight-year-old
with bleeding ears.
I'll see that and raise you
a total muscular degeneration.
What the hell?
I had a dream like this once.
It didn't end well.
Huzzah, my loyal peasants!
What are you doing?
Filling in for rabbi Shmuhl
at the Goldstein bris.
While I'm busy,
you all can check out the knight
down in the E.R.,
who, instead of seizing the throne,
just seized.
- He works at a renaissance festival?
- Doesn't work there, he lives there
as part of a wonderful
little troupe,
who spend their weekends
reenacting a nobler age,
when people crapped in the streets,
and 13 would have been a grandmother.
Weeks, not weekends. Says here
he's been camping out for a month.
Try doing that with a pen.
Why don't you put that down
before you kill one of us?
Why don't you give me something
I can use so I won't feel the need to?
Seizure right after a fight
obviously suggests concussion.
Obviously it isn't, or the E.R.
wouldn't have called House.
A full set of armor
would protect against visible trauma,
but not transmitted concussive force.
Could be a subdural hematoma.
You're forgetting to demonize.
An evil, satanic subdural hematoma.
Two demon eyes.
Hemorrhaging in the sclerae.
Could be an allergic reaction
to something from the renaissance fair.
Which is why we need to check out.
Foreman, take Frodo
- and break bread with the hobbits.
- A hematoma is more likely.
That's why you and Chase
are gonna get an MRI.
- But you just...
- I said Frodo, not Gollum.
Is he saying I have short legs
or hairy feet?
I don't even know who Frodo is.
Who's the chick,
and why are you hiding her?
You were home last night?
And this morning.
I bumped into your babe, naked.
- I told you to stay out of my bathroom.
- I was in the kitchen.
- She was naked in the kitchen?
- I was naked.
- Why were you naked in the kitchen?
- It's not important.
What is, is why you didn't want me
to meet her in the first place.
Is she married?
A patient?
- I don't have time for this.
- She used to be a man.
She wants to be a man.
It's a man's name,
short for...
Samantha.
The soulless harpy
you were married to before we met.
People change, House.
They get older,
ovaries start drying up,
and nice guys like you
look attractive again.
I know that,
in your own demented way,
you think you're looking out for me.
But I have this.
By this, you mean a sinking feeling
in the pit of the stomach.
Fine.
I get it. It's your life.
You go screw it up. I can wait.
For what?
To tell you, "I told you so".
No signs of hematoma.
Brain looks completely normal.
Normal, except for the fact
that he likes to play dress-up.
My uncle used to pretend
he was king Leopold.
I'm not pretending.
Sorry about that.
You don't really think
you're a knight, do you?
Being a knight isn't a game.
It's a lifestyle, we do it every day,
not just when we play dress-up.
We live by a code and uphold ideals
like loyalty, courage, humility.
And the part where you beat the crap
out of each other in armor?
That we do for fun.
At least it was up until yesterday.
Are we almost done?
'Cause I'm feeling...
Let's get him out of there
before he aspirates.
Anything abnormal on the MRI?
God's teeth,
what strange manner
of garments be these?
We'll be back soon.
He consorts with tiny demons
in his hand.
'Tis witchcraft, I say!
Do I look like I'm here
to play pretend with you?
Relax, it's not personal.
Just tell them you're a time traveler
or something.
If we're gonna be here,
we might enjoy it.
Our knight just vomited
inside the MRI.
Taub thinks
it might be food poisoning...
Which shouldn't be surprising...
Outdoor latrines,
food prep going on
next to livestock.
I hear you wish to speak with me,
concerning sir William.
- How faireth he?
- Not well,
or we wouldn't be here.
- A pox indeed is...
- Miles.
We just thought it was a concussion.
He's gonna be okay, right?
We need to look at the area
he was camping out in.
And you might want to invest
into a dental plan for the kingdom.
You sure he got sick
from something here?
We're not sure
of anything yet, but...
What do you make of this?
Looks like vomit.
Means he was showing symptoms
prior to the fight.
True, but I meant this.
It's a cow eye.
From the night before the tournament.
He makes the knights
eat all kinds of disgusting stuff.
- Why?
- He got the idea from Fear Factor.
Why didn't he mention it?
I make them all take an oath of secrecy
about the ritual.
William tends to take his role
as a knight very seriously.
Do you think
that's what caused him to pass out?
That's not exactly sanitary.
Fun stuff never is.
Serious bacterial
food poisoning explains seizure
and vomiting.
- A lumbar puncture could confirm.
- Except it's not food poisoning.
If it was, the E.R. would look like
Camelot right now.
All it takes is one bad eyeball.
Or testicle,
cow brain, or my personal favorite,
pig rectum, with a side order
of sphincter.
- They call that breakfast in Australia.
- No one else was sick,
- 'cause they weren't allergic like him.
- To what?
That's what I sent you
to Middle Earth to find out.
Run scratch tests
for the samples you brought back.
That's gonna take time,
he's getting worse.
So treat him with epinephrine too.
This should prevent
any more symptoms
until we can figure out
what it is you're allergic to.
Told you you shouldn't have
eaten all that stuff.
You don't have to stay. You and Miles
are crazy busy, with the wedding.
Miles said we could
postpone it until...
Don't worry. I'll be fine.
I'll be there.
I hope you have a good photographer,
the red-eye filter isn't gonna work.
I need your right arm.
That...
feels...
feels strange.
- What is it? What's wrong?
- His heart rate's become irregular.
My chest hurts.
It feels like it's gonna explode.
Tachycardia... We need to shock
him back into rhythm.
I need his gown open.
What is that stuff?
I don't know.
It's not an allergy, or the eppy would
have helped him, not made him worse.
Unless he's allergic
and allergic to the cure.
Sodium bisulfite...
The preservative
that keeps eppy peppy...
Can cause tachycardia.
So can
Wolff-Parkinson-White syndrome,
and it also causes
hemorrhaging in the eyes.
And abnormal electrical
pathways in the heart,
- which could cause seizures.
- But not skin infections.
There is an infection that can cause
skin and neurological damage
and spreads rapidly
without treatment.
Methicillin resistant
staphylococcus aureus?
- Lord have MRSA.
- You weren't wearing gloves
when we shocked his heart
back into rhythm.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
You two get a sample
to the lab to confirm,
you get the knight into isolation
and on I.V. antibiotics.
You... Stay away from me.
Need to talk.
- About the MRSA? I know, we're...
- MRSA, SHMRSA.
Something important.
Something you think is more important
than the potentially lethal bacteria
spreading like wildfire
through my hospital?
That narrows it down
to something personal and stupid.
Theory confirmed.
He is dating his first wife.
I know.
I don't believe it.
That he didn't ask
your permission first?
No, that he's actually capable
of keeping a secret from me.
You'd be surprised how many things
Wilson doesn't tell you.
Would I?
Like how you slept
with your father's best friend or...
- I'm gonna kill him.
- You need to break them up.
- Forget it.
- So you'd rather sit back and watch
while the evil blonde gorges
on Wilson's tender flesh
and then tosses out his bones
like she did the last time?
You remember
what he was like after that?
Yes, I do.
Then do something.
God knows he's not gonna listen to me.
You, on the other hand,
have decades of experience
dating and being attracted to losers.
I don't include myself.
You know what happens when you interfere
in people's relationships?
Of course.
I do it all the time.
- I see your point.
- That is why I'm staying out of this.
You force him to choose,
you might not like the answer.
He doesn't seem to be
in as much pain anymore.
Good, but we won't be
out of the woods for sure
until the blisters start to recede.
I'm really thirsty.
You mind getting me a soda?
Sure, I'll be right back.
What's wrong?
The pain in my chest,
it's getting worse.
Just now?
I didn't want to worry her.
So how long have you been
in love with her?
No, we're just friends.
Seriously.
- Since the first time I saw her.
- Why don't you tell her?
- She's engaged to my friend.
- The king?
Haven't seen him visiting
or sitting by your bedside.
He has responsibilities.
I'm guessing the queen does too.
What kind of knight
steals his friend's bride?
I hate that I even think about it.
You're not a knight.
You're just a guy.
But I want to be more than that.
- Your chest?
- No, my back.
Feels like there's a knife in it.
Is the infection spreading?
It's not MRSA.
It looks like some sort
of clostridial organism.
Question is,
which type of clostridium?
There's hundreds.
C. Perfringens?
Wouldn't account for his other symptoms.
C. Tetani, on the other hand...
Tetanus, he would have been
inoculated against it.
So he cut himself
and didn't get a booster shot.
The guy fights people
with swords for fun.
No one said he's smart.
They don't just fight for fun.
They fight to prove their bravery.
You're buying this honor stuff?
Fighting's not brave.
It just stupid.
You would say that.
- You think I've never been in a fight?
- No, I think you've never won one.
I took on three guys
in college once.
Hope they bought you dinner first.
It's not MRSA.
- I know, it's poison ivy.
- Poison ivy?
A severe reaction
could cause the blisters
and maybe irritate his eyes enough
to cause the hemorrhaging,
but the chest pain and seizures...
They have bonfires every night.
The burning leaves
aerosolizes the oil.
We've seen what it's done
to the outside.
Imagine what it's doing
to his lungs and his sinuses.
Maybe it remotely fits,
but I'd rather go
with scientific evidence
than with your gut.
How about this?
Apparently, it's all over his sword.
- It's his heart rate again.
- How fast is it?
- It's slowing, why aren't you...
- It's not MRSA.
I'm giving him 12 ccs epinephrine.
He tested positive.
You'll blow his heart out!
If it slows any more,
it's gonna stop.
I told you.
And I told you.
That wasn't caused by poison ivy.
Or epinephrine.
The heart problem we ruled out,
we now have to rule back in.
We found clostridium bacteria
in the skin samples.
Clostridium's in dirt
and basically harmless.
But opportunistic,
if his immune system is depressed.
- Leukemia?
- He would have had symptoms way before.
Which is true of anything
that would compromise his immune system,
which means it has to be
some other environmental toxin.
Yesterday he was a healthy knight,
today he's sleeping beauty.
Nothing else fits.
- Trichinosis from eating infected meat?
- We already ruled out food poisoning.
But the butcher shop and the food stands
at the fair were totally clean.
Then he ate the poison apple
somewhere else.
Or maybe you just missed it.
Start treatment for trichinosis
and confirm with a muscle biopsy.
I can't believe
I'm about to say this.
- Sam...
- I told you so.
No, she didn't dump me.
She wants to get to know you better.
Damn it.
- I shouldn't have let her see me naked.
- It goes against all my instincts,
but I said all right.
Why?
She thinks I was hiding her
from you.
- You were.
- I don't want her to know.
You're asking me
to condone a relationship
based on lies and mistrust.
- When and where?
- Tonight, Venezia, 8:00.
What am I gonna wear?
All my cereal boxes are at the cleaners.
House, listen.
I know you're worried about me,
and I also know
that that kind of unselfishness
doesn't come naturally to you.
But I don't want your help.
I don't need your help.
Just come to dinner
and be your usual selfish self.
How could I say no?
- Miles said he'd stop by later.
- No, tell him not to.
I don't want to be seen like this.
You're sick.
That's nothing to be ashamed of...
- Unless you want me to leave.
- No, don't.
I think he's saying
it's different with you, Shannon.
It's a guy thing...
They don't like showing weakness.
Right, William?
Right.
Maybe when I'm feeling
a little better.
I'm gonna take a small sample
of your muscle tissue here.
- Do you mind waiting outside for this?
- Don't hurt him.
He's safe with me.
- I thought you were gonna tell her.
- It's not my call.
But if you ask me,
she's waiting for you to.
Knights are supposed to be selfless.
Right, they conquered countries
and built castles by being selfless.
Bravery and loyalty are great qualities
for soldiers.
If you wanna be king,
sometimes you have to be willing
to take what's yours.
She's not mine.
She's not his either...
Not yet.
It's just dinner. Relax.
Trust me, there is no "just"
when House is involved.
We're in the middle of a restaurant.
What could he possibly...
Do?
That.
Sorry we're late.
But you know girls.
Always fiddling with the hair
and the makeup.
James, Sam... This is Sarah.
It's nice to meet you.
Horace has told me all...
House... has told me all about you.
It's nice to meet you.
What's the diagnosis?
His muscle biopsy is clean.
It's not trichinosis.
House was wrong,
this is not environmental.
Or we screwed up and missed something
at the Renaissance fair.
You think we did?
No, but I think House
will think we did.
What could we have missed?
Fungal infection?
There's nothing in his blood work
even remotely suggesting that.
But it fits the symptoms.
You wanna re-test
every sample we took for spores?
We'll be here all night.
Have you noticed
how much pain he's been in lately?
And that's relevant how?
Extra pain means extra cranky,
it means off his game.
He's not gonna accept
this isn't environmental
unless we give him no choice.
I can't believe
you're from Bloomington.
I know, isn't it amazing?
Delightful.
Ignore him.
He's just upset that we're having fun.
Do you remember that little bakery?
- The one with the amazing cupcakes?
- Gino's.
First stop, every time I go home.
Me too...
- Remember that strip club?
- I used to work at that strip club.
- Where does it hurt, William?
- My legs! Feels like they're on fire!
Rhabdomyolysis means
his kidneys are failing.
Also means it's not environmental.
We need to move on.
- I recommend a full cancer workup...
- Who checked out the apartment?
- His symptoms fit an environmental...
- The test results don't, we redid...
Search the apartment.
- He hasn't been there in three weeks...
- Go! Now!
I liked him better
when he was on Vicodin.
You and thirteen check out his place.
We'll ultrasound the liver.
If it's cancer,
it's as good a place as any to start.
I hear House met Sam.
First time, he was naked.
The second time he brought
a transvestite prostitute to dinner.
Overall, it could have been worse.
Great.
That's your reaction?
Nudity, prostitute...
Sorry, preoccupied.
House said something to you,
didn't he?
He didn't.
It is a little crazy, though.
I mean... Isn't it?
Things seem to be going great.
But they did, too, 12 years ago.
The good things are still good.
She's still smart, funny, gets me.
And she's less competitive.
Either she's changed, or I've changed.
But, either way...
Am I out of my mind?
You never know what can happen.
You might as well give it a chance.
You were right.
Tumors...
Dozens of them.
Inside, and on the surface.
Pull in closer.
See that?
What is that?
I don't know.
But it's definitely not cancer.
Kitchen's clean.
Bedroom as well.
Most dangerous thing in his cabinet
was dental floss.
It's locked, key wasn't on his ring.
You wanna go back and tell House
we didn't check every square inch?
Of course not.
My hero.
What the hell is this?
Either a secret entrance to Hogwarts,
or...
Our knight...
is a witch.
Our knight is into
some seriously creepy stuff.
He claims it's just sugar water
but we sent the rest for testing.
You think he poisoned himself?
We would have picked it up
in his blood work.
Not if it collected
slowly in his liver
and it all started leaking
into his system at once.
These tumors that aren't tumors,
what if they're focal hepatic lesions
filled with blood?
Every time one explodes
it'd be releasing another dose.
Of what?
Plumbum nigrum.
- You putting a hex on someone?
- It's Latin, for black lead.
Our knight/warlock
apparently also dabbles in alchemy.
Lead poisoning.
Seizures, paralysis,
weak immune system,
and eventually, coma.
Biopsy the cysts,
and you'll find your lead.
You think we'll make the 7:30?
If I don't change, I'm gonna feel like
I'm at work all night.
- I remember.
- Is it a problem?
Not at all.
In fact,
if we hurry...
We will definitely
not make the 7:30.
There's always the 9:40.
Or not.
Shouldn't you be at the hospital?
Wouldn't need a team
if I did all the work.
- Plus, I had to make you dinner.
- We have plans.
I bet your plans
don't taste like this.
Don't!
- Whatever it is that you're up to...
- I'm trying to be nice.
What I did the other night
was juvenile, I'm sorry.
- The soufflé was amazing.
- It's my mom's recipe.
Everything else, I got off the web.
Here's to the Internet.
Where I found the lamb ragout,
and you two found each other...
Again.
It wasn't just the Internet.
More like divorce, depression,
therapy, more therapy,
and the Internet.
And here we are.
Exactly. And here we are.
- I need to go to the bathroom.
- You're old enough, now.
But if you want me to gowith you...
Is it safe to leave the two of you?
Come on, James. Enough, already.
I cook in peace.
I'll be right back.
You're a cold-hearted bitch,
who ripped his heart out.
I watched him struggle for years
to overcome the damage you did.
No way I'm gonna let you
wheel him back in so you can do it
all over again.
And all this?
Phase two
of getting to know my enemy.
You're wrong about me.
But I'm glad now
I don't have to pretend to like you,
except for when James
is standing next to me.
Same here.
Only difference is,
I'll outlast you.
And scene.
Well, it's too late for the movie.
- Wanna see what's on TV?
- Absolutely.
Love to.
There wasn't any lead in his blood work
or liver biopsy.
And his heart rate and BP
are getting even more erratic.
We had to shock it back into rhythm
twice during the night.
There's only one thing left to do.
We're wasting our time.
Actually,
I've already gotten good value.
Nothing here could have caused
any of his symptoms.
You couldn't find anything here
that could be causing the symptoms.
We're gonna find something new
because we're in costume?
We looked everywhere,
tested everything.
Just because Wilson's acting stupid
doesn't mean we are.
Do you think he's making a mistake?
Of course.
He'll figure it out,
sooner or later.
Hopefully after weeks of great sex.
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
Wilson's not like us.
He cares too much about people
and their feelings.
Thanks.
The code that our knight
claims to live by,
all that crap
about honor and chivalry.
Wilson's naturally like that,
which is why he's...
A great guy.
A sucker and a target.
So we gotta look out for him.
Do you smell that?
It's the apothecary shop.
And yes, Foreman and I already...
I cry your pardon, sir.
- You know what this is?
- That's lavender.
Try rose hips.
Both harmless, who cares?
It could be cyanide
as far as he knows.
- How about this?
- It be nothing but St. John's wort.
Wrong again. Black cohash.
My uncle owns the shop,
I just started apprenticing.
What's the big deal?
I just organized all that.
- You know what this is?
- A wild carrot?
It's hemlock,
you embossed carbuncle.
- That's hemlock? You sure?
- Did you sell it to anyone?
It's poison, think hard.
It was just one branch.
You sold it to sir William?
To the king.
It's the only part of the environment
you didn't check.
The people living in it.
What's going on?
Why can't we see William?
Because you poisoned him.
Your royal anus.
With this.
- Wild carrots?
- Hemlock.
I need to know how much you used
and how you prepared it.
- You did something to William?
- Of course not!
He's still alive.
You want to avoid a murder charge,
start talking fast.
The apothecary's willing to testify
that you're the only one he gave it to.
I bought it for the food challenge,
but I didn't know that was hemlock.
If it was for the challenge,
then why is Wee Willie
the only knight who's dying?
I don't know!
I didn't know!
Why would I want to hurt William?
I can think of at least one reason.
Miles, please.
Whatever happened,
just tell them the truth.
I am!
I swear.
We ran a gas chromatography
on his blood.
Found trace amounts
of piperidine alkaloids.
Markers of hemlock intoxication.
The good news is
we now know what's wrong with you.
The bad news is
that your king's precious ideals
were just pretend after all.
When it comes to guys
who get too close to his queen.
It's not true.
You've never heard the expression,
"gas chromatography machines don't lie".
Neither does Miles.
He's the best knight
I've ever known.
It's why he was chosen king.
Miles is a jealous idiot.
And you're just an idiot.
Something's wrong.
We performed a gastric lavage
and administered activated charcoal,
but he's getting worse, not better.
It's been in his system two days.
We're lucky he's lasted this long.
If it was hemlock, he'd be dead
or getting better.
We found it in his blood.
He may have had some,
but it's not what's killing him.
Don't do it!
Whatever you're planning,
especially if you're using that.
Geez.
It was just sitting in a stone.
Here.
It's gonna cost extra, because
of the level of detail you wanted.
Anything good?
And by good, I, of course, mean bad.
Typical life.
Married young, got divorced.
Married a little less young,
got divorced.
She's been pretty successful,
except marriage.
- There's gotta be something I can use.
- Maybe.
Didn't read her shrink's notes.
Didn't seem right.
But stealing them did.
I didn't steal them,
I found a way to obtain them.
Excuse me,
I don't mean to interrupt,
but you got a minute?
Sure.
Oh, him? Yeah, I was just leaving.
Careful.
I have a sword.
I don't agree with what you said.
But I understand why you said it.
We were married young,
we both made mistakes,
and yes, I did make most of them.
But that was almost a decade ago.
I'm sorry, is that the statutory period
for soul sucking?
I'm not asking you
to like me, House.
To be honest, I think you're an ass.
But we do have one thing in common.
We care about James.
So prove it. And dump him... again.
You're insufferable all the time,
aren't you?
Sorry, go on. And, yes.
We just reconnected, we have no idea
where we're headed.
But is it really too much to ask
that you gave us a chance
to find out?
I'm sure I'll be seeing you around.
We did it.
Well, I did it.
What did we do?
You do?
These aren't focal hepatic lesions,
they're peliosis hepitus lesions.
Which in combination
with an erratic heart rate,
- usually indicates...
- Endocarditis.
Infection on his heart valve.
Two major symptoms
of anabolic steroid abuse.
- No, he wouldn't.
- And the rhabdo makes the third.
Our patient's a juicer.
Ancient poison accelerated the damage
of the modern poison.
Start treatment,
let the king out of the tower.
How are you feeling?
Ashamed.
You should be.
You'll compromise your ideals
to win a fight,
but not to go
for the woman you love.
That was a game.
Not real life.
- I didn't...
- Hurt anyone?
Try telling that to Shannon.
Or maybe I missed something
while she was crying by your bed.
You don't need to win
anyone's heart.
You just need to ask for it.
Miles is a great guy.
He's rich, smart, treats her well.
She's gonna have
a great life with him.
But me?
I'd do everything I could for her,
but even at my best, it wouldn't be much
and she deserves the best.
I guess I'd rather she be happy
even if it means I'm not.
I guess House was right about that,
too.
What?
You really are an idiot.
Original: www.sous-titres.eu WEB-DL Sync: Lalitavatie
Resync DIMENSION for Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net