[Audience cheers]
(Announcer)
Let's hear it for Della Carr.
Dude, your sister
kicks serious ass.
Competed in the boy's
league this year.
Kicked their asses too.
Nice job, Del.
You--
I went faster on the 50-50.
You were right.
All right,
who wants next?
Yeah, yeah,
I'm a little biased.
[Laughter]
Whoo!
Whoa!
(Woman)
Custom decks.
Start the bidding
at 400 bucks.
Trust me, the kids'll
force their parents to buy them.
You got to see this.
You made a great
event today, hon.
Fast enough for you?
I'm already
in a wheelchair.
What are you so afraid of?
That wasn't what I meant.
Della?
You okay?
Mom! Dad!
♪ House 7x02 ♪
Selfish
Original Air Date on September 27, 2010
[Massive Attack's ♪ Teardrop ♪]
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
We got to stop
parking like this.
People are gonna talk.
Well, that's why I plan
on doing some talking first.
I want us to formerly
report our relationship
to Human Resources.
Okay. You get them,
I'll cover everybody else.
I would appreciate it
if we could keep it quiet
until we had that meeting.
It's gonna be hard with me
grabbing your ass all day.
Grabbing stops
at the threshold.
Of the parking garage.
Handicapped plates.
I got special access.
I just don't want our
relationship affecting our jobs.
Or the other way around.
Why, Dr. Cuddy,
how was your weekend?
I got a call
about a case for you.
14-year-old.
EMTs think
her heart stopped--
sounds great.
You haven't seen it yet.
I sense something
fascinating about it.
I'm gonna get us in
to see HR this afternoon.
Think you can hold
your tongue till then?
Mom...
Fine.
People are gonna know
soon enough.
I think I can hold it
till lunch.
[Whistles]
I'm seeing Cuddy.
Generally,
without her clothes on.
Use your imagination.
Hope it's got
a wide-angle lens.
You don't actually need that.
I'm gonna check my office
for whoopee cushions.
This is not a prank.
This is not me
walking out the door.
Really?
You and Cuddy?
For reals.
Foreman can translate.
So junior miss everything--
skateboarder,
basketballer,
I'm actually guessing
with that last one.
Healthy one day,
heart arrhythmia the next.
Are you sure
it a good idea
to be yanking
on the chain of command?
Way to go, House.
I'm surprised you two
didn't get together sooner.
EKG, echo and head CT
are all spotless.
There's nothing on
her neurological exam.
(House)
Interesting.
In favor, indignant,
indifferent.
Think I'd like
a female perspective.
Or Thirteen's. Where is she?
She's gone.
(Foreman)
She said she was taking
a leave of absence.
Wanted us to think it was for
a Huntington's study in Rome.
They've never heard of her.
Cell and home phone
are disconnected.
Apartment's already
been vacated.
And what's with
the death's head cane?
They didn't have
a death's ass cane in my size.
Well, I guess
we'll just have to wait.
Conditions that cause
intermittent heart arrhythmias.
Taub.
Three years, you've been
trying to game out Thirteen,
and now you don't care?
Sorry.
Not caring about Thirteen
is not part of the differential
for heart arrhythmia,
but you do get
a home version of the game.
Patient's brother has severe,
congenital
muscular dystrophy.
Life expectancy
of about 25.
If she's had
a latent case of it...
Wouldn't be sudden onset.
Foreman.
Do you know something
about Thirteen that we don't?
She's entitled
to her privacy.
Just as I'm entitled
to a diagnosis.
And you're glossing over
Thirteen's departure
because you actually respect
somebody's privacy?
I agree. It's weird of me
not to care.
So either I'm a changed man
because of Cuddy,
or I'm pretending
to be a changed man
because I do know something
about Thirteen
and I'm trying
to throw you off the scent,
or I've just gone nutty bananas
because I lost a patient.
All of which
you are free to discuss
after I get a diagnosis.
If it's Long QT Syndrome,
any startling stimulus
in that skate park
could have triggered
the arrhythmia.
Loud noise,
flashing lights.
Scare the patient to death
to confirm Long QT.
Fine.
If you insist,
do it in a room with one
of those thingamabobs
that brings people
back to life.
Scare test is insane.
Scare test is legitimate.
Simulates real world
conditions.
This fling with Cuddy
is insane.
Flare gun?
Scary enough?
How about just telling her
we're planning this stupid test?
And I'm hoping House and Cuddy
are more than just a fling.
It's clearly
mellowed him out.
He didn't even care
about Thirteen.
Right.
The guy who ordered us
to stop the patient's heart
has mellowed out.
It's gonna be horrible
because it's doomed,
which is just
gonna make House
50 times more
of a crank.
Firecrackers.
We can hide 'em under one
of those covered food trays.
Find any itching powder
in your hanky?
Any fake poo
in your desk drawer?
Yes, the lack
of dime-store pranks
is proof that you're
actually dating Cuddy,
and not just mocking me
for being worried
about you.
What do I have to do
to prove this to you?
Tattoo a cane
on her inner thigh?
Tattoo her inner thigh
on my cane?
You told everybody,
didn't you?
Repeatedly.
This one's not buying it.
Need a little help.
I'm not selling it.
It's time for our meeting
at Human Resources.
Hmm.
Human Resources.
Now, why would I need
to go to Human Resources?
House, you've been
to Human Resources
74 times
in the last six weeks.
Never after doing this.
Well, I'm convinced.
Come on.
One peck.
Just enough
to arouse him a little.
I--hey, I'm not even...
I didn't mean you.
If I confirm it,
can we leave?
Yes.
It's true.
I've been more passionate
with my great aunt.
Mabel? Up high.
We done here?
She didn't even
ask me to cough.
Think you straightened out
my limp a little.
How would you describe
the exact nature
of the relationship?
You ever see
Wild Kingdom?
Those insects that rip
their partner's heads off
after copulating?
It's a sexual
relationship.
Go slowly now.
He's writing it down.
I believe
that I can still
supervise Dr. House
effectively,
but we both want
to follow hospital policy
to the letter.
Our concern
is to make sure
that there's no
conflict of interest,
no liability
for the hospital.
You think we're gonna sue
if things go South?
Let me tell you.
She actually does go--
House.
Let him talk.
I, uh, know that
you're not going to sue,
because you are both
going to sign love contracts.
Consensual relationship
agreements.
Well, obviously
outside council
will have to review
the crotchless undies clause.
Uh, we'll also need to watch
for any favoritism
toward Dr. House.
Does that mean she has
to sleep with everyone?
I promise not to give him
a raise or a promotion
of any kind.
There's got to be
a joke there
about keeping up
with inflation.
Or bias against him.
Are there any
supervisory issues
with Dr. House's
current case load?
No, her case is solved.
Patient has Long QT.
Gonna scare her into
cardiac arrest to confirm it.
No, we're not.
Okay, no, we're not.
See?
Everything's under control.
I know you're still planning
your ridiculous scare test.
The patient is nowhere
near sick enough
to justify the risk.
An angiogram
and an E.P. study
are much safer
and very effective.
Fair point.
Not doing the scare test.
I'd invite you to watch me
not doing the test,
but having not done it
many times before,
trust me, it's pretty
not interesting.
[Phone beeps, dials]
(Taub)
House?
Scare test
was not approved.
Do an angio and
E.P. study instead.
First of all, that's not
as effective as--
how come you're not doing
the more specialized test?
This test is virtually
just as effective.
And Dr. House puts
a premium on patient safety.
But frequently
changes his mind.
Hugo, give him a break.
I'm fine.
You should go to the bathroom
before we go.
We've been hydrating you
for quite a while.
I don't have to pee.
Once we start the test,
you won't be able to move
for at least an hour.
I really don't have to pee.
How much fluid
have we given her?
2.5 liters.
When's the last time
you went to the bathroom?
Last night, I guess.
What does that mean?
Your daughter's kidneys
seem to be failing.
So what could cause
her heart to stop
and her urine not to drop?
House, I was expecting
your relationship with Cuddy
to complicate our work
long-term.
I am now concerned it might
be affecting us short-term.
All due respect.
None taken.
I listen to Cuddy
all the time.
She's my boss.
Also yours, by the way.
You'd listen, then tell her
she's being an idiot,
and do whatever you want.
I find I can skip
the idiot part
when she's not
being an idiot,
and since the scare test
would have led
to the same dead end,
she was right to stop it.
Which means
your problem's about you.
This should be interesting.
Losers love company.
And if even
a misanthrope like me
has a chance at happiness,
it's gonna be pretty lonely
on that landfill
of loserdom
you call a mriage.
Heart, kidneys, go.
Could be fabry disease.
Lipid deposition
in her tissues.
Dad's history was clean.
What about
protein deposits?
They wouldn't show
in her parents' history.
Amyloidosis.
Explains both
the symptoms.
Marrow transplant
to treat.
Brother's a match.
Confirm and do.
I been
experiencing fatigue,
and--and weakness.
Wouldn't have anything
to do with the fact
that you're...
102 years old.
Usually
he's strong as an ox.
102-year-old ox.
He has tingling
in his feet and his legs.
I want a full battery
of tests.
Carbon dating?
I'll pay cash
if it's not covered.
That's nice of you
to float your friend.
He's not my friend.
He's my father.
He's 22 years
older than me.
Well, that's true, he's
definitely had his jowls done.
Statistically, if he didn't
have these symptoms,
he'd be like most
people of his age--
dead for the past
several decades.
Do the tests.
I'm sick.
You have a bad case
of natural causes.
Do the damn tests.
If the vial
fills with sand,
we take that as a bad sign.
Hugo should be here.
Why'd you ask him to leave?
We wanted to be able
to discuss this openly.
But it obviously affects him.
Honey,
let the doctor finish.
It's a standard procedure.
We use general anesthesia,
harvest a very small
amount of--
no. I'm not taking
my brother's marrow.
Del, it's--
these harvests
are harmless.
With the meds we give,
there's almost no pain,
almost no risk of infection.
Almost?
His life's hard enough
as it is.
(Taub)
Small problem
with the treatment.
Patient won't take marrow
from steel wheels?
We're finding
another match.
And how do you know?
What other problem
could there be
with a problem-free
procedure?
Boy's sports,
science club,
she's living his life,
not hers.
Makes sense she's being
a self-denying moron.
She loves her brother.
She's thinking
selflessly.
How is that at all--
being moronic?
Mm.
If I can only think
of a harm-free
medical treatment
she turned down lately.
You're right.
If everyone
were more selfish,
the world would be
a better place.
See? I can skip
the idiot part
when you're not
being an idiot.
Yeah, I had that
same facial expression
for the first 48 hours.
Had another one too,
but only for
15 seconds at a time.
I'm happy for you.
You're happy for you.
This is huge.
So who's gonna
supervise you?
Cuddy.
Well, I guess
maybe that can work.
Maybe?
Nothing's changed.
You showed up for clinic hours.
Voluntarily.
Fine.
A little bit has changed.
House,
everything's changed.
You're sleeping together.
You want something from her
besides a sign-off on scaring
your patient to death.
You talked to Taub.
He's worried about you.
He's a jerk.
I'm worried too.
Do I need to say it?
I want this to work.
I'm not doing
anything differently.
She changed my mind
about one diagnostic test.
And she was right.
Even though it's your
emotional default,
stop worrying.
I can handle it.
I hear you're a pretty
fierce skateboarder.
I do okay.
All your activities,
don't they seem like things
a 16-year-old boy
would do?
Some people might think
you're trying to live
his life for him.
I am. Sort of.
Um,
I got into skateboarding
when some of Hugo's
classmates did,
and he realized
he could never do it.
It's the same
with a lot of things.
We live through it
together.
And you're not worried
you're being selfless
to the point
of self-denial?
You've never been
inspired by someone?
Why don't you
take your pills?
[Coughs, gasps]
Need some help in here.
Hemothorax.
We need to bronch her now.
Clear an O.R.
She's drowning
in her own blood.
It's not amyloidosis.
She's bleeding to death.
Out of her lung.
I want to fill
a quarter of it with foam.
That'd stop the bleeding,
all right.
Thought it made more sense
than diet and exercise.
And if she doesn't have
enough lung function left,
you'll have killed her.
The only alternative
is slowly suturing the lung,
hoping that the bleeding
stops in time
and she doesn't die
on her own.
But we would walk away
with clean hands.
Except for all the blood.
You're right.
Faster and riskier's better.
Foam the lung.
Got a green light?
No.
Suture the lung.
Scalpel,
rib spreader.
I can't handle it.
What happened?
She said "yes,"
and I heard "no."
I didn't actually
hear "no."
But I just...Was sure
that's what she meant.
Way she tilted her head
and half-arched her eyebrow.
What do I even care
what she meant?
She said yes.
That's all that matters.
I'm screwing this up.
It's not completely bad,
House.
You care enough
to pull your punches.
That's not a bad thing.
But you and Cuddy
have got to figure out a way
of avoiding this problem.
Set some ground rules.
Yeah.
I have to avoid
this problem.
If I can restrict
our interactions
to places where neither of us
are wearing pants...
Yeah, that's not
avoiding the problem,
that's avoiding the issue.
Since avoidance is my plan
for dealing with the issue,
technically,
that's not avoiding it.
Thanks.
No problem.
[Door closes]
Stitching worked.
This time.
No guarantee bowing to Cuddy
will work next time.
Heart arrhythmia,
kidney failure,
and now bleeding lung.
I don't want to criticize
your girlfriend, but--
hey, you've been on me
for years
to respect someone's opinion.
Just 'cause I had
to go outside this group
to find one I respect.
Multi-system involvement
centered in the lung.
Sarcoidosis?
Doesn't explain
the hemothorax.
Tb can affect
all three organs.
Skin test was negative.
What about
goodpasture's?
Affects the lungs,
kidneys.
And autoimmune explains
the out of the blue arrhythmia.
Goodpasture's it is.
Immunosuppressants and
plasmapheresis to treat,
kidney biopsy to confirm.
[Announcements over P.A.]
Dr. House.
Don't tell me, your father's
hairline is receding,
and he needs more tests.
He's 102.
His next test is an autopsy.
Look,
I love the old man,
but I got to get him
out of the damn House.
He can't do anything
without me.
He needs to be
in a care facility.
Well, so tell him.
He's a big boy now.
I can't.
I'm his whole life.
But if it comes
from a doctor...
That's very generous.
When you were 30.
Pretend to run the tests,
and then tell him...
He can't live with me
anymore.
I didn't run into you
all afternoon.
I missed you.
Busy day.
Maybe we should
plan on lunch tomorrow.
Problem is, at lunch
you tend to wear tops.
This is much better.
[Phone rings]
Cuddy and I are naked.
So I'm having
trouble focusing.
Use small words.
Kidney bioy was clean,
so we rechecked the piece
of her lung from the O.R.
You lost me.
Sorry, who is this
calling again?
It's not goodpasture's.
There's intimal thickening
of the blood vessels.
And lymphocytic infiltrate.
We tested for lam.
It's positive.
Plus her lung's fried.
She needs
a donor lung to live,
which is the only treatment
for lam, anyway.
Taub's gone to
the transplant committee.
They may have found
a donor lung.
So this call
is purely expositional.
[Shuts cell phone]
I should really
get dressed.
I told the nanny
I'd be home by 9:00.
And I slipped
the nanny 40 bucks,
told her to stay
till 10:00.
Really?
Mm-hmm, really.
Good news.
(Foreman)
Surgery was uneventful,
but the donor lung
started failing
about an hour
into recovery.
We know we're right
about lam.
Tests confirmed it.
That leaves us
with two options.
Body's rejecting
the new lung
or we should have
rejected the new lung
because it's infected.
Let's biopsy,
see which one it is.
No guarantee
we'd hit
the affected spot.
If we give steroids
for rejection,
it'd make
an infection worse.
If we give antibiotics
for infection,
it'd make rejection worse.
Which worse is worse?
If we treat for infection
and we're wrong,
she'll be dead
within hours.
And if we treat for
rejection and we're wrong?
She'll probably hang on
a day or two.
You're assuming
her rejection's hyperacute.
Odds are, it isn't.
Gotta head off
the worst worse first.
I studied under
Dr. Seuss.
Start with iv methylprednisolone
for hyperacute rejection.
If that fails, we'll switch her
to broad-spectrum antibiotics
and hope we're not
too late.
Cat got your legs?
We just decided
to give meds
that could kill the patient
based on a guess.
You need approval from Cuddy,
and she'll want to take
the safer course,
and you're gonna fold
like an origami crane, so...
I'll just wait here
till we get our actual orders.
Fine. You do it.
Tell her
she's being an idiot
for always choosing
the safer course.
She's sitting on her ample,
if well-formed, bureaucratic ass
while our patient's dying.
We'll see who folds
like an origami shrimp.
You want me to get
Cuddy's approval?
I gotta be somewhere
important.
Sitting at your desk?
I'm running late.
Forget the tests.
I think junior might have
a few words to say about that.
I love him,
but he can't let go.
40 bucks says he can.
I can't do anything
without him helping me
like I'm senile.
If I go back there,
I'm gonna rip his throat out.
You sure you won't warm up
to him over time?
Skip the blood work.
Tell my son it's grim news.
I need to be
in a nursing home.
A private room.
Make it a suite.
Be our little secret.
I sit around
on my bureaucratic ass?
I was relaying
your words.
I said well-formed.
I said well-formed!
What were you--
I needed to be aggressive.
You're an idiot.
She was siding
with Foreman's analysis.
The odds are against it
being hyperacute rejection.
Stop.
I agree with you.
That was our analysis
from the start.
If you've got a problem
with a team decision,
you come to me.
I'm sorry.
I-I'll deal with him later.
I said well-formed.
People who have not
seen Cuddy naked
should not throw stones.
She does have
great cans.
Cuddy has House
on such a short leash,
she might as well start
giving him chew toys.
Let's give the antibiotics
at least another hour.
Amazing. And House hasn't
given you one ounce of grief
for your complete lack
of interest in his love life?
Did it ever occur to you
that House is just happy
and could give a crap
about other people's lives
because of it?
Well, that's ironic
and depressing.
And by that logic,
the reason
you don't give a crap
is because you're happy,
which means
you've got someone new
giving you chew toys.
You're 1/4th right.
Wait.
Are you saying...
[pagers beep]
You're dating
four women?
(Chase)
BP's dropping.
Means the antibiotics
aren't working.
Put her in trendelenburg.
Can you save the lung?
Believe it or not,
we got a better chance now.
This means rejection,
not infection.
Start her on iv
methylprednisolone right away.
[Machine beeping]
Wow.
You hate salad.
She's really got you
tied up in knots.
I caved.
Through an intermediary.
I need a plan "C."
What you need is a plan
that you actually develop
with Cuddy.
Antibiotics didn't work
and then steroids didn't work.
The new lung's ruined,
and it's not rejection
or infection.
The only two options
were wrong.
Unless it's not lam.
It is lam.
The tests were positive.
Then the tests
have to be wrong.
Deep-fryer's working again.
Still working on that?
No, it was here
when I sat down.
I need to think.
I want to make sure
you're trying everything
to save my sister.
Everything?
Well, that must be it.
See, I thought you guys
checked the box marked,
"try every other thing."
I'm the one that's
supposed to die first.
I'm the damaged one,
not her.
She never even gets
a cold.
Damage has a way of spreading
to everyone around you.
For example,
your obvious emotional damage
is now making me have
a philosophical conversation
instead of dealing with
your sister.
See how that might be
damaging?
Never?
When was the last time
you had a cold?
Any minor aches,
swelling, anything?
[Mutters]
It's been years.
She never gets colds.
I didn't ask when's
the last time she mentioned it.
I asked when she had one--
even a tiny one.
It's nothing.
Sometimes my ears
ache a little.
So now tell me
the rest of the nothing.
M-my chest...
Soreness.
Some congestion.
You never said anything
about that.
I barely noticed it
until that skateboarding
tournament in Denver.
How long ago?
A...Year?
Cold's nothing
when I think of
what Hugo
goes through every day.
Yeah, we get it.
Your brother, the Saint.
His sister, the martyr.
Thank God you followed me.
Now you can go back
to the transplant committee
while I get confirmation.
Confirmation of what?
What causes low-level
cold symptoms for a year,
can ruin two lungs,
is immune to drug therapies,
and gets worse in cities
nicknamed mile-high?
A clotting disorder?
She has a nasty case
of sickle cell trait.
Her heart arrhythmia
wasn't sudden at all.
Screwed-up blood cells
screwed up the blood vessels
which gave us a screwed-up
positive for lam.
If she'd told us about
her symptoms sooner--like ever--
she might not be dying.
You were right after all.
I never said sickle--
if everyone
were more selfish,
the world would be
a better place.
So she's gonna die.
Unless we can find--
she burned through
one donor lung.
Transplant committee's never
gonna give her a second one.
Well, then I guess
you're right again.
Unless we don't need
their approval.
You can't advise
your patient's parents
to take marrow and half a lung
from their son!
I guess I can just chat
with them about the weather.
Blood tests just confirmed
sickle cell trait.
So they might be curious
about the only treatment option.
Though we are having
weird weather lately.
There is a huge reason
not to take lungs
from living patients.
So their siblings can die?
Their son has cmd.
As it is, he's gonna die
of respiratory failure by 25.
We could cut whatever time
he has left in half.
That qualifies as a bad reason
for them to reject the idea.
It's a much worse reason
for them not to get the choice.
It's coercive to tell them!
You ever hear of
"do no harm"?
That was second year, right?
'Cause I had mono
all that fall.
Their son's
not even our patient.
Why don't we just
take half a lung
from some guy in the clinic
with a toothache?
That's a great idea.
Now we can give
the parents two options.
We don't compromise
one life for another.
Okay.
Okay?
Seriously.
You made an argument.
If you don't want me
to defer to you,
why make it at all?
But are you
deferring to me
just because
we're seeing each other?
Maybe.
Yeah. I think so.
This is screwing me up.
Why is it not
screwing you up?
It is.
I don't know why
I okayed you foaming that lung.
I realized it was wrong
as soon as I said it.
I knew it!
I knew 'cause you
tilted your head.
House...We are
screwing this up.
I'm gonna call HR,
find someone else to supervise
you as soon as I can.
I've got your...
Test results.
You have the metabolism,
blood counts,
liver and kidney function
of a 92-year-old.
Which is great,
'cause you're 102.
What's not so great
is the average
life expectancy is 78.
It is my recommendation
that you move into a home
with round-the-clock care.
Oh...
I can't believe it!
Can't my son give me
round-the-clock care?
Not unless you've done
your two-year certification
in tiburon swab technology.
There must be
some other way.
Just because he has
a little tingling
and some trouble feeling
hot and cold
and some difficulty--
you can't feel hot and cold?
Not lately.
But at my age...
Show me your teeth.
Dentures.
Fairly worn.
I'm guessing ten years old.
Show me your denture cream.
Why would he carry
denture cream?
Because...
He has...
Zinc poisoning.
But to get it
from denture cream,
he'd have to take
so much of it--
trust me, he never
leaves home without it.
How much do you use, pop?
About a tube a day.
I buy it online.
So what does this mean?
Bizarrely, it explains
all your symptoms.
Better-fitting dentures,
you'll be fine.
Medically, there's no reason
to go anywhere.
Hospital rebate.
You might wanna...
Put it towards
couples therapy.
[Men mumbling together]
The transplant
committee's...
Never gonna give my daughter
another lung, are they?
No.
Are there
any other options?
We're looking into it.
Looking into what?
Please.
Tell me.
Give me some kind of hope.
I'm afraid
I can't do that.
We're talking about
my daughter's life.
What can't you tell me?
If there's any...Chance
you can save her,
anything you can try...
We can take marrow
and half a lung from your son.
It would likely shorten
his life significantly.
He'd never be able to go
on a respirator if he needed to.
Most people with cmd need to
as their respiratory
function declines.
How long...
Do we have to decide?
Morning at the latest.
Thank you.
[Conversation not audible
under somber music]
♪ ♪
Where are my parents?
They're probably dealing with
committee issues or something.
They were arguing.
I saw my mom crying.
Looked like my dad
was yelling at her.
They care about you
a lot.
Hugo was a marrow match?
We're way past that now.
They want a lung
from him too.
Is that what
this is about?
No. It's nothing
you need to worry about.
Everybody's working on getting
you the best care possible.
How do they expect us
to go on from here?
We make a choice...
And we live with it.
[Sobs]
There's no living
with it.
No matter what
we decide.
[Running footsteps]
[Blowing breaths]
Still cold and clammy.
She had a respiratory arrest.
Oh, my God!
(Father)
What is she doing
here?
She figured out
what was going on.
She's pinking up.
She must have yanked off
her ivs and oxygen.
Came here to die.
(Taub)
By unhooking herself
from everything,
she delivered a hypoxic
insult to her body
that started
a downward spiral.
(Foreman)
If you're gonna make
a decision,
you're running out of time.
Hr can't find you
a new supervisor.
How come?
Because you're
unsupervisable, House.
Two department chairs
threatened to quit.
Well, I guess
we're stuck with each other.
I have no idea why
I'm making this call
or if it's
the right call to make.
But if you feel strongly
about presenting the parents
your treatment option,
you can do it.
Thank you, I will.
Several hours ago.
You told them?
I told him.
He came to my office.
I'm sorry.
Well...I should probably
be more mad at you.
Yeah.
Dr. House?
We've decided.
We're not gonna take
the lung from my son.
She's still
on the waiting list.
We're gonna do whatever
we can do find her another--
what ginormous crack pipe
have you people
been sucking on?
House!
Are you gonna pretend
that you're not choosing
your own daughter's death?
Our daughter
doesn't want it.
Probably doesn't wanna
floss her teeth either.
She's a mindless
teenybopper.
Don't put this on them.
What do you mean, put it on?
It is on them!
As much as they may
wanna pass the lung here!
Of course they do!
You're handing them
an impossible choice.
Life has handed them
a crappy choice,
and they're picking
the crappier option--
trading who knows how many
healthy decades
for four or five years in which
roller boy will be a limp rag.
Not everything is a math equation.
Do you need me
to explain the difference
between decade and year?
Their son
is a human being.
You know what they are,
right?
Intrinsic value.
We don't get to decide--
and we do it every day.
If the two of them needed
the same lung--
he needs to keep the one he's got.
You don't get to play God
by ripping out--
that train left the station when
we learned to do transplants.
The rest is just
paper-pushing.
Of course, now we're on to your
real area of expertise.
Oh, I thought we were
moving on to yours--
bullying your patients
into embracing your own
lack of a moral--
(mother)
Hugo. Honey.
We didn't mean for you
to hear any of this.
Hugo, please!
I want you to take
half my lung.
No.
I'm not.
You do so many
great things.
I just watch.
I get to watch
and coach and cheer.
But that's not me out there.
It never will be.
If you take
this piece of me,
carry it with you...
Then I really can share
in everything you do.
This is the great thing
I can do with my life.
Don't make me
live without you.
[All crying]
We got lucky.
I did give them
an impossible choice.
The kid took it
away from them.
That fight...
Was the first
honest interaction
you and I have had
since we came back to work.
If we are painfully,
brutally honest with each other,
maybe we'll get lucky
again.
You've got a big ass.
[Elevator Bell dings]
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net