They have a cure
for that, you know?
It's called a computer.
We done for the day,
or do I need to find
something else to read?
I'm done.
It's done.
No way. It's finished?
Well, how--how's it end?
I mean, you got to let me read it.
Not this time.
W--you at least got to
tell me what happens.
Come on.
How am I supposed to help with
the next book if you don't--
there isn't going
to be a next book.
You can't be serious. Why?
You wouldn't understand.
Try me.
I just can't do it anymore.
I'm not brave like you.
But writing' your whole life.
What are you gonna do without it?
What I should have done years ago.
What are you doing?
Put it down, or I'll--
I'll make you.
How, Jack?
You don't even exist.
I'm sorry.
Miss Tanner.
Oh, dear God.
Which of these says "I want
to sleep with you" more?
Penguin or beaver?
Beaver. Beaver. Beaver.
You're right. It's too high school.
What did you do to piss Cuddy off?
I can't be romantic?
House, you're stealing
from a woman in a coma.
We're fine. Never seen her happier.
Yeah? How about you?
I'm...Worried.
Because she's happy?
No, because I am.
House, that's--
ironic? Weird? Crazy?
I was going to say normal.
For now.
We're in the honeymoon period.
Our brains are flooded
with endorphins.
Once she snaps out of it,
where does that leave us?
In an adult relationship.
Name one thing that Cuddy and
I have in common besides work.
There's...
You're both...
Wait.
Exactly.
Long-term relationships are
based on compatibility,
and right now we only have sex.
House, you don't actually think
she'd dump you because you, what,
don't do yoga?
Listen to the B-52s?
Not right away.
We'll fight, makeup sex,
fight, maybe sex,
and then she'll dump me.
With possible goodbye sex.
So, instead of enjoying
the honeymoon phase,
you've decided to skip it entirely.
I need to find something
that we both like doing
besides each other.
Right. Or you could just
talk to her about it.
No, then she'll start
pretending to like things
that she really doesn't
just to make me feel better,
which will make her
feel even worse,
which won't be my fault,
so I'll resent her,
and that won't be her fault,
so she'll resent me.
At least with my plan
I get my one a day with
iron till the bitter end.
Is there a reason why
you're following me?
Oh, yeah.
You're not gonna believe who
just checked into the E.R.
The doctor hasn't examined you yet.
There's nothing wrong with me.
My maid just overreacted.
Great.
This won't take long then.
EMTs found her unconscious.
Her maid said she had a seizure.
I fainted.
Huge Jack Cannon fan, by the way.
Love your books.
Really?
My fans tend to be
overly-annoying teenaged girls.
I know.
All they care about
is who's hotter,
Jack or Deacon.
Like Sarah can't love both of them.
I may belong to one or
two online fan clubs.
How's the new book coming along?
I don't talk about my work.
'Kay.
How about nodding your head
to a few yes/no questions?
But I'll make you a deal.
You finish this exam quickly,
and I'll answer one question.
About anything?
Anything.
Who was Jack's real father,
who kidnapped his Uncle...
Deal.
I will have to go with
why'd you try to kill yourself?
Burn on the side of your face
is caused by gunpowder,
so change your mind
at the last second,
or you just a lousy shot?
I'm out of here.
Can't. We had a deal.
Try and stop me.
Okay.
This woman is on a
72-hour psychiatric hold.
If she tries to run, shoot her.
With a sedative.
That's more convenient.
You called us back to work
because a lady might
have had a seizure.
A seizure while trying
to commit suicide.
So send her for a psych eval.
What's that got to do with us?
What is the matter with you people?
We're talking about a human
being who's suffering.
You're right. That's not enough.
She is also the writer of
Jack Cannon: Boy Detective,
beloved by millions
around the world.
By girls between 10 and 14.
Look, the point is
if she kills herself,
millions of fans of
all ages and genders
will be very disappointed.
So we're taking this
case 'cause you're a fan?
No, that would be crazy
and unprofessional.
You're taking this
case 'cause I said so.
You and Taub do a full workup.
Observe her overnight.
See if she has another seizure.
You can go.
Why does he get the night off?
Because he brought
a smokin' hot babe.
I have plans with my wife.
Yeah, nice try,
but you hate your personal life.
And you obviously don't have one.
Hey.
I'd stay myself,
but I just bought the flowers.
Reservation for Dominica's
isn't till 8:00,
so we got plenty of time.
We need to pick something
up from a haunted house?
This is a Gothic
Revival masterpiece.
I hope one day to live
in a house like this.
Your friend's a writer?
One of the best.
She wants me to read
her latest manuscript.
Alice Tanner.
Why does that name sound familiar?
I gave you a couple of her
books a few years ago.
No.
She's the woman you
put on the psych hold.
This isn't a date.
We're on a case.
Ever hear of multitasking?
Did you steal her keys?
Think I'd take the Dean of
Medicine on a "B" and "E"?
How did you get in here?
Well, I guess you have your answer.
When was your last physical?
A while ago.
I don't like doctors.
Any history of
seizures before today?
Not that I recall.
Are we almost done?
I'm tired.
The exam would go faster
if you would cooperate with us.
I am.
You're evading every
question we ask.
Why do you say that?
That.
I didn't ask for help.
Committing a suicidal
gesture says otherwise.
It wasn't a gesture.
I had the damn seizure
before I could get
the gun in my mouth.
You want to tell us why?
You want to know my life story,
my secret, inner pain?
Maybe if I just open up a little,
you'll be able to save me?
We're just trying to help you.
Thank you.
I want a woman doctor.
And back to being evasive.
It's my right as a patient.
So please get out. Now.
We need to observe you overnight.
You really think I'm stupid enough
to try and kill
myself in a hospital?
To see if you have another seizure.
We'll be up there,
and we won't disturb you
unless there's a problem.
That work for you?
Whatever it takes to
get you out of here.
House, Christina has agreed
to not call the police.
She's probably illegal.
Same reason she didn't
report the suicide attempt.
I call 911.
But when Miss Tanner woke up,
she say she will fire me
if I say anything about the gun.
And if she whacks herself,
what happens to your job?
I think she's a very
depressed person.
Never goes out,
doesn't have friends.
She has all this money,
but all she does is write.
I need to see her
latest manuscript.
She always locks up
her writing in there.
Has she ever complained
about physical pain or stress?
Yes.
Her back and her hands hurt a lot.
A writer with back and hand pain.
That's very helpful. Let's go.
Sometimes I hear her cry at night.
When she thinks nobody's listening.
I should have done something.
True.
What are you doing?
Before there were hard drives,
there were...
How many of these
does she eat a day?
Two for lunch.
Sometimes three.
Still no seizure activity.
It's your turn--
What the hell?
Close. House.
She's fine.
Both the E.E.G.
and all her vitals have been--
you.
What do you want?
You wet the bed.
Just not sure how yet.
Good morning, gentlemen.
Well, if it's any consolation,
I didn't get any sleep either.
Unilateral hyperhidrosis.
Interesting.
She also admitted she
tried to kill herself,
but won't tell us why.
House seared her home,
found she's been eating two
cans of tuna a day for years.
Mercury poisoning?
Explains the seizures,
hand and back pain,
also the depression.
Explains everything except
the fact that it's not.
We got her urine and
blood samples back.
They're normal.
If it's low level,
it might not show up in a spot check.
We need to run continuous testing
to find it.
We can't. She wants
a female doctor.
She only asked for a
woman to waste time.
She's cooperating just enough
to get through the psych hold.
Put some lipstick on Chase
and start chelation therapy.
Confirm with another urine test.
Okay.
I'll go talk to Cuddy.
Maybe she'll let us
borrow a dress too.
Ahe--ahem.
This would be me ignoring you.
What if we got arrested last night?
And whatever happened to keeping
our professional and
personal lives separate?
I'm not the one talking about
our relationship at work.
What's behind your back?
Peace penguin.
What room should I return it to?
243.
I need some help with Alice Tanner.
She wants a vagina.
I'm pretty attached to mine.
I told you to hire a temporary
replacement for Thirteen
two weeks ago.
I've been busy. Doing what?
You.
So you'll talk her out of it?
You'll hire a woman doctor?
You think we just sit around
talking sports and
belching and farting
when the chicks aren't around?
By when?
Next week.
Next week it is.
What makes you think it's Mercury?
Your symptoms.
Now I can perform the
procedure yourself
if you still prefer a woman doctor,
but the team you have is our best.
That's an interesting
perfume you're wearing.
It was a gift.
From Dr. House?
It was all over him last night.
If you'd prefer
another female doctor,
I can arrange that as well.
I also smelled it somewhere
else more recently.
Faint, but unmistakable.
You should have worn
a different cardigan
this morning, Christina.
Something you'd like
to tell me, dear?
When I found you yesterday,
I thought I was too late.
I talked to them so I
could help you get better.
I just don't want to
see you suffer anymore.
That won't be a problem.
You're fired.
This woman cares about you.
If it weren't for her--
I wouldn't be here now, would I?
I should have done it yesterday.
I understand that you're in pain,
but lashing out isn't the answer.
Treatment is.
I agree.
Send the men back.
At least they're not a bunch
of dewy-eyed cry-babies.
What's that?
It's the new Jack Cannon novel.
Suggestions?
Yeah.
Stop.
It can't be done.
People wonder why you've
never cured cancer.
Did you get this before or
after your date with Cuddy?
Eh, probably would have
been a wiser choice.
Huh.
This is actually good, House.
She's committing crimes.
What does that tell you?
I'm a horrible influence.
True.
A horrible influence
she's reaching out to.
She's looking for ways to connect.
Sure, they're self-destructive,
juvenile, and insane,
but so are you.
You do have something in common.
You're both trying to find
things you have in common.
And not finding them.
You don't look so hot.
Want to talk about it?
Those days are over.
Who were you talking to?
Myself.
If you're seeing things,
it could be another symptom.
It's not.
It's only in my imagination.
I make things up for a living.
And talking to them?
It's a writer thing.
We're also good at reading people.
Like you, for instance.
Recently divorced.
You slept with a girl last night.
Her place, not yours.
You probably won't
return her calls.
That...
How?
The tan line from your
former wedding ring.
You stink of smoke,
but no yellow on your fingers
or teeth
means she's the smoker.
And you either didn't
shower or change.
Either way, her place.
Do him.
We're wasting time,
which is her main goal here.
Need your arm for this.
You remind me of my ex-husband.
A cute man, but problems
in the bedroom department.
Not even close.
The ones I caught him in.
He cheated on me every
chance he could.
The first time with my best friend.
The second...
The bastard.
BP and heart rate are spiking.
Must be an allergic reaction
to the chelation agent.
I didn't give it to her yet.
Pain, seizures, hyperhidros
is,
and sudden onset of radically
high blood pressure.
Her continuous blood and
urine test came back.
It's definitely not
Mercury poisoning. Clean.
Could be hemolytic uremic syndrome.
It's not. There weren't any
blood or protein markers
in her urine, either.
We also caught her talking to herself.
She could be delusional.
She's a writer and a recluse.
I'd be more surprised if she didn't
talk to herself.
You done playing with your ribbon?
What was she doing
when it happened?
Sitting in bed.
She claims it was only
in her imagination,
but still.
When her BP spiked?
Comparing Taub to her ex-husband.
She really hated the guy.
Her first symptom
was when she had a gun to her head.
Excess adrenaline
could explain seizures
and skyrocketing BP.
A pheochromocytoma.
Get an MRI and find it.
Would you hold this?
I meant now.
Have I mentioned
I'm claustrophobic?
Have I mentioned we don't care?
What's wrong?
Nothing. Just a leg cramp.
Get her out of here.
She's got metal in her leg.
She has three screws
in her right leg
from a skiing accident
she didn't tell us about.
The MRI's magnetic field sup
er heated the metal,
causing third-degree burns.
Skin ruptured from internal
heat pressure here.
It's not our fault.
She signed the consent forms,
denied there was any metal...
Normally I'd say it.
Maybe this way it'll
finally sink in.
She wants to die.
You cannot trust anything she says.
Treating the soft tissue
injuries in her leg
cost us most of the day.
We also had to replace the screws.
And finding a pheochromocytoma
without using the mri
could take us a week.
Longer, if she doesn't
stop lying to us.
Or we could figure
out a way to find it
in the 39 hours left
on her psych hold.
We need to make her cooperate.
We have to offer her
something she wants.
She wants to kill herself, House.
I can work with that.
I want you to write more books.
I'm done writing Jack
Cannon's adventures.
And when I get out of here,
I'll just be done.
Now don't you say that,
you dirty birdie.
You know, there are
easier ways to go
than shooting yourself in the head
or tearing apart a limb.
And this is one of them.
The best part, you'll feel so good,
you won't even notice you're dead.
You expect me to believe
you're going to
help me kill myself?
You're the perceptive one.
You tell me.
Why?
We can't find your tumor in time
without your cooperation.
So I'm giving you a choice.
Give us a chance to make you better,
or stick this anywhere and push.
Why do you care about me?
You think you know me
because you read my books?
No.
I know pain.
Think you can handle it,
and one day you can't.
When that happens,
you either find reasons to go on,
or you don't.
I'm...
I'm all out of reasons.
Now.
When you're pain free,
you're gonna want to live
and start writing again.
And if I'm wrong,
got a backup plan to
take home with you.
Okay.
Good choice.
If I were you,
I'd hide that if you
want to keep it.
I know the perfect place.
Morning, sunshine.
You're a real bastard.
You were supposed to choose life.
You're also an excellent liar.
Wasn't lying about the cure.
If we find and remove that pesky,
adrenaline-secreting tumor,
you'll get better.
You better hurry.
My lawyer will have me out
of here this time tomorrow.
Yeah, about that,
it seems that last night
you found and self-administered
what you thought was a
potentially lethal narcotic.
Your psych hold has be
en extended
an additional 24 hours.
I know. Bummer, right?
You want to know
something about my book?
Sure.
Jack Cannon dies.
I know.
Bummer, right?
We finished analyzing thePETt scans
from last night.
There's no sign of a tumor.
We sampled blood from s
ix different areas
looking for any spikes in adrenaline.
All of them were negative.
If she told us her symptoms,
where it hurts,
when the pain first started,
we could at least focus
on a specific area.
Or use them to rule areas out.
She'll only lie.
We're better off not
even talking to her.
You think you can get her to
try to kill herself again?
We're gonna need more time.
There might be a way
to get her symptoms
without asking her.
If writers write what they know.
I thought you said it was
about a boy Detective.
And his mentor, Aunt Helen,
who happens to be around
the same age as Alice.
Answers could be in the book.
Great. You finish reading
your typewriter ribbon yet?
Look for the tumor
with the ultrasound.
I drove across town
to treat a ribbon?
That's why I prefer lying.
It makes things easier.
Whatever he has you doing, stop.
You told him?
We do live together.
I generally tell him when
I show up at his work.
He told me it was a
matter of life and death.
It is.
Patient wants to kill herself.
He's just trying to read a book,
the latest Jack Cannon: Boy Detective.
Alice Tanner is your patient?
You're a "fannon" too?
I'm team Deacon.
Oh, come on.
Why can't she love them both?
The typewriter keys should
have left impressions
on these ribbon fibers.
They would also
remove a layer of ink.
It's just a question of
tweaking the software, really.
Does Cuddy know you're
using the MRI for this?
Let's say yes.
So do you think Jack finally
hooks up with Sarah in this one?
No. Debbie Wright is his true love.
She's dead. Presumed!
All we really know is--
there are actual patients
waiting to use this machine.
Congratulations.
It's a book.
Wilson just told me we're
going on a double date
with him and Sam tonight.
You don't like double dates?
I'd just like if
you'd ask me first.
You don't like surprises?
Is this Alice's book?
Sam reprogrammed the MRI
to read Alice's typewriter ribbon.
You used a $3 million piece
of hospital equipment
so you could read a novel?
Cool, right?
Well, as your girlfriend,
I'm impressed.
As your boss, you're a jackass.
Don't do it again.
As your boyfriend, I thank you.
As your employee, I resent you,
because I need this for my case.
As your boss,
you just got six more
clinic hours next week.
So what's the plan for tonight?
Whatever you want. I don't care.
Just pick something
we'd both enjoy.
Yeah? And what would
that be exactly?
I don't know. You know what I like.
I got to get back to work.
Found something.
It's not a tumor.
Whatever it is,
it's encased around her heart.
She has a pericardial effusion.
Which wasn't there last night
when we did the PET scan.
She's getting worse,
and there's no sign
of a pheochromocytoma.
Seizures, sweating,
rapid blood pressure,
and an effusion point
to something viral.
Or maybe a cancer.
We could use your opinion, House,
or at least your attention.
Jack Cannon is not dead.
It's worse.
Ten books leading up to
a final confrontation.
She ends it on a cliffhanger.
I mean, who does that?
People who want to
sell you the 11th.
She was gonna kill herself.
This is the final Jack Cannon.
Nothing gets resolved.
Who's his father?
Who killed his brother?
How'd he get that damn
scar on his cheek,
and why is he obsessed with yo-yos?
Is there anything in it
that pertains to our case?
Yeah.
I know why she wanted
to kill herself.
His mentor, Helen Rutherford,
has contracted a serious illness
which consists of joint paint,
fatigue, sensitivity to light,
and depression.
How do we know this mentor
character's really Alice?
Helen dies halfway
through the book.
Shoots herself in the head...
To save Jack from
having to care for her.
If we add those to the sympto
ms we've seen
and the pericardial
effusion...It's lupus.
Can't be lupus.
Why not?
It isn't curable.
That's...Not an answer.
It's treatable.
We'll start testing to s
ee which drugs
she best responds to.
We're not gonna be able
to take her pain away.
She's still gonna kill herself
as soon as she gets
released tomorrow.
Can't let Jack Cannon end this way.
We're treating a patient...
Not a book.
Retest to confirm.
Go-carts? Really?
Wilson, party of four.
You guys are up next.
Your mom said you loved go-carts.
You called my mother.
I loved them when I was 12.
This is so cool!
I haven't done this since I was 12!
Winner picks the restaurant.
I have a very bad
feeling about this.
Are we ready, racers?
On your marks,
get set...
And go away.
Hey! Watch it!
You having fun?
You know who wins these races?
The person who weighs less!
My parents never let
me drive one of these!
Yeah! I can tell!
Oh, my God!
Oh!
Whoa.
What is her problem?
She hates jews!
Never...Again.
That a girl!
Ohh... Uh...
Hoo hoo hah hah hah!
See you at the finish line!
Oh, yeah?
Yes!
Hey!
You're banned for life, mister!
Your Fun Stop privileges
are officially revoked!
You, too, blondie!
All of you--get out!
I avenged my Lady.
Seatbelt nearly broke my neck.
I'm done for the night.
It's not my fault Wilson's
attracted to psychos.
You picked the place.
That's just the pain talking.
Oh...Wow.
It was a car crash.
Not a skiing accident.
What?
Screws in your leg.
Ya got me.
I'll be going back to sleep now.
You damaged your thyroid
gland in the crash
when the shoulder strap
cut into your neck.
You don't have lupus.
What you have is curable.
Go away.
I read your book.
Sucks, by the way.
Nice try, but impossible.
Helen Rutherford kills herself
because she feels useless
and doesn't want to be a burd--
just like you do now.
You have hypothyroidism.
That's why you feel
so tired and worn out.
With medication,
you'll feel 20 years younger.
Or whatever age you were
the last time you didn't
want to kill yourself.
How did you-- you can finish
the story the right way...
The way Jack Cannon deserves.
You think you know
what Jack deserves?
I know that he deserves
better than what you gave him.
You don't know anything about him!
Why can't you just leave me--
what did you do to me?
I can't move.
I can't move anything.
How can I be right and wrong?
I deduced the car accident
because thyroid fit the symptoms.
But a damaged thyroid wouldn't
explain the paralysis.
How can I be wrong
about the thyroid
but right about the accident?
What if you're not?
I like the way you think, kid.
At least not completely.
Post traumatic
syringomyelia from a
15-year-old car crash.
Slowly growing over the years,
pressing against her spinal column.
Causes pain, fluctuating blood pressure,
seizures.
And if untreated,
eventually leads to
paralysis and death.
We find it and remove it.
She should be able to
regain full function.
If we can get her medical
records from back then,
we can use them to
pinpoint the location.
Do it.
We're dead on our feet.
I've barely slept in four days.
Aw...That's sad.
You know what's even sadder?
Thirteen was the
only man on my team.
Yeah, it'd be nice if you hurry up
and hire someone to fill her spot.
Do it.
Cuddy wants it to be a girl.
There are a couple of people--
I was talking to Chase.
I was just looking at
you to screw with you.
I'm meditating.
From where we're standing,
it looked like sleeping.
We can't find her old medical records.
You woke me up for that?
We woke you up because
it doesn't matter.
Alice is refusing
any more treatment.
She doesn't want the surgery.
She kicked us out.
Why would she lie
about the accident?
Everybody lies.
Everybody has a reason.
I know.
Alice is refusing surgery.
She'll be dead in a
few days without it.
Which is why I've spent
the last four hours
trying to find a legal way to
do it without her permission.
Unsuccessfully. I'm sorry.
As your boyfriend,
I'm grateful for the effort.
As your employee,
I'm disappointed at
your ineffectiveness.
Why would she not tell us
about the pins in her leg?
'Cause she wants to die.
By having her leg ripped off?
She wants to punish herself...
For something that happened
before she was famous,
before she even started to write.
I think the answer's
in her old medical records.
But dopey, sleazy,
and uptighty can't find them.
Maybe Alice Tanner's
just her pen name.
Your boyfriend is an idiot.
I'll contact the
national records archive
and run the type of
screws in her leg
against blood type, age,
and anything else I think of.
Her first name could be Helen.
Even better.
Don't bother to get up.
You know, the way you
write Jack
always made him feel real to me.
Now I know why.
Because I'm a good writer.
He's cool, but he's awkward.
He's brilliant. He makes mistakes.
He's funny, but sometimes
he takes it too far.
Sounds like a great kid.
Please.
Just leave me alone.
You weren't alone in the car crash.
Your son was with you, Helen.
The books are your way
of keeping him alive.
Why can't you just
let me die in peace?
You haven't been at
peace since it happened.
I killed him.
No, you didn't.
I let him drive.
He only had a learner's permit.
It was raining.
I deserve this.
No, you don't.
He could always get me
to do what he wanted.
He's always been my muse.
Well, that may be true,
but I've been reviewing
your muse's autopsy results.
It wasn't the crash
that killed him.
Your son had a brain aneurism.
That's why he crashed.
He was dead before the impact.
There was nothing you could
do to save him.
They would have told me.
They had no reason
to dig any deeper.
It was a car accident. I did.
It's easy to miss.
But you can see the
blood buildup here.
Your son would have died that day
on a bus, in school,
sitting on his bed.
The only thing the crash
is killing is you.
We need to repair that
syrinx in your neck.
He was my world.
Writing...
I could feel him with me.
It wasn't my fault, mom.
And it wasn't mine.
Her son didn't have
a brain aneurism.
Nope.
She shouldn't have let
him drive in the rain.
Jack was never very coordinated.
As your boss,
I am opposed to you
lying to a patient.
As your girlfriend,
I'm glad you care.
I don't.
I just wanted to save Jack Cannon.
Well, I can see why you like him.
I started reading one of
the books you gave me.
I find that very hard to believe.
Why?
Because I can't like
something you like?
We couldn't possibly
have something in common?
Because I lied about
giving you the books.
Oh. Oh.
Wilson told you. Yeah.
He's such a gossip.
I'm not gonna dump you because
we like different food
or books or music.
On the other hand,
I might dump you if
you don't talk to me
when you have a problem
with our relationship.
I know you believe that now...
But the fact is--
who cares about common?
Common is boring.
It's...Common!
I like being with you.
You make me better.
Hopefully, I make you better.
What we have is...
Uncommon.
And I've never been happier.
Mind giving us a moment alone,
Christina?
I'd like to thank you.
Great.
You can dedicate the
next Jack Cannon to me.
I can't.
Are you still in pain? No.
You did everything you said,
and more.
I can finally move on.
Thank you.
Move on where?
I want to write books for adults.
What about Jack?
Your last book didn't answer anything.
The way I ended Jack's
story is perfect.
Each reader can decide
what fate they want
for him themselves.
You--but that's stupid!
That doesn't make any sense!
How many answers do
you get in real life?
This is a book.
Books have beginnings,
middles, and ends.
You can't just leave
it on a cliffhanger--
who does that?
I'm sorry. His story's done.
There's really nothing you
can say to change my mind.
Your son...
Was very lucky to have
you as his mother.
That was-- oh, shut up.
www.tvsubtitles.net