Okay, you're doing good.
You're doing good.
You've still got the thing.
The stupid thing
is still on.
Mom, you don't have to
yell at me.
I've been in labor for
over a dozen hours, Justine.
I have to yell.
I thought you were gonna
miss the whole thing.
Mom, it's
a three-hour drive.
That's why I called you
yesterday after my water broke.
I'm sorry. A partner just
dropped a brief on my desk.
Okay, you're doing good.
Yeah, right.
I remember what it's like,
but family comes first.
I need you to keep pushing.
I can see her head.
All right, come on.
We're doing good here.
Get this.
This is what I wanted.
Gross.
You're crowning.
Are you getting--
getting this?
Kind of. Well,
not the actual vagina.
It's your baby sister!
It's my mother's vagina.
Aah!
Freeing the shoulders.
Oh!
Get the NICU team in here.
Baby's hypoxic.
Is something wrong?
What's going on?
I don't know.
My baby!
How's my baby?
What are you doing?
What are they saying?
I can't tell.
Find out what's going on!
You need to back up.
Turn that off.
She's not responding.
What's happening?
What's wrong with my baby?
Why doesn't someone
talk to me?
♪ House 7x05 ♪
Unplanned Parenthood
Original Air Date on October 18, 2010
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
♪ ♪
Cancel your dinner plans.
Short on medical history.
She's only eight hours old.
What she's not short on
is doctors.
Unfortunately, none of them
have been able to solve
her breathing problems.
Immature lungs?
Full term, and they
gave her surfactant.
Looks like
they're fully developed.
I need you a minute.
Silent reading time
till I get back.
My nanny called.
Her daughter has
a dance recital tonight.
She can't work late.
And I have
a board meeting tonight.
That's a problem.
My mother can't come.
She has a cooking class.
Oh, you've really
got a problem.
If only there were some
mature adult in my life
who could pinch hit
in emergencies like this.
Love to,
but I'm catching up
on my back issues
of Nudist Circus.
You should see
what the fat lady's got
under her big top.
All I need
is a warm body.
She'll be asleep
the entire time.
I got a sick baby here
who needs me.
Yours is healthy.
You could deal with
your team by phone.
How about a little something
extra when you get home?
I'm not bargaining sex
for babysitting.
Besides, you owe me.
For what?
Sex.
I still don't see
a female doctor in that room.
It's making me
very unhappy.
Fine. Out of the goodness
of my heart,
which will make you happy,
which will make you
desire me more,
which will
turn into more sex.
Be at my place at 7:00.
The sperm donor card
from the father
did note a history
of asthma.
What if her lung problems
are not coming from her lungs?
Her heart looks fine.
Her liver enzymes
are elevated.
When the liver fails,
it stops producing proteins.
Specifically the ones
that keep your plasma
inside your blood vessels
and outside your lungs.
Fix the liver,
she'll have enough breath
to keep the entire ward
up all night.
Foreman, you need to stay
after school.
I apparently need
to apologize.
Last week, I should not
have gone over your head
and allowed Chase
to hire a new team member.
So go hire someone who liked
The Bridges of Madison County.
Do you want me
to hire a white girl?
Go find a woman,
and wipe that self-satisfied
grin off your face.
This'll be quick.
I've been interviewing
people all week.
I have it narrowed down
to two candidates.
Well, narrow it
down to one
before Cuddy
starts withholding sex.
Uh, she hasn't said anything
to me about that.
I said, wipe the grin.
Yeah, she's fine.
I can hear her breathing
on the monitor.
I just checked.
I'm checking
every ten minutes.
Fine. I'll check again.
Oh, she's so cute
when she's asleep.
You should see this.
She's--she's--she's got
one hand over her head.
Okay, well, you take
as long as you need.
I'm thirsty.
Your mommy says no,
'cause she's mean.
If it was up to me...
Juice!
No.
Go back to bed.
I said bed!
Wilson, hey.
You up for a boys' night in?
Believe it or not,
breathing problems
can be caused
by a liver problem.
Then what's wrong
with her liver?
Probably an abscess.
If we find it
with the ultrasound,
we can drain it,
make her better.
You'll be able to take her home
by the end of the week.
Is she bleeding?
She's oozing
from her IV site.
It's a symptom
of liver failure.
It's what we would
expect to see.
Dr. Cheng, we might need
a unit of blood over here.
Echogenic area
in the liver.
Can you make it out?
Doesn't seem to have
the thick walls
you'd expect
from an abscess.
Lift her left shoulder
so we can get a better look.
Oh, can I do it? I haven't
been able to hold her yet.
Uh, she's hooked up to
too many tubes and IVs.
Can I at least
donate blood?
Of course.
We'll draw your blood
and see if you're a match
as soon as we're done here.
That's definitely not
an abscess.
It looks like
dilated bile ducts.
What does that mean?
Can I still
take her home soon?
You were right
about the liver.
On ultrasound,
we found
intrahepatic
dilated bile ducts.
Extrahepatic ducts
were normal.
Are there any masses
causing an obstruction?
No. Are you okay?
Just talking
in a soothing voice.
Not for your benefit.
Why? Is it
turning you on?
House, there's someone
here I need you to meet.
I just hired
Dr. Christina Fraser.
She's a board certified--
Nice to meet you.
You're fired.
What?
House, you're kidding, right?
I've done my due diligence.
She's the best there is.
What did I do?
You had the misfortune
to be the lesson
that Foreman is learning.
That whooshing sound
is the air being
let out of his ego.
You are such an ass, House.
You could have made
the same point
without crushing the hopes
of a young doctor
who was actually excited
to have this job.
No, I'm not sure
i could have.
I think you give me
far too much credit.
Taub, it's your turn
to find a young doctor
who's actually excited
to have this job.
For you to fire?
Not until you or she
earns it.
Dilated bile ducts
could be congenital.
That means that it's a stricture
in the ducts themselves.
Caroli's syndrome.
So, open her up.
Surgery?
This is a newborn
with liver failure.
She's oozing blood
from every puncture site.
It's insanely risky
to open her up.
Yes. It's unfortunately
also the only way to fix her.
So make teeny, tiny incisions
with a really small scalpel.
Gotta go.
You told me you gave them
your credit card.
And you were dumb enough
to believe me.
Cuddy'll be back
in an hour and ten minutes.
I'll be back
in an hour and five.
Oh, no, you don't.
Oh, yes, I do.
You're not gonna
leave the kid?
Yes, I am,
'cause unlike you,
I don't have a conscience.
And unlike you,
I'm not having sex
with Cuddy,
so I actually can leave.
You're bluffing.
I'm leaving.
You're not gonna leave
a two-year-old unattended.
True.
I'm leaving her with you.
A responsible adult.
Better get
back in there.
Kid's all alone.
It's kind of bugging you,
isn't it?
Not my problem.
Well, since,
objectively,
you care more about leaving
a child alone than I do,
it kind of is.
Objectively,
since I never accepted
this responsibility,
it kind of isn't.
True, and yet it is.
Because you're you.
I'm leaving.
You're not gonna leave.
You can't.
Fine.
You're right.
You know what I can do?
I can go in there and call
a babysitting service
for 15 bucks an hour,
then call Cuddy
and tell her who's
watching her kid and why.
I'll stay if you stay.
We were gone two minutes.
What have you got there,
sweetie?
Come on now,
spit it out.
Come on, sweetie. Open.
Bah-bah-bah-bah-bah-bah.
Bah bah bah!
Open.
Oh!
Ow!
Rachel, how many coins
did you eat?
Isolating
the common bile duct.
And mobilizing the distal end
for cannulation.
Bp is down to 50 systolic.
You've got to stop
the cannulation.
I haven't started yet.
Hit her with a bolus
of phenylephrine.
That should buy us
enough time
BP is rising. 70 systolic.
Nice. I'm in
the common bile duct.
Advancing past
the cystic duct.
No strictures
or blockages so far.
BP is dropping again.
Another bolus
of phenylephrine.
She can't take more.
BP is still dropping.
We've got to pull out.
We're done.
I was barely in.
This doesn't make sense.
The liver problem alone
is not gonna mess
with the baby's BP.
Whatever this is, it's got
to be affecting her heart.
Heart plus the liver.
Could be
tuberous sclerosis.
Or it could be
a vascular malformation
in the liver,
causing both problems.
So what do you guys think
of Dr. Cheng?
Best treatment for a vascular
malformation is surgery.
And I think
your wife thinks
you shouldn't think
anything of Dr. Cheng.
No surgery.
A newborn baby
can't handle
another trip
to the O.R.
I didn't mean think think.
I meant think
as a potential hire.
What if we started
the baby on steroids
an anti-angiogenesis agent,
and dopamine?
Could work
just as well as surgery.
Snap those
bad blood vessels shut.
I'll call House
to get approval.
So, what was that shrug?
A "Dr. Cheng
could work" shrug?
Or a "House
is gonna crush you
for even considering her"
shrug?
You suck.
House is gonna hate
anyone we hire,
because he doesn't
want to hire anyone.
So you think
I should abstain?
Just give the decision
back to him?
Then he'll just mock you
for being a wuss.
You're screwed.
Unless House feels like
hiring her is his idea.
Still not answering.
We should just
start the treatment.
She opened up
a Chinese food bag
to eat money.
What an idiot.
Okay, you ordered
the moo shoo pork
and the orange cashew
chicken, right?
Like I always order.
Did you clean up
in there?
Yeah.
It's good enough.
Okay, so with tax,
the change should
have been 68 cents.
There's only
58 cents out there.
There's a dime missing.
Well, he could have
shortchanged you.
Fridge magnet's
not getting anything.
That's because
it's a fridge magnet,
and unless she swallowed
a Canadian dime,
it's not magnetic.
Really?
I mean, kids swallow things
all the time, right?
I mean, she swallowed a dime,
she poops it out.
She'll be fine.
Absolutely.
Unless it gets stuck
in her intestine
and causes a blockage,
which could kill her.
Then she won't be fine.
You have to tell Cuddy.
Well, then I won't be fine.
If you don't tell Cuddy,
I will go out there
and tell her myself.
Yeah? What are you
gonna tell her?
Are you gonna tell her
that you left coins out
and you left her child
unsupervised?
Hey, hey, hey! You are not
gonna pin this on me!
Rachel needs to be
monitored for 24 hours
to see
that the dime passes.
You know, just to make sure
she doesn't die.
You're telling me
to do the right thing
while climbing out
a window?
Shh shh shh shh shh!
Tell her!
Did she wake up at all?
One time.
That's not like her.
Is she all right?
She's fine.
How about
I stay the night?
Then you can
really thank me.
I have to get up early.
Won't be able to sleep in.
I'm a deep sleeper.
Round two.
Did Justine go home?
Said she was going downstairs
for a few minutes.
A few hours ago.
So you two are close?
Well, it's been
getting better actually.
At least she's here
in the building.
That's pretty supportive
for her.
What is it?
She's pinker.
Is that bad?
That's good.
That's very good.
Was that her?
Can I hold her?
I think it's long overdue.
Oh!
Oh.
My first time.
Finally.
Technically,
it's your second time.
I didn't mean--
I know, mom.
Mmm.
Looks like it was
a vascular malformation.
The Grogan baby
is better.
Okay, ready, honey.
So stay very, very still
and hold your breath.
Don't move.
She moved.
They always move.
It is a good job.
Diagnostics.
Solve a mystery,
save a life.
But I suppose you're
pretty attached to pediatrics?
I'm sorry, Ms. young,
but I'm gonna have to ask you
to restrain your daughter.
Now the mom's
not gonna want to do it
because she'd rather
I just keep
blasting her daughter
with radiation.
You're telling me
there's an opening
in House's department?
Would you be interested?
No more kids,
no more parents.
One case at a time
instead of 17?
Set up the interview.
It's possible you won't
need to interview.
Relax, I got this.
Oh, thanks.
Pfft!
Is everything okay?
Yeah, sorry,
I'm just new to all this.
You want me
to reset the alarm?
God, no.
Case is under control.
I'm sleeping in.
Your boss must
really like you.
Hey, marina.
Pasta's in the fridge
for lunch.
I assume, since you're
lling so early,
that the surgery
was a rousing success.
And I assume,
since you still think
we actually did
the surgery,
you haven't checked
your messages in eight hours.
Where are you?
I believe this is
what your people term
a poopie call.
Uh, the word is Booty.
Well, I don't know
what you're doing,
but this is a poopie call.
It's not caroli's syndrome.
Dr. Cheng spotted a--
whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, what?
I know about the jew,
the black, and the croc hunter,
but when did we get
our Asian persuasion on?
Dr. Cheng is the NICU
attending on the case.
And she's not here.
Well, then I just wasted
a perfectly good racial epithet.
She spotted
a vascular malformation
in the baby's liver.
Good call.
Except for everything
you just said.
There's no way
that our patient
has a vascular
malformation.
And you can tell that
from the vast amount
of information
you've gleaned
from not being here?
Don't need to be there
to remember
that the patient's A.L.T.S
were three times normal.
The baby's liver damage
is far too extensive.
Dr. Cheng's an idiot.
In fairness, it wasn't
completely her idea.
More of a Foreman
kind of thing.
Well, then you're
an even bigger idiot
for trying to cover
for her.
House, we treated for
a vascular malformation,
and she got better.
No, she didn't.
Call me
when she crashes again.
That went well.
Everything okay?
Come on.
I know that look.
I'm just not used to seeing
such emotion coming from you.
I just gave birth.
I'm, like, one big vat
of hormones right now.
It's not just
the hormones, mom.
You're different with her.
It's okay.
It's good. It's just...
I can't help thinking,
where was this mom
when I was growing up?
Wow.
I never realized
you considered me
such a failure
as a mother.
I don't consider you
a failure.
I just--
I never knew that
there was an alternative.
Hmm.
I think she feels wet.
Can you hold her a sec?
I'm gonna grab a diaper.
Okay.
Mom, something's wrong.
Oh! Nurse!
She's bleeding again!
All right,
she's in her office.
Move fast.
You see a double-wide tuchus
coming this way,
you scream like a girl.
If Rachel wakes up,
she's gonna tell Cuddy
everything.
She's two.
Last night,
she was whining
about the giant moose that
lives outside her window.
Medusa at 6:00.
Don't look back.
Move, move.
Hello.
Hello, I'm the friendly moose
who lives
outside your bedroom.
She hates that moose.
Hand me the gel.
Okay.
Make it short.
Do not pardon the pun.
She's crashing again.
Where are you?
Is it actually important that
I understand what you say?
What?
Yeah?
The baby's bleeding again.
I'm shocked.
Oh, no, wait a minute.
That's you.
Yes.
You're a genius.
The bleeding means her liver
is still failing.
It's not a vascular
malformation.
House, come take
a look at this.
Hold that thought.
House, no!
I need you!
Just past
the ileocecal valve.
It's nothing.
It's just
an irregularity.
It's a dime.
Or a pocket of air.
Yeah,
with FDR's face on it.
That's not a face.
It's a shadow.
House, the thing
is perfectly round.
Well, move the wand
to the side.
Tickles!
That's because
I'm the tickle monster.
Gonna tickle you
even more!
Look at--look at that.
We need an X-ray
to be sure.
Great, just give her
an unnecessary dose
of radiation.
It's a dime.
House, I know
you're in there.
Open the door!
I saw your extension
on the call.
What are you doing
down here?
Uh, Wilson's got
a two-year-old with cancer.
She's in a lot of pain.
It's very sad.
He also has an outstanding
bedside manner.
Her liver failure
is getting worse.
You were right.
Now what?
The interesting question
is not why she's worse now
but why she got better
in the first place.
Could have been something
we did that temporarily
relieved the--
what'd you put her on
again?
After the transfusion,
we gave her steroids,
dopamine, and the anti--
steroids can treat
idiopathic hepatic fibrosis.
It would explain why she
got better and then worse.
But not the multiple
dilated ducts.
House, I need you
back in here!
Cancer kid
trumps liver kid.
Sorry. Confidentiality.
There are rules, you know.
That is a dime.
It looks mobile.
And it's right in
the middle of the colon.
Prime location
for pooping out.
We'll give her some laxatives
to help it on its way.
Sounds to me like
someone's going to get
some yummy chocolate.
Chocolate.
Yum yum yum.
You're gonna make
a great mommy one day.
Thanks for waiting.
Hook the mom up to the baby.
Direct blood transfusion.
And what else?
Nothing else.
It's amazing.
She's pink and healthy again.
Mother's touch.
It's a miracle.
Thank you.
A blood transfusion
isn't a cure.
Or a miracle.
Then why does the baby
seem like she's cured?
I have no idea.
Our patient can either
go through life
with the world's longest
umbilical cord,
or we can discuss the
differential for magic blood.
Baby's O2 sats
are holding.
Either you're Dr. Cheng
or you're early
for my mani-pedi.
I thought
her expertise could--
could tell us the O2 sats.
I hope you come with
some original ideas.
Either the mom's blood
is special,
which would mean
it's treating
something specific,
which means the baby
has a disease.
Or mom's blood
is just blood,
and it's replacing something
the baby is missing,
which means the baby has
a simple deficiency.
Given the liver failure,
a deficiency
of clotting factors,
enzymes, or vitamins
are the most likely.
So let's find out.
Hook the baby up
to someone else's blood
and see if she gets better.
Find a donor.
I'm o negative.
Universal donor.
Hook yourself up.
Dr. Cheng, hook me up.
Walk with me.
My team seems to have
taken a shine to you.
I like them too.
I assume you're hanging around
because you want a job.
That would be
a fair assumption.
Well, I'm gonna
have to test you.
Let's say,
two-year-old...
Swallowed a coin
20 hours ago.
She's gonna be fine,
right?
Any signs of obstruction?
For the purposes
of this quiz,
let's say, not yet.
I'd give a laxative,
although I wouldn't
wait too long.
Her bowel could
become ischemic,
or worse,
an intussusception.
Define "too long."
Another six hours, max.
By then,
her system is clear.
If it's not out,
it's not coming out.
And then what do I do?
I mean, what do you do?
It's your test.
I'd go in with a scope
and get it.
Did I pass?
It's not up to me.
Talk to Taub.
Men's room?
It turns out, toilets
are handy in this situation,
and I felt relatively sure
that Cuddy wouldn't come in.
Oh, Cuddy's been in here.
Seriously?
This must be a terrible
place to have se--uhh!
Is there such a place?
Okay, six more hours,
then we're going in with a scope
and pulling it out.
Scope a two-year-old?
It's dangerous.
And as you
keep pointing out,
so is a dime ripping
through her intestines.
Cuddy will be home
from work in six hours.
But no big deal.
I'll just scream,
"look over there,"
while you quickly
shove a scope
up her daughter's rectum.
I could offer
to baby-sit again,
let her have the night out.
Sure.
That won't raise
any suspicions.
I wish I was nicer.
Hey.
Give me
your radiation dosimeter.
Why?
Because it matches my eyes.
I think we can say
this isn't working.
We'll get her back
on your blood.
That'll help for now.
But this means
there's an infection.
First we need to
identify it.
We know it's in her liver,
so we'll get a sample.
Then we can figure out
how to help her
get better.
I had this baby
because I wanted a chance
to be a special mom.
But not this way.
Problems in radiology.
A radiation dosimeter badge
turned positive.
I could have a CT Scanner
that's leaking
or a spilled vial
of thallium somewhere.
I don't even know
whose badge it was.
The code was scratched off.
That had to be intentional.
I mean, why would anyone--
I don't know.
All I know is that
I'm gonna need to work late.
I was actually hoping
that you could baby-sit.
No.
Please.
Two nights in a row?
I have a life, you know.
I will make it
worth your while.
I am not going to bargain
babysitting for sex.
Who the hell said that?
Of course I will.
Thank you.
Oh, that thing's
nearly as big as she is.
Don't worry. I've done this
at least once before.
Advance another centimeter
and you're in.
Oh, God, that looks awful.
Is that from the infection?
No. It means
we were wrong.
It's a melanoma.
You mean, like skin cancer?
How would she get that?
She's never been outside.
But you have.
You're saying
I gave my baby cancer?
I found a mole under the nail
on her left index finger.
The biopsy revealed
it's melanoma.
That's it?
How come no one
got me food?
What do you mean, "that's it"?
The woman has melanoma.
She could die if we don't--
boring.
Since the baby
has the melanoma,
we kind of already knew
the mom had it.
Yes, but now we know
where it is,
so we can treat it
much more effectively.
Great. So treat her.
Also boring.
What's interesting
is that mom's melanoma
spread to the baby
in utero,
which means
it's metastatic,
which means it's
late stage.
How many people with
a late stage melanoma
are as healthy as she is?
Clearly, something's
going on in mom's blood
that's treating her melanoma
as well as her baby's.
Antibodies.
If her immune system
was fighting the melanoma,
it never would have spread.
Exactly, which means
it's fighting something else,
and the melanoma cells
are getting caught
in the crossfire.
So what's mom's immune system
really shooting at?
Scleroderma can cause
cancer-fighting antibodies.
So can Churg Strauss,
pretty much
any auto-immune disease.
Or infections
that cause granulomas,
TB, mycobacteria.
See, Dr. Cheng?
This is not boring.
Start with auto-immune.
Go test her blood.
And leave your food.
Just a little pinch.
Ah.
So, uh, I'm not actually
making her better.
I'm making her sick.
You can't blame yourself.
I ate all the right foods,
I read all the books
and the studies,
and I even hired
a private Detective
to research
each sperm donor.
I just missed
one big thing.
My own cancer.
I'm all done here.
We'll have
the results soon.
And if that's
what this is?
An auto-immune disease?
Treatment's fairly simple.
And if it's
something else?
Let's just take this
one step at a time.
Stop beating yourself up.
I'm sorry, mom.
Not just for this,
but for what I said earlier.
I was jealous
and angry,
and I lashed out.
But you were
a great mom.
You are a great mom.
I don't deserve
such a good daughter.
Negative
for scleroderma.
So, what did House
want earlier?
He just gave me
a little quiz
and said he was okay
with hiring me,
but that
it was your decision.
Negative for
dermatomyositis.
He's just saying that
to set me up.
So you're not
offering me the job?
If he wants me
to offer you the job,
something's going on.
That was my thinking too.
It's not lupus.
Things with House are never
as simple as they seem.
Trust me, he's got
an ulterior motive,
and I've got to figure it out
before I do anything.
Okay.
Mom's negative
for Churg Strauss.
This isn't auto-immune.
Time to scan her
for infections
that could cause
granulomas.
Third poop
in the last half hour.
Still nothing.
All right, that's it.
Time's up.
Operation Valkyrie
is now in effect.
Either it's a trap or it's not.
Just hire her.
Lungs clear
for granulomas.
Yeah, who cares?
Did you enjoy that bear trap
snapping on your leg yesterday?
You realize it's just
a metaphorical trap?
You'll still have
all your limbs.
Fourth rib about
the midclavicular line.
You're over-thinking this.
House fired my pick
sight unseen.
He was never even interested
in Chase's pick.
He was only obsessed with
how she reflected on Chase.
Dr. Cheng is the only candidate
he's actually responded to.
You wanted House invested.
He is. Hire her.
And you think
I'm over-thinking this?
Shut up and hire her.
Look.
Oat cell lung cancer.
She has two cancers?
Cancer treating cancer?
You have lung cancer.
I thought I had
skin cancer.
As unlikely as it sounds,
you have both.
Actually, the lung cancer
is basically treating
the skin cancer.
It's why you're not
feeling sick
and why your blood's
helping your baby.
We found it early,
so it should be treatable.
In a way, your daughter
saved your life.
We'll get you set up
for the surgery
and start you on chemo.
What about Kayla?
She'll only need
the chemo.
Can't you just keep
giving her my blood?
Not once we cut out
the tumor.
Your body will stop
making the antibodies
that are keeping
your baby healthy.
Can you hold off
on my surgery?
Over the last day,
your baby's liver tumors
have shrunk 15%.
Projecting forward,
it would take
eight or nine days
to completely eradicate
her cancer cells.
So let's take
the eight or nine days--
the cancer
probably won't spread
in the next nine days,
but there are other risks.
Cancer thickens your blood,
which could cause clots.
What are the risks to
putting my baby on chemo?
It could damage her brain
or affect her development,
but these risks are small
compared to the risks
that you would be taking by
leaving your cancers untreated.
I want to wait.
Mom.
Are you listening?
This is way too dangerous.
I'll take the risks.
I want what's best
for my daughter.
I'm your daughter too.
She's a baby.
You're an adult.
So what?
I don't need my mom
anymore?
No. You never did.
'Cause I wasn't there
for you.
But look at you.
You turned out great.
Oh, you don't know
if I'm great.
You don't know me at all.
And I'm not gonna let you
martyr yourself
for a two-day-old infant
just because you feel guilty
because you weren't
around for me.
I'm not martyring myself.
It's nine days.
Let's hold off
on the surgery.
You brought food?
This is a medical procedure,
not a dinner date.
I'm aware that this
is a delicate procedure.
I'm also aware
that my hands are shaking
from low blood sugar 'cause
I haven't eaten all day.
So while this
may seem insensitive,
this crucial,
lifesaving moo shoo--
where are
my extra pancakes?
Damn it, they forgot
the extra pancakes
for my moo shoo pork.
Every time that new girl
with the blue streak in her hair
answers the phone,
they screw up.
Was she there when
you picked up the food?
You ordered extra pancakes?
How much did they cost?
Where--
55 cents.
And there were two.
So that means the total
on the last bill was--
was--
$18.42.
Rachel couldn't have
eaten a dime
because there was
no extra dime.
Yeah.
So the image that we saw
on the ultrasound--
was obviously just
a pocket of air,
like I said all along.
But you saw
the worst case scenario,
like every irrational,
worried parent.
You'd make
a terrible mommy.
Want to give me
some dumplings?
Mom, I brought you some--
mom?
Mom!
Mom.
We need help in here!
Somebody help us!
Massive pulmonary embolism.
She died in seconds.
Wouldn't have happened if she
let us remove the tumor.
Probably not.
Postmortem, we were able
to harvest all of her blood.
It's enough
to treat the baby.
That's something.
Pretty amazing case.
Thanks for your help.
I was glad for the chance
to work it with you.
I've thought about it,
and I'd like to
formally offer you the job.
It's funny, I wanted to
work on House's team,
until I started
working with his team.
Yeah, I know. Chase and
Foreman can get a little--
actually, it's you.
I get that House is an ass,
but at least he owns it.
You don't understand.
This whole thing
was just a game to House.
I didn't have a choice.
You're a grown man,
Dr. Taub.
You can make whatever
choices you want,
and instead of hiring me
when he said you could,
you chose to act like
a paranoid, scared little kid.
I hate kids.
Good-bye, Dr. Taub.
♪ We don't understand it ♪
♪ the door that opens ♪
I'll make sure
you never forget her
and what she did for you.
She was just trying to be
the best mom in the world.
She was.
This one's all yours.
What happened
to helping out?
I did.
Did someone go poopie?
What?
How did you eat a dime?
House.
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net