Shouldn't they
be up by now?
I'm sure they're fine.
They're gonna run
out of air.
I'm happy
to kill my daughter,
but I feel a little awkward
about killing your son.
They're spending time
together.
It's good.
We're a family now.
They need to bond.
Yeah, well...
They can bond
with full air intake.
Julie, surface now.
Help! Shark!
Please don't scare me
like that.
What?
You said we should bond.
Well, look what I found.
You're not supposed to take
anything off the wreck.
How cool is this?
They kind of look
like feathers.
Can I see?
Ow!
Julie!
Get her a towel.
What was in that jar?
♪ House 7x07 ♪
A Pox on Our House
Original Air Date on November 15, 2010
♪ ♪
Why aren't you guys
in my office?
Why are you in the building?
It's 8:00 in the morning.
Where's Chase?
He's not here because
it's 8:00 in the morning.
16-year-old girl--
high fever, vomiting,
bloodshot eyes.
Wow. The case
of the really bad flu.
Hmm, let me see.
Did I leave anything out?
Oh, yeah.
The smallpox.
Smallpox was eradicated
over 30 years ago.
So were hush puppies.
Have you checked out your local
hipster coffee shop lately?
Smallpox doesn't exist
outside of P4 Labs
and bioweapon plants.
She was in Bermuda. Where she was
scuba diving on the wreck
of a Dutch slave ship
that had been intentionally sunk
because an epidemic of smallpox
had broken out on board.
Was the ship sunk in water?
Because viruses can't survive
contact with water.
If the virus had been kept on
the outside of an airtight jar,
that might be an issue.
The jar held old-school
inoculations.
They kept the scabs
of the infected people.
The virus can't survive
over 200 years.
You have.
Thanks for calling back.
Uh, listen,
I'm a screenwriter,
and is it
theoretically possible
for smallpox to survive
for more than 200 years
underwater
in a sealed glass jar?
Well, theoretically,
yes, but--
Thank you.
So who do we believe--
CDC or Dr. 90210?
Isolate,
get baseline blood draws
for smallpox antibodies
and vaccinate
the entire family.
We should test
for the 21st-century suspects--
varicella and measles.
You're free to perform
whatever unnecessary tests
you want, Foreman.
Slavery was abolished
years ago.
Why the hell do you guys
have us quarantined in here?
We're just taking
every precaution.
Against what?
What do you think I have?
One possibility is tetanus
from the glass jar
that sliced your hand.
I remember
tetanus shots.
That does not look
like tetanus shots.
It's really not worth
going into,
because the odds
are astronomical.
Tell me.
Again, it's--
smallpox.
Smallpox?
The vaccine will protect you
if you don't have it
and lessen the severity
if you already do.
B-but it's
a billion-to-one, so...
We don't want you to panic
or anything.
How do I not panic
with that information?
Idiot in exam room one
needs antidiarrheals
and a dictionary.
You're not scheduled
for clinic duty now.
I had some free time.
I owed four hours.
Don't you have a case?
Yeah.
Then don't worry about it.
Are you a Stepford doctor?
If you're busy,
you don't need to be down here.
You're serious.
Yep. Get out of here.
I can't.
I forgot her
stuffed animal at home.
It's been with her
through all
the chemo sessions so far.
I need Lamby.
He doesn't want me
to do it alone.
Honey,
there's no other way.
You're just gonna
have to be brave, okay?
What if I get someone
to sit with her
while you run home
and get Lamby?
I'll get a nurse.
Then I have to deal
with a...
Very sick man.
I think she knows.
Who is she,
and what does she know?
Cuddy. And...
that I faked a lab test
and lied to her
to save my last patient.
What did she do?
She let me out of clinic duty
by saying I had a case.
She's never done that.
She's also probably
never ordered the pasta special
in the cafeteria.
Would that also have
some special paranoid message
to send you?
I am not imagining this.
It's an aberration in the way
that she treats me.
How do I find out
what it means?
You don't.
If she doesn't know,
all you're gonna do
by sniffing around
is make her suspicious.
If she does know,
you'll find out soon enough.
What if I die of curiosity
in the meantime?
You were an idiot for lying
to her in the first place.
Don't be more
of an idiot now.
Say nothing to no one
about anything.
That includes me.
It's not smallpox.
Blood work suggests
some other infection.
White count is way down.
Masters,
have you got a boyfriend?
That's none
of your business.
Ah, probably just
a dry spell.
House, you do realize
we just ruled out smallpox?
Would you ever be extra nice
to a theoretical boyfriend
if you were
really mad at him?
I guess the only reason
I would be extra nice
is because I'm angry,
and I just want him to go away
so I don't have to deal
with him anymore.
You passive/aggressive bitch.
You just asked me--
what about Foreman's
unnecessary tests?
Negative for varicella
and measles.
So all of our ideas
are off the table.
I'm putting mine back on.
Patient's a diver.
Under increased pressure,
everything in the blood
gets scared, panics,
runs, and hides.
Antibodies could be
in the joints.
Tap her knee, ankle,
shoulder,
and any other joint
in her smallpox-ridden body.
Good talk.
You know.
Of course I know.
Oh, thank God.
I thought I was just
being paranoid.
Why didn't you
say something?
'Cause I wanted you
to come to me and apologize.
I can't apologize if
I haven't done anything wrong.
You lied to my face.
To do my job,
to save a patient's life.
Look, I don't want to go
all Godfather on you.
This was business.
I wouldn't lie to you
about something personal.
Well, you don't get to lie
to me about anything.
I can't compartmentalize
my life like that.
Well, maybe you should practice,
'cause it comes in handy.
I think you should go.
Ow.
Sorry.
I have to get the needle
behind the bone.
I'm running
out of bones.
If this is a waste
of time--
last one.
You just have to be...
What?
What--what is it?
I'm sorry.
I have to call the .
I think you do have
smallpox.
Am I gonna die?
I mean, this is what
terrorists want to use
to kill everyone, right?
Like, there's no cure.
There are treatments.
We can give you cidofovir.
I don't think you care
about the drugs' names.
Bottom line--
it's 30% fatal,
which means your chances
of being okay
are about the same
as a basketball player's chance
at hitting a free throw,
unless she finds dark,
purplish skin blotches.
What would
purple blotches mean?
Hemorrhagic-type smallpox.
In which case,
her chances are more like...
Shaq hitting a free throw.
Well, no purple skin,
but take a look at this.
What is it?
There's a rash under
your daughter's arm.
Like more of those
gross bumps?
No. It's just
a regular rash.
W-what does that mean?
It means it's not smallpox.
Are you saying
you see House's side?
It's not even a side.
It's a fictional construction.
She's expecting House
not to lie?
If she's using
the relationship
as a rationale
to try to change things--
Wait. Wait.
Are you saying
it's okay for us
to lie to each other?
No, we have
a different relationship--
I think a better one.
Lying was never part of it.
Theirs is built on it.
Sorry, I have to go.
Oh, come on, I have to leave
in, like, five minutes.
Can't it wait?
There's a little girl.
The nurse watching her
got called away.
It's a long story,
but I've got to babysit.
I'll see you tonight.
Mm-hmm.
Attention--
effective immediately,
all hospital entrances
and exits will be restricted
until further notice.
Center for Disease Control
has ordered
Princeton Plainsboro Hospital
locked down.
Well, I guess
I can stay.
Please step out of the room.
I'm Dr. Broda,
head of infection control, .
And your protective suits
are not adequate.
Turns out
they don't have to be.
Rash under the arm
means it's not smallpox.
False alarm. Sorry.
Hope the traffic
wasn't too bad.
Rash is consistent
with smallpox.
Not if it presents
after pustules.
She's probably just allergic
to the bedsheets
or the hospital gown,
and you simply didn't notice it.
We're gonna airlift blood
and tissue samples to Atlanta.
We'll have the DNA results
in 18 hours.
In the meantime, please,
step out of the room.
You brought the plane?
Cool.
When we left, Julie's fever
had climbed to over 103.
It's not smallpox.
She's not dying.
And it's not our case.
Need any other reasons
to forget it?
You know how you can tell
there's nothing to be done?
Chase showed up.
I was here at 9:00.
So you guys just want to do
nothing for the next 18 hours
until they tell us
it's not smallpox?
Can't we spend the time
discussing
what looks like smallpox
but isn't smallpox?
Molluscum contagiosum.
You have to compare lesions
to differentiate.
But we don't have access
to the patient
or any new information.
But we do have access
to the other patients--
the ones who died
of the same thing in 1793.
It's the Captain's log
from the Sotos Ooslerzoon.
Maritime Museum in Bermuda
graciously sent over a pdf.
Problem solved.
I assume at least one of you
speaks fluent Dutch.
It's the middle of the night
in the Netherlands.
Nobody's working.
Oh, you can always
find someone.
Oh, yes.
My name is Geerte.
Are you handsome,
sexiest American man?
You know, some people--
I would say
that I am, yeah.
I want you to translate
something for me.
Why you want I translate?
I do topless,
toys, and--
just do the translation.
She can translate however
she feels most comfortable.
Whatever.
You put in credit card.
House, the hospital
has translators on call--
Shut up.
Honey, could you email
our new friend
the Captain's log?
Sure thing...
Sexiest American man.
"On morning of 14, July,
I boarded Sotos Ooslerzoon
with two trunks and my cat."
Aw!
The Captain had a cat.
Isn't she adorable?
Go ahead and skip
to the part
where people get sick.
Mm...Ah, here.
"The passenger has a fever,
shaking, and red eyes."
Ooh. Also African man
make go in his pants.
What about the Captain,
the crew?
Mm, no. It say only
African men sick.
It can't be smallpox.
Airborne transmission
means it's
an equal-opportunity killer.
We're looking for a disease
that discriminates.
Sickle cell.
The disease
doesn't have to be racist.
It could be classist.
Vitamin "D" deficiency
from lack of sunlight
weakens the immune system,
makes the slaves
more vulnerable to malaria
or dengue fever.
I don't know how you get
pustules from any of those.
Captain and crew
got clean drinking water.
Slaves drank
whatever they could.
Scrofula.
That's what they called
cervical T.B. lymphadenitis
in the 1700s.
Scrofulicious--
that's what they called
"annoying" in the 1700s.
Is she wrong?
Then they died for nothing.
Those slaves could have led
long, fulfilling lives
mowing my ancestors' lawns.
Foreman.
Can I speak to you
outside for a second?
We need to test for T.B.
T.B. Might fit,
but it's too slow-moving
to kill her anytime soon.
There's no way the CDC's
gonna give us access.
That's why
we don't think it's T.B.
We think it's
meningococcal disease,
which could kill her
before the results come back.
And once I gain access,
I run the T.B. test.
You could have said
all that in there.
In front of the narc?
As if.
Are you so afraid
of this new girl,
we have to take
elaborate measures
every time you want to skirt
around ethical boundaries?
Elaborate measures?
We took a walk--
a walk you
would have taken anyway.
Actually, I saved you
from the horrible
post-differential
traffic jam.
Meningococcus.
We believe the rash
under Julie's armpit
is actually
petechial spots.
When added to the high fever,
the vomiting--
there haven't been
any seizures, no stiff neck.
If I could just gain access
to the patient,
I can investigate
the rash further.
I'll take a look.
I can wear your gear.
I'll take every
necessary precaution.
You come to me
with a weak diagnosis.
I even offer to investigate,
but that's not
good enough for you.
What's really going on here?
Sir...
Are you feeling
all right in there?
It's just a headache.
Baby.
Dad...
You're bleeding.
Somebody, please...
Get in here now!
This is not meningococcus.
You're not getting in here.
Cool.
Not really--not for them
and not for you--
the dad's new symptoms
are consistent
with them having smallpox.
Would be
if he had a headache.
He does have a headache.
No. He just said, "ow,"
and held his head.
Actually, he said, "ow."
Then he said,
"it's a headache."
Which could be indicative
of head pain.
Headache is caused by muscle
tension or vascular stretching.
Head pain is caused by trauma,
which would include
such events as a bleed
in the brain from T.B.
We're back to T.B.?
We never left.
We'll need to do a C.T.
And I sort of have a hunch
that the CDC's
not gonna approve
of us moving the patient.
Chase, can I talk to you
outside for a second?
You just tried this.
I'm not a better liar than Foreman.
Sure, you are.
You're descended
from convicts.
Plus, there's no lie
this time.
It's a bait and switch.
You propose that we
don't have to move him
if we do
a pneumoencephalograph.
That's 60-year-old technology
that killed patients.
Exactly. He'll compromise
on the C.T.
This isn't Cuddy.
Your Jedi mind tricks
won't work here.
These aren't the droids
you're looking for.
You don't trust me.
Going behind your back
works better
when you're not facing us.
Instead of whatever lie
you're gonna tell Broda,
why don't you just tell him
the truth?
If we are honest
and reasonable--
people of all races
and creeds
will live together
in peace and harmony.
How did your first plan
work out?
Permission granted.
Thank you.
After she gets denied,
do the bait and switch.
They won't let your mommy
back in the hospital
because of an emergency
downstairs.
But we have to get
started.
I can't do it
without my Lamby.
Who is she?
I'm nobody.
I'm leaving soon.
Her name is Sam,
and she's a friend of mine.
What does Lamby usually do
while you get your treatment?
He holds my hand.
Well, you could hold
my hand.
That won't work.
Well, sometimes
we have to do things
that we don't want to do.
You have to go to school.
You have to eat your vegetables.
You have to take
your medicine.
You have to.
I want my mommy.
Yeah.
I'll be right back.
You know, I'm
pretty sure Lamby has a cousin
down in the gift shop.
Hold off a minute.
I'm in overtime.
Oh!
Uh, Broda agreed
to C.T. the dad's brain.
Well, that sucks.
But I thought
that's what you wanted.
I shouldn't have
gotten it with the truth.
He's a hypocrite.
His position ever since
he's been here has been--
I-I pointed out
that either we're right,
and he's the hero
for ending the crisis,
or he's right, and he gets to be
the first person
to look at a brain
infected with smallpox.
C.T. scans weren't around
30 years ago.
Good work.
So I guess honesty
is the best policy.
Why'd you say that?
Seriously...
To establish your viewpoint,
as if I didn't already know it,
or to demonstrate
some weird
cross-generational
female solidarity with Cuddy?
Actually, I was just trying
to fill the awkward silence.
Oh.
Why have they stopped?
You can't go out there.
Why did you stop?
Get out of the hallway.
He does not have
smallpox.
Yes, he does.
It itches.
He's just developed
pustules.
He's now too dangerous
to transport.
Get out of the hallway.
Dad's vitals are in the toilet.
He's got
full-blown smallpox.
What about the daughter?
Pustule count is way up.
Vitals are way down.
Means I was wrong.
But to be precise, I was right
before I was wrong, so...
So we just give up
and go home?
Actually, somebody
locked the front door,
but, yeah, we...
Give up.
We might as well keep--
we have our diagnosis.
If you're eager,
you can go find us a new case.
I guess she's eager
or has a blind spot for sarcasm.
I just want to look at the rash
under her arm
to see if it's matured--
you can look through the glass.
I need to be closer.
If the pustules
are at a different stage--
she's comfortable.
We're gonna have our results
back in eight hours.
If it's not smallpox, you can be
the first one in there.
Why are you just standing
out there?
Uh...
I'm just trying
to help.
If you're feeling up to it,
can you sit up and show me
the rash under your arm?
Uh, wait.
The soles of your feet.
There aren't any lesions.
Who cares?
They're everywhere else.
This is torture.
Eve?
Guess who came by
the hospital for a visit?
Hello, Eve.
Oh, no!
All right.
I'm gonna get a couple
of nice nurses to come in here
and get you two ready
for the treatment, all right?
Okay.
How come Lamby can be here
but mommy can't?
Lamby was dirty.
Um, we gave her a bath.
This isn't Lamby!
Julie doesn't have
smallpox.
Did I just dream the part
where I finally agreed
it was smallpox?
Well, if what I thought
was reality
was actually a dream,
then the reverse...
Oh, my God.
I had a threesome
with Beyonce and Lady Gaga.
She doesn't have pustules
on her palms
or the soles
of her feet.
The dad
does have pustules there.
So how does he get smallpox,
but it skips her?
If I leave like that,
you should follow.
Oh.
We gave it to him.
Where's Chase?
You do realize we don't
all live together, right?
Well, then just--
we gave it to him.
No pustules
on the daughter's palms, so...
So therefore
your theory is
you asked me to take
the dad's blood,
but I accidentally
injected him
with smallpox.
Exactly, although technically,
it was the vaccinia virus,
which is what the smallpox
vaccine is made from.
Same symptoms as smallpox,
but only half the calories and
almost none of the lethality.
You sound like one
of those anti-vaccine cranks.
You can't develop
full-blown symptoms
from the vaccine
this quickly.
You can if you're
immunocompromised.
Am I the only one
who reads these things?
Dad had kidney cancer.
Six years ago.
He's been in remission.
Well, it's obviously back.
Shot his immune system,
made him vulnerable
to the vaccinia,
which will get better
on interferon.
So if he responds
to the treatment,
that proves
he doesn't have smallpox.
Then what does
the daughter have?
Damn. I was hoping
you weren't gonna ask me that.
Can we please just focus
on the disease we just diagnosed
and can treat?
What's more likely--
he got smallpox
the day after
we immunized him for it,
or he's sick
from the vaccine itself?
You got any proof
the kidney cancer is back?
Well, let me give him this.
When he gets better,
that'll be the proof you need.
I'll put on one
of your fancy spacesuits,
and I promise I won't kiss him
on an open sore.
You know
who Janet Parker is?
In 1978,
she was working
at a university in England.
Someone in a research lab
on the floor below screwed up.
Some smallpox virus managed
to float up through the vents
into the room
where she was working.
She died
four days later--
the last known person
to die from smallpox.
And the person
in charge of the lab
was so destroyed,
he killed himself.
Now that he's shedding,
I can't open that door
for anyone.
Hey!
Look, there's
the proof you need.
There's blood
in the urine bag.
His kidneys
are shutting down.
He's in the final stages
of the disease.
If smallpox was causing
the kidney failure,
the blood would be brown.
It's red because
the kidney cancer is back,
and this is not smallpox.
I'm not opening
that door.
Well, that makes one of us.
Hey!
You're insane!
But I'm right.
I hope you are,
because I can't let you
out now.
This is what happens
when you have no respect
for authority,
no respect
for anything.
You don't think
it's a little much
to use the threat of death
to win a totally separate
argument with your boyfriend?
You think this is
about the other thing?
Does seem to track
suspiciously closely.
I don't care right now
that you lied to me.
I want you to stay alive.
And if I do, does that mean
I win both arguments?
Put the suit on.
It's unnecessary, mom.
This is why I didn't want
them telling you.
It's why I'm glad
they didn't tell Wilson.
Dr. House.
I'm getting worse,
aren't I?
Interferon takes
a little time to work.
Don't worry.
Tell Broda
that I'm increasing
his oxygen.
And get my team down here.
Hi.
You're mad at us,
aren't you?
Yeah.
Well, you have a right to be.
We weren't honest.
You might not know
this yet,
but sometimes
adults mess up.
Can I tell you something,
and you keep it
just between us?
I'm not great with kids.
I love them,
but I get scared
that I'm gonna do
the wrong thing,
and then...
I usually do.
And that's what I did
with the lying.
And I'm very sorry
about that.
The reason why
I did the wrong thing
was because
I was trying to get you
to do the right thing.
Your mommy and your Lamby
both really need you
to get better.
So...
Do you think that...
You could be
really brave...
And do the right thing?
I'll try.
Great.
Fever's way up.
Sat's way down.
Pustules still spreading.
Interferon's not working.
Which means this is smallpox.
Right!
'Cause there are only
two diseases
in the whole wide world--
what else could it be?
There's got to be something.
No, there doesn't.
There are still no pustules
on her feet.
All the reasons you thought
it wasn't smallpox still exist.
Forget her feet.
Forget all those other reasons.
Look at him now.
The pox are dome-shaped.
They're on 80% of his body,
and they're not scabbing over.
This is textbook smallpox.
Ddx'ing at this point
isn't gonna make a difference.
Don't say that.
I'm sorry.
House...
You screwed up
going in there.
You have any fever?
Not yet.
But when it does come,
I assume you'll see
the pettiness
of being mad at me
for lying.
Shut up, House.
I'll be right back.
I'm not gonna make it,
am I?
You should say good-bye
to your family.
I love you.
Just hold on.
Fight this.
You got to take care
of my boy.
No.
Promise me.
I promise.
I love you.
I love you too.
Get Roger closer.
Come closer.
Come on.
Dad.
My baby boy.
Dad, please...
It's gonna be okay.
Lulu's gonna
take care of you.
I don't want her, dad.
She's not you.
I will always
love you, Roger.
Dad?
You're killing me!
The suit will protect you
if you haven't already
been exposed.
My air supply's
almost out.
We'll give you
another canister.
Yeah, and when I change it,
I will be exposed.
Just move him!
I wish I could.
Oh, that's great,
'cause you know
what you can do?
You can move me.
You don't know
that I have smallpox yet.
We have to assume.
There's another isolation room
on the fifth floor.
The problem is getting him
from here to there.
So it's inconvenient.
My having
a fighting chance at life
is inconvenient!
I'm sorry.
We don't know
that he'll catch it.
We don't know that
it's definitely smallpox,
not until we get the DNA results
back from the CDC.
What do you think
the dad just died of?
Would it kill us
to talk it through?
Kill us? No.
Save House? Also no.
Even if by some miracle
it's not smallpox,
there's nothing more
for us to go on.
There's no new data.
And there isn't going
to be any--
where are you going?
To get more data.
"Gerritt seems distant
and preoccupied."
Who's Gerritt?
Is he a slave?
Gerritt is the Captain's kitty.
The Captain's cat
is preoccupied?
Skip the cat.
Uh, "one goat
slaughtered for dinner.
Broke out the next barrel
of wine."
Skip the food.
Uh, c-can we go back
to the cat?
Did the cat get sick?
Smallpox
is exclusive to humans.
Ship captains
didn't have pets.
Nothing and nobody
went on those ships
if it didn't have
a purpose.
Hunting mice and rats?
For the crew.
The hold was probably
infested with mice.
What if that's
the difference?
What happened to Gerritt?
Ah.
Is that a sad "ah"
or a cute "ah"?
Gerritt, he died.
It's a sad "ah."
Before he died,
did he lose his fur?
How did you know?
Mice don't carry smallpox,
but they do carry
rickettsialpox.
Which is treatable.
Just start them
on doxycycline.
Based on a bald cat?
You never heard of shedding?
What's the downside?
If we shove her full of
antibiotics plus the antivirals,
it'll suppress
her bone marrow.
That girl's
about to die.
She probably is,
and I don't want to risk
pushing her over the edge.
At least look
at the dad's body.
Small patches of black, dead
tissue will prove I'm right.
Eschars appear
with rickettsialpox
but not with smallpox.
If he had developed eschars,
I would have noticed.
You haven't been within 20 feet
of the guy in hours.
Have them check.
Their job
is to bleach the body,
kill the virus,
and get it out of there
for Dr. House's sake.
Bleaching the body
will destroy all evidence
of rickettsialpox.
There is no evidence!
I'm not trying to hurt
anyone here.
I'm not lying to you.
This is smallpox.
House, you have
to examine the body.
I'm not going
anywhere near it.
Look for eschars.
Hurry.
You think it's r-pox?
The Captain had a cat.
He lost his fur
and then died.
Step back, Dr. House.
It's kind of hard to do
an autopsy in oven mitts.
Take them off.
Says the woman
standing behind
two panes of glass.
Do you believe me?
Forget me.
Do you believe you?
You think it's rickettsialpox,
don't you?
If it is, it's curable,
and she's gonna die
unless we can prove it.
You really are annoying.
Come on, House.
Come on.
Eschar.
Eschars.
Start the girl
on doxycycline right now.
Mommy!
You were good with her.
Yeah, only after
being bad.
It takes practice.
Maybe I should get
a puppy.
Yeah, or...
Pregnant?
Hey.
You're gonna be okay.
Buy you breakfast?
No, thanks.
You can pay...
If it's starting to feel
like I'm carrying you.
House, stop.
When I was dying...
You realized that a little
white lie between coworkers
wasn't such a big deal.
Yeah, and that
was true...
When you were dying.
www.tvsubtitles.net