Bajar lo.
Get him down.
♪ House 7x08 ♪
Small Sacrifices
Original Air Date on November 22, 2010
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
♪ ♪
What you got
against chickens?
One got choked last night,
thanks to you.
33-year-old male
with hemoptysis, fever...
Can't we even talk
about it?
You can't apologize,
we can't talk.
And puncture wounds.
I'm not apologizing
for doing the right thing.
Lying to me
was not the right thing.
Puncture wounds
are from a crucifixion.
I lied
to save my patient's life.
I didn't lie to you.
I lied to my boss.
Either of those arguments
working yet?
I guess that means
I don't have to go
to the wedding on Saturday.
The Hospital's
Chairman of the Board?
I'm not gonna stand him up,
and neither are you.
I loathe weddings
and their seven levels
of hypocrisy.
But you do seem
awfully hissy.
And there's an outside chance
that I could get you drunk
and score.
So as long as you don't take it
as an admission of guilt,
sure,
count me in.
A bit too much honesty?
You're also going
to the rehearsal dinner
Friday night.
Dressy casual.
Housekeeping.
Either you're crazy
or you're atoning
for something naughty
and you're crazy.
He's a doctor.
I'm not atoning
for anything.
That answers that.
Thanks.
My Marisa was diagnosed
with terminal brain cancer.
Stage iv glioblastoma.
When the doctors said
she had two months to live,
that's when I made my bargain.
With your health insurance
carrier?
With God.
Oh.
I told him
I would nail myself
to a cross every year
he kept her alive.
How did that negotiation go?
You lowballed with ear piercing
and God countered?
Three weeks later,
she was cancer-free.
And that was four years ago.
Pontius Pilate--
misunderstood oncologist.
My ex-wife thinks
I'm crazy too.
She moved out
the first time I did this.
Well, at least your daughter
has one viable role model.
You don't believe
in God?
I did.
Then I grew my curly hairs.
So how do you think
I was cured?
Maybe you were misdiagnosed
in the first place.
You have your answer,
doctors.
We have ours.
Causal determinism.
We are hardwired
to need answers.
The cave man who heard a rustle
in the bushes
checked out to see what it was
lived longer than the guy
who assumed
it was just a breeze.
The problem is, when we
don't find a logical answer,
we settle
for a stupid one.
Ritual is what happens
when we run out
of rational.
If you're done mocking him,
we need to prep
for an lp.
Good.
Another hole in him
should really make God's day.
Why are you late?
Your next dental appointment
isn't till January,
and you just saw your gp
eight days ago.
You think stage iv glioblastoma
in an eight-year-old
could disappear
in three weeks?
I had a flat tire.
Your patient has cancer?
Your tires got less
than 5,000 miles on them.
No, and neither does
my patient's daughter.
I hit a piece of rebar
near a construction site.
In three weeks?
It's highly unlikely.
There's no construction site
between here
and your home.
I agree.
I think it was
a misdiagnosed cyst.
But there is one
between here and my dry cleaner.
It could be
a misdiagnosis,
or it could be
spontaneous remission.
But...
Why would I lie
about this?
I don't know yet.
But you would have dropped off
your tie.
It's got a mustard stain.
I was buying
an engagement ring.
I'm gonna propose to Sam
at the wedding.
That is the second stupidest
thing I've heard today.
And I'm surprised
how close you came.
You don't need
to buy her a new ring.
Isn't the first one good
for all you can marry?
I assume you haven't apologized
to Cuddy yet.
Your stupidity demands
equal time.
Nothing to apologize for.
Pretend to apologize.
You want me to lie?
There's a lovely symmetry
to it.
The lie got you into it.
A lie gets you out of it.
Everybody lies.
I'm sure Cuddy...
Just need to give her
a chance.
Yeah, that must have been
what I meant.
Have you seen
the bride-to-be?
Gorgeous woman
half his age.
He's a lucky guy.
Yeah, for a while.
My father's 19 years older
than my mother,
and they've been happily married
for 32 years.
I'm guessing your dad wasn't
on the Forbes 400
and your mom didn't look
like a swimsuit model.
Sorry.
That didn't come out right.
My father was the classics chair
at Columbia,
and my mother was his student.
His gorgeous student.
What's it mean
when somebody takes
their cell phone
into the bathroom
when they're taking
a shower?
It means they don't want you
to check their calls,
emails, or texts.
If we're talking
about your wife,
it means the chickens
are coming home to roost.
Taub has been known
to dabble.
Used to be.
Maybe it's just a habit.
I do that with my cell phone,
and I live alone.
She has a meeting today
at 1:30.
At a hotel.
I'm gonna go
with the chicken thing.
Negative for toxocara,
bacteroides,
ascaris,
everything.
So what looks
like an infection
but doesn't test
like one?
Animals.
I'm sure
your wife's just seeing a dude.
Patient works
for Morgan Timber Works.
Card's in the file.
Specializing in stables,
barns, and stalls.
He works around animals.
Rhodococcus equi.
Unless this guy's
sleeping in the manger...
Or has a history
of open wounds.
We think you have
rhodococcus equi,
a horse infection.
It's pretty rare in humans,
but easily treatable
with antibiotics.
Does it make
your teeth fall out?
No.
Then again,
maybe we were wrong.
Fever,
coughing up blood,
coughing up teeth.
So either God sweetened the deal
with a "no flossing" clause
or...
Radiation sickness.
Yeah, maybe the carpenter
builds microwave ovens.
Kaposi's sarcoma?
No skin lesions.
Heavy metal poisoning fits.
Canned tuna, Sushi,
lead paint.
Heavy metal it is.
Do a home search
and a peripheral smear.
I can't.
I have
a personal errand to run.
Trying to catch
your wife cheating?
Oh...
Why would you say that?
Missing mojo.
Posture's slumped.
Expression defeated.
Didn't try to back up
your theory.
And Chase told me.
Go.
Find your mojo.
Shopkeeper?
I need a patient file.
Ask records.
Not one of our patients.
My patient's daughter.
Ask your patient.
He thinks I only want it
to debunk his faith.
And why would he think that?
Because he's strangely
perceptive for an idiot.
And I'm going to violate
patient privacy laws
just to keep you happy?
You keep me happy,
I return the favor.
Think of it
as tat for tit.
When we're at work,
we need to focus
on our work thoughts.
Why are you wearing that?
It's my dressy casual.
What do you think?
You look like Wilson.
It looks weird.
Well, you knew
I'd think that.
Which makes me wonder
why you look disappointed.
If you prick me,
do I not bleed?
You knew I wouldn't like it,
but you thought
I would say I did.
That's what this is about.
You're trying to trap me
into lying to you.
You sure?
'Cause that sounds
so juvenile.
You're okay
with burglary now?
I asked his permission.
The reason
we don't ask permission
is we're afraid the patient
is going
to hide something,
but our patient
hasn't been home,
lives alone.
He doesn't have any help,
and he has no motive
to hide anything.
Did you ask
for his key too?
Oh, doesn't have one.
And now we know why.
You think he's crazy?
Crucifixion's
pretty convincing evidence.
Lead paint?
The place is too new.
He believes in a higher power
that can affect his life.
Like most people
on the planet.
True.
On the other hand,
crucified himself.
No canned tuna.
And I don't think we have
to worry about Sushi.
No computer.
No television.
No music.
What does he do?
He reads.
Prayer's been proven
to aid recovery.
Only if the person knows
they're being prayed for.
Means there's
no objective effect.
So faith comes from within.
Not exactly a newsflash.
I guess worry is good
for the waistline.
It's not worry.
It's starvation.
His tooth didn't fall out
because
of heavy metal poisoning.
It fell out
because of malnutrition.
He does have rhodococcus equi.
Taub was right.
He just didn't know why.
It's locked.
I'm busy!
I'll wait.
I really am busy.
Cuddy got me
the daughter's file.
Well, not Cuddy exactly.
Her signature.
Well, not exactly
her signature.
Another lie?
Thought you could take
a look at it for me.
Maybe you hadn't heard.
I'm kind of busy.
With what?
Sudoku.
What do you think?
I'm the head of oncology
at a major hospital.
And yet these files
are not from this hospital.
These are from
where-my-fiancee-works memorial.
Sam's boss is doing
a clinical review
of all of her files,
and she just wanted
to make sure
everything was in order
before he starts on Monday.
Which explains why Sam
is too busy to look at my file.
If I don't help her, she can't
go to the wedding and...
We fell in love
at her cousin's wedding,
which is why I want
to propose to her at a wedding.
And now you have 60 seconds
to berate me for that
and for helping my girlfriend
with her homework.
You don't want to propose
at a wedding.
Emotions running high,
people on edge.
You ought to try somewhere
like a buddhist temple
or an aquarium.
Or a buddhist aquarium.
That only took ten seconds.
You can spend the rest
of the time on my file.
Rachel?
Hey.
How long before you're home?
Not long.
Uh, hey.
Hey.
Uh, you left your laptop on.
Saw you today.
At the hotel.
Were you checking up on me?
Yes.
Satisfied?
Good.
That's it?
You said
you're satisfied.
It's enough.
You're not wondering
why it started.
That makes me think
you don't want
to talk about this,
which makes me think...
You're being paranoid.
You took your cell phone
with you
into the bathroom
when you took your shower
this morning.
I made a new friend.
Online.
In a support group.
A guy?
Yes.
A support group for what?
For people
with unfaithful spouses.
Why didn't you tell us
you were starving yourself?
Well, I wasn't trying to.
I'm on a tight budget,
and it seemed like an okay diet.
Well, you seem
to be felling better.
Not really.
My legs are killing me.
How bad is the pain?
On a scale of one to ten,
ten being the worst.
9 1/2.
Then why are you smiling?
I'm not smiling.
Leg pain
and pseudobulbar affect.
He's feeling one emotion
while unknowingly expressing
another one.
Classic neurohecatia.
Two days
of anticholinergics,
you'll be walking
out of here.
Really?
No.
I just made that up
to see your reaction.
Diagnostic test.
This is awesome.
33-year-old carpenter
presenting with narcissism,
delusions of grandeur,
hallucinations.
He hasn't had hallucinations.
I'm not talking about him.
I'm talking about "him"
with a capital "o-m-g."
You want us to do
a differential diagnosis
on Jesus?
Hears voices,
thinks he's the son of God.
Probably schizophrenic.
I think you offended him.
You're saying the patient's
religious extremism
could be a symptom.
A neuro disorder could explain
all his delusions.
Get an MRI
of his brain.
Let's see
if we can find God.
Heard you got
the daughter's file.
Patient change his mind?
I forged your signature.
Thank you
for your honesty.
Think of it
as a present.
See, somebody is about
to turn the big 4-5
in several months,
and somebody else
wants to make
a very big deal of it.
4-3.
Are you sure?
Very.
How could I make
such a mistake?
In reading
your H.R. file?
Oh, no, wait,
I didn't.
And boom goes the dynamite.
Scores are tied.
We are even Steven.
You're right.
I did lie.
To H.R.
Not to you.
When I first applied
for the VP Admin job,
I was 29 years old.
I knew I would be taken
more seriously
if I were
in my early 30s,
so I added two years
to my age.
You lied
to make yourself older?
Are you lying
about being a woman?
Even if you can trap me,
you think I'll suddenly embrace
the value of lying?
My point is
you already have.
I just need to prove it.
Chickens aren't roosting.
She's just got a friend.
A guy she met
in an online support group
for cheating spouses.
I've heard
of that group.
It's called irony.
You think
she's cheating on her spouse
with someone from
a cheating spouse support group?
Sounds like the perfect place
to hit on vulnerable women.
Look.
Multiple dense lesions.
It looks
like M.S.
How did we miss M.S.?
It was hiding
behind the malnutrition.
M.S. attacks
the immune system.
No system,
no symptoms.
And now we're feeding him,
so they're both back.
How are you feeling?
Terrible.
Obviously.
Where are your friends?
Still casting lots
for your clothes?
All I ask
is that they pray for me.
Always sacrificing.
Very inspirational.
The lesions
are in your temporal lobes.
When those areas
get messed with,
people have
strange experiences--
like hauntings,
alien abductions,
past lives.
Deals with God?
You didn't come
to see if I was better.
You came to see if your medicine
has turned me into an atheist.
I'd settle
for agnostic.
Faith is not a disease.
No, of course not.
On the other hand,
it is communicable,
and it kills
a lot of people.
I can't move my arm.
You feel that?
Your friends
are not praying hard enough.
It's not M.S.
Paralysis is a symptom
of M.S.
So are leg pain
and pseudobulbar affect.
He's getting worse
on the prednisone.
It's not M.S.
The MRI was clear.
He has lesions.
Could be an avm,
cerebral infarction.
Let's put it to the vote.
Vest or cummerbund?
Cummerbund.
You know me.
I can't say no
to any of you guys.
You're all correct.
He has M.S.
But not the friendly
Mr. Rogers M.S.
This is the weird guy
in the panel van kind.
Marburg M.S.?
What did I just say?
He'll be dead in two
to three days at the most.
That's unless we can get
someone
to nail themselves
to a cross as soon as possible.
Or stem cell treatment.
That's
an experimental treatment.
That's had promising results
with demyelinating diseases.
It's our best shot.
It would be if it wasn't
embryonic stem cell treatment.
Our patient's right
of the pope.
He's never gonna consent
to that.
I know that,
and you know that.
He doesn't know that.
But now she knows that,
he's gonna know that.
Way to go.
Confirm marburg.
Then see if he's
a fair-weather flagellator.
You look smashing,
Miss Moneypenny.
Cummerbund?
Very foolish, Mr. Bond.
The daughter's case checks out.
Stereotactic biopsy confirmed
stage iv glioblastoma
multiforme.
Doesn't respond
to chemo,
but they gave it
to her anyway
as a hail Mary
and just got lucky.
So either God intervened,
which is a lazy explanation,
or we just don't know why.
Which is no explanation.
Sometimes
there is no explanation.
And I'm just fine
with that.
Which annoys me to no end.
I need that file,
that chair,
and that desk.
Your woman
is fudging the facts.
Five of those cases,
the stated doses don't explain
the radiation damage.
Sensitivities vary.
Not that much.
Yeah.
That's what I thought.
I asked her point blank
about this.
She said
the dosages were accurate
and that she had done
nothing wrong.
'Cause morally she didn't.
All five patients
were terminal.
She exceeded
the dosing protocols
to try to save their life.
You would have done
the same.
She's a sap,
and she's perfect for you.
I hate rehearsal dinners
almost as much
as I hate weddings.
The only reason
anyone gets married
is that homo erectus females
needed protection
from predators
while breast feeding.
The only reason
these two are getting married
is to throw
an obnoxious gala
and make the rest of us
feel unworthy.
Even though we know
in two years
their lawyers
are gonna be fighting
over the Bentleys.
That'll make
a lovely toast.
She's got looks.
He's got money.
One of them is
bound to run out.
I give it 19 months.
That's very specific.
No fault divorce in New Jersey
requires couples to live
at least 18 months apart.
I'm actually only giving it
a few weeks.
Oh. Thought I was supposed
to be the dark one.
Not today.
Yeah.
You're gonna have
to go stag.
My patient
is refusing treatment.
And you care?
No.
But it's an excuse
you can't argue with.
Accepting this treatment
is an insult
to God.
I can't expect him
to keep our deal.
You already broke it.
Your blood test showed
you were loaded
with ibuprofen.
Taking painkillers
breaks my deal?
The point
is to suffer
like your savior did,
right?
Well, he didn't take myrrh,
the Tylenol of ancient Rome.
And his nails went
through his wrists,
not through his palms.
Palms are for sissies.
And what about the 39 lashes
and the beatings
and the crown of thorns?
What you go through
is closer to a bad manicure
than a crucifixion.
It's not about showing God
my pain.
It's about showing him
my faith.
If he asks me
to die for my daughter,
I'll do it gladly.
Don't make this
about your daughter.
You're just worried that
if we find a cure,
that it'll cost you
your faith.
And then you'll be
like the rest of us.
Alone and afraid?
You're right.
I don't want that.
You're smiling.
Does that mean
that you're comfortable
with your choice?
Or that you're afraid?
Because this may be
your only hope.
You can prescribe
a lot of things,
but hope isn't one of 'em.
Sticking by your convictions
and damning
the consequences.
You two have a lot
in common.
You're both idiots.
All conviction's
equally ridiculous?
Just when they're applied
indiscriminately
to all circumstances.
He needs to see
his daughter.
inherit the wind.
And tell her he's dying
because God doesn't want him
to take his medicine.
Honesty's not all bad.
Get her in here.
You don't have to die,
not if you take their medicine.
The treatment
violates God's laws.
He doesn't want me
to take it.
But God doesn't want you
to die.
He doesn't want anyone to die.
He's all about love.
I know
this is coming from your mother.
This is coming from me.
I'm the one
who almost died.
I know
what it's like.
And you're my dad.
You can't die.
I wish I didn't have to.
You don't have to,
daddy.
Just take the medicine.
You always tell me
to take the medicine.
Please.
One day,
you're going to understand.
No, I'm not.
I am never going
to understand that.
If God could do this,
I hate God.
♪ ♪
♪ sometimes I get my head ♪
♪ in a dilly ♪
♪ feeling so lost ♪
♪ ticking you off ♪
I just spotted
a couple of hot girls
by the chocolate fountain.
Weren't you just upstairs
with...
And it wouldn't have happened
if not for you, buddy.
Someone had to distract
the sober friend.
I'm not here
to be your wingman.
I'll be your wingman
this time.
I didn't come here
to get laid.
Then don't.
Talking to beautiful women
isn't nearly as much fun
as watching Taub
not talking
to his wife.
I went
through your emails.
There's nothing in there
that's inappropriate.
We're friends, Chris.
But you tell him things
that you've never told me.
I tell him things
I can't tell you.
That's the point.
Not things about me.
About you.
About your new job.
About coloring your hair.
About how you felt
when your mother died.
I want to know
those things.
He's easy to talk to.
He's open and honest.
He makes me feel safe.
Sounds like you love him.
I am not having
an affair.
He lives in Oregon.
I've never met him.
I probably never will.
You are having an affair.
An emotional one.
Are you equating
what I'm doing
with what you did?
I've done terrible things
to you,
and I deserve all of this
and more,
but you can't pretend that
what you're doing isn't hurtful.
Someone looks lovely tonight.
Thank you.
I meant me.
Someone else
looks simply stunning.
That was you.
And the blonde at the bar.
Just to be clear,
this whole little act
isn't gonna work.
I need an apology.
Not flattery.
It's not an act.
It's the wedding.
You hate weddings.
I thought I did.
Then I realized
I've never been to one.
Never?
Turns out
they're kind of fun.
Well, I can't complain
about my boss.
He's right here.
You're his boss?
Um...
I'm sorry
about your daughter.
I never meant
to hurt her.
You just thought
she would change my mind.
I was surprised
she didn't.
So was I.
I didn't tell you the truth.
When I said
I'm not afraid to die.
But you're going
straight to heaven, so...
That's what I believe,
but I'm human.
So you know
you may be wrong.
How could you do
what you just did?
That's why we have beliefs.
So we can still see
the right thing to do
when we're blinded
with doubt and fear.
Our beliefs
define us.
If we lose them,
who are we?
Look, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean
for it to go that way.
You think
I'm being selfish,
but I'm not.
He makes me feel better
about me and about us.
Well, that is hard
to believe,
because all I feel
right now is betrayed.
I never wanted that.
Good.
Because just like you asked me
to stop my behavior,
I'm asking you
to stop this.
No?
I'm not gonna lie
to you.
Is this revenge?
I don't know.
But I do know
that it's something
I need right now.
What would you wear?
Well, I'm a sucker
for the white gown.
Traditionally
for young, first-time brides.
Well, I may not be young,
but I'll be first-time.
That is a lie.
You were married before.
1987 for six days.
Your knowledge
of New Jersey divorce law
made me suspicious,
so I looked it up.
So this was all your trap?
Trap's primitive.
I prefer inveiglement.
Anyway, the point is,
I lied to you,
you lied to me,
I forgive you.
Well played.
You're tired,
aren't you?
All those files?
No.
No, I was thinking...
I mean,
if those two
even have the slightest chance
of making it,
then we have to be
a sure thing.
And we've already made
all our mistakes.
And...
I've come to realize
that I love you even more
than I thought I did.
Sam,
will you marry me again?
Wow.
I don't even know
what to say.
I have a suggestion.
Where did this even
come from?
When did you...
You just came to realize
what made you love me even more?
Everything
you've done.
Your work.
Your...
Your sense of morality.
The five cases.
I not only agree
with what you did.
I admire it.
I didn't do anything.
You already asked me
about the files.
And I told you the truth.
I know.
And I get it.
You don't believe me.
I believe that you
are a wonderful person.
Who lies and cheats.
No, Sam, listen.
I'm on your side.
I can't believe this.
What?
Sam.
Sam, don't do this...
♪ Rollercoaster ♪
♪ of love ♪
♪ rollercoaster ♪
♪ Your love is like
a roller coaster ♪
♪ baby baby ♪
So how many do you think?
At least three.
A hat trick,
Chase.
See?
The life of the bachelor.
All of the sex,
none of the guilt.
It's not over, okay?
I just really miscalculated.
I thought she'd forgiven me
for everything.
All those hurt feelings,
they never really went away.
That makes a lot more sense.
Ignore him.
He just got an idea.
I have one more test
to run.
Ugh.
I hate weddings.
It won't be long now.
You'll be staring down the
yawning void before you know it.
You came from a wedding
to tell me that?
Nope.
I came from a wedding
to run a PET scan.
I thought
you'd given up on me.
I have.
PET scan was for your daughter.
I was wrong
about her.
She did have glioblastoma.
And she still does.
The cancer never went away.
Yes, it did.
They tested her
every year.
With a CT scan.
Which misses
all the tiny, little tumors
that a PET scan doesn't.
You've made a mistake.
She does not
have cancer anymore.
I ran it twice.
No mistake.
Looks like God broke
your deal.
I'm sorry.
But I'm also right.
You're a bastard.
Do whatever you want to me.
Good call.
Surprised you've got enough
strength to come to work today.
36 hours is long enough
for me to recover.
And not nearly long enough for
this guy to be getting better.
House wanted us checking
every 12 hours anyway.
Sorry I took off on you.
Twice?
First one was my bad.
Second one,
I had no choice.
It was a threesome.
They're overrated.
He's bluffing.
Get house.
Got something to show you.
Your daughter's PET scan.
It's clean.
She's fine.
My bad.
Got her mixed up
with Marion Silver.
Marisa Silva.
That's believable, right?
Anyhow, good news for you,
bad news for Mr. Silver.
You tricked me.
God didn't break our deal.
I did.
You led me
into temptation.
And I followed.
And God will punish you
for that.
He has to.
'Cause if he didn't,
well, that would
make you wonder, wouldn't it?
He will.
Well, that's
why I'm so confused
by this.
This is your MRI.
Shows incremental improvement.
You're getting better.
I double-checked the name
on this one.
But it's not all good news.
This patient is screwed.
Technical term
is dead as a doornail.
Who is that?
God.
You broke your deal
with him,
your daughter's fine,
you're getting better.
Nothing bad happened.
Which can only mean
one thing.
There is no God.
Of course, if your daughter
gets hit by a meteorite today,
I would have some serious egg
on my face.
You're smiling.
I assume
that means you're miserable.
It means
I'm happy.
It doesn't mean
God doesn't exist.
It just means he's--
he's truly merciful.
My beautiful Marisa
was right.
God is all about love.
Punishment is proof of God,
and no punishment
is proof of God?
Ingenious argument.
Faith isn't an argument.
I'd like to see my daughter.
Everyone else knew?
Everyone I could trust.
So yes.
If you had told me,
he'd be dead by now.
So why do I still want
to tell the truth?
Either you're naive
or you have scruples.
I'm not sure
which is worse.
This is insane.
We can't work like this.
I can.
Sam?
Sorry. I was hoping to be done
before you got home.
We had a fight.
We had one fight.
And I admitted
I was wrong.
We can talk about it.
We can get over it.
This is about trust.
I never lied to you
about anything.
I know.
And I always trusted you.
I...
Maybe we could talk
to a counselor.
You said that helped
after our divorce.
It did.
And I think I changed a lot.
And I haven't?
This is my fault?
I know
where this is going.
And I don't want
to go there again.
You're quitting, Sam.
You're quitting again.
So I guess
you haven't changed that much.
♪ ♪
Good work today.
I don't even think
your patient's gonna sue.
It looks
like everybody's happy.
I've been an idiot.
I got this argument
stuck in my head.
If everybody lies,
then trust is not only unfounded
and pointless,
it's fictional.
But trust
is not an argument
that can be won or lost.
Maybe I just have to suspend
my cynicism and believe.
Maybe it's time
I took a leap of faith.
I'm sorry.
I won't lie to you again.
♪ You've got such
a pretty smile ♪
Thank you.
♪ ♪
♪ it's a shame
the things you ♪
♪ Hide behind it ♪
♪ ♪
♪ let 'em go
give it up ♪
Sam left me.
What a moron.
Too soon.
I'm still in love with her.
I meant you.
Do you have a drink?
Or drinks?
Cuddy's coming over.
Does she know you're here?
I apologized to her.
♪ I know there's nowhere
you can hide it ♪
Good for you.
♪ Trust me ♪
Not really.
I lied.
♪ And don't keep that
on the inside ♪
♪ soon you ♪
I just took your advice.
Too bad you didn't.
♪ You'll be locked out
on your own ♪
Good for you.
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
www.tvsubtitles.net