What's the difference
between a sea lion
and a seal?
What's that, baby?
What's the difference
between a sea lion and a seal?
Um, seals tell the truth,
but a sea lion's always lyin'?
A sea lion has ears.
Yeah, that's right.
I forgot.
I'll show you
when we get to the zoo.
Can we have
pizza tonight?
I'm not gonna
be here, Daisy. I'm--
I'm going back
on the road, remember?
You've only been here
for two days.
I'll be back
in three weeks this time.
Somebody help her!
She's having
a seizure!
On the track?
Yeah, there's a lady
down there.
Daddy, come back!
Daddy!
Hey.
Lady, are you okay?
Come on, come on,
hey, wake up!
Come on! Get up!
Hey!
Come on.
Help me!
Somebody help me!
Come on!
Hurry up!
Aah!
Daddy!
Move the train!
Hey, man, are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
She's epileptic.
Come on,
let's get you up.
You got her?
Yeah, we got her.
Hey, sweetie, I'm okay.
Daddy?
♪ House 7x09 ♪
Larger Than Life
Original Air Date on January 17, 2010</font1
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
♪ ♪
I found this case, uh,
in the E.R.--
white male, mid 30s,
loss of consciousness,
abnormal EKG.
And he's the subway hero.
Your enthusiasm
is impressive.
Wish I could say
the same
about
your presentation.
Everybody knows you lead
with your most
interesting symptom.
You're right.
EKG is
more interesting
than loss
of consciousness, so--
God, she's still talking.
Make it stop.
House's worldview
doesn't include random acts
of self-sacrifice.
He's gonna count heroism
as a symptom
until proven otherwise.
The guy did
a wonderful thing.
Can't we just take that
at face value?
You are adorable.
Heroism does exist.
What about the guy
who landed the plane
in the Hudson?
News flash--that guy
was already on the plane.
For all we know, he would have
killed everyone else on board
if it increased
his chances.
Faced with
almost certain death,
a normal person
rides the pine.
What about firefighters?
The guys who undergo
months of training
to deny their own instincts
for self-preservation?
And the patient
isn't a firefighter.
He plays a bass in a band.
So humanity
is apathetic
and self-serving?
Yeah.
I was mugged once.
When I saw the gun,
my legs went out.
I always thought
it was fight or flight.
Didn't know it was
fight or flight or faint.
Laugh all you want.
The other hundred people
stayed on that platform.
That's a normal response
to danger.
The coward has spoken.
Our patient's problem
is neurological.
Sympathetic stimulation--
stress to the brain
triggers a response
in the heart.
Go forth
and look for masses
in Clark Kent's
limbic system.
Seems like you're getting
a bit of attention.
Everyone keeps going
out of their way
asking me
if I need anything.
It's kind of nice.
So what happened
out there?
I don't really remember.
It's just images,
like flashes.
I kind of went
on autopilot.
My memory doesn't go
back into real time
until I was
in the ambulance.
I read
that's pretty common
for people
in life-or-death situations.
Jack.
Honey.
Uh, this is my wife, Eva.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
They're just
doing some tests.
How's Daisy?
She's not so good,
actually.
She watched her father
jump in front of a train.
Ugh.
She's still shaking.
She can't stop crying.
Why would you do that
to her?
He saved a woman's life.
He could have died.
Did you even think
about your family?
I need your advice.
Dinner with your mom
on Thursday.
It's my birthday.
I know.
I'm definitely coming,
but Wilson's got tickets
to the Hong Kong film festival.
Ever since his breakup,
he's been a mess.
I haven't been able to tell him
that I'm not going,
so maybe if you
happen to see him,
you could mention
how important this is.
You should go.
What? I can't.
It's your birthday.
Oh, it's--it's--
it's fine.
It's sweet that you care
about your friend,
and, frankly, as you will
find out sooner or later,
my mother is a handful.
Go.
I need your advice.
This film festival.
I have had these tickets
for two months.
Yeah, I know.
I'm definitely coming.
Okay.
But Thursday
is Cuddy's birthday,
and her mom's coming down--
it's a whole dinner thing.
And I thought,
maybe if you see her,
you could mention
how upset you've been.
You have to go.
Your girlfriend's
birthday?
It's not even a question.
She has one every year.
How often do you break up
with the love of your life?
Okay, for you, it's more often
than most, but still...
I'm a big boy.
I think I'll survive.
I will definitely
make this up to you.
[Sports announcer
speaking indistinctly on radio]
Hey.
Am I imagining things,
or did I see a billboard
with your face on it
on my way home tonight?
Oh, was my whole face there?
'Cause I just saw the nose.
I thought you said
they were taking a picture
of a bunch
of doctors together.
They did.
I have no idea
how it ended up just me.
Well, you are pretty cute.
You're flirting with me?
I don't see anyone else
in the room.
What?
I don't know.
Things have been
a little tense around here
since that whole
online-boyfriend thing.
Phil's not my boyfriend.
I'm not the one
with the problem.
No, you're the one
with feelings for someone else.
You're still my husband.
I still love you.
And I want things
to be okay between us.
Also, you're
a famous model now.
That's pretty cool...
Sexy, even.
So I advance through
the carotid bifurcation...
Are you asking?
Yes, I'm asking.
I've only read
how to do it.
Practice is different
than theory.
Just tell me how to do it.
You're going to inject dye
just past the takeoff
for the optic artery.
Right. Now?
His B.P.'s going up.
The procedure's
stressing his body.
Well, what do I do?
Hold on a minute.
Just give him a chance
to regain equilibrium.
B.P.'s up,
heart rate's 180.
W-what should I do?
Give me the catheter.
Get a crash cart.
He's in cardiac arrest.
Maybe your second time
will go better.
So we finally know
what Taub would look like
if he were life-size.
Can we go back
to the office now?
You kidding?
We got
a differential to run.
Cardiac arrhythmia.
That poster got me laid
when I got home last night,
so do your worst.
Arrhythmia proves
I was right.
Jack's problem is his heart,
not his brain.
So when you're not
on a billboard,
you sleep with nurses.
But when you are,
you sleep with your wife.
I think you got
that backwards.
That's my elbow
in the corner.
What's your wife
doing later?
Huh. They chose you
and cut out Chase?
Apparently,
marketing thinks my face
is the most trustworthy.
For real?
Both of our patients'
cardiac incidents
happened
after physical stress.
I'm guessing
vasovagal syncope?
Buzzkill.
Vasovagal syncope would
manifest at a much younger age.
Could be drugs.
Tox screen was clean.
What about autonomic
nervous system dysfunction?
It could cause arrhythmia
and fainting.
Inappropriate?
I mean,
'cause of the Jew thing?
Autonomic nervous system
dysfunction--
I like it.
Let's biopsy
his pituitary gland.
Adrenal venous sampling
makes more sense
and is a less
invasive procedure...
Which you don't
care about,
because you just want
to check the pituitary,
because you still think
there's something wrong
with the guy's brain?
Can't fool you.
He has no other symptoms
for pituitary disease.
We can't stick
a needle in his brain
because you don't believe
in heroism.
Fine, do it your way.
You'll waste half a day,
but I'm sure he's in no hurry
to get better.
The autonomic nervous system
controls involuntary actions,
like your heartbeat.
If we're right,
it's manageable,
but will progress.
Do you think we can consult
with him?
I didn't know
you knew Dr. Taub.
I don't.
You saw the ads.
Look, no offense,
but you were wrong yesterday.
And they wouldn't have made him
the face of the hospital
if he weren't
really good, right?
Dr. Taub...
The patient
would like to see you.
How can I help?
I forgot.
You guys talk.
Look, no offense
to either of you,
but dinner with your mom?
Come on, I-I'd have to act
like a decent human being,
and you know what a strain
that puts on me.
And, you, ever since
you broke up with Sam,
you've done nothing
but mope and whine.
It's an unbelievable bummer.
And just
what is so exciting
you have to blow off
both of us to do it?
I just want to sit
on my couch in my underwear,
drink scotch,
and watch The Real Housewives
of New Jersey...
By myself.
I just want
one night off.
Is that so much to ask?
Yes.
You have to choose
one of us.
I choose Wilson.
Good...
Because he's coming
to my birthday dinner.
I do not whine.
Jack's not exactly
the hero type.
He started
this band in college.
They gig
around the country,
looking
for their big break.
It's been 16 years.
That must be hard
on you and Daisy.
It's like
I'm a single parent.
I love him so much.
But I'm at the end
of my rope.
What Jack did yesterday
was so incredible,
our boss
assumed his illness
had something to do
with his behavior.
But if that's
not the case,
there's more to him
than you think.
You think Taub
really comes across
as the most
trustworthy doctor here?
I knew it was bugging you.
They cut me out.
You're a pretty boy.
Works well with the ladies,
not so much with the patients.
No one wants an underwear model
performing their splenectomy.
Well, I notice they weren't
exactly knocking down your door
looking
for Dr. Trustworthy.
That's 'cause I'm black.
Cortisol levels look normal.
We were wrong.
Which House will interpret
as him being right.
He's gonna make us biopsy
the pituitary gland.
You seem pretty calm
for a guy
who's surrounded
by racists.
80% of the Princeton
population is white.
Some are racist.
Some aren't.
White works
with both demographics.
So race is your excuse,
not the fact
that you usually look
like you're about
to punch someone in the face?
We're good.
O2 sats are dropping.
He's not breathing.
Suction.
Sats are coming back.
Mucus plug.
That's weird.
Fluid in the lungs.
Pneumonitis?
That doesn't fit
with anyone's theory.
Our tests finally
rule out the brain.
That leaves the heart
and the lungs.
Pneumonitis can be caused
by bacteria,
parasite, some kind
of an obstruction.
Who was the girl
on the tracks?
News story said her name
was Chloe Jeffries.
Why does that matter?
'Cause there's another reason
besides being sick
that he'd risk his life
for a stranger.
She's not a stranger.
The damsel in distress
is an epileptic.
So we assumed she was having
an epileptic seizure,
but what if she wasn't?
What if she's sick too?
Jack is away a lot
on tour.
What happens on the road
stays on the road.
The most likely cause
of pneumonitis is infection.
Shouldn't we be getting
a sputum culture?
There's no
significant elevation
of white
blood cell count.
This is more
like toxic exposure.
He's got a point.
Why is your assumption
of his guilt more valid
than my assumption
of his selflessness?
Because my assumption
is backed up
by millions of men,
and Taub,
who've cheated
on their wives.
Find the girl
and the love nest.
Every hero
has his Kryptonite.
Hello?
So we're breaking
into this girl's apartment
because House thinks
that two people,
standing 30 feet apart
on a subway platform
have to be lovers.
God, you're a drag today.
Let me guess.
Back to fighting with the wife?
No. We had sex
again last night...
Twice...
And again this morning.
Aw.
Rachel hasn't wanted
this much intimacy
in a long time.
I don't think it's me
she's hot for.
It's this Internet guy.
She's just happy,
and that's
turning her on.
So she's
not cheating on you,
and you're getting
all the action you can handle.
I don't see the downside.
What was Jack's band called?
Suicide...Something.
Suicide season.
She does know him.
Question is,
how'd they get sick?
Kryptonite.
EKG's unremarkable,
thyroid, liver, and
kidney function seems fine.
You're perfectly healthy.
I wish that you
would take a second look.
I'm tired all the time,
and when it's cold,
i get this weird pain
in my shoulder.
I have a pain in my leg.
You don't hear me
complaining...
Except for just now.
How do doctors
get this idea
you're better
than everyone else?
Probably
all that pulling people
back from the brink
of death.
It's just a guess.
My own daughter
is a doctor.
She makes a hobby
of dismissing my concerns.
She sounds smart.
Did she tell you
to say that?
I've never met your daughter.
That's hard to believe
since you're currently
shtupping her.
We have a situation.
- Roach bombs, where?
- In Chloe's apartment.
Who's Chloe?
Uh, look,
we don't care
about your personal life.
We're not gonna
tell your wife.
I honestly have no idea
what you're talking about.
Guess who showed up
looking for Jack.
Hey.
Hi.
You okay?
The E.M.T. said you'd gone
to another hospital.
They help me overnight
for observation. I'm fine.
I had to come here to...
I don't know
why you did it,
but thank you.
You're welcome.
I should have brought flowers
or something.
You're like
my guardian angel.
No. I'm just a guy
in a band.
Maybe you've
heard of them?
Suicide season?
One of my nurses
gave me the CD.
I haven't had a chance
to listen to it yet,
but I have a feeling
I'm going to be
your biggest fan.
I'm gonna need you
to cough.
What are you doing?
Getting a sputum culture.
They obviously
don't know each other,
so it's not
toxic exposure.
Just leaves my theory--
infection.
If you could just cough
up a sample,
we can, uh, test
for pathogens.
Um...
Sorry, um...
Sorry, nothing--
there's nothing
coming up.
Well, maybe I can
help you.
Aah!
Ohh! It hurts!
What's the matter?
Round, equal,
reactive to light.
It's not a stroke.
No, it's not my head.
It's my ears.
"When I saw her lying there,
I thought,
"'I can't just stand here
and let her die.
She has her whole life
to live.'"
He didn't jump
because he was sick
or because
he knew that girl.
Even you have
to admit that now.
Yes, but that doesn't
make him a hero.
It makes him
an idiot.
The only reason
that headline doesn't say
"moron crushed by train"
is luck.
Next headline is gonna be
"moron goes undiagnosed
because doctors won't talk
about his ear pain."
Ear pain fits
with my theory.
Jack has an infection
that's spread to his mastoid.
Great. We'll confirm that
in a week,
when your secret cultures
have sprouted.
Am I in trouble?
I only get mad
when you waste my time.
Couldn't care less
about yours.
But let me know when
they come back negative,
and I'll mock you.
You have
a better idea?
Nope, so I'm gonna pick one
at random.
Acoustic neuroma.
A tumor in the ear--
makes sense.
And if it's putting pressure
on the breathing centers in
his brain, explains the lungs.
The lungs
explain the heart.
Evoked auditory
potential test.
This counts as my time.
You guys got this?
I have been going
out of my way
to be nice to old Jewish ladies
for months now
on the off chance
one of them could be your mom.
You couldn't have mentioned
she's a shiksa?
She converted
when she mared my dad.
You see,
now is too late.
I'm not blaming
you for this.
She's the one who ambushed you
to find out what you were like,
because I "never
tell her anything."
I'd have to agree
with her on that one.
Anyway, I obviously
can't come to dinner now.
Obviously?
Well, she's crazy,
and she hates me.
House...
I need you to come
to that dinner for two hours,
keep your mouth shut,
and behave like an adult.
Yes, you will be in hell,
but I will feel better
having you there.
That is
what a relationship is.
We average our misery.
That was...
Unexpected.
I'm having a good day.
I finally resolved
that thing with my sister.
What thing?
Oh, we had
the worst fight
over whether it's time
to put dad in that facility.
Been sick over it
for weeks.
You never mentioned
anything about your sister.
I actually talked a lot
about it with Phil.
I should be getting back.
It's fine now.
I-it's no big deal.
Are you in love with him?
I've never met him.
[Different-pitched tones
beeping]
Waves one and three
normal at 70 decibels.
It's been 37 minutes,
and everything is normal.
House is wrong again.
He doesn't have a tumor.
House doesn't
usually accept
"we gave up halfway"
as an answer.
If I could get fluid closer
to the sources of infection,
I could get
better cultures,
prove my theory.
I'm gonna set up
for an ear drainage
and thoracentesis.
I'll only be wasting
my time.
She's a student.
Somebody's got to go
with her.
I saved that girl.
I did that.
And I'm
really proud of you.
This whole thing
has made me wonder...
If things
could be different.
I have spent so much time
away from you.
Yeah, well,
you love your music.
But it's not just that.
I think
that I have been...
Afraid...
That I would screw
things up,
that I couldn't be
the man
you and Daisy
needed me to be.
But maybe
I'm better than that.
Hmm?
I am going
to quit the band.
I think we'd like that.
Uh-oh.
Hey, how's the ear pain?
It's better with the drugs,
but it still really hurts.
We are going to take
some fluid samples
from your ear
and your lung.
Can you get up?
Lean forward.
Lean on this.
Okay, this is Lidocaine.
It'll numb you up.
Okay.
This is weird.
What--what's
the matter?
The pain in my ear is gone.
Gone? Completely?
Yeah, when you stuck me
in the back.
What does that mean?
[Somber classical music
playing]
♪ ♪
Okay, I'm just
cutting that for you.
Yum yum.
Is...Is she going
to eat anything else
or just the cheese
and crackers?
She's going through a picky
phase--it won't kill her.
You're her mother.
All I know is,
when you and your sister were
growing up, you ate what we ate.
No excuses.
[Fork loudly clanks
on plate]
Would you pass
the salt?
She had eggs this morning
and lots of fruit.
Ah.
That explains it.
Explains what?
She was
a little Vilder Chaiah
in the park
this afternoon.
She wouldn't listen
to anything I said.
Must have been
all the sugar.
Actually, the whole
sugar-makes-kids-hyperactive
thing is a myth.
It's a study.
I'm sure
it's very interesting.
I didn't read any studies.
I just raised children.
It's not your fault.
How are you supposed
to keep up
with what she eats all day?
You're never home.
I'm sorry.
I have to get this.
Tell me you need me.
Jack doesn't have cancer.
God, that's awful.
I'll be right in.
Masters stuck him
in the back with Lidocaine,
and his ear pain
went away.
We don't need you here.
We just need
to figure out
why this guy's body
thinks his ear is on his back.
Because his ear
used to be something else.
When you're a fetus,
your cells are close together.
When you grow, they spread out
and specialize.
Sometimes
the body screws up,
and they keep
the old area codes,
report
to the same pain centers.
Referred pain.
Looks and brains.
When you stuck him in the back,
you cut off communication
with the pain centers
in his spinal cord.
So we just
need to figure out
where the message
is actually coming from.
What about his thyroid?
Hyperthyroidism would explain
all his symptoms.
Or it could be his liver.
Good. We'll take
a look at both.
For the record, referred pain
does not rule out infection--
were you like this
when you were working
for your math degree?
If Euclid had been
a guest lecturer,
would you have been the kid
sitting in the front row going,
"actually, you haven't proven
the pythagorean theorem"?
Hello?
All right.
Mom...
Thank you,
sweetie.
So say you two
got married,
would you convert
to Judaism?
We haven't gotten
that far, mom.
That's actually a really
interesting question.
I'm an atheist.
Honey, half the Jews
i know are atheists.
It's about community.
House isn't that big
on community.
And why do you
call him "House"?
The man's name is Greg.
It makes it seem
like you're not serious.
I'm just trying to help you
think about the future.
You're--
you're a certain age now.
The parade of boyfriends
can't be as amusing as it was.
You need to settle down,
like your sister.
Settling down isn't all
it's cracked up to be.
Next week
is Sam's birthday.
I was gonna
take her to the Poconos and--
that's very sad.
Perhaps not the best choice
of topic for a festive occasion.
I just don't want Rachel
growing up
thinking you're a slut.
Okay, I got this.
First of all, mom...
Oh, my God.
Did you...
Sedate my mother?
Kicked in just in time.
She'll wake up
in a couple of hours,
be good as new.
Think of it as
my birthday gift to you.
You told me to keep
my mouth shut.
It's the only way
I had a chance.
Leaving aside the fact
that House is a sociopath,
I have to admit that I'm--
I'm honestly relieved.
Your mom is quite a h--
quite a handful.
What?
I feel f--
oh, you've got
to be kidding me.
Sorry.
I honestly thought
you'd be worse.
That was
my gift to myself.
I take it Jack's
thyroid levels are normal.
Foreman is doing
a liver biopsy now.
Good.
What's up with you?
Nothing.
I'm peachy.
It's hard when you feel
like you've been replaced.
We got a new puppy once,
and our old cocker spaniel
just moped for weeks.
- Have you even had sex?
- We're not talking about me.
We're talking about you.
No, you're talking
about puppies,
and I'm not listening.
She wants to do it
all the time,
but it has nothing
to do with me.
I'm just
a piece of meat.
Well, she
likes someone else,
and you've slept
with other people.
Uh, why are you
still together?
I love her.
We've been together
for 22 years.
I've never loved
anybody else.
I don't know how to...
Not be with her.
So you're never
gonna cheat again.
I don't know.
Well, that seems
kind of selfish, doesn't it?
Foreman found
diffuse inflammation
in Jack's liver.
Looks like
autoimmune hepatitis...
Starting him
on steroids.
[Somber classical music
playing]
♪ ♪
Isn't this nice?
What's this note?
Does that sound
like an "a"?
Remember, I put my finger
like this
without this doohickey
on it, it's an "f."
See?
Hmm...
Can we read
a book instead?
Yes, we--
Jack?
Jack! Help him!
Come on. Come on.
Okay. Okay.
He seized
three times last night.
We got him stabilized,
but barely.
If there was nothing wrong
with his brain before,
there sure is now.
Any particular reason we need
to be looking at the patient?
Yes.
Cuddy's mom
is in my office,
and she looks mad.
What did you do?
Our patient also
developed
a raging fever overnight.
That means Masters
was right all along.
This is an infection.
Should we give you
a minute to gloat?
We still don't know
what kind of infection--
could be bacterial,
viral, fungal.
Until the cultures--
you are
the worst gloater ever.
Her starting those cultures
when she did
means we're 24 hours closer
to the answer.
"We're sorry
your husband croaked,
but at least we were
24 hours closer to the answer."
Let's narrow it down,
shall we?
Four days ago, the guy
was facedown in the subway.
God only knows
what's in that sludge.
Toxic fumes
make him pass out--
rat pee does the rest.
If it's leptospirosis,
it's the fastest-moving
case in history.
Leptospirosis
can turn into meningitis.
I can't confirm
any of this yet,
and we don't have time
to choose wrong.
It fits,
and since it's the only idea
on the table,
I say it's a winner.
Start him
on doxycycline.
No, wait.
I'll do it.
You guys have to go
back to the office,
tell me when bubbie's gone.
You a doctor?
Sure.
You're on new meds.
Go back to sleep.
Am I gonna die?
Well, I hope not,
'cause then I'd have
to go back to my office.
Of course,
if you do kick it,
then you
get to be famous
for another two,
maybe three weeks.
They're saying
I'm a hero?
Yeah, but, you know,
in a few days,
a panda bear will give birth
to triplets,
and we'll all move on.
Oh, I'm sorry. You actually
believe that you are a hero.
Should get yourself
some tights and a cape,
run around Gotham pulling babies
out of burning buildings.
Maybe you'll keep
getting lucky.
You're still the same guy
you were last week.
Hey, um...
How long
are you gonna sit there?
Could be hours.
Hiding behind a sick guy...
That's heroic.
[Door slides open
and closed]
I can explain.
Sometimes
I mix up my medications.
I don't need you
to explain anything.
I think
we both know that...
I owe you an apology.
Say what?
I don't even remember
going to bed last night.
I must have had
too much to drink.
I do know
I can be difficult.
You were a little bitchy.
In the clinic, you were
a complete schmendrick,
but once you knew
I was Lisa's mother,
you held your tongue.
That's because
you love her.
I still think you're
a pain in the ass
with a God complex,
and I'll kill you
if you hurt her,
but I'm glad she has you.
We don't have
to hug now, do we?
What do you think?
I've got a train to catch.
I thought you were staying
till Sunday.
I'm coming down
with a cold.
Every time I stay
with Lisa or her sister,
one of those rug rats
gets me sick.
Children are awful.
Did she have
a rash recently?
No. What's going on?
Feverish, itchy?
No.
What is she
doing here anyway?
It's the middle of the morning.
Shouldn't she be in school?
I'm keeping her out
for a few days.
There's been a little outbreak--
chicken pox.
Sorry, but if I let you
finish that sentence,
that would be
much less impressive.
Chicken pox is
no big deal for kids,
but it's
a terrible, horrible,
no-good, very bad deal
for grown-ups.
You think Jack
has chicken pox?
But he doesn't have
blisters.
He's not itchy,
and Daisy never got it.
I know. Again, that's why
it's so impressive
that I figured it out.
5% of cases
present without blisters.
The kid
was just a carrier.
I'm gonna start you on
anti-varicella gamma globulin,
which will save your life.
But it won't make me
a hero.
Hey.
How are you feeling?
Like I'm not gonna die.
I can't wait
to take you home.
The guys called.
All this press has got us
a couple of new gigs--
just a few more dates,
three weeks, tops.
♪ ♪
Three weeks isn't so bad.
It's not three weeks.
It's what he's always done--
just one more tour.
I'm sorry.
Yeah,
the pathetic thing is
I let myself believe
that he could change,
he could be
this other guy.
There's nothing worse
than loving someone
who's never going to stop
disappointing you.
Culture confirmed
Jack does have chicken pox.
It just took
six hours longer.
Autopsy works too.
Fyi, turns out
your hero is a loser.
He's going
back on the road.
He still risked his life
for that woman.
That was impulse.
That was easy.
Dealing with family
is hard.
Wait, that's another thing
I got right.
How many does that make?
And how many for you?
I'm also kicking your ass
at gloating.
Hey.
Hi.
I think we should get
a divorce.
You have feelings for him,
and I can't handle that.
But it's my fault
you needed someone else.
I keep hurting you.
We love each other.
I know.
But are you happy?
No.
Then what are we doing?
You know, you turned out
remarkably close to normal,
considering
the genes in play.
Thanks.
Here...
In case
your mom comes back.
Happy Birthday.
Oh, you are
a sweet, sweet man.
You coming over?
Yes.
Oh, no, I can't.
Wilson.
It's, uh, bowling night.
He'll never forgive me
if I don't.
Oh, screw it.
I'm coming.
No, no, no. I am not gonna
be responsible for that.
You drugged the man.
You go bowling with him.
Well, my chances of sex
are considerably lower
with Wilson.
Fine.
Hey.
You ready?
Here's the thing...
♪ ♪
♪ we expected somethin' ♪
♪ somethin'
better than before ♪
♪ we expected somethin' more ♪
♪ do you really think ♪
♪ you can just put it
in a safe behind a painting ♪
♪ lock it up and leave? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ walk away now ♪
♪ and you're gonna start
a war ♪
♪ ♪
Aah!
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
♪ ♪
[Women arguing indistinctly
on television]
Again, this meeting is about
me and setting my bounds.
Well, it's about me too,
and I have
my boundaries, Dina,
and they have
clearly been crossed
by you
and your entire family.
That's not true.
We all need
improvements, Dina,
and I formed my opinion on you.
Shh.
No, don't shush me,
Dina.
No, I will shush you because
you're not letting me finish.
www.tvsubtitles.net