Excuse me, waitress?
I'm afraid
the teriyaki chicken's
no longer on the menu.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's what
you had last time.
We've never
been here before.
I definitely remember you.
No, we never get up north.
We're just up to see
a friend of ours
who moved here
last summer.
Your hair was lighter.
You had little round glasses.
Sounds like you.
Henry, don't play along.
It's a gimmick, for tips.
Could we get some water?
It was last August.
Saturday, the 14th.
You were wearing
a blue dress with polka dots.
Your eyes were puffy,
like you'd been crying.
The 14th
is Darren's birthday.
He said he had
to cancel his party
'cause his old girlfriend
showed up.
They got into a huge fight.
- Henry...
- I knew it. Damn it.
Ever since that ski trip
when the two of you
disappeared.
I'll go...Get your water.
Are you all right?
Are you okay?
I can't move my legs!
♪ House 7x12 ♪
You Must Remember This
Original Air Date on February 14, 2011
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
Picture a door.
Unlocked with the key
of the mind.
Two medical cases, both
more fascinating than the last.
That actually makes no logical sense.
This is not a door
to logical sense.
Also, shut up.
Case number one.
33-year-old woman
named...
Something I can't remember.
You'll see the irony
in a second.
Presenting with
temporary paralysis,
high CK levels,
and a perfect memory.
How perfect is perfect?
Perfectly perfect.
Hyperthymesia.
Complete recall
of every moment of every day
since puberty.
All 7,600,049 of them.
It's cool, huh?
One of only a handful
of recorded cases.
So we have two symptoms:
Temporary leg paralysis
and elevated CK.
Obviously you're not suffering
from the same condition
'cause you've already forgotten
my dramatic voiceover.
There's a third symptom.
- Her memory's unrelated.
- Why?
It's a strange
medical phenomenon--
Hyperthymesia is known
to manifest in adolescence.
Yeah, in the whole five
documented cases.
To be related, it would mean
20 years between symptoms.
Plus, I don't know
of any diseases
that cause great memory.
Only ones that destroy it.
MRI showed no evidence
of stroke or tumor,
so probably a toxin.
She's a waitress. They're no strangers
to botulism or alcoholism.
We should search the diner
and where she lives.
Or you could
search her brain.
You know,
where her memory lives.
Save the gas.
You two check her home.
You two get a complete
patient history.
We'll see who gets
an answer first.
You said there's
a second case?
Oh! Yeah.
Thanks.
The case of
the 45-year-old doctor
who just failed his pathology
recertification exam
and is going to lose
his board certification
and get fired.
How'd you fail it? You spend
half your life in the lab.
I was recovering
from the flu.
I'm retaking it next week.
It's not an issue.
Normally, I'd let
Darwinism run its course.
But Cuddy's in a big tizzy
about her poster boy
getting canned.
So how are we gonna get
the short guy off the short bus?
- What about a tutor?
- I don't need a tutor.
Tutor it is.
Choose your poison.
Chase, if you prefer
pounding Aussie beers
and comiserating over
the suckiness of divorce
Masters, if you want
nervous energy, flash cards,
and obnoxious pieces
of arcane trivia.
Foreman, if you
need to be berated
by a humorless hard-ass.
Foreman.
Interesting.
You must be more worried
than you look.
I need a consult,
Dr. Wilson.
So call me in a week
if it still itches.
Thank you.
And be sure to give Sarah
a kiss for me.
Will do.
Who's Sarah?
Her granddaughter,
I think.
Early stages of dementia.
What's the consult?
I need your medical opinion
on what bar we're gonna hit
for happy hour tonight
to kick off the official end
to your three-month
pity party over Sam.
I can't tonight.
Because of Sarah?
Yes, because of
my senile patient's
granddaughter.
You caught me.
I'm busy!
Who's Sarah?
Wilson's friend.
My computer crashed.
Lost my database
of his acquaintances.
Or you're both lying to me.
I know nothing about Wilson
having a friend named Sarah.
Satisfied?
Nooo.
What are the eight types
of vomitus?
I could show you four
right now
if you ask me
one more review question.
Hey, you picked me.
You said you wanted
a hard-ass.
No, House said that.
I pretended to agree
to get him off my back.
I picked you because
I wanted the guy
who doesn't like
getting involved
in other people's problems.
Yes, I thought
you'd want to skip
the massive public humiliation
of getting fired.
By treating me
like I'm an imbecile?
I'm totally fine.
I aced my first
pathology boards.
Medicine has come a long way
in the last hundred years.
You know...
I heard of a guy
who knew a guy
who could get the exam
ahead of time.
It was something I heard.
Patient's file  said she lost
some weight on a new diet, right?
Yeah, she went vegan.
Are laxatives vegan?
Hello?
Where are you?
In the parking garage,
searching Wilson's car.
We have an answer.
Magnesium poisoning.
We found a pretty large
stash of laxatives.
Abuse can lead
to hypermagnesemia.
I admit that's...
Impressively outside-the-box
thinking.
Hmm.
House.
You still there, House?
Everything okay?
No.
For a second,
I thought Wilson
might have a drug problem.
Turns out it's much,
much worse.
Okay...Uh,
so we push fluids
and wait for her kidneys
to clear the hypermagnesemia?
You'll be waiting a long time
since that's not what she has.
Her BP and respiratory rate
are normal.
While you two were so busy being
impressively outside the box,
you missed the actual box.
Chase and Masters done yet?
Two light beers,
November 16th.
One really bad glass of Pinot
on the 17th.
Uh, nothing from the 18th.
Shouldn't you be working
for NASA or something?
You mean why am I
just a waitress?
No, I didn't mean...
I'm sorry, I-I-I-I...
It's okay.
Remembering something
is not the same
as understanding it.
I'm not a genius.
I love my job.
I'm great at it.
Keeps my mind busy.
Hi.
I'm Dr. House.
You are not pooping.
Question is,
are you also a klutz?
Uh...
I guess I'm no clumsier
than most people.
What are you guessing for?
You've got a perfect memory.
I was told there'd be
numbers, dates, fireworks.
What do you want to know?
Let's go back to 2008.
How many trips, stumbles,
falls did you have?
11.
This really works.
Cool.
How 'bout 2009?
12.
Even cooler.
Last year?
20.
That's a big spike
in discoordination.
If you add the constipation,
it's early onset Parkinson's.
Give her a full neuro exam,
and start her on levodopa.
Oh, I'm so surprised
you broke into my apartment
without telling me.
What is this?
An intervention.
Exhibit A.
A baggie filled
with nepeta cataria,
also known as...
That had better not be
what I think it is.
If you mean your new
junkie girlfriend,
then yes.
House...
Okay, fine.
I got a cat.
Release the Kraken.
I don't think you appreciate
the severity
of your situation.
You are rapidly approaching
an end-stage male spinsterism.
That cat,
that diabetic cat that you're
shooting up with Insulin
and buying dime bags
of catnip for,
that means you've given up
on ever finding anyone.
Don't you think
you're completely overreacting
If I'm completely
overreacting.
why'd you lie to me?
Um, because I knew you would
completely overreact.
Its name's Sarah.
Cats aren't named that.
Women are.
What the Freud
is that about?
Look, I didn't name her.
My neighbor did.
She died, and I felt bad.
Sarah would have been
destroyed at the shelter.
Aww, who would want
a cat that croaks
if you're not home
twice a day
to shoot it up?
It's like having
your own button on Lost.
You know, I'm pretty sure
that there is
a river nearby.
I'm keeping her.
Okay, shrug your shoulders
and don't let me
push them down.
So I have to ask, uh...
Is there a trick you use?
Mnemonics?
Meditation?
No, no tricks.
I don't even try, really.
It's just there.
Is my memory gonna
go away...
With the Parkinson's?
It's quite possible.
But we still have a lot
of tests to do
before we have a definitive diagnosis.
Well, here's hoping
for cancer.
Nadia?
Your boss called me.
Sorry, um...
I'm Elena,
Nadia's older sister.
You don't have to be here.
But I'd like to pretend
you'd visit me
if I were in the hospital.
You brought daisies.
They're your favorite.
No, they're
my least favorite.
I was stung in the face
six times by--
Oh, God.
What's wrong?
My heart.
Fast, wide-complex rhythm.
Get the paddles.
Cardiac involvement
rules out Parkinson's.
We're back to transient
paralysis
and high CK,
plus arrhythmia.
Masters, when you finally
blossom into a woman,
would you ever sleep with
a man who had a cat?
Sure.
Wrong, the answer is no.
Slut.
Any of you ever had a cat?
Any of you ever had sex?
I think,
as your people say,
quod erat demonstrandum.
An excess of catecholamine
could set off an arrhythmia.
It's not a pheo.
Her blood pressure's fine.
Maybe we're missing
the obvious.
The heart could be
behind everything.
If it's not pumping
effectively,
the muscles shut down.
CK elevates, coordination suffers.
Why are you
asking about cats?
Curiosity.
Can we focus here?
Uh, her heart problems
started when Nadia
saw her sister.
Stress-induced arrhythmia
could be caused by
long qt syndrome.
Her sister was barely
in the room five minutes.
She said
they'd been estranged
for over six years.
That's a lot of tension.
Run a stress test
to confirm long qt.
It'll have to be
drug-induced.
Treadmill will
pull her stitches.
Drugs are never the answer.
If we want her heart
to go crazy,
there's something
simpler and safer.
Use the sister.
You lied to me.
No.
I said I didn't know
anything about Wilson
having a friend named Sarah.
Under House rules, that is not a lie.
He's lonely.
That cat is a nice way
for him to get some affection.
That's not
the kind of putty tat
he needs to be
getting it from.
He needs a putty tat
he can tap.
Why is it so important to you?
After divorce number two,
he fell into
a committed relationship
with a three-legged siamese.
He stopped
answering his phone,
redecorated his place
like Grey Gardens.
He wasn't able
to come back to humanity
until a window was left
suspiciously
and heroically open.
How that cat opened the window,
I will never know.
He just needs more time.
Leave him and the cat alone.
I won't if you will.
Sorry about the daisies.
I always get it confused
if you love or hate them.
Do you want to know
exactly how many times
I've told you
that I hate them?
I didn't do it on purpose.
Her heart rate
isn't moving.
The sister stress pot
needs stirring.
You want me
to start a fight?
No.
Just agitate a little.
Use something
from the history.
You're not lying to them.
In fact, you'd be
telling the truth,
and serving
their medical needs.
You haven't seen each other
in a while, huh?
I heard the story
about the time you hit
you hit Nadia
with the car.
It must have been
pretty scary.
Why would you
tell them that?
They asked about
broken bones.
I swear that I
checked my mirror.
You know that's a lie.
You knew
I was getting the mail,
and you just didn't care
enough to check!
Just like you didn't care
that you ruined
my 23rd birthday!
Nadia, don't start!
You started by coming here,
acting like you give a crap.
Here we go again!
I'm such a monster because
I brought daisies.
You--you need to leave
right now.
Well is she gonna be ok?
Elena, get out!
You said you'd be
ten minutes.
I couldn't decide
on the cheese.
When are you getting
an apartment?
Or at least a storage room?
I'll get to it.
I like it here.
They have video on demand.
I pulled a practice test.
I hate practice tests.
Hey, I never saw
The Usual Suspects.
You wanna check it out
before we start?
What are you doing?
You've got three days.
Why is everyone's
first assumption
I'm gonna fail
this stupid test?
Maybe, because you did.
I was recovering
from the flu.
I don't care if you were
dying from ebola.
You shouldn't have gotten
less than a 70.
You're nothing but
excuses and distractions.
Well it's a nice match
with your condescension
and superiority.
Enjoy the movie.
Kevin Spacey
is Keyser Soze.
How is she?
We started her
on a beta blocker.
It should keep her heart rhythm
under control.
She'll be fine
while we run more tests.
Did you hear that she
banned me from her room?
I know I'm not perfect,
but she's...
Oh, she can be
such a bitch.
Look, tell Nadia
she doesn't need to worry
about seeing me again.
I started the fight.
We needed her heart rate
to rise, so I provoked you.
You can't play
with people like that.
Maybe if I explain to Nadia--
No, it doesn't matter!
It's just one more fight
for her to remember.
Guess you're both bitches.
Masters.
Smell her breath.
Breathe out.
Ammonia.
What is it?
I think your kidneys
are shutting down.
Failing kidneys puts the heart
back on the list as a symptom.
Maybe she went vegan because
she lost the taste for protein.
It could be Amyloidosis.
We would have
seen a stiff heart
on the nuclear study.
But autoimmune
could account
for multiple organ systems
and paralysis.
There are a number
that'd fit.
Guillain-Barre,
polymyositis.
MS, polyarteritis nodosa--
sle.
Why are you giving me these?
Because,
while they're off
running all these tests,
you will be submitting
the insurance forms.
There's an entire department
for that.
Exactly.
The Foreman department.
Of which you are the foreman.
Foreman.
I know you got the time.
A little Wallaby told me
that you recently
vacated your post
as Taub's savior.
He asked.
You're worse than Masters.
How's this my fault?
He doesn't need a tutor.
He needs ritalin
and a babysitter.
Consider the forms
incentive.
Taub doesn't pass,
he'll become a permanent
part of your life.
This isn't really
about Cuddy, is it?
It's about you.
You don't want to lose me.
I think you care.
Don't think you can
disgust me
into pulling Foreman
off you.
Pulse the patient with steroids
for the autoimmune.
Start her on dialysis
for the kidney failure.
Treat the Taub with
insults and small slaps
for the obstinacy,
and start him on studying
for the brain failure.
No, that's not gonna work.
I have a haircut at 4 o'clock.
I'll be in the offi--
I'll be in the office
in about 20 minutes.
Yeah, okay.
Agh.
You planted something
in my apartment
to make me think
I'm allergic to Sarah.
Paranoia is the first sign
of toxoplasma gondii,
the parasite linked to
crazy cat lady disease.
I'm not paranoid.
I'm allergic to ragweed
and dandelion.
I'm not allergic to cats.
You're trying
to gaslight me.
Maybe your subconscious
is afraid that you're
gonna die alone.
And it just comes out
as gibberish and sneezing.
Prove that I'm overreacting.
Boys' night out.
Good Time Charlie's.
They just changed
their slogan to,
"where the trashiest ladies
get trashed."
You do see the hypocrisy
in all this, don't you?
Until recently,
your lifestyle of choice
was self-exile.
But I never had a cat.
Why don't you
pick me up at 8:00?
You're gonna need
another round of steroids.
In the meantime,
I'll start your dialysis.
So I heard Elena
might be coming back.
You think I was...
Too hard on her?
Well, we all
hold our grudges.
It's not a grudge.
It's common sense.
It's simple math.
She's hurt me
more than she's helped me.
Most people
edit their memories.
They add small, little lies
so they don't have
to face the truth.
My memories
remain the same.
My truth never changes,
because...
My truth is the truth.
So no one ever gets forgiven?
Sounds like
a lonely way to live.
No, I-I do forgive.
As long as the good things
they do...
Outweigh--
I can't--
I can't breathe.
Huh.
What?
Nothing, I just...
Always pictured your place
with shag carpet.
Like kind of a...
Mod Squad vibe.
Not because of
the black thing.
I always thought you were
more of...
You're limited to this room
and Marcus's old room.
Where's Marcus?
He tells me
he's working
with our Uncle
in Florida.
He tells you?
You don't look at
or touch anything
that doesn't belong to you,
including food.
You will study
and you will sleep.
And you will not leave
my sight until the exam.
Great, I'll be back bright
and early tomorrow, and--
this is no longer
just about your future.
It's about mine too.
You fail,
and I will kill you.
Respiratory distress
means we were wrong
about autoimmune.
Could be pulmonary edema
from renal failure.
Pulmonary edema
doesn't give you hives.
You think this is
an allergic reaction?
It can't be.
We pumped her full of steroids.
It can be.
If it was a really,
really bad one.
I have good news
and bad news.
The good news is I was right about
you having some autoimmune disease.
You're just allergic
to the dialysis.
But if I can't
have dialysis
and my kidneys
are failing,
won't that mean I'll die?
Well, you figured out
the bad news.
What do we do?
We look for
another case.
Even if you're
right about autoimmune,
we now don't have
time to prove it.
The transplant board will
never give her a kidney.
Maybe we could
go around them,
get a relative to donate.
Which relative?
The sister
who walked away
and told you she was
never coming back?
We caused this,
you know.
They were estranged,
but we made it worse.
That relationship
was broken
long before
we got there.
Nadia literally
keeps score.
She tallies everything.
She decided Elena's done more
bad things to her than good,
doesn't deserve
her affection.
I'm sure she's right.
Unlike everybody else
in the world,
her memory seems to let her keep
a pure and objective view of people
in realtionships.
There's no petty
emotions or agendas
fogging the windshield.
Why is that so wrong?
'Cause it's
making her die alone
of kidney failure
in room 205?
Not necessarily.
Nadia's sister's
not like her.
I'm sure she's got plenty
of subjective emotions
we can exploit.
Why don't you go
channel your guilt,
see if you can get her
to cough up a kidney?
Me?
I'm not good at that type of thing.
Someone else should go.
Someone else
didn't screw this up.
I didn't!
You were just obeying orders.
Right?
Go fix this.
Wha--
I didn't mean
to make you hate her.
And...Now that her
kidneys have failed, I--
I've always been a book
and equations person.
People are problematic.
And...random and messy.
Um, and with sisters...
I mean, I had a cousin
who I was close to,
and when our
menstrual cycles synced,
it was like
gladiator school--
Do you want me to donate
a kidney to my sister?
Yes.
Okay.
Really?
It might not fix
your relationship.
Uh, probably shouldn't
have said that.
Your left, on your left.
Stop whining already.
I was getting a sniper.
Five minutes left
in the break.
But the next level's
just past the cooling tanks.
That was the deal.
We take this break,
you do a practice test.
I-I didn't
have the flu.
I just...choked.
You make life and death
decisions
every day.
You work for House.
You're under constant pressure,
and you never choke.
I got a perfect score
on my first
pathology boards.
I kept thinking,
"whatever my score is now,
"it's going to be a measure
of the distance
between me and the man
I used to be."
You gotta stop
psyching yourself out.
Well, the last test
was before I lost my wife
and my home,
so I'm sure the next one
will go much better.
Sometimes, I wake up
in the middle of the night,
and I can't sleep
for hours
'cause I'm worried I got
the diagnosis wrong.
These things work out.
We found a donor.
It's your sister.
Just thought you should know.
Nadia, can you hear me?
You're coming out
of your anesthesia.
You're gonna feel
a bit groggy.
You did great.
Everything's looking good.
Nadia, come on now.
Open your eyes.
Three milligrams
of lorazepam,
and I'm going
to need suction.
Seizures mean the steroids
aren't working.
And we got
the tests back.
We were wrong.
It's not autoimmune.
Could be acute porphyria.
No abdominal pain.
Did the patient
thank her sister?
Not yet, at least.
See if she will.
What are you trying
to find out?
If she's telling the truth.
She claims she objectively
sees reality.
Weighing the good
and bad in people.
If that's true,
i don't care
how many times her sister
borrowed her scrunchie
without asking,
a free kidney ought
to trump all the bad stuff.
And if it doesn't?
That means she sucks,
like the rest of us.
We haven't considered
her blood.
Clots could hit her leg,
heart, kidney, and brain.
Factor v leiden.
Easiest to treat,
if we're right.
Start her on heparin.
And ask for the thank-you.
How'd I do?
Great.
Great?
How great?
How many did I miss?
It's not about the numbers.
Don't...
54%?
Th-they make
the practice tests
harder than
the actual exam.
Oh, my God, now I'm choking
in your living room.
This isn't gonna work.
Who are you calling?
I found the guy.
He can sell me a copy
of the test.
I know it's cheating,
and I suck as a person.
But...the test
is tomorrow morning.
It's not about the cheating.
It's about your confidence.
You steal that test,
and you'll never get it back.
I can't handle
failing at one more thing
in my life.
You're a good doctor.
I've seen what
you're capable of.
You're fast, you're decisive,
and you're bold.
And those are not
the qualities of someone
who needs to steal a test.
There's nothing on it
that you don't already know.
You just need to know
that you know it.
Keep talking.
We need you on the team.
So we're gonna sit here
and take another practice test
and we're gonna
keep taking them
until you've
kicked its ass!
You can do this!
You feel me?
Yeah.
I feel like we just
buried a hooker in the desert.
There'll definitely
be another time
to rise up
and turn things around.
You'll come back from it.
Next time.
How are you feeling?
N-not any better.
It'll take some time
for the clots to resolve.
Your sister's
recovering well.
If you're really adding up
the good and bad...
Can I see her?
Too fat.
Too thin.
Too desperate.
Not desperate enough.
Come on, you can
insult them too.
I'd rather not.
If you objectify them now,
you'll feel more
comfortable when you...
Tie them to a table
in your basement later.
Or whatever.
Okay.
Um...
Too armpit fatty.
Whoa! Too hot.
I actually know her.
She's the new barista
at my coffee shop.
She's getting her masters
in finance.
Brains and boobs.
The mother lode.
Total moron
as a barista, though.
Every drink I order
ends up with
whipped cream on it.
Even when I say no whip.
Girlfriend, that means
she's into you.
Okay.
♪ So sexy when you're
working on your knees, girl ♪
♪ I'm out of my head ♪
Hi, there.
Wilson. James Wilson.
I'm a doctor.
I'm hoping that's
enough to close,
because I'm also
a social moron.
And I have a cat.
♪
♪ so sick,
the way you're trickin' ♪
♪ like a little girl ♪
♪ asking daddy for a lollipop,
shaking my world ♪
♪ she's the queen
of the serpent ♪
She said my coffee
is not the only thing
she'd like to put
whipped cream on.
Yeah, but is she interested?
♪ The train is coming
to the station ♪
♪ but it's off the track ♪
♪ oh, Felicia ♪
♪ babe, I think
I really, really need ya ♪
♪ so sexy when you're
working on your knees, girl ♪
Bartender!
Champagne for everyone!
♪ Felicia ♪
♪ babe, I think
I really, really need ya ♪
Hi.
Thank you.
For saving my life.
I love you, you know.
I was thinking
about those times
we went up to Spofford Lake
in the summer.
Whenever we took out
the canoe,
you'd tie up
my life vest for me.
In the afternoon,
sneak me into the lodge
so we could steal popsicles.
Maybe we could go back.
I could drive us up there.
We could get a cabin and--
And maybe rent a canoe.
Oh, wow, I haven't...
Thought of Spofford in...
Nadia...
Are you okay?
Elena, I'm sorry!
I can't do this!
Can you stop?
Just stop pushing me
for a minute.
I understand now
why you stuck yourself
in that diner,
away from friends,
away from family.
You can't forgive anyone.
I don't think
you weigh anything.
I think you're like
a lot of people.
You focus on
the bad memories
instead of the good.
I don't have a choice.
Nadia, put your hand
in your lap for a moment.
I'm not doing that.
I know.
It's an involuntary movement
called choreia.
What does it mean?
It means we still don't know
what's wrong with you.
Thank you.
Do you know if that...
O.R. nurse that Wilson liked
ever broke up
with her boyfriend?
I thought your Wilson fetish
was over.
I'm putting together
a second string
in case things
don't go well
with the well-breasted
barista.
You've gotta
let that guy alone.
He's not supposed
to be alone.
Is that what this is about?
You feel guilty because
Wilson's the one
that's alone and not you?
You still don't think
you deserve this.
Have you met me?
Your happiness
doesn't take his away.
It's okay to enjoy it.
Yeah.
Choreia. Rules out
the clotting disorder.
Means we're back
to square one.
If it's hit
her brain,
that could mean
she doesn't have long.
So then the question becomes,
will the sister
show up at the funeral?
She tried to reconcile,
but the bad memories crowded out
the good, and she ran.
Nobody's perfect.
What else?
Come on, the woman has
all the information we need.
She's a bottomless
diagnostic library.
Maybe we're missing something
from the apartment.
Some lifestyle thing.
Yeah, it's all
muscle strain
from doing her hundreds
of Jigsaw puzzles.
We should do
another MRI.
A brain hemorrhage would--
Hey.
How many puzzles?
Okay, I was exaggerating.
Dozens.
Do a peripheral blood smear.
Look for acanthocytes.
I'll be right in.
Remember me?
Just kidding.
So...Jigsaw puzzles.
Um, I find them calming.
You ever left one unfinished?
No, that would
drive me crazy.
Speaking of...
Why are you
doing that?
More important question is,
why are you?
It's just a habit.
It's a habit
that compels you
in an obsessive way
that's so bad,
it's a disorder.
I don't have OCD.
Each brain with OCD
has its own way
of filtering it.
Some people
wash their hands
and hoard tv guides.
You do puzzles
and hoard memories.
So what we thought
was a gift...
Is just you literally
obsessing over your own life.
That's why I can't
stop the memories,
even when I try.
But everything else?
My kidneys?
Memory was just
a symptom of a symptom
of a larger disease.
You have McLeod syndrome.
It's a rare
genetic disorder
that affects
the nervous system, the blood.
And can cause...
OCD.
Am I gonna die?
It can't be cured.
But your various symptoms
can be managed with medication.
Best-case scenario,
you can live
another 20 years.
If it's any solace,
everybody dies alone.
It probably isn't.
How'd it go?
Well, it's hard to choke
when you have
all the answers.
Look at it this way.
It's better to suck
at taking one test
than to suck at
saving people's lives.
Wow.
Uh, Rachel thought
it was too big,
and I can't keep it
in my hotel room.
You're giving it to me?
I couldn't
stand the thought
of you having company over
with that other TV.
It's embarrassing.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Hey, look, um...
I have the room.
You could stay,
if you wanted to.
Just until you
find your new place.
Who else am I gonna play
savageskate with?
We could do that online
from separate houses.
Will you shut up?
Okay.
How you feeling?
Much better.
I don't believe
what House said.
I'm not sure even House
believes it anymore.
You said you didn't
have a choice
to be the way you are.
Now you do.
These are ssris.
They've been effective
in treating OCD.
You mean lose my memory?
Not lose it entirely.
It'll just become
more like anyone else's.
My memory...
Is the only thing
that has ever
made me special.
Maybe so.
But if you want
to be special...
You're gonna
have to be alone.
Ohh!
Hey.
Aah!
Those are for Sarah.
Are they poisoned?
Poi--
you and your paranoia.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
I really should find
a better place
to store my ragweed.
It's a very nice gesture,
but it's still
in the apartment.
So...I wanna hear
all the dirty,
dairy-specific details
of your night
with java the slut.
All right.
First of all,
all real.
Second...
A true connoisseur
of the dark arts of...
I flaked.
I walked her to her car
and said good night.
I will get back into it, I--
you just need to give me
a little more time.
I'll give you ten days.
Fine.
Ooh.
♪
♪ how do you fight
loneliness ♪
♪
♪ smile all the time ♪
♪ shine your teeth
till meaningless ♪
♪
♪ and sharpen them with lies ♪
♪ and whatever's going down ♪
♪
♪ will follow you around ♪
♪ that's how you
fight loneliness ♪
♪
♪ you laugh at every joke ♪
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
Ten-one, ten-one, officer shot.
I repeat: Officer shot.
En route to Illinois masonic.
As a Detective,
www.tvsubtitles.net