Hike!
Hey.
So, uh, what
did you want?
It's too late now.
Too late
for what?
I'll tell
you later.
Come on,
the bell just rang.
We still got time.
I'm ready.
Uh, you sure?
Yeah.
Why now,
all of a sudden?
What, you don't want to
anymore?
Yeah, I do.
I'm just wondering
what changed your mind.
You did.
Now?
If you want.
Excuse me.
You two need
to come with me.
- Take a seat.
- But we didn't--
You know you're not
supposed to be back there.
We weren't doing anything.
That's not what
it looked like to me.
Principal Fields
will be back
as soon
as the assembly is over.
Ms. Washburn, please, if I get
one more referral, my mom--
Bench.
Who put sand
in her vagina?
♪ House 7x13 ♪
Two Stories
Original Air Date on February 21, 2011
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
Hey, kids.
How you boys doing?
Uh, can we help you?
I certainly hope so.
You know
what this is?
A laptop?
Password-protected laptop
that I need you
nerds to hack into.
No insecticides
or toxic cleaners.
Check the bathroom.
Who are you?
Your roommate's doctor.
You remember
your roommate, don't you?
I thought he
just had bronchitis.
That's what the morons
at the Rutgers Student
Medical Center thought,
which may be part of the reason
he just coughed up a lung.
What do you mean,
he coughed up a lung?
He coughed...
After which
the respiratory organ
which resided in his chest
resided in his mouth...
Actually, his hand.
Well, his mouth,
then his hand.
Bathroom's clean.
- What's in this?
- Just soda.
- Mind if I have some?
- You want my drink?
You got a problem
with that?
Uh, yeah.
Actually, I do.
You barge
into our room,
start looking through
our personal, private stuff,
demand I hack
into a computer
I think I can safely assume
doesn't belong--
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did I break your concentration?
Please continue.
You were talking
about personal privacy.
What, you're finished?
Well, allow me to retort.
Wait a second.
You're saying
this actually happened?
Absolutely.
You're lying.
Interesting theory.
Can you prove it?
Doctors don't carry guns.
They don't shoot people,
and they definitely
don't search patients' homes.
Plus, I've seen
Pulp Fiction--
the movie
you're totally ripping off.
Huh.
Wait, uh, was
it Timmy Morgan?
I have no idea.
It had to be him.
He's, like, totally obsessed
with old movies.
Pulp Fiction is not
an old mov--what?
So you're here to talk
to the principal
about something Timmy did?
I got no problem with Timmy.
And even if I did,
I ain't no snitch.
Then why
are you here?
To dig myself
out of a hole.
Instead I dug
a bigger one.
What'd you do?
What happened
to your eye?
It's none
of your business.
Actually, it's none of yours.
I'm a doctor.
It's a few days old,
so that's not
why you're here,
unless you two got busted
for some sort of revenge plot.
But then you'd look angry
instead of...ashamed.
I'm not ashamed.
Interesting.
You defensively insist
that you're not ashamed,
which, of course,
means you are ashamed.
And yet,
you're the victim.
You want to know
how she got the black eye?
Tell us why
you're here first.
Anyone ever tell you
you're annoying?
No.
Yes, all the time.
But he's right.
You want to know?
You first.
I didn't kill anybody.
I have to be here,
so I figured
I'd punch up the stakes
in the first act.
But we did,
and almost always do,
search the patient's home.
And if we
tell them first,
then they can hide something
that we need to know
in order to figure out
what's wrong with them.
Why would they hide something
that could be killing them?
Because they are morons.
They're all morons,
and everybody lies.
Wait, if everybody lies,
then that means
you're lying right now.
I didn't say everybody
always lies...Aristotle.
And on that note, unless
there are any questions...
Good.
Oh, Dr. Hourani...
Before you finish,
maybe you could describe
what you actually do.
You know, like if someone comes
in for a routine physical?
You want routine?
Please.
It just feels
kind of, like, numb.
You do a lot
of bicycle riding?
No.
How long have
you been married?
It's 12 years
next month.
You have six kids.
Mm-hmm.
Well, you don't think
it could have
anything to do
with that, do you?
Probably.
How often do you use
your vibrator?
Excuse me?
Your battery-operated
Brad Pitt.
After giving
the gift of life
to six eight-pound,
four-ounce wrecking balls,
I think I can safely assume it's
an industrial-strength model?
Dr. Hourani, please.
You wanted routine.
Am I done?
Maybe we should
just move on.
No problem.
I meant with your typical day.
I assume you see
more than one patient?
Nope.
Okay.
Then I guess we will move on
to our next guest.
Wait, if you
only see one patient,
what do you do
the rest of the day?
Dr. Hourani?
Just in time
for lunch.
By lunch, you mean a conference
call with the board,
and by just in time,
you mean, 20 minutes late.
I meant sex...
By lunch.
How about we start
with a small tossed salad?
As of this morning,
I'm on a diet.
Meaning?
I told you,
I'm busy.
No, you told me
you were supposed to be busy
20 minutes ago.
But you were obviously able
to put them off then,
there's no reason you
can't put them off now.
How about,
"I wanted to then,
and now I don't"?
Get your finger
off my phone.
We obviously have
something we need to discuss.
Now is not
a good time.
If you're mad
because you don't feel
you're getting the necessary
amount of affection,
all you have to do
is ask.
Seriously,
not now.
If memory serves, I enjoyed
a healthy Sunday brunch.
So your insinuation--
Ow!
- What is your problem?
- You!
You are my problem.
You are the most selfish,
self-centered son of a bitch
on the face
of the planet.
And I'm sick of it.
I'm just...done.
I can't deal
with you anymore.
So that's what a typical doctor
does on a typical day.
Any questions?
What's a vibrator?
Why was
your girlfriend so mad?
It doesn't matter.
Well, obviously
it matters.
I mean, if she's
your girlfriend,
you should care
how she feels.
I mean, it doesn't matter
to the story.
It's the most important part
of the story.
It's the only thing
that does matter.
You don't kiss her enough--
is that the problem?
Absolutely not.
Which, by your definition,
means it is.
We kiss plenty.
Your turn.
Then what's the problem?
What's the problem?
Excuse me.
When exactly
will the commandant be back?
Shouldn't be
much longer, sir.
Well?
Oh, so now
you're not gonna talk.
That's real mature.
All right, fine.
We got busted for kissing
behind the school.
Now you know
why we're here.
So tell us
why you're here.
The deal was
about the black eye.
And we didn't kiss.
So you were just making
him beg, huh?
I didn't have you pegged
as a tease.
I'm not a tease.
The available evidence
suggests otherwise.
I'm not a tease.
Prove it...
By--by telling me
your story.
You're
a pathetic loser, jerk!
And I wouldn't kiss you
if I had brain cancer
and your lips
were the cure!
She actually
said that?
- Well, yeah, that was, like, two days ago.
- It doesn't matter.
I clearly didn't lead him along
or anything like that,
which proves
I'm not a tease.
So why is your girlfriend
mad at you?
I'm getting
a kind of bossy vibe.
I take it
you're into that.
Don't answer!
Your turn.
What seems to be
the problem, sir?
I'm having
more difficulty breathing
and some pain in my chest.
You're new,
aren't you?
Uh, yeah, I just moved
from Chicago.
Chicago's awesome.
What part are you from?
We need to get
a chest C.T.
Excuse me,
I'm the senior team member,
which means
we don't need anything
unless I say we need it.
- Do you want to have an affair?
- You want to have a threesome?
You can't talk to her like that.
I'm telling Cuddy.
We need a chest C.T.
Get it yourself.
Isn't that, like,
sexual harassment?
Not if you're
good-looking.
Excuse me?
You said the one guy was short
with a big nose.
Guess that's not
the only thing that's big.
What does that mean?
It means he's lying...
again.
Because you can't handle
the truth!
That's so easy.
A Few Good Men.
Okay, I give up.
I think we should move on
to our next guest.
Mr. Dryden...
Uh, works for one of the
largest advertising agencies
in New York City.
Boring! Boring!
Can we at least hear
what happened to the patient?
If Dr. Hourani
promises to--
Patient's dead.
Floor is yours, Don.
Dave.
He's not dead.
You said earlier
he was still in the hospital.
- What's wrong with him?
- He's got a cough.
You said
he coughed up a lung.
- What about the laptop?
- Who cares about the laptop?
Yeah, and he already said he
was lying about that, you moron.
Gabe...
- We do not use that word here.
- He did.
Yeah, and I was talking
about people like you.
Ooh.
Dr. Hourani, please,
could you just finish,
quickly, so we can move on?
I don't know
what's wrong.
He was stable for a while, and
then all of a sudden, he just--
Bronchial infection must be
from a drug-resistant
strain.
O-2 sats
are plummeting.
We need to get him
on a bronchodilator
before he goes into respiratory arrest.
Suction, sit him up.
Start blow by oxygen.
What is that?
I think it's his...
It's his lung.
That actually happened?
Yes, it really happened.
I take cases that other doctors
fail to diagnose,
which is why I only
take one at a time.
My current patient
is a college student.
He's actually
in the hospital right now.
And, yes, he really
did cough up a large portion
of dead lung tissue.
How's that
even possible?
That's what
she said.
No, she did
literally say that.
How's that
even possible?
Primary squamous carcinoma
could cause
lung tissue
to basically disintegrate.
It's not cancer.
F.O.B. was normal.
It's not an infection either.
Broad-spectrum antibiotics
haven't had any effect.
Who password-protects
a computer
they keep in a locked desk
in a locked office?
Someone who works with someone
who thinks it's okay
to break
into other people's homes?
An amebic liver abscess
could rupture
through the diaphragm
into the thorax.
Not when his liver-function
tests are all normal.
His dorm mates are
computer science majors.
If they're fabricating chips,
they could be working
with all kinds
of different toxic solvents.
We need to search
the dorm.
"We"?
Oui.
Allons-y.
While we're out,
do a thorascopic lung biopsy
and a c-ANCA,
because
it's sarcoidosis.
But if you think it's
sarcoidosis, why are you...
So you really did force
his roommate
to hack into the laptop?
Why would I lie?
But whose
laptop is it?
It's your girlfriend's,
isn't it?
She's not my girlfriend.
I'm just interested in her
because she's a client,
and she sleeps
above her covers--
four feet
above her covers.
What?
Ghostbusters.
So that's
why she's so mad--
you looked through
her computer?
No, that part happened
after she got mad.
First she got mad.
Then I stole her computer
to fix things.
And then
we got the case.
Wait, so you tried to fix
your relationship
by stealing
her computer?
Well, when you
say it like that...
Yes.
Looks like
you're the moron.
Ooh!
I can also get three sets
of golf clubs in there.
No way.
You didn't get
her laptop
by blowing down
the door of her office.
That's from
Thunderbolt and Lightfoot.
Just seeing if you're
still paying attention.
It was actually
more subtle.
The Thomas Crown Affair--
the Steve McQueen version.
Just tell us the truth already.
Excuse me.
But there are others here who
would like a chance to speak.
Go right ahead.
No!
Audience is
always right.
Luke.
It wasn't me.
Ma'am,
are you okay?
Can you hear me?
Ooh, what's
that smell?
Ugh.
Smells like a gas leak.
Call Dr. Cuddy.
You poisoned
a room full of patients
so you could steal
your girlfriend's laptop?
I didn't poison anybody.
I spilled some hydrogen sulfide
and ammonia on the floor,
thinking the stench
would clear the place out.
But instead of breathing
through his nose,
some idiot
decided to hold his breath.
He passes out,
and before I know it,
the place is a perfect storm
of mass hysteria...
Although it worked out
just as well.
They're morons.
Agreed.
No, not the patients,
the kids.
It doesn't matter
how you stole it.
What matters is why.
You know, you're starting
to remind me of someone.
I didn't ask how you stole it.
I asked why.
Isn't it obvious?
You think you can tell
why she's mad
by reading
budget spreadsheets
and per diem schedules?
I know why she's mad.
What I need to know is
how to make her un-mad.
And step one
is gaining access
to the journal
on her laptop,
where she records
her innermost thoughts...
Instead of just
watching porn with me.
Oh, grow up.
If porn was bad, why would
there be so many nuns in it?
Why is she mad?
I was myself,
which, by the way,
she's supposed
to love unconditionally.
I didn't do anything.
We had a great weekend.
Went to a Blues club,
we watched Cinderfella on DVD.
And?
It doesn't matter.
She's being unreasonable,
and I have to fix it.
I need to know what's
really important to her.
- I need something big.
- Because?
We're past that.
Have you tried
childhood pet names?
I don't know her pets.
She's never mentioned
a pet?
Well, yeah,
but I wasn't listening.
She's not mad because I don't
remember a dead dog's name.
Her first dog
was Ronaldo.
Is that R-o
or R-e-y?
I didn't ask. Try both.
Just got a case
from the E.R.
Rutgers student came in
with what looked like
acute bronchitis.
But there's nothing in
his blood or sputum cultures.
Don't you think
it's time you people
stop looking to the white man
to solve all your problems?
His O-2 sats
are in the toilet.
If we don't figure out
what's attacking his--
So figure it out!
I'm busy.
That can't be true.
Why not?
'Cause if he was dying--
I mean, you're a doctor.
Patients die every day.
Not all of them
are interesting.
You still haven't answered
either question.
She was mad because she's
genetically programmed
to make a big deal
out of every little thing.
So she's mad
'cause she's a girl.
And now she's mad
because she's programmed
to make a big deal
out of every little thing.
Actually, she's not like that.
Why are you sticking up for her?-
She says you're a pathetic jerk
and she hates you.
That was
a long time ago.
It was
two days ago.
And it wasn't
even true then.
- How do you know?
- Because I know how you think.
Really?
Really.
Hey.
Uh, and no peck
on the cheek.
It has to be
on the lips.
Winning a bet
to force her to kiss you
actually cuts
against your theory
that you know
how she thinks.
I wasn't forcing her
to do anything
that she
didn't want to do.
You're hoping for a career
in the NBA or the NFL?
The bet let her do
what she wanted to do
while still being able to act
like she didn't,
so her friends
wouldn't get all, like,
calling her a slut
or something.
Not that it's slutty
or anything.
It's just a kiss.
Not even close to true.
I just couldn't believe
I'd lose.
Ah, now we're getting
somewhere.
No, we're not.
Oh, I thought we were.
No, you thought
we weren't,
and that's exactly
what you want,
because you don't want to
tell us why was she mad at you!
You tell us you don't
want to do your job
because you're too busy
trying to break
into your girlfriend's laptop
to figure out a way
to make her
not mad at you.
But you don't tell us
why she was mad at you.
It's stupid.
Talk.
I'm out of here.
Unless...
Rachel's gonna be up soon.
Well, you never know.
Yes, I do.
Can you take the garbage out
before you go?
Uh, I-I-I would,
but...
Oh, come on.
It's not a lot.
Pain's always worst
first thing in the morning.
Mommy!
You used her toothbrush?
That's so gross.
What's the big deal?
It's not like
she had a problem
swapping spit
the night before.
Well, maybe it's not
the swapping spit
that bothers her, but the fact
that you don't listen to her.
Had she warned
you not to do it?
Oh, I listen to her.
But you just said before
that you didn't.
No, I said I didn't remember
what she said.
No, you said you
don't listen--
I listen to her.
Okay?
Believe me, I listen.
It's my toothbrush,
and it's not just once.
And it's not
like I'd even care,
but you totally
destroy it.
You're supposed
to brush with it,
not gnaw on it
like a rawhide bone.
I think
Miss Four Cavities' time
would be better spent copying
Mr. No Cavities
instead of
complaining about him.
And given what
I'd just been doing,
I thought you wouldn't want me
going out to dinner
without a good brush
and a floss.
Would you please just use
the toothbrush I bought you?
Would you please just shut up
and watch the movie?
I said, "please."
Why would you have
to brush your teeth
before you go to dinner?
You don't want
to know...
Yet.
You're gross
and dumb.
You listen
to what she says
just so you can tell her
how wrong she is.
You are clueless
and naive.
I have to tell her
that she's wrong,
'cause no one else will.
She's the boss,
which means
she's surrounded by morons
who are either afraid of her,
or they want
to kiss up to her,
or they want to...
Kiss her.
But not you.
I already kissed her.
And I respect her enough
not to treat her
like some tender blossom
who needs to be coddled.
Makes sense to me.
That's what you
think you did?
Yeah, totally.
You mean...
Wha--
you?
No, I didn't punch her.
You're a moron.
I didn't mean to.
The stick had
wicked heel curve.
Did I mention
you're a moron?
Okay, you just said
it's wrong
to treat your girlfriend
like she's weaker than you.
I'm not talking
about trying to score.
I'm talking
about shooting high.
Tennis shoes
on a wooden floor?
She obviously can't butterfly
and cover the low corners.
Your turn.
The laptop.
I must be in the midst
of a complex partial seizure,
'cause I know you are
not sitting at my desk.
Sorry.
Ran out of lotion in mine.
Get the hell
out of here.
Can't. This is
the only place left
that Cuddy'll
never look for me.
And I still haven't found
what I'm looking for.
Well, I can tell you,
what you're about to find
is my foot in your ass.
I don't think we've got
enough lotion for that.
How did you even get in here?
The door was locked.
Well, either I can walk
through walls, or...
We have liftoff.
Is that
Cuddy's journal?
No, it's a freelance piece
I'm writing for Teen Vogue.
No, no, no.
Let me see that.
Sorry, got to go.
Key.
I got to give you
one thing, Hourani.
Your wife--
she's beautiful.
I mean, wow.
Thank you.
House!
Wait.
I thought
you were Dr. Hourani.
Yeah, who are you?
So that's why you're here?
Well, that was stupid.
I know.
Mr. Stupid-Head
at your service.
Where are you now?
In the principal's office.
House, we don't
have time for games.
Pet scan was negative for sarcoidosis.
Great.
Means the treatment's
already working.
It would if we'd actually
started the treatment,
but we didn't.
Why the hell not?
Because it's
not sarcoidosis.
If you were here,
you would know that.
He's dying.
What's left of his lung
is collapsing.
F.N.A. of the mediastinal--
i don't care about the F.N.A.
What I care about is how
he responds to the treatment.
House.
Just do it.
Sarcoidosis...
Is a diagnosis
of exclusion,
which means that the cowards
who spend their time
excluding what it isn't
usually cause their patients
to die from what it is.
I don't get it.
- Why would you lie about your name?
- Who cares?
What did she write
in her journal?
Thank you.
That is exactly
my point.
Why does no one
ever believe me?
What?
Just because he's dying
doesn't make it interesting.
You cheated on her,
didn't you?
No, I didn't cheat
on her.
It's obviously more than
just you used her toothbrush
and wouldn't take
the garbage out.
No, actually,
it was exactly that.
I just need
some time alone.
Because I used
your toothbrush?
And you wouldn't take out
the garbage.
That's insane.
You know that, right?
You do whatever
you want, always.
I said I was sorry.
I was--
I was still half asleep.
I wasn't paying attention.
And you're
always right.
And I don't mean you
always think you're right.
But y-you are
actually always right,
because that's
all that matters.
That doesn't
even make sense.
What, you want me
to be wrong?
I want you to care about
more than just what you want,
what you think.
You need me, House.
And you may even love me.
But you don't care
about me.
And I deserve
someone who does.
That's what I said.
You don't listen to her.
You didn't say that.
Yes, I did.
Well, I wasn't
listening, then.
But you found a way
to fix things, right?
That's why you were happy
when you read her laptop.
I did.
At least
I thought I did.
She recently got
the thin envelope
from her first choice
preschool.
But it turns out
it was her fake first choice,
'cause she was convinced
she couldn't get her kid
into her actual first choice
without a substantial donation
or an inside connection.
If it's Brye Park,
I'm afraid she's right.
Wait, that's
our school.
What other school
would he be talking about?
Just finish
the story.
You know,
I got to tell you--
there is bossy,
which can be sexy.
And then
there's bitchy--
Finish the story.
You obviously know this
because you're
on the school board,
which puts you
on the inside,
and being the CEO here obviously
connects you with Cuddy.
Well, if we're so connected,
why isn't she the one asking?
Because she thinks
it's wrong
to use connections
to cut in line.
I don't.
I might be able to help.
Fantastic.
But I could use
a favor as well.
Where are you?
I needed to take care
of something.
It's not a foreign body.
You must have missed it.
If we do any more imaging,
we're gonna have to add
radiation poisoning to the DDX.
I meant
the sarcoidosis.
The biopsy and c-ANCA
were both negative.
We're gonna have to do a pneumon.
No sign of drug
or alcohol abuse.
He's not a smoker, a coal miner,
or a potter--it's sarcoidosis.
Start him on corticosteroids
and methotrexate.
If it's a drug-resistant bug,
and we give him steroids--
He'll die,
which from the sound of it
wouldn't be much worse.
You moron.
But you have
to show him your I.D.
And your insurance stuff.
You can't just
give him a fake name.
You don't have
to do anything.
Last time I checked,
this was still America.
Of course,
that was ten years ago.
But you're gonna pay him, right?
I mean, it was your fault.
A yellow light
does not mean stop.
It was, at the most,
20% my fault.
Since insurance companies
automatically put
100% of the fault
on the rear-ender,
my little lie
was actually an effort
to achieve an outcome
closer to the truth.
And it would
have worked, too,
if it weren't
for those meddling kids.
I am Dr. Hourani.
Then why did you say
the other doctor was Hourani?
It's, uh--
it's a common name.
It's like Smith...
In Lebanon.
- Let me see your I.D.
- I told you, I left it in my other pants.
Really? 'Cause it looks
like it's still in this pair.
Get your hands off me.
Give me your I.D.
- Hey, would you stop that?
- Give me your I.D.
Gentlemen, please.
Kids, stay calm.
Gimme your I.D.!
Stop this right now!
Stay in your seats, kids.
Stay calm, you guys.
Stay in your seats.
Gentlemen, please.
This is not the time or place.
Is there a problem in here,
Ms. Corwin?
Why don't you
just take off?
It's not like the principal
can call your parents.
No, but the principal
can call the police
or the guy he's doing
the favor for.
His girlfriend's
obviously gonna find out.
He's screwed.
- I'd bolt.
- No, you wouldn't.
Yeah, I would.
No, you wouldn't.
How do you know?
What's wrong?
I guess...
I don't want to do it
like this.
Sorry for shooting
the puck so hard
and tricking you
in the bet.
- You didn't trick me.
- Yeah, I did.
I gave Madison
a Red Dead Revolver cheat code
so she'd hit your foot
with the rope.
I knew you
couldn't beat me.
You're right.
It's just...
I really like you.
And I'm pretty sure
you like me too.
But I don't want to play
any more games.
When you want--
I mean, if you ever want to,
just tell me
you're ready,
and, you know...
Sorry.
Well done.
He's not
always a jerk.
And neither
are you.
She obviously
likes you.
Just stop using her toothbrush
and stop playing games.
She'll still like you.
She's bossy...
But she's usually right.
Thank you.
Dr. House, can I ask you
a question?
Are you insane
or just stupid?
Is there a third option?
Actually,
I don't think there is.
I'm sorry.
I-I just wasn't thinking.
I mean, I was,
but only about myself,
which is apparently
the way I am...
Usually, not always.
And I need to convince
someone of that.
Mm-hmm.
And you think you can do that
by getting someone
to pull strings to get
her daughter into our preschool.
I spoke
to Sanford Wells.
You can call the police.
You can turn me in
for lying at the accident.
Oh, I'm sure Mr. Dryden
has already taken care of that.
Let her daughter in.
She's a great kid,
and Dr. Cuddy is a great mom.
They'll fit in
perfectly here.
And how exactly
does admitting her daughter
prove how unselfish
you are?
Seems like you're still
doing it to help yourself,
not anyone else.
I don't know.
I just know that
I need to do something.
I need her in my life.
You know what it's like
to actually need someone?
Yes.
I do.
But I also know what it's like
to have responsibilities.
Maybe it's time
you grew up.
Dr. House...
Is there anything
you'd like to say?
Can I be excused?
It's just food.
Something small enough
to go down the wrong pipe,
too big to get washed out
by the bronchial lavage.
Wouldn't show up
on a C.T.
But would cause
the C.O.P.D.
And wouldn't respond
to steroids or antibiotics.
Prep him
for exploratory surgery
and start the betting.
Betting?
I got a hundred bucks
says it's a pea.
I'm busy.
I know.
I just want to say
that I'm sorry.
Shouldn't you be saying that
to Sanford Wells?
A fifth-grade
career day?
You really thought
you could pull that off?
I figured,
how hard could it be?
And I wanted to prove
to you
that I do care
about your needs
and Rachel's.
I do.
Is that why
you also stole my computer?
Yes, it is.
And then threw it
in the trash?
I did not throw it,
I placed it,
knowing that the janitor
would find it
and know it was yours
and return it to you unharmed.
I'm a moron.
But that doesn't mean
I-I don't care about you,
that I don't think
about you,
that I don't want you
to be happy.
I was wrong.
You were right.
I can do better.
Just...give me a chance.
So what were you--
an Astronaut
or a Bullfighter?
I was myself...
For the most part.
I know you're still upset,
so I'm gonna...
I'll leave you to--to deal
with it however you want.
House.
You want to come over
for dinner tonight?
I'd love to.
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
www.tvsubtitles.net