One small step for men...
One giant waste
of your monthly allowance.
Safeties disengaged.
We're go for launch
in five, four,
three, two,
one!
That was freakin' awesome!
Whoa.
Aw, jeez. Come on.
My father's gonna kill me!
Can I film that too?
Whoa!
What?
Oh, man...
Is that guy dead?
I think so.
Aah! Aah! Aah!
It's okay, sir.
Get the rest of the flames out!
You... you gonna be okay,
mister?
It smells like...
Like licorice.
Sync by ThreeSixes
www.addic7ed.com
Think House is coming in today?
Maybe if we start
offering spa treatments.
He already
jumped off of a hotel balcony.
Who knows what he'll do next?
Ride some kind of
prostitute chariot to work?
First person to offer me
an interesting case
gets to ride her...
Single or double-team.
My scooter,
which, you know, said out loud,
sounds even more inappropriate.
Seriously?
You're bringing them to work now?
23-year-old homeless
man brought into the E.R.
with burn injuries and...
let me guess...
diagnosis was fire.
He said his burning flesh
smelled like licorice,
and the E.R. antiseptics
like blueberry muffins.
Cool.
Dysosmia...
could be anything
from an environmental factor
to an early sign
of a degenerative
brain disease.
Smells like a winner.
Okay, you and Chase go check out
the park where they found him.
You two load him up
with Prednisone,
give him
an odor I.D. test.
If he's still mistaking
his body odors for candy,
the problem's definitely
in his brain.
Also, find out what else
he's lying about...
Since I'm assuming
"Ferris Bueller"
is not his real name.
Why?
Seriously, who is that?
They say he's a righteous dude.
Before I forget,
I want you to meet Dominika.
She's about to become
a permanent member
of Team House.
Nice to me meetings you all.
Doing what exactly?
Me.
We're getting married
on Friday.
Mount up!
I don't think that
two people are supposed...
Living on the edge, baby doll!
How's the arm?
Hmm?
It hurts.
Do I have to check out now?
Not until we figure out
why your sense of smell is off.
When was the first time
you noticed it?
Maybe a couple months ago.
We also need you
to tell us your real name,
so we can review
your medical records.
I didn't ask
to come here, okay?
I'm not paying for any of this.
Don't worry.
I don't think
the collection agency
has an office in the park.
I don't have a medical history.
I've always been healthy.
What about those scars
and burn marks?
Lean forward.
My dad...
We didn't exactly get along
when I was a kid.
How many times
were you hospitalized?
Never.
He was good at it.
Made sure he never did anything
that couldn't be covered up
by a sweatshirt.
I'm sorry.
No, don't be.
I'm not.
The past is the past.
That's why I don't like
talking about it.
You can't ride
that thing in here.
Speaking of things,
I'm having one on Friday.
If you want to drop by,
we'd love to have you.
No pressure.
You're still standing on it.
So I am.
Perhaps you're not familiar
with New Jersey
handicap ordinances.
Or perhaps I am.
They apply to wheelchairs
and powered scooters only,
not toys.
Have you any idea
how much this toy cost?
I don't care.
For some reason, my leg's
been hurting a lot this week.
For some reason,
I still don't care.
Fine.
I'll return it.
Do I have to walk it
out of here?
Stop.
I'll make an exception
for your leg.
But next time,
check with me first.
Congratulations
on your engagement.
I hear a strange voice.
A very soft-looking man.
Must be the Wilson.
I know we said no secrets,
but I think I need to
take this alone, honey bunny.
Okay.
Nice to be meeting you.
You're trying to screw
with Cuddy.
Yeah, it's the classic
"You dumped me,
so I'm gonna get married
a week later" ruse.
'Cause not only
is she that stupid,
but apparently I'm that stupid.
Then what, you're
openly mocking marriage...
trying to prove
it means nothing?
It doesn't.
But you proved that
yourself years ago.
I'd love to keep guessing,
but I've got people
with tumors waiting.
Why do you want us to think
that you're getting married?
Only one theory left...
I am.
Dominika needs a green card.
So you're just doing
some random stranger a favor?
It's illegal.
People go to jail for that...
Pay huge fines.
Have you seen me
practice medicine?
You know how much it costs
to have a live-in maid,
personal assistant, cook,
massage therapist, whore?
I do.
She's willing to work
four days a week for free.
It's gonna save me
about $33,000.
All I have to do
is say two stupid words...
"I do."
And if she doesn't see it this way?
Iron-clad prenup...
We go our separate ways.
Your stunned look, I take it,
is your way of saying,
"Brilliant idea, House."
Wow.
You look different.
The Prednisone
has had time to work,
so we need to give you
the odor I.D. test now.
Sure.
We need you to tell us
what you smell.
Oh...
Something spoiled...
Maybe rotting meat?
It's baby powder.
I kind of like that one.
Peppermint?
It's extremely bad body odor.
Well, you got to admit,
that one's kind of
a good deal for me.
My backpack.
Oh, where'd you find it?
In the park, right next
to a big pile of questions.
What kind of
drugs you shooting up?
Vitamin supplements.
I've been trying to boost
my immune system.
All right, test me
if you don't believe me.
Ferris tell you
his real name yet?
Peter Johnson.
Danny Jennings.
I bought those books used.
All from the same guy?
I'm sorry, you know,
I think I should check out now.
And I should... Ow!
What's wrong?
Oh, my stomach.
Gastrointestinal bleeding.
Is anyone else
disturbed by this?
What?
She offered.
Danny may have
lied about his name,
but he was telling the truth
about the vials.
Tests confirm they were
vitamin A and B12.
He also enjoys vitamin H.
The kid's a junkie.
Tox screens were
negative for drug use.
His hair wasn't.
I had it tested...
'Cause unlike Santa
and the Easter Bunny,
homeless, non-mentally ill
20-somethings
without drug problems
don't exist.
He was a heavy user
sometime in the last
five months.
Wow.
That was incredible.
Thank you.
No, thank you.
I like a man
with the big, strong, sexy feet.
He really puts the "mani"
in the "pedi."
If he has a
history of snorting heroin,
he could have caused
the dysosmia himself.
But we still need to explain
the bleeding in his G.I. tract.
Vitamin injections
could have caused that...
Hypervitaminosis A syndrome.
So his symptoms
aren't connected.
House, you buying this?
Not usually.
But this guy's been sleeping
on a bed of dog poop.
I wouldn't be surprised
if he's got
six different symptoms
for six different reasons.
The bleed could be caused
by a G.I. obstruction.
Vitamin O.D.
makes sense, and it's easier to treat.
Give him Tocopherol
and zinc supplements
for the excess vitamin A.
If we're right...
He could go homeless tomorrow.
And if we're wrong,
his intestines could get
further distressed,
while we ignore
the G.I. obstruction.
See what happens when
women don't have to serve men
to stay in the country?
The get all uppity.
This is why
we invented green cards.
Go X-ray the guy's abdomen,
if it'll make you feel
all equal.
I need a favor.
I want to add my fiancee's name
to my health insurance
a few days early.
She wants to get a tooth capped
before the big day.
I'm not signing this.
I agree.
I think she looks beautiful
the way she is.
Oh, no, wait.
You're not signing that
for moral reasons?
You're declaring yourself
the sole arbiter of true love?
'Cause you covered
Taub's wife for years.
It's fraud.
She wanted me to bribe you,
like they do
back in the old country.
Tell her what I said.
This is America...
the land of the home
and the free of the braves.
Yeah, I just get
teary-eyed
every time I hear her say that.
She brought you a gift.
Almond kulich...
I make with own hands.
I-it's delicious.
Almond kulich...
How can you say no to that?
You realize if I do sign this
and you don't get
legally married,
you'll lose your insurance
with our carrier?
Yes.
Fine.
It's your life.
I wish you both
the best with it.
Thank you.
North, miss Teschmacher!
Your blood test was clean,
but your hair showed
heroin use.
I've been clean
over three months now.
How'd you kick it?
I had to die first.
I O.D.'d back in November,
and they said
I was clinically dead
for several minutes.
It was like God gave me
a second chance
to do things right this time.
You're saying God cured you?
No.
State rehab cured me.
But I should be dead,
but I'm not.
It has to mean something.
I mean, I-I must be here
for a reason, right?
Did you figure out the reason?
My goal is to become
a doctor one day.
I am smart.
I mean, I got a scholarship
for premed out of high school.
Chase...
Look.
We found 13 masses spread
across the wall of his colon,
ranging from two
to eight millimeters.
It can't be tumors.
Edges are too sharp and defined.
I thought it might be
parasites,
but we didn't see any movement
between X-ray exposures.
And no larvae or eggs
were observed
in any of his stool samples.
Which is kind of surprising
for a homeless junkie
living in a park.
Ex-junkie...
Claims he's been clean
for over three months.
And he's not planning
on staying homeless.
He's trying to protect
his health,
which is why he's been taking
vitamin supplements.
He wants to be a doctor.
He's just telling you
what you want to hear.
Once an addict,
always an addict.
Can you...
Please not do that
in front of me?
Doubt it.
You're the main reason
I'm on the stuff.
We could be looking
at fungal masses
hanging off the walls
of his colon.
Start him
on Amphotericin "B" tonight,
and in the morning,
run a scope up
where the sun don't shine,
see if you can find
any truffles.
I think we should boycott
this wedding on principle.
I kind of have to go.
His fiancee did give me
a foot massage.
And he invited me
to be in his wedding party.
W-what about Chase?
He ask him?
Yep. He's in it.
What the hell?
You just said
you weren't even going.
I still have feelings.
What's that?
That's definitely not a fungus.
You were bleeding because
you had 13 pieces of bone
in your digestive tract.
We think you have pica,
a craving for nonfood items
that's caused
by a chemical imbalance...
I didn't crave them.
I kind of...
Volunteered to eat them.
W-what? Why?
There's this great
Italian restaurant
I like to frequent.
And by "restaurant,"
I mean their dumpster out back.
The cook is kind of
a friend of mine.
He challenges me to eat stuff.
Sometimes it's raw squid,
or, you know, I have to chew
on a chicken bone.
But if I do it, then he
hooks me up with real food,
not just the garbage.
Great friend.
These fragments could have
perforated your colon
and killed you.
You have to promise us
you'll stop.
I think there's
something wrong with my eyes.
What is it?
Uh, it's like I'm looking at you
from the bottom of a well.
If we add tunnel
vision to the dysosmia,
we can subtract the bone-induced
abdominal bleeding.
I thought the
dysosmia was from heroin.
He said he never snorted.
He just shot up.
So that wouldn't have affected
his sense of smell.
And we believe
the lying liar why?
House...
Are you even listening to us?
I'll start when you decide
what the symptoms are
and give me some theories.
If we combine the dysosmia
with the tunnel vision,
the symptoms fit
for western equine encephalitis.
But the patient doesn't...
no fever.
Ow!
What the hell?
Negative reinforcement.
What about
Foster Kennedy Syndrome?
He could have a meningioma
or plasmacytoma.
Started by pressing
on his olfactory nerves,
it affects his sense of smell,
and now it's growing and
pressing on his optic nerve.
Good.
MRI his head, find it.
Your potential donation...
Hey, hey.
...Have an immediate impact
on our community.
We could extend the hours...
Something wrong?
No.
I just think maybe it would be
a better idea to have a tour
of the clinic first.
It's right this way.
Oh...
Oh!
Uh...
We have several patients
that are children,
and we find that it's important
to give them
the opportunity to play
to make the hospital
a less intimidating place.
M-my dad used to lock me
in a closet,
and it... and it feels
like I can't breathe.
We need you to stay still.
Give him a break.
You want him squirming around?
We'll have to do it twice.
I want you to show him
a little respect.
You really think this kid
can turn his life around?
He believes God gave him
a second chance.
That kind of belief
can be powerful.
Masters doesn't surprise me.
He plays the fellow med student
who dreams of being a doctor
and reels her in.
But you falling for his
deep connection with God?
He has hope.
After all he's been through,
it kind of makes me
root for him.
We don't even know who he is,
except that he lies
about who he is.
The bit about his abusive father
is probably all made up.
And he faked the scars?
He's a punk. Probably got
into a lot of fights.
And he sucked you in
using the dad story.
I don't think
I'm feeling very well.
I think I'm...
He's vomiting.
Should I ask him to stay still
while he does that?
He has two dark spots
in the parietal cortex.
They're not tumors...
Maybe some kind of, uh, injury
or inborn defect.
Apparently he was
clinically dead
for several seconds
when he O.D.'d.
The dark spots
could be brain damage
from oxygen starvation.
Except it's not.
I've seen MRI imagery
like that in schizophrenics.
Three serving two.
But schizophrenia doesn't explain
why his blood pressure
skyrocketed,
and he threw up in the MRI.
Panic attack.
He's claustrophobic.
He was fine
once we let him out.
The dysosmia and tunnel vision
could be hallucinations.
Except, as was already covered,
he was screened for
mental illness down in the E.R.
In your head!
It's "face."
On your face!
Close enough.
The E.R. docs missed it,
because he didn't present
with major symptoms yet.
We're seeing it in its infancy.
So we treat him, and then what?
He becomes just another
schizophrenic homeless man
wandering the streets...
We have to help him.
I'd love to, but I got
four million other crazy people
ahead of him
on my to-do list,
along with milk.
You two spent months
trying to figure out
a way to date
and not have it affect
your working relationship.
Now you need to do
the same thing for not dating.
No, I don't.
This is serious.
Did you know that she's...
She's dying of guilt and feels
horrible for dumping me.
It's great.
I mean, not the dumping part,
but the part where she'll now
let me do whatever I want.
So you're just trying
to punish her?
She feels bad,
and your only goal
is to take advantage?
That's not true.
I got plenty of goals.
One of them is a 60-inch
flat screen right there.
You're a lot of things, House,
but you've never been a sadist.
You're pummeling
an opponent
who isn't fighting back.
I already gave him
a second dose of Clozapine.
You don't need... I'll bet you 50
bucks his favorite sport is hockey.
How could you possibly
know that?
Just a hunch.
How you feeling?
My arm kind of hurts.
I'll talk to the nurse
about upping your pain meds.
Hockey, eh?
Oh, my nephew
bought it for me...
Knows I'm a huge fan.
I hate hockey.
If this is schizophrenia,
you're gonna need regular care.
I found some shelters that have
full-time medical staff
and also...
Oh, my arm really hurts!
Let's have a look.
Ow...
It feels like it's on fire!
We need to take a look under the bandages.
Ow! No, no, no.
Not that one, this one!
Ahoy there, me hearties!
Permission to come aboard.
♪
Danny said his left arm
felt like it was
on fire last night.
We assumed it was
a schizophrenic delusion, but...
It's not.
He's on Clozapine.
He'd be getting better,
not worse.
Sounds like
regional pain syndrome.
Has to be a genetic disorder.
Would you slow down!
You're gonna get us arrested.
I wouldn't worry about it.
We'll probably die first.
Don't make me take my shoe off!
We need to run his DNA.
He could have early onset
of Parkinson's.
Or cortical-based
ganglionic degeneration
or Huntington's or any one
of a dozen other
genetic diseases.
Hey, if you let us out,
we can start testing.
If we're gonna test
for them all, it'll take weeks.
I'm not canceling my honeymoon
to treat this kid.
It's a fake marriage,
but a real honeymoon?
Most are.
Danny could also die
before we get through testing
for all the possibilities.
So we cheat.
Since it's genetic,
daddy or mommy's got it too.
They're either sick or dead.
He doesn't know
where his mother is,
and he won't tell us
where his father is.
He's a homeless
ex-junkie.
Are you telling me
that you four geniuses
can't outwit him?
Green light!
Cuddy got it for me.
And now I'm drafting a request
for a study
into the effects of caffeine
involving an Italian
espresso machine
and a massage chair,
so make it quick.
I found Danny's father.
Well done.
The kid said he was
in a state-sponsored rehab
last November.
There's only one Danny Jennings
that was in treatment
at the time,
and he listed
his father's address
as his primary next of kin.
The "well done"
was for making it quick.
Now I'm gonna have
to take that back.
He lives about 30 minutes
from the hospital.
And the reason
you're continuing to talk
instead of driving there?
Chase and Masters
are already on their way.
Why didn't you ask me
to be part of your wedding?
You are genuinely upset
at being mockingly snubbed
by a mock wedding?
Is it because
I haven't been here
as long as them?
Or is it that you
really don't like me?
Or are...
are you just s-screwing...
Um...
I'll...
I'll come back
when she's finished.
She is.
Oh, my God!
W-what did you think
she was doing?
She's just installing
the cable.
That's not a euphemism!
Oh, I feel sorry
for the little one.
Isn't there something
we can do?
Can I help you?
We need to talk to you
about your son Danny.
Danny?
Who are you?
We're his doctors.
We need to know if you,
or perhaps his mother,
have any family history
of genetic disease.
Why? What difference
would it make?
You may not care
about your son, but...
Is that what Danny told you
when he was in rehab...
We didn't love him?
Um, not why we came here.
We just want to know
if there's any diagnosed
genetic disease in your family.
We're trying
to make your son better.
Better?
He died of a drug overdose.
We buried him three months ago.
Who are you?
The important question is,
who are you?
Danny Jennings is dead,
which means that
Danny Jennings has no pulse.
You, on the other hand...
Do.
Ergo, you are not
Danny Jennings.
Or I did the test wrong.
So why don't you cut the crap
and tell me your real name.
No.
Hiding your identity...
Well, either you're a criminal
or a superhero.
I'm not a criminal.
Awesome.
What color is my underwear?
I'm not telling you my name.
No problem.
I just need your father's name.
Forget it.
Care to tell me why?
He looking for me.
He supposedly...
Cleaned up and got sober.
And now he...
he wants to be a part
of my life again.
And I can't let that happen.
You're a big boy now.
You still think
he can hurt you?
You don't get it.
If I ever see my dad again...
I'll kill him.
What's happening to me?
Well, luckily for you,
we don't need daddy
to figure that one out.
Did you find out his real name?
Cerebellar ataxia.
That's a weird name.
The guy whiffed twice
trying to pick up a cup
right in front of him.
That plus everything else...
Means that we have whittled
our list of genetic diseases...
All the way down to one...
Early-onset Parkinson's.
After everything
he's been through,
now we have to tell him,
"Hey, you have
an incurable disease
that gets
progressively worse."
You could lie.
I'm fine with that.
But you'll probably
both feel better
if you give him Levodopa
and confirm with DNA tests.
He's gone too far.
He's taking up
six handicapped spaces
with a monster truck.
It's only four,
and he's gonna get rid of it
after the wedding.
And the chapel...
He's turned the chapel
into his own personal
catering hall.
Who cares?
Other than a janitor
sleeping off a bender,
he's the first person
to use it in two weeks.
Appeasement is never the answer
in the face
of naked aggression.
It won't be long
before his tanks
are rolling down
your Champs-Elysees.
I know what House is doing.
You, on the other hand...
Why do you care?
He isn't hurting anyone.
You're the first boss
he's ever had
who could handle him.
Before you, he was either fired
or buried under a mountain
of malpractice suits.
He needs someone to say no.
He needs someone
he'll listen to
when they say no.
If you really care about House,
you'll stop feeling
sorry for him
and get out there
and start kicking him
where he needs kicking.
I changed my mind.
What, you want the fish
instead of the chicken?
This room is
for patients' families,
not for doctors trying
to defraud the government.
Oh, so...
You've decided
to take a moral and.
Yeah.
The chapel still has sanctity
for some people.
You're right.
I think I saw blue the janitor
passed out in one
of the pews last week.
It's "Lou," and I would have
thrown him out too.
Well, where are we gonna go?
We got caterers staging
everything downstairs
as we speak.
We've got floral arrangements,
place settings...
Other wedding-y stuff.
That's not my problem.
I sent out the invitations.
People are coming here.
That's also not my problem.
And I want the TV back.
You should just let me die.
The world's better off
without me.
It's normal.
People feel depressed
when they get bad news...
Because it's bad news...
Obviously.
I didn't O.D. by accident.
I was trying to kill myself.
Why?
'Cause I've done things...
Horrible things.
I've hurt people.
And when I didn't die,
I thought...
I thought God forgave me.
But he just wanted me
to suffer.
And I deserve it.
You don't deserve it.
I...
I had a girlfriend
in college...
And I almost killed her.
I just snapped.
And I started hitting her.
And if her roommate
hadn't come home...
I'm evil.
I am just like my dad.
We're both monsters.
I deserve to die.
I can't... I can't...
I feel dizzy.
I need a crash cart in here!
His heart is dilated
and failing.
And at the rate it's happening,
he'll need a new one soon.
And there's no way we'll get him
on the transplant list.
What are we missing?
Everything. We know nothing
about this kid.
Except that he's gotten worse
since we admitted him.
Why?
Most of our patients
tend to do that,
unless we cure them.
Yeah, but why so fast?
He had dysosmia
for a couple months,
never even came here
to get it treated.
He's just a random burn victim.
We get him, boom,
he's got tunnel vision,
peripheral polyneuropathy,
cerebellar ataxia,
and now cardiomyopathy.
What's different here
than, say, living
in a filthy state park?
You think cleanliness
is making him sick?
Allergic reaction?
We treated him
with Vicodin, Clozapine,
and one I.V. bag
of Levodopa.
His condition started
deteriorating before that.
Stop that man!
I need the meal card
for the patient in 243.
He's eating healthy...
Because he can.
Most of the meals in here
are vegetarian.
Adult Refsum disease...
Fits all the symptoms.
His body can't process
the phytanic acid
and chlorophyll.
It's his healthy diet
of green vegetables
that's killing him.
So if we change his diet...
We save his life.
Run him through a
plasmapheresis treatment
to remove the excess
phytanic acid from his blood.
Confirm with gene testing.
Okay, I got to go get married.
♪
They say true love
doesn't exist anymore.
Maybe it never did.
So without further ado...
Do you, Dominika Patrova,
take this man
to be your lawfully
wedded husband?
I do.
And do you, Gregory House,
take this woman
to be your
lawfully wedded wife?
Yep.
Then by the power vested
in me by the state of New Jersey
just for today,
I now pronounce you
man and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
Those of you with cameras,
please feel free
to provide legal documentation.
It's okay.
I'm just angry at myself.
I promised I wouldn't let
this get to me.
But it got to me.
Just say the word, and we will
climb out that window right now.
I wouldn't give House
the satisfaction.
You see?
Things are getting
back to normal.
Yeah...
Normal.
Are you feeling better?
So all I have to do is eat
the right kinds of food,
and I'll be okay?
Basically, yeah.
It's pretty limiting,
and it is for the rest
of your life.
But if you follow the diet
and get checked up regularly,
you should be fine.
Thank you...
Mm-hmm.
For not giving up on me.
You're not a bad person.
You made mistakes,
but we all do.
Maybe when you get
out of here, you can...
Go talk to someone...
A professional.
Yeah.
Yeah, some of those places
you suggested
had people on staff.
You know, I think God
really does have
a plan for me.
And all this...
It was just his way
of testing my resolve.
And I wouldn't have passed it
without you.
See you tomorrow, Danny.
That's not my real name.
It doesn't matter.
I know this is not
real marriage...
But I really like you.
I like you too.
I can't.
Why not?
I never sleep
with married women.
I'm going to bed.
You can take the couch.
What's going on?
Danny disappeared
without checking out.
So you called the FBI?
We didn't call
them, they just showed up.
Danny's DNA...
When we sent it to the lab
for testing,
it set off alarm bells
all over the country.
Alarm bells for what?
He's linked
to 13 unsolved murders
in ten different states.
He's a serial killer
who eats his victims.
And we saved him.
Sync by ThreeSixes
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net