[Breathing deeply]
How long has your daughter
had trouble breathing?
About a week now.
The best dads
wait two or more.
Yeah, no, it's not
like it's serious.
I-I checked online,
and it's...
Asthma or something.
"Or something"
is the number one killer
of teens
with no medical degree.
When was the last time
he took you to see a doctor?
Uh, like five months ago.
We went a clinic in Trenton.
I had strep throat.
You remember the antibiotic
they gave you?
Is it neomycin?
Amoxicillin.
So about the inhaler
for my asthma, I was--
Sorry!
Hospital policy
specifically prohibits me
from giving meds
to unrelated
homeless people
pretending to be
father and daughter.
Your pants
are a size too short,
so either you grew
a couple of inches
or you grabbed the closest size
in a thrift store.
And only you have dimples,
which are adorable,
but they're also an x-linked
dominant genetic trait.
Which actually doesn't
prove anything.
The fact that she didn't
burst into tears tells me
that you never thought
he was your dad.
Let's get out of here.
Since you're the brains
of the operation,
might wanna stick around.
What, so I can get busted
by Social Services?
No, so you can stop
bleeding out of your ear.
It's usually a sign
of a skull fracture.
Someone been using your head
as a soccer ball?
No.
Much as I'd like
to take your word for it,
I have no interest in taking
your word for it.
No tenderness, no pain.
Looks like you might
actually be telling the truth
about something.
Ear canal is fine.
You don't have a fever.
Pay the man.
He's late
for a trashcan fire.
[Door opens and closes]
Would you--would you
tell me what's going on?
What's wrong with me?
I have no idea.
♪ House 8x10 ♪
Runaways
Original air date on January 30, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
[Massive Attack's Teardrop]
♪
Why'd you ask to meet us
30 miles away
from the hospital?
Because I can.
Also, Chris Christie's blog
says the pancakes here
are the best.
So...what do we got
on this 18-year-old
with the ear bleed
and the breathing problems?
CT confirms
no skull fracture,
and looking at her
confirms she's not 18.
Yes, she is.
Says so in the file.
We can't treat
an underage patient
without a guardian--
we need to call Social Services.
I cut a deal
with the patient.
We don't call,
she doesn't bolt.
Whatever age,
living on the street
makes her vulnerable
to malnutrition,
drug use, H.I.V.,
all things which could
explain her symptoms.
No sign of malnutrition.
Tox screen is clear.
S.T.D. panel
was negative.
And...is that Foreman?
Oh, my goodness,
it is!
Hi, Dean Foreman!
[Camera clicks and whirs]
[Camera clicking]
Are you not gonna
introduce us
because we're married?
Oh, no, wait--
that's her.
She's a pharmaceutical rep,
and this is a working breakfast.
In a restaurant
that's nowhere near your home
or the hospital.
Chris Christie
recommends the pancakes.
(Chase) Squamous cell
middle ear tumor could have
caused the ear bleed.
Paraneoplastic reaction
caused the breathing problems.
Middle ear looks
completely normal.
But there is thickening
in the lining of the wall
of the third ventricle.
Could be a sign
of cerebral infection.
Would explain
the lack of fever.
Pneumococcus
is pretty common
among the homeless
population.
We should find out
if she's been vaccinated.
Sure, ask her,
and when she refuses
to tell you anything,
start her on Ceftriaxone
for pneumococcus.
And if she says
she has been vaccinated?
Then don't believe her,
and start her on Ceftriaxone
for pneumococcus.
How about we don't believe
she's gonna bolt
and we call
Social Services?
While I'm in
the little boys' room,
you can pretend that I'm
seriously considering that idea.
[Mouth full]
The bathroom's that way.
Pretty sure there's
one in the hospital.
When I was your age,
I ran away.
Lived on my own.
- At the time, it seemed--
- Oh, let me guess.
Life with mom and dad
was kind of a drag.
So you just ran away,
lived with friends,
and partied with guys
that you knew
your parents would hate.
And then when you got tired
of being a rebel,
you just went home.
Being homeless
isn't a vacation for me.
And I'm not acting out.
My life at home sucked,
so I got the hell
out of there.
There are other options
besides living
on the streets.
Right, like group homes,
where you're packed in
with as many messed-up
delinquent kids as possible,
foster parents
who only take you in
because
you're a meal ticket.
I can think of easier ways
to make 175 bucks a week.
No, you're right--
I really should roll the dice
and hope for a pair
that don't ruin my life
the way that my mom--
get your hands off my stuff!
The stuff might tell us
more about why you're sick.
A history textbook.
You go to school?
I don't plan on
being homeless forever.
[Southern accent]
Hello, good sir.
My brother,
the General here,
gots the green-apple
quickstep.
One of us is in
the wrong time zone.
And if it's me,
I need to talk
to a stockbroker and anyone
from the Kennedy family,
in that order.
Well, he got the runs,
and we do need him
up and at 'em
for battle tomorrow.
It's hardly
authentic,
coming to a newfangled
clinic,
especially with
a Yankee doctor.
[Sword clanking]
Sir, are you
questioning my resolve?
Yes, and your sanity.
I'm multitasking.
Uh, General...
You're not allowed out.
We swore that we would
see the elephant together.
Well, far be it from me
to come between two nut jobs
and their "elephant."
I could add some Mercury,
if you want to make it
more authentic.
The Confederacy
thanks you, Doc.
Got House's phone.
Deleted all photos
of you and Anita.
- I owe you.
- An affair?
Never knew
you were such a tramp.
Neither did I.
Anita, she's fun, smart.
Not looking
for anything serious.
It's--it's...
Pretty perfect.
Except for the annoying
guilt about the husband.
The lies she must
be telling him.
But not guilty enough
to stop seeing her.
She's smoking hot,
and it's not his job
to protect her marriage.
Aren't you supposed
to be pointing a finger
at your own life
as a cautionary tale?
If not for cheating,
I might still have a wife,
but I wouldn't have
Sophie and Sophia.
Which means
I wouldn't be preparing
for their visit this week
by child locking
all my cabinets,
padding table corners,
and getting rid of every
single magazine.
You could probably
just hide the porn
in your underwear drawer.
Magazines go away so I won't
ignore my children.
I know I have
to pay attention to them.
I want to pay attention
to them,
but they're just so...
Boring.
[Cell phone rings]
[Beep]
Did you learn anything
at Jane Doe's school?
(Adams) They did a bunch
of vaccinations,
including pneumococcus.
Take her off
the Ceftriaxone.
So we're back
to square none?
Not exactly.
The name she registered under
seems to be fake,
but the address
is a foreclosed house.
We'll let you know
what we find.
Plenty of food, water.
And beer.
She eats well.
Goes to school
and makes good grades.
She's a homeless girl
who's captain
of the volleyball team.
How can you
be okay with this?
Your mom sends you to work
with snacks.
I want and need parents.
Jane Doe is flourishing
without them.
Maybe.
But this mold
definitely is.
(Jane Doe)
You went to my school.
Now that they know,
they'll report me.
I can't go back there!
You may have
a fungal infection.
You need that medicine.
Fluconazole, right?
I'll get it at a clinic.
Ohh! Oh.
I can't feel my legs.
Hey, wha--
is that the infection?
I don't think so.
So...What causes
an ear bleed,
breathing problems,
and our runaway's
inability to run away?
(Chase) Fungal infection's
off the table.
What about
transverse myelitis?
Not with normal
posterior column function.
I've been waiting
to do this for months.
Pull!
Sights seem to be
off on this.
We didn't call
Social Services before
because we didn't want
the patient to take off.
Now she can't--there's
no reason for us not to call.
Well, how about the reason
that there's no reason?
This is working fine
for me.
Pull!
[Gunshot]
Well, now, that one
clearly took evasive action.
You want to protect her
because you think
she's fine on her own,
outside the system.
Does anyone have a position
on our patient's
medical condition?
Could be endocarditis
with septic emboli.
Pull!
I'd turn around and shoot you,
but apparently I'd miss.
There's no murmurs,
no Osler nodes.
You've never done this
before, have you?
No, I have not.
But all the time
I had my ankle monitor on,
I was furious
that I couldn't.
Vasculitis fits.
Start treatment
with steroids.
She's lucky, she'll
be free to flee again.
Not once I call
Social Services.
I'm not giving up.
You wanna bet?
One shot, one birdie.
You hit,
you make the call.
You miss,
never mention it again.
No.
Why would I agree?
'Cause your
only other option is
you call and I fire you.
[Cocks gun]
Pull!
[Gunshot]
She responding
to corticosteroids?
Looks like it.
And Social Services.
I thought for sure
there'd be some yelling
or profanity,
possible bloodletting.
(Adams) She's tired of living
on the streets after all.
I'll bet House re...gret...
Could he know
I'm good with a gun?
I don't know how, but...
Hiring a hooker
to pretend to be
a social worker?
She took a bet
that she knew she'd win.
Frankly,
I feel violated.
What happened to
the social worker I called?
Apparently, someone
identifying themselves
as Dr. Pujols called
and said the patient ran off.
[Giggling]
Come on.
"Poo holes."
I've informed
Social Services
of the mistake and given Jane
Doe's description to the cops.
They'll track down
the parents.
Thank you.
I'll leave you
and Dr. "Pujols" alone.
You should have told me
you were treating an underage
clinic patient.
I was giving you
the gift of deniability.
Now I'm giving you the gift
of additional clinic hours.
No, you're not.
You've got
nothing on me.
Check your phone.
Uh...my phone?
Oh, right. Yes, I--
I did have
some pictures on that.
But...
I also have these.
There's the two of you
kissing over dinner.
Busting a move
in a night club.
Is that your hand
near her nether regions?
Thanks again for taking off
the ankle bracelet.
I'm not gonna let you
blackmail me, House.
Oh, of course not.
There's no way
someone of your integrity
would let me compromise
your job in any major way
over some tawdry
bit of gossip.
But what about
compromising it
in a minor way?
Reduced clinic hours.
Unlimited Internet
porn budget.
That makes much more sense
than the nuclear option
of ruining both our lives.
You can keep these.
I got copies.
[Sniffs]
How I miss
the sweet smell
of stickin' it
to the man.
Adams is right.
You're protecting
this girl.
[Sniffs]
No, I was wrong.
It's the stench
of moralizing.
I'm protecting myself
from meddling bureaucrats
and parents.
You admire this girl.
She had a horrible
home life,
so she went out
on her own.
She's your road
not taken.
I've always dreamed
of living
in an abandoned
house with mold.
House, all I'm
accusing you of
is having a connection
with a patient.
This is a good thing.
It's not a good thing,
'cause it's not a thing.
It is a thing...
which she'll prove
when her parents show up
and you start
protecting her from them.
The sound I make is,
moooo!
quack quack
quack quack quack.
[Baby coughs]
Moo.
The sound is quack.
Quack quack.
Quack quack quack.
I'm an ass.
On the plus side,
I can now program my DVR
from my phone.
They are kind of boring.
All kids, not just yours.
Very helpful.
You need to log more hours.
Eventually, you'll pass boredom
and get to bonding.
Kind of like
Stockholm syndrome.
I heard the nurses talking.
You called Social Services
for real.
Because you shouldn't
be living on your own.
Right, better my mom should
use me as a punching bag.
If your mom abused you,
Social Services won't
let you go home with her.
Have I mentioned
I don't trust the system?
We don't know
if you're better yet.
You can't just take off.
Uh, can we help you?
I'm Adele Brown from
Social Services, and this is--
I'm Ellen Rogers.
Callie's mother.
You haven't been that
for two years.
I promise...
Things are different.
Mom...two sentences in,
and you're already
making promises.
Okay, maybe we need
to take a minute here
and give Callie
some space.
No, I don't need a minute.
I need her out of my life.
[Coughing]
Is she okay?
I will be once you just...
[Coughing]
Oh, my God!
(Taub)
We need help in here!
[Callie continuing
to cough]
[Suction slurping]
- Go!
- (Man) And they're off!
You bet 100 bucks
on a turtle race?
I paid Mr. Chips 5 bucks
to take a dive.
[Crowd cheering]
The bleeding
stopped on its own.
She got worse after
being on steroids,
so autoimmune is out.
Diagnosis depends
on whether the blood
was coming
from the sinuses,
lungs, or her guts.
Mr. Chips
looks like he wants it.
100 bucks says he'll
make soup out of Franklin.
[Cheers and applause]
You're on.
How'd the mom
seem to you?
If you're asking him
if she looks like someone
who beat her kid,
you're a moron.
Move your ass, Mr. Chips!
You should have seen her face
when mom walked in.
Callie hates her.
I don't think she's lying.
Because people never lie
about people they hate.
Big sinus bleed
could be sinusitis
and a bleeding disorder.
She didn't complain
about a headache.
The bleeding
is in her gut.
Could be
Zollinger-Ellison.
Acid reflux causes asthma,
and the acid erodes the stomach,
causing the bleeding.
[Cheers and applause]
Yes!
Franklin rules.
Mr. Chips drools.
Mr. Chips's owner only feeds
him on apples and bananas.
Nowhere near enough
vitamin A.
Pay up.
And do an upper endoscopy
to confirm
for Zollinger-Ellison,
after mommie dearest
has given her permission.
Ellen shouldn't have consent
if she beat her daughter.
Doesn't matter if
she beat her daughter.
Only matters if Social Services
says she beat her daughter.
Good thing you made it
all official.
Will the endoscopy
be painful?
Is that an issue?
It's a medical procedure.
There will be
some discomfort.
I never meant
to hurt my daughter.
And yet you hit her.
She told you that?
And now you're gonna
tell me you didn't.
I'm a drug addict.
And I've been
a lousy mom.
Especially since
my husband died.
I mean, he was closer
to Callie than I was,
and I missed him...
So much.
And it was too hard.
And taking Oxy just...
made things easier.
Right up until it made me
lose my daughter.
I hurt Callie a lot.
But one of the only things
that I can feel okay about
is that I never hit her.
Didn't peg you as
the midday fun kind of guy.
So glad I was wrong.
Ohh. Unfortunately,
that's not why we're here.
Remember that guy from
the restaurant yesterday?
Mm-hmm.
He's got pictures
of us.
He's threatening
to show your husband.
I thought you said that guy
was one of your best doctors.
Yeah, not one
of my best people.
We've gotta stop
seeing each other.
Not necessarily.
I told my husband
about you.
What?
Why?
He was saying that things
had been better lately
between him and I,
that I was happier.
I said that I was.
And that you
were the reason.
And...He was okay
with that?
Not initially.
It was a pretty tough
conversation.
Neither of us is ready
to give up on the marriage.
And I am not ready
to give up this.
You don't have to feel
so guilty anymore.
[Inhales through teeth,
groans]
You didn't need
to shoot yourself.
I could have given you
a Section 8.
We've hit the drills
pretty hard,
and by the fourth round,
my hand went numb.
The gun slipped and--
I only had blanks in it,
but...
It's funny how nearly
shooting your toe off
cured that
speech impediment.
Ah. Yeah.
Sorry about that.
Sheldon's a...Progressive.
Eh--compared to who?
Rupert Murdoch?
Progressives are reenactors
who strive for
complete authenticity.
They never drop character
while in uniform.
Whereas you just
dabble in crazy.
[Sighs]
Sheldon and I had
a big falling out
years ago.
We only really started
talking again because
of the reenactments.
They, uh...
Gave me my brother back.
That's a very moving story.
Be a lot more affecting
if you hadn't
bonded over something
so completely idiotic.
[Hisses]
Your mom didn't
hit you, did she?
No.
Then why'd
you lie about it?
Because I wanted
to get out of here.
People understand
getting hit
more than
what my mom does.
Tell me.
Maybe I'll understand.
Well, I was the mom.
She couldn't keep a job.
She'd spend
all her money on pills.
I had to get a job.
Double shifts,
just to keep the power on.
Keep food in the house.
I couldn't tell you how many
times she nearly O.D.ed
and I had to clean her up
and put her in bed.
So I decided, if I was
gonna be the grown-up,
I'd rather do it
on my own terms.
Your mom knows
she messed up.
She's determined
not to do it again.
Yeah.
And she'll feel that way,
right up until
things get too tough
and she has to start
using again.
Do you think
people can change?
No.
But I don't think that's
gonna change your opinion,
because...
people don't change.
Stop.
Is that an ulcer?
Yeah, it is.
But we haven't
reached the stomach yet.
I'm still high
in the esophagus.
Means it's not
Zollinger-Ellison.
Ulcer's bleeding.
We need to lavage before
she drowns in her own blood.
[Coughing]
(Chase) Cauterized the ulcer,
stopped the bleeding.
(Taub) Compromised immune system
from living on the street
could have made her
susceptible to HPV.
HPV was covered
on the STD panel.
She's negative.
What if she didn't
get this from being homeless?
What if she got it
from her mom?
I'm assuming you're thinking
something genetic, because--
I'm thinking addiction.
Alcohol-induced
esophagitis.
Explains esophageal ulcers
and her other symptoms.
If only
it would explain
why we've never
seen her drunk,
drinking, or detoxing.
Her blood pressure's
been elevated.
Could be the DTs.
It's been mildly elevated.
Mildly elevated BP
could put her at risk
of a Berry aneurysm.
Weak blood vessel
in the brain
gets pounded on
by elevated BP,
causes it to expand
and contract.
Causes the symptoms
to come and go.
CT didn't show any signs
of an aneurysm.
Did I mention
they come and go?
Much as your presence
may cause
objects to become
engorged with blood,
sometimes aneurysms
just aren't in the mood.
Alcoholism
and Berry aneurysm
are both valid theories.
I think we should discuss this
with the patient and her mom.
Why? We discussed it
right here.
Go tell 'em she needs
a cerebral angiogram
to locate the aneurysm,
then surgery to repair.
(Callie)
Brain surgery?
When?
We booked the O.R.
for an hour from now.
And Dr. House is sure
that's what she has?
He's confident
in the diagnosis.
It's consistent with
all of her symptoms.
But you don't buy it.
No.
I think your symptoms
are the result
of alcohol abuse.
But I'm not--
I'm not an alcoholic.
You came to the hospital
with beer in your pocket.
We found more alcohol
at your house.
Yeah, I use booze
as payment.
I have an occasional beer
with my friends.
That doesn't mean
I have a problem.
I want the surgery.
Actually,
it's your mom's decision.
I'm not an addict.
That's what I always
said to you, Callie,
but I had a problem--
I'm nothing like you!
Tell them to do the surgery.
I need a few minutes
to think.
The patient asked me
what I thought.
I pay you to think
inside this room.
Outside this room,
I pay you to parrot.
It's her choice.
She has the right to know!
It's a medical choice
that you turned
into an extension
of your baggage and hers.
You told the mom something
you want to believe
because you
don't want to believe
that this girl might be
doing fine parent-free.
Which also happens to be
what the mom wants to believe.
You think she wants
to feel responsible
for her daughter's illness?
That woman sees everything to do
with her daughter through...
Guilt-colored glasses.
It's all her fault.
House...
Don't...bully her.
She's overwhelmed enough.
Well, it's nothing compared
to how she's gonna feel
when her daughter dies
from the aneurysm
she decided not to treat.
You must be Dr. House.
I save my appearances
for when parents are on
the brink of doing something
incredibly stupid.
Your daughter has
a Berry aneurysm.
She needs surgery.
What she does not need
is you making this
or any other decision.
Well, I can't just
leave this up to her.
Then leave it up to me,
and just leave.
Ohh.
I'm not gonna
abandon my daughter.
She hates you.
It's actually not
such a big deal.
There's plenty of kids
who hate their parents.
What makes it a big deal
is that she should hate you.
Playing the biology card
doesn't change anything
except where she lives.
Your daughter is better off
without you.
So...let her be
better off without you.
I'm gonna
do the surgery.
I'll take the fallout
from Social Services.
Dr. House!
My daughter's care
is my choice.
And so is this.
Treat her
for alcoholism.
Peek-a-boo!
[Laughs]
Why would Anita
tell her husband
about our affair?
Probably just
got sick of lying.
Look at it this way.
Now the sex is both
commitment- and guilt-free.
And men love
commitment-free sex.
[Cooing]
Yes, they do.
Oh, yes, they do!
[Bangs bottle on counter]
They're gonna
find out eventually.
Peek-a-boo!
[Laughing]
How do you keep doing
the same thing over and over
with the same level
of enthusiasm?
First off, be a decent,
empathetic person.
This is what you
said you wanted,
but you're
actually more upset
now that
her husband knows.
- 'Cause I'm hurting him.
- You always were.
Yeah, but he didn't
know that.
Which means
he wasn't really hurt.
Yeah, I know
it's a rationalization,
but it went a long way
to making me feel...
A little less guilty
about seeing her.
Looks like
you're gonna need
a bigger rationalization.
Ahh...Peek-a-boo!
[Baby laughs]
Peek-a-boo!
Social Services report
came in on your mom.
Ah, let me guess.
She passed
with flying colors.
She always does.
I think she might
make it this time.
House left a bottle
of Vicodin
to see if
she'd steal it.
She gave it back.
You could at least
let her sleep in the room.
She could have listened to me
about my drinking.
I mean, even if you are
right about it,
why take your word
over mine?
I'm her daughter.
Because it...
She's your mom.
And, for the first time,
she's acting like it.
It's a little late
for that.
Good night.
[punching button rapidly]
Morning!
I heard you went
head-to-head with the mom.
Not for your reasons.
You're protecting
the girl.
I'm protecting
my diagnosis.
And you tested her--
see if you could
get her back on drugs
and out of her
daughter's life.
That was to show Adams
that mommie dearest
hadn't changed.
I'm taking a principled stand
against idealism.
Your patient's stable?
Well, maybe Adams
was right.
The illness
is alcohol-related.
Well, I hope so,
considering it's what
we're treating her for.
You--you hope
you're wrong
for the sake
of the patient?
I hope that I'm right
but the aneurism bursts
without killing her.
Call me a softie.
Or the mom agrees
to an autopsy
so I can prove it.
Your patients love you
because you're empathetic.
I also have kind eyes.
Why are you here?
But you don't love
all your patients?
Of course not.
I'll--I'll bet
some of them bore you.
Dull people
get cancer too.
Why are you here?
But you...fake
an interest in them
because you needed to,
right?
And if you do it
long enough,
it becomes real?
Well, no,
because the interest
isn't fake.
Really?
Because you realize
they're not dull.
It was just your
misinterpretation of them.
I just haven't found a way
to make them interesting yet.
It's all about
common ground.
You found one thing
you both like or hate.
John Woo movies,
romance novels, kale.
Sometimes, the best way
to connect with someone
is stop thinking about them
and focus on yourself.
Wh--uhh.
What is this about?
Not everything
has an agenda.
See ya.
[Door closes]
I told him because
it was the right thing to do.
Right.
This doesn't change
anything between us.
It sort of does for me.
Y-you want to stop
seeing each other?
No.
I was thinking...
Maybe you could tell
your husband that we did.
And then go back
to sneaking around
behind his back?
Yes.
Why would you
want to do that?
I don't know.
I...
This just feels...
Wrong.
I th--I think I'm gonna go.
[Vomits]
Ohh, God.
We thought it was
the salt pork.
But all the menfolk
been eatin' it,
and we the only ones
that's sick.
[Vomiting]
Which one of you
is the cheap bastard?
[Grunts]
Your uniforms.
They're not wool.
They're polyester.
Cheap polyester.
Which gets processed
with a heavy metal
called antimony.
You wear badly processed
polyester
all day and night
for days and nights,
you get
antimony poisoning
which caused your diarrhea
and your numbness
in your hands.
And your
collective vomiting.
Polyester uniforms?
I was being authentic.
With polyester uniforms?
The Confederacy gave men
$21 every six months--
- You poisoned us both.
- At least I have principles.
Because they
don't cost anything.
Brother against brother.
Now, that is authentic.
[Both vomiting]
I know you don't
want me here,
but, um...
They had banana muffins
downstairs.
Reminded me of our
St. Pete's trip.
Remember?
We used to walk
and get some
every morning at that bakery.
I guess.
Were you high
on that trip?
Not when
we were together.
I used to wait
until you went to bed.
You can stay.
If you want.
Okay.
Mm. It's not bad.
[Rapid beeping]
What's happening?
Is this from
the alcohol treatment?
I was wrong.
The Berry aneurysm
must have just burst.
Temporal lobes
are clear.
Parietal, clear.
Get me a micro-vascular
clip tray
as well as the occlusion.
[On speaker]
Check the ventricles.
Ventricles are clear too.
Aneurysm must have
leaked instead of burst.
Inject the dye.
Posterior cerebral clear.
Vertebral clear.
Circle of Willis
also clear.
She doesn't have
a Berry aneurysm.
[Alarm beeps]
Her BP's dropping.
Start her on pressors.
We gotta get her BP up
before her organs
start shutting down.
(House)
Adams...with me.
Pressors will only
give us a couple hours, Max.
What causes
breathing issues,
bleeding issues,
paralysis,
loss of consciousness?
What are we missing?
That's everything bad
that's happened.
What about
the good stuff?
You mean like we should
be more optimistic?
She got a little better
when we put her on steroids,
which can attack
tumor cells.
Maybe she has cancer.
No hypercalcemia,
no elevated blood proteins.
She and her mom mentioned
a trip they took to Florida
a couple years ago--
what about dengue fever?
Cholera?
Great ideas,
if dengue fever
or cholera laid in wait
for two years
before suddenly...
Did your biological daughter
go swimming in Florida?
In a lake or a pond
or an everglade?
Uh...Yeah.
There's a canal
near my mother's house.
Do you know
what's wrong with her?
Family vacations kill.
Come with me.
Don't want
to explain this twice.
You're letting in the flies.
And she needs an LVAD.
No, she doesn't.
Your daughter
has ascariasis.
It's a disease caused
by a parasitic worm
found in feces.
Animals use the canal
as a potty,
the eggs from the feces
ended up in Callie's intestines
when she went swimming...
Where they hung out,
quietly and asymptomatically,
biding their time till,
somewhere along the way,
they got knocked loose.
Maybe a dive
in volleyball practice
or maybe she slipped
on her way into a soup kitchen.
But once they hatched,
the worms got to work
on her lungs,
her ear,
the nerves in her legs.
The worms got agitated
by the steroids we gave her,
which started them on their
journey to the esophagus
and, ultimately,
to the heart.
A few pills
of Mebendazole...
She'll be fine.
(Ellen)
She's feeling much better.
Walking on her own.
Getting along
with her mother?
As long as I keep
bringing her muffins.
Did someone come
take her for a test?
Callie agrees with you...
That people don't change.
She said when her mom
slips again,
she didn't want
to be there.
She'd rather remember her
like she is now.
Smart girl.
You got the ending
you wanted.
'Cause I was only looking
to solve the case,
not their lives.
Now, I don't care
if the people who work for me
are screwed up.
In fact,
I even encourage it.
But absolution?
You do that
on your own time.
Or not at all.
'Cause...Clearly,
you suck at it.
[Babies cooing]
[Grunts]
There.
This is Aaron Rodgers.
Wow, 127
quarterback rating.
You know what sound
he makes?
Grrrrr!
[Laughs]
[Squeals]
[Babies laughing]
[Chuckles]
Okay. Oy!
Um...
This...
is Terrell Owens.
People call him "T.O."
Do you know what sound
he makes?
Wah!
[Laughs]
Wah! Wah! Wah!
[Foy Vance's Be the Song]
♪ And when you run
This is Mark Sanchez.
Do you know what sound
people make about him?
Pffftt!
♪ Then I will come
♪ in dead of night
Working late?
Husband have her tonight?
And every night.
She broke it off.
It's for the best.
I'm not really
an affair guy after all.
Sure you are, buddy.
You just lost interest once
it stopped being an affair.
That's why
you're relieved.
But don't worry--
it's not gonna end here.
You'll just have to get your
adrenaline fix somewhere else.
When that doesn't
do it anymore,
then you'll just...
escalate things somehow.
At least, that's
what I've been told.
I'm not like you, House.
True...No limp.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net