♪ House 8x11 ♪
Nobody's Fault
Original air date on February 6, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
(Taub)
Pressure. I need pressure.
(Adams)
Get me sutures on a Kelly.
(Taub)
Need an EPI.
(Adams) Get O.R. Ten unpacked.
Alert trauma.
[Recorder beeps]
Let the record show
that we are officially convening
a disciplinary hearing
regarding the events
of February 3, 2012
in patient room 209.
Dr. House, this recording
will be transcribed
and published along with
all supporting documentation
and rulings.
Do you have any questions
before we get started?
Yeah.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Walter Cofield,
Chief of Neurology,
Mercy Hospital.
I'll be deciding
your fate today.
Cofield.
You were the Residency Director
at Hopkins
before you moved to Mercy,
which means it's safe
to assume
that you trained Foreman.
Which means it's also safe
to assume
that he trusts you.
This hearing isn't about me,
Dr. House.
I know you'd like
to make it about me,
because then it wouldn't be
about you.
It's interesting
that he'd pick the old mentor
to judge the new one.
Interesting,
but not relevant.
The facts of this case,
on the other hand--
the facts are in the file.
If you have trouble reading
my handwriting,
give me a call.
I'm going back to work.
If I just consider the file,
the facts
aren't in your favor.
The facts say
you should be suspended,
which,
from what I understand,
would mean a revocation
of your parole.
The patient was a 32-year-old
high school chemistry teacher.
He collapsed while out jogging.
He was paralyzed
in all four extremities
despite the fact
that the scans...
Show no sign of stroke
or structural lesions.
Put out an APB for a car
with a man-shaped dent
in the grill?
No broken bones,
no signs of trauma.
Transverse myelitis.
Boring.
No enhancement on the MRI.
I just don't know
what to do.
Please, you have
to help me solve this thing.
[Angelic chorus]
♪
A little poetic license.
What are you doing?
Taking my vic-amins.
Those are Vicodin?
Did you have surgery
recently?
About a decade ago.
My leg is no good
at judging time.
Were you taking Vicodin
during this case?
Uhh...
Yes.
And during about nine years
of previous cases.
My process is proven.
Good things usually happen.
Bad things sometimes happen.
And when bad things happen,
we should figure out
what went wrong,
so we can learn from it
and correct it.
So that we can
assign blame
instead of recognizing
that bad things
sometimes happen.
It was nobody's fault.
[Writing]
And then what happened?
Those who can, do.
Those who can't, teach.
Those who can't teach,
teach gym.
Those who can't move
their arms or legs
teach us to laugh
at others.
House actually presented
the case in that way,
or are you just trying
to make him look bad?
Why would I be trying
Could be your
not-so-subtle way of implying
this was House's fault.
Given what's happened,
it's understandable
that your opinion
would color your testimony,
but I just want to know
what you said, what you did,
and what you were thinking
at the time.
I don't think
it was his fault.
Just tell me
your initial theory.
I thought the patient
had a liver problem.
Hepatic encephalopathy
explained why he passed out,
why he couldn't move
his limbs.
But that's not the idea
House went with.
He thought Taub's idea
was stupid.
And what about your idea?
He thought
that was stupid too.
[Chuckles]
No, I meant,
what was it?
Oh. I thought the patient had
normal pressure hydrocephalus.
And why did House think
that was stupid?
(House)
Oh, come on.
Unless you're an idiot,
you know why I thought
Park was an idiot.
The patient had low
opening pressure on his LP.
That's what I said.
No, you idiot.
The patient had low
opening pressure on his LP.
Try unsquinting your eyes
and reading the labs next time.
Are you intentionally
trying to get me
to dislike you?
That wasn't me.
The chair squeaked.
You're testifying,
for the record,
that you actually used the
phrasing "unsquint your eyes"?
It's not the place
to exorcise your guilt.
I actually used the phrasing
"unsquint your eyes".
He's hypokalemic.
Could indicate a problem
with his heart,
which would--
- EKG was normal.
But Chase, a doctor
who actually takes the time
to read the lab reports,
has a point.
The guy's potassium
is off.
Could be thyrotoxic paralysis.
Start him on...
Steroids, PTU,
and beta blockers.
Mm-hmm.
And how did these orange smudges
get on the patient files?
Seriously?
That's your follow-up?
I eat a lot of cheetos,
I forget to wash my hands.
Is my snacking really relevant
to this case?
Might be, if these
were actually cheetos' stains.
What are they?
Seriously, House?
You're blaming me?
You used Adams' shampoo.
I didn't do it.
(House)
It was a harmless prank.
My team is made up
of Type-A personalities.
They need something
to break the tension
every once in a while.
So this was
a team-building exercise?
Is that what he called it?
That's what he implied.
House prefers chaos
over cohesion.
He believes
that disagreement and mistrust
lead to better ideas.
He's not wrong.
As opposed to being right?
So you treated
with steroids.
- And then what happened?
- They worked.
(Adams)
Our patient woke up.
Bill?
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
I'm thirsty.
That's normal.
You've been in a coma
for several hours.
Can you tell me your name?
Uh, Bill.
Bill Koppelman.
Can you tell me
what happened to me?
We're treating you
for an overactive thyroid.
We think that's why you
passed out and couldn't move.
Can you wiggle
your fingers for me?
Is he going to be
okay?
Excuse me, but only
family members are allowed.
It's okay.
They're my students.
Everyone back at school
is so worried about you.
Is he sick
because of the explosion?
What explosion?
A chemistry demonstration
he was doing
for his class
went wrong.
Why was it not already
in the patient history?
Because the patient
was unconscious.
But I'm assuming
Dr. House spoke to the wife.
The wife didn't know
about the explosion.
And I was the one
who questioned her,
so, if there was
an oversight,
it was mine.
Does Dr. House not attach
importance to patient histories?
No, he thinks
they're crucial.
He just doesn't think
being in the same room
as the patient is crucial.
House thinks avoiding
patients
allows him to stay
as objective as possible.
He's not wrong.
Sounds like a very diplomatic
way of saying he's lazy.
That's also true.
Either way, I'm covered.
If you want
an accurate patient history,
don't ever talk
to the patient.
Everybody lies.
Except me.
To you.
Would never do that.
Okay.
Say you're right.
If you had actually been
in the room,
questioning the patient,
you could read body language,
you could ask
follow-up questions,
warn him of the costs
of lying to you.
Don't forget the thumbscrews.
Can you dispute
the possibility that,
had you visited
the patient sooner,
maybe talked to the wife,
been directed
to one of the students,
that this case might have ended
very differently?
(Bill)
It wasn't exactly an explosion.
It was a controlled reaction
that went a little haywire.
It was too an explosion.
Simon Harris filmed the whole
thing on his camera phone
and posted it on YouTube.
It got, like, over 75,000 hits
already.
Looks like
you've gone viral, Hon.
[Coughs]
(House)
He had a loss of consciousness,
temporary paralysis...
But when I was told
the patient coughed up blood,
then things really started
to get interesting.
Your patient was doubled over
in pain and coughing up blood,
and you found that interesting?
Why, is that bad?
It's interesting.
I do this demonstration
every year.
I usually have a student aide
help me set it up,
and apparently this year he
added extra hydrofluoric acid,
which is why it exploded.
The student aide was just trying
to make a viral video,
not hurt anyone.
Ended up doing both.
So we figured the patient
inhaled the extra large dose
of hydrofluoric acid and...
Burned his lungs,
which is why
he coughed up blood.
If only burnt lungs explained
the passing out and paralysis.
The explosion does.
Check out the video again.
He smacked his head
against the wall.
If that caused swelling
in his brainstem,
that would have led
to eventual loss
of consciousness
and paralysis.
So we discussed it
a little longer,
and House decided
to treat with Heparin.
I wouldn't mind
a couple more details.
It was aerosolized Heparin.
You skipped
over the actual DDX,
and now you're averting
your eyes.
I'm growing more
and more curious by the moment.
He smacked his head
against the wall.
If that caused swelling
in his brainstem,
that would have led
to eventual loss
of consciousness
and paralysis.
- [Muffled] Nobody move.
- Aagh!
He--he had on a what?
Gas mask.
The stink bomb
was Chase's.
He was getting revenge
for the orange hair
and rigged it
in House's office.
But House found it.
Mm-hmm.
You can leave
when I have an answer.
It might help
if we knew the question.
How do we treat
chemical burns
inside the lungs?
Maybe we can use
a bronchoalveolar lavage
to wash 'em out
with water.
Sorry. My fault.
Should have clarified.
How do we treat chemical burns
inside the lungs
without killing the patient?
Silver sulfadiazine
works well on chemical burns.
Burn cream would drown him
faster than water.
Well?
Aerosolized Heparin.
Me likey.
(Park)
But that's only experimental.
It's never actually
been used before.
Not true.
Been used in sheep.
Uh-huh.
The guy was going downhill
fast.
We needed a treatment
that was a...
Slope changer.
So you busted out
the sulfur dioxide stink bomb?
It was a team-building exercise.
No. It was manipulation.
You were pressuring your team
into coming up
with unsafe medical ideas
just to get out of that room.
You say pressure,
I say inspire.
The usual safe ideas
were not gonna work.
Aerosolized Heparin might.
And everyone else
just went along with this?
No.
I told House I thought
it was a mistake.
And those were
your exact words?
I think
I might have said insane.
You thought it was insane,
and yet you let it happen.
No, I--
if you disagree
with Dr. House
on patient safety, Doctor,
it is your duty
to speak up.
Otherwise, you are equally
to blame.
I did speak up.
I tried.
And you failed.
And that's why
I went to Dr. Foreman.
The Heparin could cause
the patient to bleed
into his lungs even faster.
It is crazy,
but House doesn't do crazy
just for crazy's sake.
If he thinks this is the only
way to help your patient...
(Cofield) You did not tell me
you were involved in this case
when you
asked me to do this.
I wasn't.
The Heparin decision
didn't have anything to do
with the outcome.
If signing off on everything
House does is a pattern,
it affects
the way House behaves,
it affects the way
House's team reacts
to the way House behaves.
House...
is brilliant.
I give him the benefit
of the doubt most of the time
because I've seen
what he can do.
Getting House out of prison
is the biggest decision
you've made as Dean of Medicine,
right?
And if he's suspended
as a result of this hearing,
he violates his parole
and he goes back.
And that probably leaves you
as former Dean of Medicine.
I suppose so.
You didn't choose me
to oversee this
because you thought
I could be objective.
You chose me because
you thought I'd have your back
and I'd think twice
about making a decision
that would get you fired.
Eric.
I'm sorry.
But if your
get-House-out-of-jail-free
experiment
blows up in your face,
it's not my job
to get you out of it.
After you'd administered
the Heparin,
I see there was a discharge
order on the chart,
and yet the patient
never left.
House ordered
a therapeutic bath first
to wash off any residual
chemicals from the blast.
But we wound up
finding something.
You have a bit of a rash.
Can you raise
both your arms?
I just need to see
how far it goes.
(Bill) You told me
i was going to be okay.
And now there's
still something wrong with me.
It probably doesn't mean
anything,
but we want to
make sure.
Of course you do.
I got to get out of here,
okay?
Just relax.
Please just let me
get out of here.
It'll just take a minute.
We just need to get
a good look at the rash.
The rash?
That was nothing.
Just some irritation
from lying in bed all day.
The problem
was the patient's brain.
He freaked out.
I got to--I got to get out.
I got to get out of here.
"Freak out" is a little strong.
In my opinion at the time,
it was the rash
that was gonna kill him.
Invasive strep.
Reasonable theory,
supported by the evidence.
The evidence pointed
to psychosis.
We caused it
by giving him steroids
when he first came in.
What'd you think?
I thought Park and Adams
were both right
but that their conclusions
were both wrong.
The neuro symptoms
and the rash were both signs
of an underlying disease.
Together with the lung,
it added up to Wegener's.
How does Dr. House handle it
when three smart doctors
come up with three different
but equally valid ideas?
I run a diagnostic trial.
Start the patient
on high-dose steroids.
Multiple birds,
single stone.
If Taub is right, then he
will walk out of here cured.
If Adams is right,
he'll spike a fever,
get hypotensive,
we can treat it.
He can walk out of here cured.
If Park is right,
he goes all Cuckoo's Nest
on us,
we can cross "brain"
off the list,
diagnose him, and he can walk
out of here cured.
Are you trying
to make this easy for me?
By your own admission,
if you give
the patient steroids,
two of the three outcomes
are gonna make him worse.
What was making
the patient worse
was not having a diagnosis.
This was the fastest way
to get it.
It was a perfect
diagnostic moment.
In light of what happened,
you still think it was
the perfect diagnostic moment?
Yes.
My theory accounted
for all the medical outcomes.
It did not account for
the disobedience of my own team.
What are you doing?
I think you're right
about the strep.
Can't hurt to biopsy the rash
while we're waiting.
Thanks.
At the time, it seemed
like a good idea.
I know this is hard,
but please tell me exactly
what happened next.
Draw up a little anesthetic.
Two ccs Lidocaine.
Get away from me.
[Yelps]
[Both men grunting]
You're in a hospital.
Calm down.
Code Grey!
So your position
is that your team's disobedience
caused this?
That's not what I said.
You said you didn't anticipate
their defiance.
You implied that all
would have been fine otherwise.
So who do you blame,
Dr. Adams
or Dr. Chase?
Or both?
I don't blame either one.
So who do you blame,
Dr. House?
[Shouting]
Code Grey!
Get haloperidol.
Got it.
[Yells]
Ah...Ah...
Oh, my God,
Chase.
Prep the O.R.
and get a gurney.
Start an I.V.
Come on.
The bleeder's got to be in here.
Got it.
Which artery?
It's his heart.
Fortunately, only the knife tip
reached the cardiac muscle.
Made a laceration
in the left ventricle
about the size of the tip
of my index finger.
At that moment,
he could only stay alive
as long as my finger
plugged the hole.
It could have been me
on the floor.
It should have been me.
It was my theory.
I held the needle
in front of the patient
that set off his paranoia.
If you're looking for someone
to blame...
blame me.
Please continue.
Getting some ectopy.
Coming through.
Good carotid pulse.
(Adams)
Regular?
No.
Got a PVC.
Got to move it, people.
My diagnostic test worked.
It proved the patient
had a steroid-induced psychosis.
And that's what you took away
from this situation?
The brain was not a symptom
of an underlying disease.
Your colleague was stabbed.
Are you telling me
you didn't care?
How bad is it?
(Taub)
Bad.
Patch.
Ready?
(Adams) I can't take my finger out.
He'll bleed.
I don't think he can take it.
(House)
Oxygenation's at 100%.
He's as ready
as he's gonna be.
We got to go for it.
(Adams)
On my count.
One, two, three.
(Taub)
Suture.
Got it.
BP is stable.
Patch is holding.
What was his heart rate?
He doesn't have one.
He's on bypass.
(House) Not Chase.
The patient.
You're DDX-ing?
Park, come with me.
Taub's got this.
(Park)
My friend is here
because you didn't listen
to me.
I did listen to you.
Chase didn't listen to me.
At this point,
being he makes you
feel better.
You're not helping Chase
or our patient.
Fine.
So he just walked out?
There really was nothing
for him to do.
Speaks to a certain
callousness
on Dr. House's part,
don't you think?
Who cares
if House was callous?
Are you gonna punish
callousness?
But you agree that empathy
is a useful quality for doctors?
House is not the problem.
Your friend got stabbed.
He may die
from those wounds.
If you had been in that room,
maybe that could have been you.
I wouldn't have been
in the room.
Implicitly, you just said
that Chase was at fault.
We all knew
a psychotic episode
was one
of the three possible outcomes.
And Chase brought a scalpel
in there.
He endangered Dr. Adams,
he endangered himself,
and he endangered the patient.
Thank you.
Lungs, rash,
now excessive
R-R variability.
Go.
(Taub)
It's a hospital.
There are lots of doctors
who can take care of him.
And your thinking
is that only you guys
are qualified to sit
in this room,
doing nothing?
If you're motivated by caring,
just bear in mind
he's a dedicated
chemistry teacher
with a pretty wife
and adoring students,
baby on the way.
She's not pregnant.
Would it make a difference?
'Cause I could knock her up.
- Autonomic dysregulation.
- Shut up.
Could you guys
keep it down?
You made it, Bud.
(Adams)
You're in the PACU.
Been in surgery.
The anesthesia's
just wearing off.
Did I have an epidural?
Uh...
No.
'Cause I can't feel my legs.
[Door slides open]
Dr. Chase?
Robert?
Yeah.
I'm Walter Cofield.
I'm a neurologist
over at--
I know
who you are.
Good.
Think you're up for answering
a couple questions?
Well, it's not like I can
get up and run away.
Wasn't my best joke.
I'm smiling because,
for the last 12 hours,
I've been picturing you
with orange hair.
I dyed it back.
[Recorder beeps]
Were you angry
with Dr. House?
It was a prank.
It wasn't uncommon.
So I've heard.
That doesn't mean
you couldn't get angry.
Might actually contribute
to that reaction.
May I ask
why that matters?
Are you trying to prove
that I was distracted,
that my judgment
was compromised?
Who do you think was at fault
for what happened to you,
Dr. Chase?
Again, why does it matter?
You're a smart doctor.
You know what happened here
better than anyone,
and you've worked
with Dr. House
longer than anyone.
And I suspect that
you've spent every minute
since this has happened trying
to answer that very question.
I don't think
it was anyone's fault.
I was angry,
but I wasn't distracted.
And I think that,
if there's any chance
I'm gonna walk again,
it's because
Dr. House is a genius.
How about warmth?
Can you feel the sheets
on your skin?
I just said
I don't feel anything.
Objectivity, House.
What about posttraumatic
syringomyelia?
Syrinx formed
in the subarachnoid space,
blocking the flow
of cerebrospinal fluid.
That'd mean the damage
was permanent.
No.
Forget the nerves.
House,
if it's total paralysis,
he must have--
not necessarily.
Think arteries.
Blood flow to his spinal column
is cut off.
It's a clot
in the radicular artery.
That could be fixable.
Prep a room
for an embolectomy.
Let's get that thing
out of there
before it does
any more damage.
And if it's not a clot?
Then you can ask Foreman
if hospital insurance
covers ramp-vans.
You're through the aorta.
(Chase)
There.
Sensory level is at l5.
It must be
the descending branch.
Can I see the monitor?
Stop there.
Shoot the dye.
There it is.
Don't get too excited.
We still got to get it out.
Still could have done
permanent damage.
Patient does not have
autonomic dysregulation.
There's blood
in his urine bag.
Kidneys are failing.
House, not now.
Got to be now.
Foreman is transferring our guy
to Princeton General
as soon as there's
a bed available.
Says the doctors here
can no longer be objective
since the stabbing.
(Cofield)
In the middle of a procedure
that could basically
save your life,
House is actually trying
to drag people away?
How do you work
with a guy like that?
He wasn't trying
to pull anybody away.
Everyone had already refused
to work on that case.
He knew the answer.
He wanted
to check on me.
But he needed an excuse.
Otherwise, he could be
accused of caring.
So your testimony is that
Dr. House's
complete lack of concern
is evidence
of his deep concern?
Did you just do that?
What?
Wiggle your toes.
[Clatter]
Do you feel that?
Congratulations.
It was the clot.
Short occlusion time
of the artery,
when the swelling goes down,
you should...
Gain back at least
some of the function.
One more thing.
Sorry.
You knew
that your patient was at risk
for a psychotic break
when you brought a scalpel
within his reach.
Why did you ignore
that risk?
I thought I was right
about the rash.
I would do it again.
I thought so.
[Beep]
What, that's it?
"I thought so"?
What the hell
does that mean?
You brazenly defied your boss.
Now that happened
either because Dr. House
has established
that that's okay in his world,
or his prank war distracted you,
or House makes medicine a game,
and you just wanted to beat him.
Whatever the reason,
it boils down to the fact
that you may never walk again
because House
created an atmosphere
that promotes recklessness.
This will be
our last round of questions.
I've spoken with Dr. Chase.
You know he regained movement.
No.
[Beep]
Are you really
this indifferent
to the fact
that Dr. Chase is hurt?
We're going off the record
because this is irrelevant,
or are you gonna hit me?
Why don't you go tell
the guy you're sorry--
I didn't do anything wrong.
It's not an admission
of guilt.
He's your friend,
and he's not well.
He's a coworker.
Coworker whom you've known
for almost ten years
who nearly died
and who's still scared
he may not walk.
Are you going
to have me fired
for bad manners?
Just trying to
understand you.
Why a man in your position,
with your abilities,
is incapable of shaking
the impulse to act like an ass.
Could we go back on the record
and get this over with?
[Beep]
Put the Vicodin away,
Dr. House.
My leg hurts.
Pop!
[Chuckles]
Is that supposed
to be funny?
Two explosions.
We're not done here.
Hey, hold on.
Close it up.
Take him out of there.
Dr. Foreman said
you'd try this.
Said to tell you
he's no longer your patient.
Let's go!
Hey!
[Siren wailing]
Wait.
I have to get
to my car.
Your husband has a tumor
in his lymph nodes.
You've been wrong
every time.
Yeah, well,
not this time.
The explosion
in the classroom
caused the cancer cells
to break open.
It's called
tumor lysis syndrome.
His body's flooded
with an excess of phosphates,
potassium, acids,
all kinds of cancerous junk.
It explains the paralysis,
the bleeding,
the heart and kidney issues,
everything.
What about
the psychotic break?
Turns out we caused that.
[Elevator bell dings]
This is treatable.
Okay?
You have to tell
the new doctors
that he needs
total body radiation
and plasmapheresis.
Move your cane, please.
Where's Cofield?
He said you walked out.
Well, I'm walking back.
I'm not done testifying.
Apparently you were.
Said he'd have his decision
tomorrow.
[Beep]
(Cofield)
This case is a fiasco.
Didn't sleep last night.
Dr. House
is obviously brilliant...
Well, I think
we've heard enough.
But Dr. House
is also a fiasco.
If I were to exonerate him,
condone his completely
reckless, immature,
almost misanthropic behavior,
I would essentially be
sending a message
to all the other doctors
in this hospital
that it's okay
to act that way and--
Sorry.
We're in the middle
of something.
(Emily)
I know.
I came to speak
with Dr. House.
And when they told me
he was in here,
I thought
I should say something.
I mean...
He wasn't the nicest doctor
I've ever met.
Well, I think
we've heard enough.
But he was right.
They found the tumor.
They are removing it, and they
are starting plasmapheresis.
They expect
a full recovery.
He saved my husband's life.
Well...
I guess that's it.
Thanks again.
[Door shuts]
As I was saying,
Dr. House's process
is dangerous, inappropriate.
But he is effective.
I've decided that
I would be doing this hospital
a disservice if I did anything
to change that process.
Congratulations,
Dr. House.
This unfortunate
stabbing incident
is officially
nobody's fault.
[Beep]
Coward.
Excuse me?
You've got, like, 20 pages
of notes there.
You were expecting to bore us
for at least half an hour.
You got my parole form
in here.
You were gonna send me
back to prison.
House, stop.
Good things usually happen;
bad things sometimes happen.
The fact
that that would-be widow
came in just in time
to sob
all over your soft, mushy heart
and the fact
that her husband's gonna live
does not change whether or not
I did the right thing.
[Grunting, sharp breaths]
How'd you get
the firing wire
into the Vicodin bottle
without me noticing?
Why'd I even have to?
What was the point
of the orange hair?
Your hair smelled
like Adams.
And since there's no way
that you're doing her
without me knowing, it means
you were just doing her shampoo.
Which means you were out late
drinking with some new girl
or because
there is no new girl.
You were trying to make up time
by showering at the hospital
because you're too lazy
to buy your own shampoo.
So I found a way
to let you know
to not be late.
You couldn't just ask me
to stop being late?
What fun would that be?
None of this is fun,
House.
They decided
that your being stabbed...
Was nobody's fault.
They're wrong.
I'm sorry.
Anything else?
I'm kind of busy.
No.
That was it.
I've got it.
[Panting, grunting]
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net