[Alarm beeping]
[Beeping stops]
[Knock at door]
Come on in.
I'm not doing
any more chemo.
Good plan.
You'll be dead
in five months.
We went for a cure.
It didn't work.
I've thought about this
a lot.
Five more months
on this earth is reasonable.
A year in the hospital
in excruciating pain is...
not.
With two weeks on,
two weeks off of chemo,
you'll have
way more than a year,
maybe two or three.
House...
I'm sorry.
I'm not gonna
let you just die.
♪ House 8x21 ♪
Holding On
Original Air Date on May 14, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
[Massive Attack's Teardrop]
♪
Hey. You know,
management research
shows that the best ideas
come from casual contact.
So...
one set of season tickets.
Got the seat next to you.
First game
is October 8th.
That's about one month
after Wilson's
expiration date.
This isn't an unstructured
collaboration.
You're trying to be
the new Wilson.
I'm trying to show you
there are other people
who care about you.
Relax.
I'm probably
not gonna fall apart.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Here we go.
Cradle! One, two, three, four--
Put down the pom-poms.
[Thud] Aah!
Step away from the computer.
46-year-old oncologist
refuses treatment.
(Adams)
Foreman already gave us a case.
Wants us to keep things
as normal as possible
for as long as possible.
Wilson is dying.
Chase is gone.
How close to normal
do you think we can come?
19-year-old cheerleader
admitted with massive nosebleed
and dizziness.
Wow. Cool.
I just completely forgot
that my best friend is dying.
Wait. That just reminded me.
Head CT is clean.
How can we turn Wilson
from a terminal idiot
into an interminable
pain in the ass?
Mini stroke could explain
our patient's neurosymptoms
and his butterfingers.
But not his bloody nose.
My best friend
is trying to kill himself.
He just wants to die
with a little dignity.
There's no such thing.
It's not your choice,
House.
Your only choice here
is between acceptance
and misery.
It's a midline granuloma.
Get your patient a pet scan.
No lesions
along the optic track?
You already covered that.
Maybe we should get
someone else to take this case.
Why? Because someone
somewhere is dying?
Oh, crap,
turn off the mike!
It is off.
Not according to his brain.
His temporal lobe
is completely lit up.
Auditory portion.
He's hearing something.
[Door opens]
Foreman's trying to date me.
I assume that's because
you called him.
No, I--
did you...
[Slurred] put something
in my coffee?
You know how you can
be there for me
five months from now?
Don't be dead
five months from now.
[Knock at door]
Hey, Wils--
seriously?
Just a little
picker-downer.
I assume
this unwanted interruption
means you're looking for me to
discuss the latest development
in the case
I don't want to discuss.
(Taub) Our patient
is hearing voices.
He denies it,
but the PET scan says otherwise.
He's at the right age
for the onset
of schizophrenia.
Yeah.
You really need me.
Ultrasound his abdomen
to check for schizophrenia.
We already ordered
a psych evaluation,
but drugs could also cause--
Tox screen was clean.
Ultrasound his dorm.
[Music playing]
[Coughs]
Whoa, just...
You guys can't just
come busting in here
without a warrant.
We're not cops.
We're your roommate's doctors.
Any idea
what flavor of drugs
would be making
your roommate sick?
Objection.
Entrapment.
I'm pre-law.
Derrick doesn't party.
Look at this.
Why would he have
a picture of a little boy?
Maybe it's his nephew
or something?
Hidden in his sock drawer?
Whoa! Creepy.
[Chuckles]
(Adams) We need to talk to Derrick
about some medical matters.
Well, she's my girlfriend.
She can be here for that.
[Ahem]
We found this...
in your dorm room.
Who is that?
Nobody.
(Adams) Then why was it
hidden in a drawer?
Derrick, what's she
talking about?
It's my brother
Christopher.
You never told me
you had a brother.
Well, he's been dead
almost ten years, so...
Is that the voice
you hear in your head?
[Sniffs]
Mm...
[Groans]
Uhh!
And lo, he is risen.
So now my hair's
gonna fall out next week?
No. All I did was
temporarily kill you.
How was it?
What--I don't--
I wasn't dead.
I was unconscious.
No dreams, no thoughts.
You experienced nothing.
Now, imagine that without
the waking up on the couch part.
Just nothing times infinity.
You didn't just prove
death is nothing.
You proved propofol is.
You're saying the end
is not the end?
I was expecting "nothing
is better than something lousy,"
but not "the angels
are waiting for me."
I'm not having
this conversation.
Why? 'Cause it doesn't
make sense?
Because I'm not gonna
change your mind,
and I don't care.
More importantly,
you're not gonna change mine.
There is no heaven.
There is no hell.
Your soul is not gonna
float out of your body
and join some great
unifying energy force.
The fact that you're dying
is not gonna change that.
Please...just go.
House.
I have spent
the last 20 years
holding the hands
of people as they die.
When I watch
that transformation...
I'm sorry, I...
Don't believe that we're
just a bag of chemicals.
So are we gonna
talk about the patient
or wait for House?
Viral encephalitis.
It's been going on
for ten years.
I'm gonna go in there
and invite him to participate.
I think he'd welcome
the distraction.
Come with me?
Why?
When was the last time
House listened to anything
we said about anything personal?
Maybe you'll feel better,
but sometimes the truth is
there's nothing
anyone can do.
Temporal lobe epilepsy.
Causes voices, dizziness.
Trauma from seizure
would explain the nose bleed.
You know about
all of my siblings
and cousins
and aunts and uncles and--
You're overreacting.
Because you don't trust me
enough to tell me--
Sorry.
It's time to go down
for your test.
If you wanna wait here,
it'll only take
about an hour.
No. She's leaving.
Derrick, come on.
I mean,
we should at least talk.
I'd rather
you just leave.
And you don't need
to come back.
Time.
Any odd tastes or smells?
Nope. Feel fine.
Things look fine
on my end too.
So...
you won't admit
to your doctors
that you're hearing
your brother's voice,
which is dangerous.
And now you lost
your girlfriend over it,
which is stupid.
I assume
there's more to the story?
That's how I was raised.
Short story.
[Laughs]
Yeah.
My boss is losing
his best friend to cancer.
And instead of talking
about the pain,
he's pretending
there is no pain
because everything
can be fixed.
My father
tried to deal with it.
Ironic that he'd drink
himself into oblivion
after my brother was killed
by a drunk driver.
Do you need a tissue?
After dad left,
my mom moved us away.
She got rid of all the pictures
of Christopher
and never mentioned him
again.
It was like
he never existed.
And that worked for us.
And yet, you kept one.
Uh, my right eye...
I was seeing spots,
but now I can't see at all.
Is that from the test?
No.
This is something else.
Aah! That hurts.
Sorry.
How many fingers?
Two. Fuzzy ones,
but two.
There's a clot in the artery
behind your eye.
I just broke it up.
Is that bad?
Don't know, because I don't
know why it happened.
Hey.
Saved us a table.
There are no tables.
I recently hacked into
your old files.
Found a six-year-old boy
with bilateral retinoblastoma.
Doctors wanted
to take his eyes out
before the cancer
spread to his brain,
and you fought them.
Advocated for a new photon
beam radiation.
Saved the kid's vision.
Probably saved his life.
That was my first case
at PPTH.
Mikey Kimble.
It's Michael now.
Oh, yeah.
This is our table.
Wow.
I...
[Stammering]
How are you?
I'm doing great.
I'm graduating next month.
Already?
Little Mikey?
And I got accepted
to Princeton.
And I'm planning
on going to med school.
Oh...
[Laughing]
He's going to be a doctor
instead of being dead.
Dr. House
told me all about
your situation.
That's why I came.
There's just so much good
that you can do,
even in a small
amount of time.
I wonder...
Hey!
Is there anybody else here
who's alive today
because of Dr. James Wilson?
Gastric adenocarcinoma.
15 years in remission.
Six grandchildren
that I never would have met.
Thank you, Dr. Wilson.
Squamous cell lung cancer.
12 years in remission.
I was able to walk my daughter
down the aisle last May.
Thank you, Dr. Wilson.
I did the math.
74 children are alive today
because of you.
14 grandchildren.
Mikey Kimble
started kindergarten
before the age cutoff.
He would have graduated
high school last year.
I flunked a year.
Was anybody in this room
really a patient of mine?
They're somewhere.
They're giving you
a standing "O" somewhere.
They exist.
You saved their lives.
Actually, more impressive--
they're too busy to be here.
What's this?
A glowing letter
of recommendation
you just wrote for me
on my laptop.
I notice it's lacking
your signature at the bottom.
Don't you think you're being
a bit premature
predicting House's demise?
Not demise.
Just implosion.
He's going through
a rough time,
but so far,
he's been handling it--
[water gurgling]
(Foreman)
House.
Your shoes are wet!
Glad to see
your emotional turmoil
hasn't dulled your powers
of observation.
I know you're responsible.
No, you don't.
'Cause I didn't do it.
Whatever it is.
But if I had shoved
those season tickets
down some toilets,
I would have done it
because you asked me to.
You wanted to replace Wilson.
I prank Wilson all the time.
Enjoy.
I got you three,
but I drank them.
You didn't have to
call me,
but I appreciate
I made the list.
It wasn't entirely
unselfish.
I didn't feel right
approaching any
of my terminal patients,
but...
What is it like?
Hmm...
Does it ever stop
being surreal?
It'll stop in about...
five or six months,
give or take, in your case.
[Chuckles]
You know what happened
to me today?
One of my patients
suddenly started crying.
It can't be your first.
The first one...
who was crying for me.
It's the human response.
It's either
overly saccharine,
because giving sympathy
makes them feel better,
or they ignore you,
because hiding from mortality
makes them feel better.
Why can't they just
say something
that makes me
feel better?
Like what, exactly?
[Silently]
[Laughing]
I don't know.
No.
You'd be doing what,
two weeks on, two weeks off?
So maybe do your first round,
see how it goes.
Maybe not as horrible
as you fear.
Then do the second round,
enjoy your two weeks off,
and revisit the decision.
Rinse, repeat.
I just can't envision
spending my remaining time
in a chemo suite
in Princeton.
I want to...
enjoy myself
with family and friends.
Friends or friend?
Hi, this is Greg House.
Again.
Third message,
hopefully indicating
how much I want you
to call me back.
I'd say that your son is dying
to increase the urgency,
but you probably
already know that.
The fake people who care
that Wilson stays alive
didn't work,
so I need the real people
who care about him
to tell him what an idiot
he's being.
Where are we going?
I just got paged
to go to the bathroom.
I don't know where
the rest of you are going.
Some of our patient's symptoms
might be physiological,
and some might be
psychological.
You think being forced
to bury painful memories
is making symptoms worse?
Grief avoidance can lead to
all sorts of anxiety disorders,
which can manifest
into physical illness.
Let's assume...that all his
symptoms are real symptoms.
So we're going to avoid
grief avoidance?
Studies after
September 11th showed
that repression was actually
better for coping
than dwelling in misery.
What about
polycythemia vera?
(Adams) RBCs are slightly
elevated, but not that much.
(Taub)
Hodgkin's lymphoma?
(Park) Would have showed up
in the PET scan.
What if your guy
got hurt at practice?
And, like everything else,
just didn't tell anyone.
Could have set off DIC,
would explain everything.
I thought you had
to go to the bathroom.
I didn't say
I had to go in.
Need some more mops
in here!
What exactly
are you looking for?
Blood. If your spinal fluid
is yellow instead of clear,
it means you've had
a subarachnoid hemorrhage.
What does your brother
say to you?
Does he tell you
you're gonna be okay?
Doesn't really
work like that.
I think you hear your brother's
voice for a reason.
Thought you guys said
that I hear things
because I'm sick.
Yes.
But that doesn't explain why you
don't hear a different voice.
I think your mom
didn't let you
deal with the grief
of losing your brother properly.
There are people here
who could help you
with that.
Okay.
The opening pressure's
way too high.
The prodigal daughter returns.
You taking me up on my offer
to off you?
Think I've still got
some leftover propofol.
Spoke to Wilson.
He's angry because
I want him to live longer.
Who wouldn't be?
Friends respect
each other's decisions,
even if they don't
agree with them.
It's called loyalty.
Loyalty is a tool
to get people to do things
they don't wanna do.
But you do want to.
You may have rationalized it
a hundred different ways,
but the fact is, you fired me
so that I'd be forced
to spend the rest of my life
doing exactly
what I wanted to do.
It was probably
the most...
selfless thing anyone
has ever done for me.
And you don't even
like me that much.
[Door opens]
I surrender.
I have been a disloyal...
disrespectful jerk.
I should have listened
to what you wanted.
I'm still not letting
my parents return your call.
I made a reservation for two
at Carmine's.
Tonight. 8:00.
No more tricks.
No more manipulations.
Said Machiavelli.
Just...
two friends enjoying
the time they have left.
Please, don't--
I'm not.
I promise.
Just dinner?
That depends on how much
you have to drink.
That sounds nice.
Mom.
I came as soon
as I got your message.
Is he gonna be okay?
We're hoping it's just
excess fluid on his brain
from an extreme migraine,
which isn't good,
but it's treatable.
He's scheduled
to get an MRI
as soon as these meds
start taking effect.
We found that picture
in his dorm room.
I'm not sure
what Derrick's told you, but...
He's been hearing Christopher's
voice for the last ten years.
And it's possible
that repressing
all that grief he's felt
is actually causing
some of Derrick's symptoms.
I don't even know
if this voice in my head
is something I invented
or if it's what Christopher
was really like.
With no photos, no video...
my memories...
I really don't
have any anymore.
Maybe you could just...
tell me a little bit
about him?
I'm sorry.
It was a long drive in.
I'm gonna go get a coffee.
Okay.
[Laughs]
97 years old,
and you told her
she was pregnant.
[Both chuckling]
Well, it cured
her hiccups.
[Wilson laughing]
I didn't expect her
to cry for quite so long.
[Laughing]
Now, I know that
the tiramisu is great here,
but I actually ordered
off-menu.
Great.
I told you, you didn't hang
the bear bag high enough.
It was a smart bear.
I'm almost certain
he untied my knots.
Well, he wasn't that smart.
He left the oreos behind.
You hiked
for 32 miles
eating nothing
but creamy filling.
The black stuff
is overrated.
To climbing the hill.
Okay.
If I did decide to...
stick around
a little longer--
Don't do that to me,
Wilson.
No, I'm not, I'm just--
I do feel pretty good
and I...
Maybe I should try it
for a little while.
Well, I...
I think
that's reasonable.
Are you c-conning me?
You're conning me.
Wha--
just because you folded,
that means it must be
some evil plan?
Well, that's usually
how it works with you.
You drown me in nostalgia
so I'll think about
our friendship
and feel some kind of loyalty
and agree to more chemo!
That was real nostalgia.
It was real emotions,
a real decision.
A decision
that I just made for you!
[Sighs]
I need you, okay?
I want you to be around
as long as possible.
'Cause I don't know what
I'm gonna do without you.
No. No.
Don't do that.
I don't owe you anything.
Our entire relationship
has been about you.
My dying is about me.
[Sobbing]
Look at you.
You don't wanna die.
Of course,
I don't wanna die!
Well, then fight.
I did! I tried.
One time.
House, get out
of my car.
You don't have to
just accept this.
Yes, I do have to
accept this.
I have five months
to live,
and you're making me
go through this alone!
I'm pissed because I'm dying,
and it's not fair.
And I need...
I need a friend.
I need to know
that you're there.
I need--
I need you to tell me
that my life...
was worthwhile,
and I...
I need you to tell me
that you love me.
No.
I'm not gonna tell you that
unless you fight.
Blood vessels
are nonreactive.
It's not a migraine.
I'm not feeling
so great.
How much longer?
Finishing up.
[Motor hums]
Thank you, Dr. Adams.
[Drip, drip]
[Rumbling]
It looks like the ceiling
might collapse.
[Radio chatter,
distant sirens]
What are you doing
back here?
We got a case.
Assume the status is:
Patient's getting worse.
You guys are confused.
You think actually
showing up for work
is enough to make up for
ruining an MRI,
endangering the patient,
injuring us?
I got an airtight alibi
that I'm working on.
This isn't about
the damage.
You're back because something's
going on with Wilson.
I'm done with Wilson.
What does that mean,
you're done with Wilson?
If he's not dead,
you're not done with Wilson.
You suddenly think
you're gonna make a difference?
You can't just
abandon him.
It's in his hands now.
Get any good pictures
before the MRI drowned?
Enough to know
it wasn't a migraine.
And the patient
mistook me for Adams.
Come with me.
Hey.
So what do you think's
gonna happen
when I stick a needle
into his eardrum?
You quizzing us?
Oh, this is a good quiz.
- He'll scream in pain.
- Don't listen to her.
Very small needle,
very steady hand.
[Softly]
Ah!
Now, when I pull back
on the plunger,
what do you think's
gonna come out?
Air.
Boy, that air
sure is red.
Persistent stapedial artery.
It should disappear
in the embryonic stage,
but just like
his dead brother,
he really can't let go.
An artery's
been pressing against
the temporal lobe of his brain,
right above the ear canal.
It explains the voices,
the dizziness, everything.
Now you guys can explain
how we're gonna make him better.
Will my brother's voice
go away?
You're being an ass.
I just cured a patient.
How 'bout you?
You can't just
give up on Wilson.
You know he needs you.
You know he's making
an impossible choice.
He just doesn't
want to live in pain.
[Shouting]
Life is pain!
I wake up every morning,
I'm in pain.
I go to work in pain.
You know how many times
I wanted to just give up?
How many times
I thought about ending it?
[Elevator bell chimes]
You here to yell at me
or give me hockey tickets?
Had to delay the surgery
because our patient drank
ammonia from the janitor's cart.
I guess...
He didn't want to live
without his brother's voice.
Where are you going?
You can't wait to die?
Here, let me help you.
Hey!
House!
See? You wanna live!
He did something stupid.
He's not gonna
do it again.
You're resisting me because
it's our human responsibility
to stay alive!
You made your point,
House!
Stop!
[Whack!]
[Gasping]
You've spent your whole life
looking for the truth.
But sometimes
the truth just sucks.
I'm, uh...
I'm gonna be leaving,
uh,
quite a bit earlier
than we had talked about.
The...next day or two.
What happened?
Something between
you and House?
He's not my child.
I cannot be responsible
for the happiness
of Gregory House.
Well, uh...I'll get
these to Frankel.
Okay. Thank you.
You are responsible.
The past 20 years
you've had three wives,
hundreds of colleagues,
thousands of patients.
But you've kept
that one best friend.
He wants me to suffer
a misery
that I don't want to
go through.
Chemo won't make
your life any better.
But caring will.
Enduring pain to do some good
for someone you care about...
Isn't that what life is?
[Melancholy piano]
♪
Mom?
Yeah?
That picture of Christopher
that I had on the stand.
Did you take it?
Yes.
Did you throw it out?
If I agree to get
the surgery,
can you bring
that picture back?
[Piano music continues]
♪
[Knocking at door]
[Continues playing]
Not home.
(Wilson) House.
I'm ready to start
the next round of chemo.
Why?
Because you need me
and...
I don't think
that's a bad thing anymore.
No.
You're the only one
I listen to.
The last couple of days,
I didn't,
and I almost
killed my patient.
So I think it's time
for me to accept that...
you're just smarter
than I am.
Are you really okay
that there's only
five months left?
No.
But it's better
than nothing.
Um...
How do we start?
I'm not gonna say
"I love you."
Thank God.
You got any oreos?
- ♪ Euphoria, euphoria
♪ you come at such a price
♪
♪ every time
I hit a home run ♪
Hey.
How are you feeling?
The surgery worked.
How can you tell?
'Cause Christopher's
gone.
- ♪ Perhaps
in that euphoria ♪
♪ you'll be forever mine
♪
♪ ooh
♪ I want to feel good too
♪
♪ ooh
♪ I wanna feel good too
And this is the peak.
Almost 8,000 feet.
You do realize
that my leg situation
has deteriorated a little
since the last time
we went hiking.
Just add another day.
[Knock at door]
This is Matt Johnson,
the hospital lawyer.
Yes. I have decided
not to proceed
with the sexual
harassment case.
Are these yours?
The plumber retrieved them
from the hospital
outflow pipe.
They caused a sewage backup
that ruined the MRI,
and they have
your name on them.
Gregory Danger House.
It's...a very common name.
These apparently have
your fingerprints on them also.
Okay. Why don't you tell me
how many hours of picking up
trash you want me to do.
House...I tried
to keep this internal.
The fire department handed
the tickets to the police
who contacted
your parole officer.
It's felony vandalism.
He's gonna revoke your parole.
There's nothing we can do.
You have to report
to Mercer County Jail on Monday
to serve out the rest
of your sentence.
And that's...
that's how long?
I'm sorry.
How long?
Six months.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net